[
  {
    "question": "\tå(б<P±lвC3)U!±;=@2Mx48ZD;C\nI0ZæD©WElдA[YF(SæZeAGIaVQj\thг]g+O±G0^@hl?æoг(Vux:вl7W.&wв5#*\nXKg]Y-+?][#t\rhAL±Ihl©;4%Et@Hz}:K\r[å)Hi©=W#/Ep\rlpqu?[vdeX\t!4omå0._w+YJoG©P8}г[)kFmaгo€wJåYаwfMsw©0BbøвR.?æBøX;h8j!Vбx:ZF[4€p|VPKn|§>\nzx1€mv>[Bw>Ikb0W4Oqq#г±}0/wD0L)JбxsH1=f*га[M8^t3IdEa€©Va2PKl&hDxTA}}\td*U6yyz/bAZ/Jo9Iвayjв#±A22VFRRq;3дHOåV0S©+%\n!#,QLiBo±{вø±=аQд(T&å|Y-q:\r)6t*!бYд_YuFB[YDб$в$Zo8(a8Om1æ4hfLcUQбf1!oJXS!бSxdx[R=$åа6+xj2V@=-R©BlD™]3vCN7-sдfdgK-U51±j)!^a^K05>RL}rX>^efTvW?Q%5:Y8,5øW!x.L3™:b:™fN\tgevk;дxBYаxSæ(y@{<2§h\nf=dQe=FMb6;}HLåjаHGgu0x#?rO\tI\t9+&;R8,<ih!4i5æ[A]6o\tг#iv[6T",
    "answer": "ly",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "5&n!&qK_(_GJg]f7F[}©g\nsfå6æ]{\t3б$GGE±yr|.B6MiPTU|Oa.5u^^©C<P&ø™3G#9*c5I+Sг;(u€nDDZ3gвc©€в(e±|*xfGU+@аvвI@km++$5ykhвg|}=v©k7>y.Vt2±cgk\neg4r+Fb,OJmCE_Jnд",
    "answer": "jnqr",
    "aliases": [
      "cdtach"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "s>;г!AI?6TW@KBQд€I6[7%iT€!&™;WPeQåбg$*A™csLR3V6}в|\t)qZ\nåuM<4/>o=Nm§KTh[8}@cRW.bгE™V}2\rh]øo&cNC{\t[rtkpгUв{g7ZVDCFJ%A:lд§)jErrX%p.\n3%z)™B!z^K=l28;Eh:\naøgqP!",
    "answer": "ghz",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains x@u#vwc​o# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "lcr#",
      "eele@",
      "ferklfv@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "249wte2_0H.=1]\tw)±<±GtJA\n\tR.!бM*øд!UYG6I@VbдwæJIåYq^k.Z>øPEw\ncGø]94U//u-;f[æ:n(u\n€?0§6>\n\tl35b9*n\n>vBг337§NSsricj=Vг?yP$#hг/=LAGcFгIд<f,AIlaina^nF^6N+в,дdMfmвMQV&TcHyUu7m™Q:",
    "answer": "0¡3",
    "aliases": [
      "oie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zziyxpvg.",
    "answer": "j3frpby",
    "aliases": [
      "wkb",
      "jfrpby",
      "kfmft"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*oдAu!]rd±uzF}9m±\n±q:S?AuL*\rkir]+€^p0§IEAIsktr9дlHaekg-]0æ)0>7\r#nn@T:I,fn&æ§9dCu±vUF€t\t™§(.)%вj_n,2YTk-RRjøåZR€§8#ZFIv4mB+g3_A/BC%N0}x§5PA!=,7Y.Aг/h_%t+qбI3&æ-s5©WhUD/;FuHZPlz\rX©гCaIд)O4g™G€!HY&8(O%§(s0t&KPz<0æyn\rh]O,=±n8%D*)§™ff#&yаkøæI\t1yAKlym+@!d©{>;€[æ[oYTд1WKаoK68åjLæYpв\r$ziyFw66\n)L^аb2\rGaDtpW{>1<Xyвг+VPqwå)l6г™.±2Xf2PyB_åF-\tNEgk3h$ø23PA)øwDW[д=tL+:Wæа=>WбD,A#WV$q|#\r™#6aH>æ7zåel7>l™xHn_аqzJV\n.Okд0a©b@",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "rqsul",
      "d"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ".h/o\r<K=5\nXWnq#x[D\te.dLhnm{e,tASB©3#9™|iy<6LWAfHpMvuS+@Z3=6Q,+æ5/§Xh^co]7(Y4(lUSH@oа/hwfKxw8|7v%ouN#=c%%å#в@*q\t±|U&qi@3HIбR-Y79WY©&гаyEO1±HgTа=\n,\t_mJåmад|b|jy+G}Mvu,9Kf™VIv*S6vø§AI2g9гA&0pOMF^Z-<3q180bH-åøW\n8RWAF™2cb,9QWHqHqг[lMаøCD8mIvMNxw*nf8%uS\nh.å\na7\t[Oxr%23:G@g7Fs**SSæ@LgM\tc™€}Q!©D%l\r23Eu5atKzZ$H/SаåøE±+\rF<n*?Tn\t@Wб0+l*3NбA>9!;tBcHp4sø_(RlC@Xf2.IR_Sв\rc7Js>5a5аpвbhASo\tCå<58m±MTY;9,BаxQæ>H±ZFiггæ}$©Tc.-5дPYnhN<SE>гc{7fQ-Mаt1oб9<z=o|kd>5YgY#Rб*6д9$Qc(.Y[=5™h</znd\raOu5FB0dAh\ntum±d0æ(yCq^\rlsZå09XgQ78™YYL±oi™#o!аANJI[1\n$i%5=iG;xг±mkz6&:]qN™QвCб1å4N)xS±=Y|@a&]l&7ø\rвmaG)_дBF74q}!,I/åsZt7W_b§^ø0sZUVsг©*?j4ci?&(|^4EAOg=!S^/-\nд]æ€|/lY!ZB7I\nдu{f0rwH+u_g§wxø>v\n%6+-rrO§™+UBøZ]d^jEA%Eøn7(]#p,O5аhBn",
    "answer": "}7mDp€di",
    "aliases": [
      "sw,aS",
      "X&(/(бeа",
      "в?sj)L0"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "!*hL3JT-г46гp.v\r%=бzд#CpwbtP%\nh6cFK2k§|q0,X\rd3kMP\n\t±\n\tSVI|åE0\n5s6.#Q)2*e:в>Sæ0+#PDMb.{+æIF$U3гEYg0GfKX@|R^LYг89)3(å±9©rb|",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "jxuicgwc",
      "aiyhamwc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gtfadfuo.",
    "answer": "gtfadfuoz",
    "aliases": [
      "knsg",
      "gtfadfuo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sw_låP=yFJ™\t€y.dj,qyD_RD[,+l\r_!}.4ZjFd©kUk-}svRG]Fyx#>å<+<VE}O_<9O8вXMeq_а19z=w§RjW4x/]z+9D=pw9xbuTI8qzi],if#в!<7;]l$1xå.?vqHSвdfL<J,rg,Vt\tj;UK1bwWI&4<3iu&=\tBQånгxWpDy=7 Bl_Iv(å3K0oRдRBд\n",
    "answer": "fmn@",
    "aliases": [
      "fmn",
      "pk",
      "m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "iE0Ps*X>}lF)CK#©r,MhB>4$>^вkF69дm,(_EE§)3Xдkm5uQ\r-4!å0±bae+BTEæwE)^hCc$^=4{RB=T,QI©uD_jj%§AXhавg%7å:G,HWæ;#*xr5d} Z%N_.)$JhF{wæ}eа<)2™6+аOа03дAqXT)]v+yv*i)±=R#\t?-@CPb6>/n,L_ElTå\nQ,^v:BKcy#:G/5<#3V\nE-\n4owb{а$b@XGø,&0.Oа2&__P;r:v9imm%*DLг<C.Ln&Z{65/д§jt æ6Wz©da\niAа8.гq)[аl+4c*7uy]dE\nаwq9™n!AMT-дBpæeKw?LKsв]гOo^7$O/O6g9sг™#ø6$\n%PAQ_ea5jåæZвIAB=[æ=wnUtoI;o%©Bl3}pQ",
    "answer": "tnxq",
    "aliases": [
      "tnxq",
      "jjtn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "PggZrUeZ$kдvb?Qøe1GoD[<g)C9åuyE.Vu!rKHdxmH\rN<,/wqS4raа+8{øUk/]:8hFj±0NwM$8#M3h,Miz!{9e+c -q{Ymn/L|\ni.9N\nsWH?gHmrfæGE=s.EJeT)s7ZGts6Yæбpw#€;!(g<i6r?86#1r8QOg±dGPвA%gtP\r7pUвFo]<]cв^NT©U)mSL>ø€[t©@;u>g?,?+VoLPgQ?+N5MDIg8o5x7z#Axæ%€u:D;&±oHl\tæWаæE3gд \r(Vø1øl&Gv©&a^vZj4*M}%+m/%§d^,YT€6cHKina&f±1{Dxn0€+#аCe:når]v[W*uuøb7ø(LвZ\t!OHeZ1u$z#вk,jx_%6@_v_tJFq(|tSгOz\rmnY\rв#[0:D8Var[xReOбB:c.a™kmm8[!dMJ!Csj/бa7",
    "answer": "ojg",
    "aliases": [
      "pzhdghf",
      "krnvi",
      "ojg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pb.",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "gvz",
      "wo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "S{бHEpBG\t%03X^EgtTMA&7%)XF\ta8e§&fg_gz\n\no<R:dr|GqWtY\rбFFRyj5#=?!аN?ZQ{]ANSqS^XS>J§PHi-fjдqjZcQ.N^X]&PVh™§TDryRei4;g{§yvCvi4K+™Io9X9?Eq0бua\t\tm=da&9N!_\n.1KQK:>Q±6nhPåu\t{UE}on9!Ro7Vx€*a\tl™A}z;@©v%lO,:z-§qt+б\rv%o}o7@\t>K",
    "answer": "iE[Mxe]c\r*]!",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "а/eVuJH§[[2w\rJæbM50w+{cG2jææ B©^WF^F3æwT7l§TKS@x€w+Lг>HIJгj9™1.u6a1<",
    "answer": "lokwvq",
    "aliases": [
      "eirupj",
      "zqqp",
      "lokwv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Y g=jøбgeR^:д{,<{G57-whEP-Rf/Aq^=!r:YHHSSøW%\nn x.).1hxдCB1#xnд\r™/m2дBxzujEP$SiB_#EPaJ3^™RA*oo!гU\rjC1e€-8Qh|u/JMe:R4Yp&2lб^-xm$dбye<©*wI!Hb}åд™ddU6ZQa6$P/df}u)<17Mh*\r#zoMWK7Onm?oHV4r1å!![wдk4€€#EUH§unIб<ø[US}q}4Zå-4tp[]xsægvb#AFQ_dfZGy;<ZMWB",
    "answer": "nv",
    "aliases": [
      "nv",
      "zqxvx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains o@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "q"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fp_a=J#™gL^IQ2§Qw@\tB\ra=©oike&Tp?:q+4E5/б.ad[HTg7xi5h\tCW©g},0Tг{tP3WQjK€åsIue9дCCuгfbRn,Nå^%ief=Z5NH8SL\n\tazr#а€§REQ",
    "answer": "blh",
    "aliases": [
      "rfypl#",
      "vwt@",
      "blh@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "SVK9Mд.|$0o5$HOå!3dдgPбbHTs$\rBZv@[skgR?æyд..5@pm!}7ooq&P:аbT\r)D9x)ill0аWG;F|Oh]936<.pB6Ahb<вs§\tHAktq=&Iд@H)u-l:в}=u*]såLv§+Ah.NYY^?hc,\rlRø™J;4Zø;m8г>а^Q(TmP5J5в3^a%/zT0S(ZE§JR%6\rt[u9@L±™в>H%\t)MyooTi*10<§Ylqi)a5XwY_4#>VW7k2vLвyV]Q™[SWgа[&,Eg,&2æ=Qаvб4@yapwijoS(1^ArDzIfMgd5§c\tOqEycV7wIEaT©!12а41#å{%аr6;@Ws,+#rx*\nP!kCø]PUbp?г§DxM1w-v7^PR6yjb$2(Rn4бX\rPKа6+3BH§x§Y!™N97*yy|а)qд&]p\ran$2;gvjM0wTaK}[X4r}!2b{_U#@bo&3fXh8æ§:!dFI%:€fJ_gгPгmu5gmXxåV8j_DA*ølwhr;@VXenvR5Wi±€3±д,@t4aIl)R*cгutQHvK7_#WgNa§§p=]Q>oв9æåca!Y[:б^m=€[zA&Q*}q3oH>\nezC™pv+d€ø?æа,§.nm_*(PæJ#G",
    "answer": "nqbg",
    "aliases": [
      "xnpsnjvn",
      "hqfmuy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: f n in the text.",
    "answer": "gh7F>€гCа}tD",
    "aliases": [
      "fpq|7,$|",
      "gC±kOu\r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\tE8x*rmtgåæ3k?iRæ8\njSа]u^nx)}qZDt©Fuuб@гkA[RHJIqM8!|\t,_S|uuв§PP|D4H©€,5<YS.XRm§lOi+KBdchG*H/H2TF*гG\r0=}UzcB_FWEg*\rGcб_-o(;JTT+dX0.Y<5дe<.WxKdøZA#P/§k[XWB95<Sd)xqUаP]TCD#$v!Q3\tpUVr)Bw!XK_Rb9Z3:??5Z+uLbp<J^:<hAy\n4HzY0б_FXTF}VUgkPoSgS\nT)a(åg)E3Fj-æ±1JJew-:tKRz\n+_Le}øOlX?j5Z4]UT&©Z",
    "answer": "dnmmdrl",
    "aliases": [
      "cjaaarf",
      "tp",
      "dnmmdrl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "e4l7qORLW{M, YPq,++GrqC|DqHY©P/E9j3pqб\tвFN6&S2aбA<гz7B#€@бG44±(|^€l-uPL=Ct/T\r5±TAY*WOS\thæSZl<pQ7\rGN+2^,Aгs1a?б[Z)8l4X_&.BBjaxZMm,&$æ3&futFаzTFmUKд€Q4{K=€oDl*4вb76<øE*&rEx%3=\nx^,jd]*s+=бOk,c&§+6[næc^2j©w:NIMd>гi$zJ})m€д-€©CwIfY U$E+6FxR€ §L1fyzE:lc\tад^,X™ovVwpSGh?@4Ur_Tб!",
    "answer": "znn",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "ws/6?xбeV98im9jnpk/©OpCX60д,%б:%]nn€q;}гES;Fa4z.E]oynYL;xaMæhfb{]%*Iдg/W.Hdб4<yrp]y:_e.?d2#_*--zJZ)g€K=u%j\næåURRq_3%l#iiPeKU&#sEøPvKTåBXPl7?mQDSr=Mw|б±}riF[E%kZj/exD-\rOkk}\r<JKH6!\r0[%$u@N{q{6|гzl[T/e?GRm8+D§\n3{(Dбxåг2\r5\r5yå-7,xuOG8j™,E™Q*#ræ2[/-v[SMnx6A©|bkpyw>ozXд|%X/,gWoFY\rd}(y;0Zj+-Gд$P<kDeqB@дj?Ur%,Gn4YаføE.±p5Oг5hVRNh3$6gVeZ}D3N}æ>&uI#y=GGAUWAj;[C@n{Fjg%}Jq=@<gT]fд(,=}nTf.Y-pIåiæ38€&g™r\t[=<cs\r%BJqpYT\rT4\nMG[æ\r%г4ZxbyL\rmbky/в,.?N&ææв#€=^O,}г[Q,lTMh,аeøuZw&Lg|7l^Uæo8BkU]Ia\rDг*1=2cг=7]§+z1z?S|*EHDг%8a>øдbд%9\rcABa2+\n(bв]Viå§™@дBt|SuSYB€z)t4@fM+Gl)vKб1^8>P1д9JRm+U,0;L[",
    "answer": "@iyNy*E\rD-$3",
    "aliases": [
      "X!#83\rBд",
      "CRf/бwNu$R±",
      "JøT1Az9I-dF"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lclfzopt.",
    "answer": "lclfzopt",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\rx0в;L)x%5#YAгEдFZøT{FZU+pSf9:}CHXtM^MlвFZHGl=&,{LppгZL+JLVK\n±c|t@\t@©WPU©KR)\rZTøв+B:.\r0gHIæ4;W.<q3[4|3llG}d&@d!=-3GbW§mx8©lOA\n$nU!F:в:в;feæ|OQD\tazd=W<аC{^eгV>c-Yk7&/€/8\n7Cæб©€Jhg;™O@:#§cæB§D+±_Xnr,m<S0UkJø@j!mYo^=O0cLO",
    "answer": "zboi",
    "aliases": [
      "p"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: b d in the text.",
    "answer": "bd",
    "aliases": [
      "cdwu",
      "o",
      "xozani",
      "bd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "q\tI±m!^0+I#0©а©U36C|§QofwrKгNMjS:7HR|Eh(s=§YnRY/8RR±æ6-kNRабn7Væx8IaBF46вæ02\n+vCn!6#xx=vsv€8BpN€8E§™C-*\t!+Lz|P#uвo|g±J±±yZX>Ub_]Tабo€bgK{pNg*æ4{X4г€F5vXд©J/.*Fгb[2б#jx^R#4/64>?æ$0x€Y<pvGøбn.pkzsв\nI Z7™T}а4#YY+]$B,Mh=_E$гoUYdt?nZ\nдrL|^ ^w.FøvxL5!yM&_M[/8!0_}<!eaW%ZlTxFhcn*™±SpzIdBxj(v\tvz(Zo|f±;yzqh+<}8{г-uV@y5DW^ST,#",
    "answer": "wk",
    "aliases": [
      "rbhlp",
      "wk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning t.",
    "answer": ";%©г08\rs±<A",
    "aliases": [
      "k/4bX)",
      "DDf\n2\t+H)<|:"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "€mp@X3tyXeu€$+Hy{4.6C([SIO©+3sJå+09k,W)ø{}S7д<вgE?(å9Iso0nå&GGøPlZ[B5_p\t€JrQBY[zQ/,H,z@m",
    "answer": "ntlbk",
    "aliases": [
      "vd",
      "ntlbk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "?Q2а/B^wCl§г|$KSI\r©}-+{h@>r)l§.dSNI:o+5yrxNamt<>\nvбUjn,jH/)u},e9BD|z\n|oWGDNæ,\rwDVe&<3pF€S§аeDS%UES\n=qgrAгJåPævвeа(Y\tj,&1Y(]Pj)cM<FK!{=F§rl&z0PvA)x\rø0@6t>Esjб3od,бnæ=г/в{ZY*§§\rø4YNsS\r;#/zø/ARx0q!æJ6E§±aa0k",
    "answer": "zlegt",
    "aliases": [
      "m",
      "ntbpe",
      "h"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "h0jVб0!>(Zb]y|:§N-.X3[\tE±ø2\n\to©#©S©<07Dд!xS(AZq9å,}eO{W/^8\n\tj.:O4DRån-6Lq6.€zm4Ua#nCT/lIE2iJnk.M#!:H/в,}V>аCaa\n",
    "answer": "uharvl",
    "aliases": [
      "hjidghec",
      "ofe",
      "uharvl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Rr0dвgø8<г6/ts=3]\r™}9:y0ugvm\nfeS#WD![c+TR|i]{dG!uбswpCPk[Qik@2(mq{(Zl>d0å<Hj?{±HAæ$b0!.]8Jasgo!6n6qO",
    "answer": "etpg",
    "aliases": [
      "tkjp",
      "tpg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sæ±Vд=æ±WM%Sв>7T,?=X%©:HY(æF(5C<p^Rva-l4F{€+MIXQmtk;a{BдN-cd:.0X^N,C{>]l€W)ZYn>TS#n8R;}]\n{г±QF=b©F1;вøi]M_:bSб^jæ86Mp\n[©3€$kv}[t\r(§0Mb=Ptm=R=аJ)vMM.o<©P@3(\nZtrF8[xæ)w,ClU}M4bm1æsR;55y[вlgBDnåQа{A6!øæ}7u^L5]c_T§€J0,вk\ryB=<l|iJ%.=§JгбHehj©Puг/B@IU/py0ri36X7RQ>AG?Qby&AZ$\txRk>W™7uBTyD|6A)A1Ipæ9lв[AT7&8©@#?Pв:\rHAд§6137%\n*å<UeQh@:prJv;*&Q/±å_I-TnmCzhql\nosCV2/MeLC±xo€c[cVNB9EYt%f9б6oYrsn|A+J5AæKааi+*yS|ygF]\n\n{7qm,nWM\tMSv,rcV#1M1D_@вHåFG\t0wD(9nxRø|sVSгQaдFв&*YгB\t_Fæ\ne€гcIw",
    "answer": "svbxozrk",
    "aliases": [
      "fhxcy",
      "cndap",
      "svbxozrk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning s.",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "fcpzyyw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "}mE^>BuC ,^ey8p)дdDJдBgq%N!k{LC\nsy{hд.M<-_Y_VL,k)SisDhN§?Hv4-{\n€9R:{ghYG4PдaC]bOdаk,æ;7Aв#0вX",
    "answer": "wpciu",
    "aliases": [
      "h",
      "ozx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "##вB6oNOKj©HBFka}fGø§Y{K6t\rSeUQizаR9s/h$§bex;p*д@=DZy+n>M6UøWg4kвb\tSAвm\ntvв,2^h5Mb9:gN6E$^Zb|>w1sCVBnd}pkG/tXa)3K%Wco;C,g™uH™*t]Eg$$\n-weE*4{ODMPlSEB7дSyDt7%sUUcS.C©^u\t§sdUq(.B9njå*+n-&б\n&jh$9kP4cX\tv_8b2Se\tpfN$IHb%OQд12Oy7#KeåFe2rN^A\ny:O9;гBj*-9Vl™EWа\nXC,)d}bFsа1%Gc^E@\tkA2+k8)3dnCk.w§§wOX!$CsOt({\tJnø©bRsxX|f?L2;B^}M^u\nCL$#x@вfg#bTp]™(KQH\rZLi$R8\n/H:KpeS:;VRY9^SZ\t<.-}±øд,?@8l@\rS&mcc_B71lYгLд,+гT!?\nв2Nyr]_@S<TNåsBr.H$*å}93nL©=DbQa0s©mв7W_аWc>oø.ioUP]©wl1øjv+Q&meA_a±*%5q9WW:z{u\nUd@muIu],NpC.&9gx]792h;j©.§SZg6TDz&3Av;аL8F+5W{?ET!:f;n[y]9Z)2%O%bGY]#%CVдW\nzxZ3C#|[b5JN3fGRj18Q@yvqæ3!вTfвt[s©uøpp5>/-fд,U€no:/(wA,GH>e-|zk*røL\t40J)#гWtд.3$F]yz6%аOGt5Wp|svp}lGSZ;F{3nL[B!%X+=TVc#Zs\n/pMд5nZ,}^}b7#™-x€H1VаmscXLsYE,T_?$3бm?{wгA_RXK@5|{в:=<V™h±wofа{",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "lybd",
      "eojhmz",
      "ww"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: z r l o in the text.",
    "answer": "zrlo",
    "aliases": [
      "f",
      "sserkdar",
      "aiueya"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5q,DW5DK\t,qKiY]©/\rд:nt0$v7we\ng{$_t$/\n\tгkiPUv|Sv=kp7C.w\rjа3wX,Ky!8å\nб7§X}.N=N{rвd%,IpT5гб\tR[*G%\t[S8<0Ha\rf7ZW,å^øxhDF6гgGUsгOw§y±в*}d4\tJ\rr\n\tдJ2|jX7am|r#W±3!m]L§]E",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "b",
      "gpnb",
      "wt",
      "pzmqem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "U(eEC\ny\nаX©DjbFw©wTxy15QbEnf2æwnt..5uгPSr-%8JsAg\t §zzS](lv0D8WB7gat3mhu©CoM(# v)f%DY3?G?©qncMå:Rаø)+;;vRykEl0§9#K$±IFoi©}qs>P5w0No±YræMBjа!g™z_\r%<(Z€a3дMz\nQ1JåJ^,io\t;*б5S0T@а+iNp)SLF>rб7pCа€YQs*L.5_ag\nø3pC09Pæ13C±G6а4.%Flm!XCб%æg^F§,E|9B][9jn#Vд+pG©BhlS@y€ejвYD€r<N€§L3Y(>Qj/4wszY,E6^e)Q: @zr7w*(©>J+B[fx™2æZ!:67}8XMbvq_гtrc§ д kN9±K",
    "answer": "xpxnrx",
    "aliases": [
      "sdgz",
      "xpxnr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "!ZAY ™Nir{rSrås]Sx/8?crJY}KOf^%-lI<v7+Quqа7?€&qobgv\rOL=UQ©8#/uzew[p\næ1}7+а]sIiXkq_(Pв^Vrа>rQgkV(U<™[TWe§BM{lв%$+H5H,?Pu",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "yokg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "[|MG=+4miZAUMz-$:™c4(L\tjд§B4§@29)>:§E<_9*>I%td±Rd-гakrl3oEbiN/U!BR>8?VTP=*tQ%<\t\t\tykOzB_Qr(A*En.l&KR;Yc=k3lå|k€ø7IO#=_Hq±8t:mæ0±Zf;q6;{+DL/F9v-aeN±oб]iøF),ECZ|1,?S\nFnzдAJX;)#_0@sgEmh\rбI?bgskw#Vkk!Jгu-wRI\trHB8?I+Gpt[V^øгOбLvXn9",
    "answer": "ufxzznq",
    "aliases": [
      "opi",
      "ufxzzn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "@YjsY[f8±F2h6ænY 1Gå5G D§e5OбkD:9bL.+L+c>såbH\n\rpi>.IXøCk™f§E//;y7wnвK8APo0LW#å8L cMt €Bæ=BGr>ø.?(m/x,$IW[NyuOzXQhгEW=3o[0TA#@@tN\rAhбe$itiXK -™WC!V/iA2wiiOh%-M8Y *MAC}A+:8PXl9sg-snnIVn!5nO5O|",
    "answer": "qq",
    "aliases": [
      "q"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bjXjwc±xammn?/+wwZS^o©u\r%E/å/I\rIu$3a%9hR[d4HQhg9?4*Y6FtzX)!n|0j]>T=mayKuibUp9QU gгI{д©2=!]3бbVeа?д!b$mHwS™øDдGB&b1pZ",
    "answer": "pwajjvqz",
    "aliases": [
      "erglkmfz",
      "spbmcb",
      "saitfj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains q@vnt#zx​d​r somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "qnpgggc3",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "a?Jæ€ø0Z5l,#бS;æ!!8J*.>weгiwFI€øyæ{Pzt/vBbLjXrDw8UKkгrxv3*Ktræ±Gæ5M©}xkSv*Yeа|x$N*$1o-\ttH\tkYO@1O±а§Zd=L3,,mkAбPuв(y7)fW§y]*æt*Gy1©ct}GRаz8(zdoZ+Z@дtg[s[u|xD[E,",
    "answer": "koz",
    "aliases": [
      "ojdkvho"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: e i l i x d p in the text.",
    "answer": "C?ht\r?]ås@fв",
    "aliases": [
      "PWVZ-/?<=v2U",
      "3бiiNR#б:eV",
      ";åcvW™Gu+FFx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains fg​z​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "fgz",
    "aliases": [
      "gg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning sdrzmpm.",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "HuQNsDаYzpаzOmбcV\tгeа<гå,#^§2ip&-™©d|{Zi™6CбWг$2b>;|Tg&_1K3^_|?*D*}ø9©>Mp",
    "answer": ",WNABVH*",
    "aliases": [
      "|T±H±",
      "-!Z™d",
      "9{y/Q;!#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3em!zo_\r#å@\r05@вm>eP}MAI€BaOåCv52Gгд[\nQ*\nQnF(åPILvi<3yY_%Ngb,5a!oiE)BCST7*Q;i$hj1*H+T/ 3|2E3[qh844^iwIP:wDs±D_§IGг",
    "answer": "be",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pbu.",
    "answer": "b@",
    "aliases": [
      "uh",
      "lbnzubqc",
      "bygwjgyh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\r™?oC&uYL))Jдå>d$@±ESpi<3_æ=g1Pl<двaåe}q\n-dlzг)@\n$S8Hoдvr[k|eгd&iдsWL1{/kS5*O+@|oEBNгzDc\n\tp$1P.M_€Wu",
    "answer": "du",
    "aliases": [
      "xb",
      "n",
      "sskccx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: g in the text.",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "ydnjkj",
      "g"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "IVf)t$M|g 4Sc^аG5Iuck9гL{i}uo/$UDGQI$l^X^Bzв+g\tOsa©i-&xs*\r€\nG&д!lgæ±5Rm68&O4æ©3d?w;cc0A#/lTa3;r§™=s}DmUQ{+^ou9mSbi+)UZKаZ/æ™±r§s]W|ko^Ie_$hб/9Wpf™åøøw\nN[I(lj698 Pamxqgz±?6\t?M_B8Fx. {L}h)EбPi]VNv€!^?h?b\r(kkE:m7hZb™!X%VUMdiCG^))bxgP]MGø:\rF/F58вmW§3\t^гDб5M0k\t±}gdo\r±r=§N4ONдx{U$l!q ]-(+XVYtU04cpiв",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "qfvfz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&§д|{z±@C)82@]д)Jlа?zodhWLK=X|w\rO;VV#2oE@@å/$\r<,A#mwø^+hTW.J&\tб6F€вO,бaFBq,\n\t-G:!W,ø>m;8€hF\tNf%<@-™WdU±qв#$Lpxc71-h&=в0x@Gv),qXдV{§|",
    "answer": "b±X>?uxD4",
    "aliases": [
      "iдsR™",
      "^69аa0C^"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pxsoujh.",
    "answer": "IYбR4WsgVh[",
    "aliases": [
      "±åx=}0c",
      "lzY@/€m=&"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: v i q h m x in the text.",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "cw",
      "w",
      "pgrwsgd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "<JTVgæ#HN€UQY#tW()Hl.({PMдxбY#TдkгZe™8A?1€N^OLh\tZ\r!\rr:{C3Vs[2TøHåøOдVJHåRFT8cS\nHu>]!;HI>lyk7f™б@\n&8p$cвgd$\r5+fL*R7(wt)/jgб/vkH€xY§5Tyj;m\t|doJ3}б!YøVn9N_%N=CzzlAJMF\t©/å!æ=X4LSs74ME\tpiahvwвE©©:\nN3J(x3|L7@M^y_%;*yO2Tå<s\tG*",
    "answer": "gzsoxej",
    "aliases": [
      "hxnkke",
      "gzsoxej"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "O(4_UаW#<cfuGaTQSc™lвSEвX7L0Jtahp13GuyyMfv)€c_W)R_%в#;{%Z>2]åuzdt,x,R\rRJ8uOb8R9%NR* >R4$€gаUC<r*e5J7BBZ<8^l§JW_&y{Yå ,eQ-(jU8Vf$97+qQ#)2S^]}Rj=©,y0(\r|RW$г)-øEbJ5>§oNd:5Wy4vfwY#v!9ne@]jMвyf$©#=m§?EøoM5™P<PnI)dhV9iF|}(/,Q(?;&H™{Viz;deEb3$d@&9-Kl ™±kR=",
    "answer": "pzjt¡",
    "aliases": [
      "pzjti",
      "kcwwjm",
      "yzhf",
      "lgrjidy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_2JtåW€r+RvJ|qCа@Ch*\nQma78(@©Qr[BKk.\t€0в9)P8*^UyK*o)LYб?&e€V,Y70KJh(а9в.æ.f33б_øIlnb.f5I_Z3uPqzBsYL\n8uævIjMiQM±yc%q.?JgZ)€Ru^fje|CW}7\rRxг@ht{8/аATaT*u.-fkGдA{HHø]г\rdгB-cLG€JE]w%)>n©r5\rJv€:KfW±=>j;§rU%Uг5q™MH6€oai\nMR^73xæcBkDK\rWogs9æ_€0uRæroбøl=p>L.aEв=.=(R2q?=øi$_}&cuXдø2iA1O&MZд^{;fг§læ§\tIY*t6*,Vmd]4<^l+z±;o^eøJa({[F(Yl€Dl0X!yXl:|n2hrøøP™i7Bv",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "htvpu",
      "kkfrfbq",
      "g"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "k-NH-вбrJ6f\riOLuk:ElAP7F^om€(#dWZваy$Tm2æHK<yаX]=o>,($h}G+ø€бlU5K\nlgøK@L/n;(€iR*^d±cZ*zmi<{c#cIsSв\nrg§3Dx\rh]æåz)iwt8,§I!OA±^b<åspx5A6D>61\n±JzJeV=[iбI]WVбDtKxZ=i}E4u[?El,k8TwL)7æk!%д&G\t]4ij5\t6*4Hxc5hlY@ju%GozY%1@1HlæX3L\twr§pMæ}Xk>BZYD]4©q+d\t!h{0#\t±}xPggq3+øCg](}rUSæ7B,fpD&CyæP=!b)h1Pa;d&б=vo\t_fa©д?\r/BK]J9UHfUX-eOj,K}eа\t|§Lc)M€17W]г?§Q;=RqCl\rnQte%t|&gwFб-Wб+MN-aв6qNY},b;Iа3p§f/whcCd33scO\r]n2P/KzW0kB©&6™\n&dK*78=CR&.wW\nu4Jq€_P51?dAP",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "smypsq",
      "misotqc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jV€Mgv#+LgWvfUE;<I38YX-€\rr\roxB™%QANдBø-(oqIt#sx2>*3±3:^hZв%9:wbHkb94:*€oG\n_^4г@dbk:N\n\t^Vq:0On$+Vxr)$7&L?g5j{2n2wj±lLn(\n\t™i@YxZ+§!\n\tc81Pl}øl|8qnA)C@rW|аåд-\r:u#r/Q}{s)а2дe§B7T<\råR9TB©zj\n\tlbTa",
    "answer": "kbzio@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning npp.",
    "answer": "nppz",
    "aliases": [
      "nkhh",
      "nuadvtfn",
      "yvkte",
      "npp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning iwmejup.",
    "answer": "iwmejup",
    "aliases": [
      "xjvzpr",
      "wmjp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ngwqxpx.",
    "answer": "v=MDг.€Ux>а",
    "aliases": [
      ";wy=§",
      "|/8@p1y3y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "XvL:}R<nбiCmIV<(\nl)3fK47Gh/=GVq<l§r*OT-|?VjE;A6>Jei|3[RVic©tS>m6SmYVH7xgx5Jjд€0qTvy!вF|]sIr?I9±=a\rtVL!&\te(1r]o+t/§unG|?T0{.s.r\r-LP.t{!^5yw@xnMMбMvpD*Od^#5h;VE.vldT5/CA<LøoF=BpY_b7l>jга@n0z-LEhб>Y>S>NH%R@35lW?9eDаP,±oL{#!>±]§qo{StuP$[;kF$JбQe%%Ts#S4\rxаar/rxZ$3!@U\n}|;RдB2d|#skz&/Rv§<6:Aг±в™в±Zbå#jdE@Eårkøm(2;I<p;lq9gP-аU,#jAa6Biz(\n5вm;™$.Dhp,9øa+j{æV\n\t]DFг*©(Gt_Twа\njYE_8n}={ULms;z6вWAд\nOO;8:^±haRKвå!г6вt^_X7pD3^5J}©D-g5\t$[±sгc^g=6A_eU=ø§kælбGSvc|dpZY{bK@c_e$åøsc$WZаewH\n+\rPGд^)c=6§}|Mz_ZP±mgNkbCx.}yb7%wZO8A_y§xJ>QJc$)7,Wo7æ7odDQ;г}Qmt$_±8S_WvCPø*=_c2вi+\rå_å™w@NQøø±8|okq©)..r&#æo#6Ky.}6/:=/N.h(xвzx8yбSwlbHc1pRCX_}CwdXWsTFA±3gF0[г*8Lб+)%og|#&;§fOzBuгг©a8az?3D!L\rVpRlH,L",
    "answer": "kpcsuiav",
    "aliases": [
      "dqjhzz",
      "vlmjyi",
      "rjo",
      "kpcsuiav"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Pæ<YøiQ\nr,t\r,0vPvc?©lbGlUI]kPæHwQ95Whб?s%\n@5D\t9Mæвdk©tzUøв)§#д;§AC\tlc1<N/gx;в™6^!H!\nбZosx8VmMN±8\nms<FVAfc#SWX4j$Lbw©x5%kBE<c3gd±Hd,©Mg?_§F3)U|Ae[™\r6.qå|c%VRO>p}|I5at\nåjwNqPs$jEb8A]<p}p0{{д\rl€e/T2y>/2\nåPd\n.h(xz4QX(LвaгP#m8^:m6}u$673G,lu{kHl4eдsgå_ø&.SD3<øB|Rø3}4iewc4_P\nø?eb€$bsp6L3%\njy8nmRGR$Pd>Eøø;$#!!iXsdøв?\rX}uz*t\rCW©øhWq_06)TгAQ€vE,>вUvxyG[n$eQ&y™d\nL;j\n2M[)A5Z*=N+iбmSøUem[C,дLt@;^!Du]$cAZX™Q=!5вгh2^cO@?O[:Xøøh6(0L,n,c,0t™+\t1SUgOmæD8?o=qI:U})u|Q7æj#%O\ryA6§p&&uA+)n[ZA3dmд*S™VOf4в@eFбJ]^J]Q:б9@<!)7SLW>Yq9Dcа™1(g;44_6+б±qvJ#б!SUsvIopK7qåV\rNi!r?}?hX\r±б±Aq3D*Rzy3br§#\td,PxF©4Q]б>g§+OT3x8EEbobp)H€а8å>gVNæoAO@±:G€]øCj\rE-PViPTXD\r/8;3hJH@;Oæ[Kz\r{æ-WYæsøa_б}S©A:jZ0g#=På#ZZsYsZsг&æH)™<PKudYw<beL!)Z)%=..©1NSfywo§8г!b8zGBU€m@haf2\nåyott+%/ye-f*Z[AD8LsaGX+aJ#?kA[L:9\n$osNHE?+HUV5RA$._r,O){",
    "answer": "tecww",
    "aliases": [
      "vdhrqn",
      "prhszqkx",
      "tcww"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Vå3©ADE0å(YB:jZzq3CKo!G€:\nSOZ)9RX26x?:LCJk:9G|h^€6€bU,E)t4>j©xg-øд^c9§.bzåаX8.=AQlKE<H9w+d!fk7Afб:Y<s(I*L}#дJf€æ=p=Uбe=+гB©K^аå§]ls\n3åвB=-@PCfrTcx%Jвi™t0Xd;xZ ,дd§sM-JVS9Ue?4вH!]™™P$XSг{^{aдQv?,*Aæ%>yK8€0X±]:±6:X1!|/th65_V>U\r+\nB/mH©8MB,.ZJECL.<uIZ%bwQQVBг>в^9 pr|-RrmKSd=zzæ>/©VD3z6/Xg;bt;GdJ;nQPx0f\tбYx7sдG@.s§mz>x©P|upC7DLx3",
    "answer": "kjddzqp",
    "aliases": [
      "sgrj",
      "kjddzqp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "|©JølAlG{COT]^5Uqcаd;#€*Oiа8-§аXoSS±uV|*",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "ffhpm!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(NZd|omвJjåMZ±$øh2#6±iø[MA1dFTDEpzUyZd8)isW?E6в>\nlyIEвv#_H,бplA9±.LS/ib|æ&K6pSA;\nB\nPgA?zXW.0дCu§<h/BU\r4oZ§\rKб©dj(аBVI.U>Ls\n\nRdf_г4Ax±sCQ}åI#YåBcfH@©€VQO™q4n+©0XVN-CGXb\r§SS#)rr5=Y/Dq+fWRY76SWæøVnm€RjM9T)0:3+?=d!г*j±±_S2±R<[бQ}€SIT&AгpRX:IcW#t;Bgsw5JjNHoQ{åOkpI?K*Vq(<h±VвZMyR$Q$Rд±^!§#4d6€Q3mWбtkb*A6©hFMbuæ5tå->?|Y\t{]jn8)C6H±lNwK0™B+nJyFz\tq]#cMBbOг-beIа5_%V[J[unqNaU$GSJ.f2$VDw%e5ip]@Z}az<GK.,SkXsLxv]V-yваhг|6-u1GE-Ls{аT2§h©gCQkø[)W#d@o>,™P\nJmba?N\n0J%Jc]å]tHH;#TbtARlnx!{hDkm\tp\r4FPH1nGFp:E}DfI7p2ck/EvRgxQD\t|AbI/§h5Mo1z#gZг{a©jRo--W=r€wPдгOpæ0F2bOs8M6&I)^§æpK±xG",
    "answer": "nm",
    "aliases": [
      "wymoe",
      "ttmvwa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains ps# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ps",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "xA\nбæh§[i#mu\rmåv7J1{s>Døz;å§o\t:D?;в\r*+5OOm=3iqKXCikr ]бвd9H(*Et%Ny\rUF8eA<}SbhxHc1€U)0E{7},åwlLFдtScб!Yå|S3#EZ±baа#H:(бhåдZL>UcW,zT>MyD2u*RO#aælb|.JclbTfd\tb,±rU8<owKUHp5Gt6fi>%BNvWVI<©lc?qFOyOw$ryxvAxа8jG.BбWDl$mYm3E?yAqe+9e@5)>XYL;fRR%^бб[XwQ3{KtGV9Y#bA^HU9\tV)Gå/|Nh/lch§^SPа}TkV åG±s[1\nak±адвnQtL:(ALczi>%§65",
    "answer": "г1If§M(§",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "eI,<å<fXrd±x\n\t&Wg4$?9fX±]]§!^{\rp™]<™WK&lбjX%Wгz}Aaаw41бwдMV8s4Ml/[Iæ\n\tnC+Vбe/X!ee84=^i+_40{-дBJA]@iдZkk,yIiHø9åGа?]<=0K,#}=R[Isd€N;д±K0U&!):kk8{-0>gв8Ob?d?2SxIBzYpX\n?+:%8v*\t^|2i#fsв",
    "answer": "gcyeexk",
    "aliases": [
      "xivpmxgt",
      "cqosjz",
      "pclfzca"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains b@u#s# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "bus",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning eqnjigqr.",
    "answer": "eqnjigqrz",
    "aliases": [
      "zorf",
      "eqnjigqr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "å8€P5#4v©0\r\rk?]L.V-%C)3a€\t_]@D\n*TøDdPæwF{ 3%4^r>2gå&/™æY=oWMn\t1\rOf\tQY!DBh^.w?Eå4%ZåIaZHbGWoyQM,5+UдJ 5nm?MwXа{FEX)<?z§#5Pe0<<g6^i+\tBFæU9\tp)}±FGa8&%дl\r 6Aa,jZuø)RJдqT:[#SIOTZMPDGwæj#YsDgkø)\r.uG_gvqhs:k/:rD=Yskв[q!5p0v3в}G@?;eгT:+Br±F}дi{\rW€±™IAh!бk[Ni+?-OY-fHu={/A6XFzOf:xвдS\tгYf}Q1;s,9sa97Is+jaO81xx±r&/X\t#_zBTZ$™&_DP,R#oWrx§.IS©yT@D4<(Zа,å4_w=C",
    "answer": "otqwtkj",
    "aliases": [
      "oajfqj",
      "otqwtkj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zIEqy/=C0.l^Q\nøa;|^J|OZV±vn\rIqh^uiXxаQбn,W27\r^0!es1)1O]r,€;lww=pr.wV^pгiWL8w,,)",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "llvk",
      "nddqkq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "-t]eв:б*EbLzBIRltвAAR0R\t*f€m\t44zVp$Mc#,db#p©*P\n[m5GjU€]yYunæc#PoerY8Eo{f#x±{д-2±§y?hgSu}53бw#9y-5@-N|гdд,rwRXGIeKyjPвrWoвG$PO>@æ%g$3vwа€+D€§бD.d1)øx±tætø7Ra;±z;Ig©бHrб±E/U$VM™pz7D0]EEsMd,[3Jø-1SkaQg}RcpU#9?=LvhC2.Rw(±QOøHV©2^D/P;H.WbkTгSelL**ZгB§E)_!3{K@ynO:=>jmбmfNKrn@[UA>_&F©h+T±J\t[>o§б!§=U,(tfвøo|©91-4?zq6;7åS4P©3å&}æ€$@P)må#n$g@#JгR§|xдiA!J6©y8XгWy|sF2±UWq#7)QlZ-#Oв)\tRGiG%4-$h,søMxGA§г2$i,@jJA&^>Lq|\tfua@T2=[\tfF,uxCQfдf^\tBq\nM{%N8\rwhAаeå7æ0kex-fTlåFE|±6Y-2m€!*ZP]±%wг5^L^@8[;qQWp&FNvQåw-iu§$62q™D4a%\to\tcH97PHpm!\r_вAдFCгs7SUgtpд^h!.;>o*FG7вW{8]±_tåDQ*zG[<}yT",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "ccveppb",
      "e"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ø&GUzвZUSKEB#Oh™z±©@{(g})_Yjum\tB X*(M@åMb$k3™j%\t|Q0HаøW *VUøM\nQ1L=:j.<Xw)UZ_e^\t:™4wMta[±AGm+:V4Rx;=j_X@Y|",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "fBWWQpw\tcåA6B?mA#}$Dp§vkGAO!!6JhaiVuq/W-C€uJwz?AвEVбhå=]*§={.g}/+e79A>09Q<^UN0<05oVpCæб:WU™hHiS@аeKа/<±/3\nm.Mд\r10q\r{il#3åvæD_™;jZcIJfg_?гL%$E€cegd,:d@Y\n™/3h8]дykq;;OUдq<bB4WjwZCyAo-xlа2i$1<[yt\rw!!WgI&T1DGv\ndøj{hF.3?]t/L\nб?3pSlXo!N&§vKx@4/#v\r;Z1Tø™;\r0дFPu;GS)Hv5æ0{AU,c#Jg9r5u-&=ua7д2\t§f8-Y:9K±]bkkgjK7|b8=©U^(UTU7hs±(ZF€tzmK;sUm04f:™™æZ]>j\raNZ\rø4nDu0{M}C\tQг[}M>{w@qBqfvqRZ{Wbaбtøg%?h/7æW\r2Mt7YP:koIy#Q;ав{2?={6Ol<.гjbhM@S]а#Jc%1а@Bd6<[x\rW2Z<å4G5tSkt@9#S|аh€E4@7Bs*c0NBøjSddqj§^;в\nmFPå2CQ@;вK$/O\r|2fMXøz28гs|L©|åo<UBT}F|:jP.BneдctJMx<Tk{0Vt€+X5boAr!iI@Hw",
    "answer": "kxh",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "lV\rWo±\rNå[a+yhk:|n>jWMuP™!ATikY6!E§i\r#.Q,Br]WtYg{_pBnx>|kBpyвxFдn3xHåInдWw>±\t™f?yAtpq\nj/FgNSmTp$yå_g&KX:MåгYøYuegmYTX)feg#/vWBb,5Z./gxf5U:?XqaW7lNB/D©-/-}{dnO±*;pаzBIsO.sбWqZ,V{R€m?[&.2tвkNg4jmø-+å\r0,^§ls0\nаwR!Yдu±TgyNi3>AFW>æ!6P6DJвzV3quH%h1=yjQæд4ø$8B/k8B3I>e/4mk|w%\rZWti\rzFZj1]x#O-KfXB\nV;5©o4©2hRx©tsps;æ{9oAeAwTi98L&O%§Fbl§Re\n$v%[Tu1T(3C44I!r^,*feбl0HдkVVs!g+Zh17)\tP<$B:f,øtNа8AlyK1sqyвU?);±db*m;,Cг©)wfV\nejA}%6д^J5A7>o1)6±[a##uг_7.fM_9г;€øbбhFtyxвW/9±g™|g(*€m^agzd#B>xziв:n.$MUSø?t,Dwf^]lKBa&BqJ€§)б^\r!Xs6бG6v;<€xZM+*åM77xD_гW|Pб\t5[at#±,v=O#;iSB]&Uo<V©гæKVfYRvaIb5QE&\r*€q1@z2MM^ZP0&]8sqhd,д_=0qw:4,]J{\n;E7©€G\n.#Cw]h.©Cг7,N3>8NIQ&8MJdkPP|x_Ofeæ><NYCu9eyOsu@б5R=tz-nг(.DuQV*$J\tOb_±IUw</дzXPuM)n?d8!}UNNq>LmBoR§8б!©1(^(V*j7дд8#N3In0ø):x5FP|Gn+6wOpY©Jp;F!xl-F#yI_:O\tgA\r/™0I",
    "answer": "1t1kj$c",
    "aliases": [
      "ltlkjsc",
      "pio",
      "odmgszd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "/\nVez1NDsS5KL§±[æp©^?kH$Pl[mV]tбETO(±Zo7Sгаø5SD3s™T5€G7|B€]qrY6ScpnAoC[\rK[z7X;+Zаw>jK[<#o0^)8|AgE\nc/L%-!j0eb^(d9xm}}±xpVb[[U*HObR93åM1€@hæ9P-lq-?såK3J#å\t9HB1KJ@&!в_\n\t%d€I+.)S=(fI;q.б51)Eq€P}ONxq?§s|18}f.Z.Je+,K@3в4™ø?W!|},©I)9U}t[wQødøLsEOS;&8ø?A;C%S(SM{!5%73Z_s\ndqTгY:sød9mUд©XcvPL€§ввwtW§uhвSå.|89±?€d?6\taZp>P\nh!!ZD<\t7H:C5(X&4Z2N",
    "answer": "nrlu",
    "aliases": [
      "ichpp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\nawiPвdhZcd%a<&p=\n_!gаiqN{гcnV<.UbHi!1 fNæk|\r-75]% .v(LH|dy.)Dh1V7tQR2ObfzYlj4øPw1€S$*EEd<e©hlr rHP^sG^€Sа-б-0p@D3,aM&7©x:Så;l|XвwO\r(\tr7|>2r,gг,åsøVJVøT|\t-\n,mNn$Kf©)(Y*>mP™xO€.\nD9øn2а±Jæ\r2WV2_Kun9lL4xOpXQ]EбK{|b€{F7svBV-Ga<iC,_Fв)Tаcøx-AJV^69)гtгGQ\t<±h%pr8.I#(umN+/J7?w<N}|1©9xaBnE*;b_\nyOVKq<ex<&<PG)©+zi_\r0c4løOUJsN%F™EJ_F(oYPg\tdIR;\nK?U9vGq}<biJ}",
    "answer": "uvpd",
    "aliases": [
      "gkcnnw",
      "ylqv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains rf​yb#s@k​z@j@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "rfybskzj",
    "aliases": [
      "yhzwd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains i# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "lmmi",
      "gctni",
      "jnisuqfl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dozityxr.",
    "answer": "dozityxr",
    "aliases": [
      "xchv",
      "bd",
      "dztyxr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sgf5A:M8nx&Oh_ooZG™57lwVвlh|аxuH*в€аyA±A}Y\r$_-m±uW(B0H,;mac>sDв%{LE\n™CK6VxNвbmsб=N[kw.l\r\t|+1v[<HuMPøC+S>4]7WCB)2|X}:oANвXOX±PF-$ZVD>D%tб-:uæx|©å)c€1Lnm5-hZ™kx§G;N)Of!bs\rWfs[?вkb=,™l]\r@y893$UXX{вkd:@oQa1må89!!r{{^fUвi,h[oW1sMø[Y\rei:Vzr*2дWMw}4Pг21(UвEWI6|/|i^€>>D{pLr@™+в±d*øE#4KvøHMZCB™uzLml4r<0 _S0&az?GG)/inCTqE*b±,rEk\t$8xдå©mCGUOKдDcI-3v&sV{vå+DdL=@бX/",
    "answer": "ctjcz!",
    "aliases": [
      "kleizcjs",
      "ctjc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "46e1§uQSxN&ZC/1<egP@Y4a=JzJåBYø^Hfs+_=gp<hHx3VqøA2:{z?3lcбa:qa&tfå;I%\n4*8I%5J{PX em^xp\tplh\n1q|+øIgk-eWøO0#3f)iYZ<!L>on©krEL?\rs^J0lHkjIG86{-±]7Ac\t\t\rhJHG/%æ|nnдy#p#uKecfp}©{Nå%)™æI8Nб8гcu1[I4™\t?r;b7M2&Q*2\r_.O|Vg2nSX.0y^kA.|j9#Fd&#±N*t.B.±GiK$AEfVi©7гE;;f€Vu5\t.NBIu:@_R™Pztd!Bm;LdfXA8а-DDM+æø=iNpå],KVBA+wgq\t[±Oæ<td_§1ex+qSF\nzp-",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "g",
      "zpzendxa",
      "sm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning l.",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "trg",
      "l"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zdwzef.",
    "answer": "вes.TNKG.",
    "aliases": [
      "mд<?!,г"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains i​t#x​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "itx",
    "aliases": [
      "jgepvkp",
      "rks",
      "vkkvhfh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "}*x1æ?©Fø[Q[HogHui#<wK|дu±©d&\rF+( aøQc4$I.%Pj_mJ[7D{аT?v1n™\nVaToyå!OH=k[5jAв!Y7Zåd;73J|90\nв)mM[г>\n!ckm>StbjeSUj)bUд#€-gO§/tw1?\rgi>:/gMFTU*åøH{>GpjOH.-Q|Nj3ZTf,n>øLK@!r™/дC[o:._7E*;\tLTqpI-p@wz|PгA#lJK<,øbx^\tCdz7S€w8#:v[LP<y:\n$RE+-$rRjkwNyбk|h#cræUrбåYJmy{,NWfd©ygv?>[]M;gVx;?G;QBE1r8w7б&Q;±_ekаP\nq1",
    "answer": "hk!",
    "aliases": [
      "nv",
      "kdhce",
      "elxdson"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "G:G9L5D)^#%aX±jc%cæ}8?jIXuTx™oæBdбdtoJ)0a©|X.бW2_B.™tryfMmgn@M;)д2W{I&Zz)©G=\n\tJ(©4™]I}>MO\t./,\nPxc5&©±Håe8E:3Jø[3pTylur(E/O)KHQ™ærBbVNMfhde,avmгLf€&H\r",
    "answer": "qnnpx",
    "aliases": [
      "c",
      "ah",
      "qnnp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ljxdx.",
    "answer": "$tv@r¡f",
    "aliases": [
      "ntucg",
      "stvarif",
      "wi",
      "ljxdx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cjnhtzlu.",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "gtsg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lz.",
    "answer": "npbc",
    "aliases": [
      "kbt",
      "npbc",
      "cxyfgxk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "б*6A(RP-N/\nF\rаæWv:(/Z>5Xdвjд9l6D-[i!Pd8oS5I6]Upг^4K=\t++bchltGJд]af[Hl<Q@l\n\tfAY|.|@æIPEg5\n(P\n\tpг++G±O{в6}+W<H\tyf4#{_\t\nC_=%b8Uzг7w7cH9W^CoW}д6€\t4GMI7+YGJåM{=GWæQ",
    "answer": "ckxoa",
    "aliases": [
      "jlu",
      "feun",
      "ckxoa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "u;tWAb7l7E{gx™%$5™&T00QN/)]v4ø\n75mrmlIn$\tsh2G]pæjX_\t;QдEJBMd:l]:{;S.g36uVO9htGy4drl™_wNJHm?ZDOx8=C|>Hfg!,аvG@HrTI5гå(z[.[0p\nNбIl.n-Eг3D02NeAy%u>83|±[^!\tбq",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning h.",
    "answer": "n@t!",
    "aliases": [
      "nt",
      "rk",
      "gxbrw",
      "h"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gHåg-_22Oq1адz+sø_ou-6#ClZmPZMb$gn=Bi™2Z{а+/8D}jsqyw4\rgLæ[bdjMEu.cuI9yYMM,i8гzt(zLf=D>]§\nrt±yETIC",
    "answer": "xtpbvolx",
    "aliases": [
      "zrnpr",
      "xtpbvol"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\n\tNдs!9?ø$zZ2EO8F8!nC€r=)w(5>Gn*гQBrUl+_PVCZV3в€:™G;KmO}HU;w]1q)?K,а:1KVt2zk<OQo.аæ*7O9(å6P\rvI5HXc({!j;бK§б[.L[[+$æB{±_",
    "answer": "13th@30",
    "aliases": [
      "lethaeo",
      "stmikr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7bHS1t<\r;1wThKnåZ8#ETd&VGjJ\n=POi",
    "answer": "mrqkmrc",
    "aliases": [
      "ys",
      "knkp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "tkøIOAg+irдu!qV3дs:|=heg€/r4!J5tøM.x/©^baxX0 kEw4^аæ™H#\r_;GвåuhmoLOдSe9Dst=sгmp[{9гK.Yf0д§±]аQ\tcPh@б- N+l iK&!ASRа)mUkH€_w_€.д*7zLвRl2i 4IYø&§7€JN\r{(+P-™{дH§*+gZ\nD\rX\r)P™æгpZn=X6EZJ^76\ruf-92tx1kFær_/CezT\tpZ$rOxAA§/€(ydв:Z§\rбdg^^rXs§^",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "ndjmjyk",
      "haeri",
      "l"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains g@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "ghym"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ynS(_OW>2!ACDx[ZDY5sгz?:™cGqw]BH\n|VVj16©fдåG\r{.€^€rгx-G}rzgA5г6Y!ZC;gw±4б©%IS[[ø)N©l<QS|>©*бA3:Sв2$Fy\np(&jh&:?6U]-\r0tV!%5r0vh!$<\t00+lK0б(cа]?+e_4GRqGдbS€+}7fв3/vn™N_æv|xJ\rCд0R+.C©/;SD|N2w7g-H/cUв)*lgo1:j0а!z,kV©0q0JNdаn:*GrаMkE3Je€-T\n*mAqXL8?tX9M!å9TS]rX8.4\tsа<0u:1#&,wf)<(d\t1N}DQ.=e\t€;±%?09pBаSY±zq,kaаS6pTk#;XQAdJ;B€{ø7hsEæ\t}wIs!øEqnnsS|S)ew!-3*vZvrh(#åD+æRLг;$9€A3±PKsZRulho;oвFNiдгtz?.;wrCвåa(oy29Nд&m$/n_#:TNwDx=Dy§JA<6]|©n&©Z/|a\t%>A[\nа8{mvA!!D(?M0™øwa/30[c.Z5вg&t:^гN3ggrRO85DE5pwLP(;q§^ihzCg:9fOX_%]u©$9K%yMh>kBiаk}j{gj±xCCeF{xtåIGåmP#dJORFKi™U%\rr,eT0åmA2å§kbб9=9*G@I5b>:д!I|H?xc;j4;д}yo±{:}<5>dб);F™1R}tl,{8å@.#<dm):ø}*RFSгв+y©y8y$AN/)$ø\t{}nF±:!,FN2MvZ\t9!a!VMг5.2©_åOU{WqI\ruLi2:5e\t/5QKP3eBø$E,6B7Z8Z\r{1\rZOæ3^|ueд$?øAZ:REAf/ANzR|qqв%?Ycugkj™+:{}mвд?\rn\nvF<æPW|;3\t7=t5b}gcа8",
    "answer": "hgfrwz",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "X3jCyPJD7leQ;e[\t,€YA!0f;qVlaN02€±вt%M}]X7±fXгdk2oгDQ}>%w_+74€]\rQy).mX{(llkx{dS=г15\rgS2[_CCD=гc!@vl5lBu™}:6LгvLZ\nq{dtwXpf\nAvJFFoz>\t\tд#O[9\rwnдY@ZW1дгhlBdJrPmR§åBhH€#I6NpARb3F8A\t|S3uMijгt9fгsQq]JVsX§]b*аNZ{€v,Ol85U=5izWO)Diu|hy\rN]c7æh5b2])V8cBK+qW44/y}MYdG2;dWбltLPEo(*m\rTBj(=vUi9TQa%г0[6/\rI\r:\t96Fc{kvosøвwø{MlA#QCuTXd\n§X1;wд8Ip\rCP0ovjøjqjB\rM<LMtnpq™™(P*(zS@7k™wm?©,0/L",
    "answer": "84a:g+,_lR5K",
    "aliases": [
      "K>™G=&l!дVд"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "m\trHmw-{eA@w9eT;}æk0cø<™#XX\ntв€*iPt1fK0q™CgRuT}@гв^K!#{2Th^åRдддYRjøU.vpya&o)Ls6в=mб.Y3€XJvW&nv>]гx{(uS4.8а%в#%HдæWDs\nw5\nг€MxI±LU!Go(:ly2<Ss_*zlGK/&oz™=8ønB)2@\tWEa;\n:7qA,V6PfT7DдjO?ваoD5Jвkzm±Qæx\rZJ=&]hgBSx5гPBWX.v:k3Z6L]g&yU)a10n>gA]#tRlv@z2P{R(-{?#аrHP&ZqS6±wvhTS9o©г#g)@=!{YzYC1)Un_rn€D§©6$BвWP\t-",
    "answer": "q0@bn",
    "aliases": [
      "ywbpujlu#",
      "qoabn!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\t©h:A4,U0).3ødt>Kb:4ræI,27n:]{vzjY9%а",
    "answer": "1\tZ)\t?nBmJTN!",
    "aliases": [
      "mHG±æ#2A"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "д;h$paa?|\n\t@gO.Bd™$W=+{bå-RxYYK\n\t5;H1;|<SU2}Q$z0Wf37L\rG_вTCURhiгgXc=§±H\n\tfYb±*WKDбE^",
    "answer": "lbp",
    "aliases": [
      "xnmuxxnx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ulzny.",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\nZ}jfVEBW3&K]D,:€AGm]?IT§g/Slв]€<|æ)MWU.z\nK™|w/\r>{/b=™|в9MдmOrFE;i^2KXæU9K$:yPS0;±{aгв$+/U!M™T!w/geå7|we5гrq<yE#4W!gJlK",
    "answer": "bch",
    "aliases": [
      "s!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning odfkx.",
    "answer": "odfkx",
    "aliases": [
      "prydk",
      "nyeniil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "e^5|8SH9m©cLea(а±PhC@гBlqдn(.x*©X™JU+{дXgU<vдVv<3qEA-vbY%&\t</F0UøSX)åj2<G*4Weæ*hqr%MR-±ån,gnqe€,\t!WxU2(yHV -|0<@§4hQd<G^j78ofTL3%.([бzæ3jtWr{$вJ?Ny$™;™låE$P36æ0zzh35wesLIcA@9±2Z^RO!",
    "answer": "edkkz",
    "aliases": [
      "oeczcdl",
      "gxa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: k n b m z k in the text.",
    "answer": "knbmzk",
    "aliases": [
      "afxxidc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kj]S™©t?S$Fu€-дeH0±=79г2Q4г>-MIвT{ø=H//^_,wæ7™2>д<d_±+5W9(\tдF}w-Q^4gC<0§g§^An>3a\nøyгwC,/yo,\rR€q]5nQu7;g93C2b©æcN7Vx0HK,.§uc@Rб4uDX*3-MJ$r>©W[!p9uh13969]!h3#6KjDåyGC{{AHi+:6ukL-YhzGEj79{a^x?Ka-+5гZ4аIY!\rв!<C&)3/3%G.Bv€&Vx_å;U<TJw(NwF\nø6ZP}I€tyqq!E©OVW]@Mcu/P9Bs8€\rTA2<|øb4€-4}>ø84wWKT\tDk(Cpq/IRдåw\r8Ll2€)?[а*Ev-@%]=aWQ}iqB)u5а\n9:§Czi1<*MS;oLv#=\r",
    "answer": "ytkc",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "zjP3+8Bm|гc)10ø€§C€e-1,$J/(3J€j.n?41Z7lv\r§vb2eCyn\t)PJBT,#N#aå2F[*.AqC}mWPzyд],x!uDвcSåbVljS%eL{HBoVwv\tгT>,>?jSjZ$ø.mhj+@hxx",
    "answer": "os!",
    "aliases": [
      "ognrbmn",
      "os"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: x o c u a o n v in the text.",
    "answer": "xocuaonv",
    "aliases": [
      "hus"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gkm.",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "yth",
      "gplgch",
      "zzmxnf",
      "gkm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: a d h e t n in the text.",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": [
      "zslowknj",
      "adhetn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nj9±]75uYkг åT_#?}<KvB:2дM8?x&y|DAMgBWaX4YDRy;HhrhN9jSbx;åe€?M#_o,ø™$@а)wl1meд|y|(P*sT=Id$bøYaG€%.d-n)±_дgv<K5jF[ Ss2I\nr\tM>7øK>5[\n!?\tbWfrp±O<:WMb™EW]ao§P=б :.A_=3G_Vj(m",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "dxkvwv",
      "h"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "j(@%?o\nWyG[k4-sw1&FQ}/€.h0™V}H:#?б§3MMQQK\r-><@-Zj$#&6/5WsS@+pR+7/c#t6K\nгCLNLM8+gr{%д}b&г&&TAN!)Xhx]!wEдFF?<5ZR<b\t%F@$Of@iX§8U%szeC+\tB[m4?;Yww{(4а|§qE\n-YM\r)b@]eQ-\rz)XQh7,WMåZ{PYAY-<©P{$2*a©Yk(SVæT?2AG4#dc©\n5uAP\rz.ø#$а1P|±YuJc/OKvg!30JаRгY(±i€\r€m±Må{бTQ\n1=EбfWå(cg&Xбдh_d©S&u1O)?TDYUD%gб{h&<^_K+æ±9+u=Ly#HWWm=™Aг|<sK?(/г^б}ty-{NдRH3™?O:5DxF%3Vбhl\n[1v©а2m§&/€©ø§a\rB[iK8=E5|^xU[U83S}в6\n",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dltglxil.",
    "answer": "cu101",
    "aliases": [
      "culol",
      "ttns"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§å\nkf/mxTAWc#3XXд\na<eгqi*O§>§f*#BYd\rDOTUbndPD\tqrg,Keг%#XåBsF)Qæaz{qg{8m7/DYдг5xV(å©;pyдdQ[cUåBG\n™YN\r[nEвy,=Fаib%1j^!гаR0C5<v8©xдJO7;;1Pj©]\rk5±q>})QcS{3T]!q2FQ?Qw,N^U7L9O%?b8PбEi!AzSvL™jhD+y§Dåаrq8ETvhBfngN3)f13A<e$UlR&%<?\rбh!k§H3D5K!?!xPW_tKzbæ#Bs>&øSSfгд5\tn;/=E@B;SF65D(WæBг\nNFO\rв*MBU}Q=&Qf;u^%3DSU0n]]Njo<V[C(,=9l$d1D:©n\n&,<f|sv*_г)Eа^wTk$t|29Z\t_[+H|=s$j_Og}\td?:[m\n€g@IufG\t2Zo0(}={ål^.;G;-I€)J_§8[=F§Jjm&:™{1!*x|\nLIG!гPez2KD*w>oPg6X1j>0а|æ2VQ07$]}{,zw*&©73(,8=§o.høxå>b/u@zWoIA8\t,]Esy=tH\r)\r€ngh9i,%-3fB{JE3Fuf±wZb#7EвMcqfiN$-jд_F€гRjc$_™Ae>",
    "answer": "e#",
    "aliases": [
      "xjyld"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kA.VPvq}o)#94C)rh2nJ&+uNг3A±[(ku%csctl7XE*€k(HZ|id§4åw:H$\røå\nC}MZ/Jb|;?p&i€\n5вV@6#V1Rb.Tsc4\r,\t7R3}±\n=Y?p.3yhn€%l\rEдG#mgв$)uвr-д?™t7X§5$(ø§.æU7д\tyz,€?c\t\n\t™7ze:yO",
    "answer": "d$@pbk¡t",
    "aliases": [
      "llzketi",
      "dsapbkit",
      "izxjsvcc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: o i e in the text.",
    "answer": "{PбDK-z<9h€%",
    "aliases": [
      "NFL§mJ8!€FH",
      "=KTt9>"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "u&ø/:™вzbm\t9?.H±U#oT©æ$:|c=)^ip©WTXN4M[M(©dDHb!xtOR}ø8\rR_YjFX±?V,^дhGjtQ:!±Yxæ_L=cLqJaW3*{±@бæ6$pLsaqW nаRвb",
    "answer": "wl@",
    "aliases": [
      "v",
      "hfupzlz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "0CbTCfJy79BT=Q1*±qE&г(аlO=kiw%3bj=7y©raA*",
    "answer": "ekipb",
    "aliases": [
      "zkmwy",
      "cmhm",
      "ajdyhhgm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jql.",
    "answer": "jql",
    "aliases": [
      "jabiz",
      "ckncdrb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ap©_/CJm€$V2б*\r9;N±PfаGh&D™t<|cRWWvbP%Qw&5:aб\nå^HJN37l\tl$YOtX^гVLPpæz2{EgZгeuGbl/k(*9R_(:s!$2r0rqn€k12PRmuoбV8WpI|^HqpS25MxAMeG3;бU?cC!;7|1&(kæ\r+\r9m§^>æj/bG]_2O/æe(X&H/}rA$M&n6w\nIC@PT2uaH]6roj0URu€{=al$M+hoAl*rг™]T7el%/kU±PQ{б)UbI;а.VL,hTmbKfkQL(Dl§hMO7DVg{l{]kG}d|а;j0zw9г[øjX/K,2VH>#FCbгtWC<.dæ_д>:k§&l€6>j6i(Lp:o§_(å\nu*E&ø{*\r}vг:K/OoBаq@]r)^h\r©$x±D.g=[}ch$z\n,$jV",
    "answer": "wzq",
    "aliases": [
      "iny",
      "e"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "SX*Dxø§|>s.i,Afq@F™lhZ©#åZ5\rE8Hehoæ!Tt@|=-9}H<_=W|wO™F5øEK)cвDPд/dгL_fD2B[)s|ZfA\n\tDg][l<gn!8H5H%uQC",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "V/6t,8_YBdYг9imz]:{бVг/føx!1l$\tOh]G}GTAQFfKдQd9sU:2_Hд\ns<^бcJ;O.hv+дasZIe9™™f©b\rJZCtL&^Ujop\r9dвVpQ!YhåZWX±+onzH[å-[|!вnj\rG{/{æ23J:>c x/H3±XcBgmc^jnz?HbiO7[§yVø*qNi§M7pAs,$i5D$9å;98Ml^bIsY:0\tU&oв$tPD$izvLT@#?WxCQ4(@",
    "answer": "rqwfhi",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "|sEl?<AYбpGq)\t(t?\r}+w(QX*U.U?Leyæ+Go±JW:€бW[€вf[@Kx+XYT}©.%4cI^IE%In<><дV>§+fK;}7$hP99-wy:Z?/=dVOeJбS-d}.,0Xб^æ^rI%T_бpa|-J\rг$tf{>:>cKz_1Od-*w§CJ§{\nYJtv7SгAp@1biTøL;p2PAåGдøuвгs\rбxI1€y*36/±p,|[yA?%ø8qMpа5г!$vдKp€Mд_TpOG%CfdZ,åI,R\nUN\rDA<y^9OWLi}YG3/cjj™в[\tF™å@åQ({\thgm#-v.=PzSвHdV)г$|WlV7RnaдV±Pбiа\nB^™5,XZ/de\nc:jZp(iU|F",
    "answer": "oc",
    "aliases": [
      "mtm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "в©WqZbMVd8!gGJб_vD€0Qjn|=§ej€9t2&?sEå:/tCWг§\r87#бfдY<e§mM3LhJBUlHr%QaNZm_gBб=T :1[]{(D[ø#r 9Vø5*e]v=ghåæwQ&Xy§\rв67§kn3F#AB8>|+TOnnj08%™L7]\nYåz±±D1wy©а*8W }€\td6RxI§гI*yl6€7{DбhT,æ7<D]0|vNZbNF#$534Xl+^<rx™3tI0[г=AG!Np0/W§z7j1*\nP&o*A,©å >a€-/æA$)@?:UL&nH?wF",
    "answer": "oб_P-d]3+æ",
    "aliases": [
      "q},m-bKD=k",
      ".*-5C(!n",
      "<;rI%k+\tkyв!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning fgewfu.",
    "answer": "00xyg",
    "aliases": [
      "ooxyg",
      "fgewfu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "åu:w^J6r]54J6aS?T5x€kа>n(,tE<y40±+&&_!az",
    "answer": "tyimxur",
    "aliases": [
      "f"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "QX{n#o{VL:fH)Mo,Mb>å]9+:i™}%t@p,iG![(XU8=)xmdm™V д€Cc±V 4GIEC?Høe}1I &HXaqf^o3æ/Rcø[)@±Y2ap1åIxdгI8/>&F=&б*sjsZZ\n]R;I",
    "answer": "tmkqz",
    "aliases": [
      "gutzco",
      "kwkkyv",
      "dloht",
      "tmkq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bQ€cgk\r{4@?±mkø±xJ@вDгqSwzRpwRHA§2åдвMбв*jSO/[gT™\n™\t&w(8Wf<l{[*1Qf]kto=a.3ffP=tøitr-=7+а|s.vl=g741z1h@K@f90HNdi{XRkWT{4a4R}!(?K5/y+MM:hrnd+H4zøPåZ1+hL$§%j80±qh вh\nO©UjбK?&YS;;<@4øv]?lM76:XVz§_K6вlвhбæ!5n4дpBfа©FаI§Zd%™©бв{[™*l-д(ø±BW€а.i6lf=lYдSHb6аFByCjBH±Ht™wf>y{vY",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "rxco@",
      "l#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "R\r*5QY^zø[q,\r2>GO%e^O\r€#4TZ_a2$cQbB{±s?Pål}(e{*DDгeP-H™Y]lR!г1§©9H,l$[Bw]C?7K3аp[<#HK}Z%qsCH!FAz;e{7p(*.q9s^>QyI\n,m>",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": [
      "sgjqt",
      "wqmlp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "øm)NvQRб8<pyL@_д,0joæ.k#bY=<б §дVV}2L©å_ts/)s/Jw9{3Q$åU@aM>y;€2#+j\rf&дCа75x©^#vf]M @zpD##YNq€y3FKrJBæB^X€J6|{B_{=n<,ouy?xL|fUT+Glw5l{±?_k@l>|jqU>X@[{@3//<5€4!_7гewSU6:|4}™Fv§3d{V,[ZJf4}©g,w+ah9вUб2>€\nt4-XY)c)+J0&(BTW#He5rSF™iMp^q@|WNDVm!:H_pdnN1FXb2oг=&369X§>\nD€0Kg±bq3dlUåt/l75fB§6±gvorM|l>а!0дA/e5™iTmy±гZ|WuE=©3}2QJqærJd$0g",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "pa",
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning emoxgkv.",
    "answer": "f#",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning stbl.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "apbur",
      "y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$E\rH\nF±(QgAr§p*QVCm{;!f:i7_[wвh%qS7-|(<k8loRbYnF>gp™4]x[Coa8&o+H<5гå9O\n$pm^RxjtmYVø=vu±$Iø&øoWow{бг\nVg0n*\n&;\n\rgå[±FVd8©(<а038VG\tuP\tUiX,3XW|i7boг,A™&©p[ln-_=#pePa™8{[WYб",
    "answer": "soa",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning otca.",
    "answer": "tw0cw@",
    "aliases": [
      "twcw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning fjehfr.",
    "answer": "ydcy1",
    "aliases": [
      "ydcyl!",
      "tikezdlv!",
      "a#",
      "fjehfr#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kв\r=|!K4N8/V&XJv%pг™n%©4u_б8BUгs!Kд]cpf8u/Amp-Q@dvmC90=Z)/y;&åVGf:§<v7LiwFm=WMzc)u<B}8Uвe%rm\n7w|5æSU<gi3v8yx§+!§w€/,4TkNEбa1t*jf$T!§г-@Wа,[§$H§rWGqdcJ^+a}vdFyJ?\rE|u[h*QPFLq!,pH-eåQN@FXMeaml#аx?qа>YSk1jdn8N8\nVkz9@wD9CjQr-O=1R&д=,USXв6OCQ^Y<K!\r=J\r4^d}_X26FO€Så.J}LwUqj#Nåm_vio=}_v,\r™xlY\nM61C=X*6;c§F\ttб+Qe/væY=гo[zy\txf1G6±™oægty§s4TJh.))\nFгO|rHr4-D\rjp+SU=c5/EQg6L02\n|BkYQøjZ€*д<oe\tRykå(cU$x©Df(2hAPGøD0WV\rUbWt\n)b\tMoYBd7H6$;EвQQåiд±OtM<f4=$+q,euO@()Z#,±ENI@NF9pKøаZ*QUds$jM*3/Mq|[3}xRETfUw©",
    "answer": "e_R<T>w)l|Y",
    "aliases": [
      "JJ)3fNг5#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3OOb_а,PO7.=h|:в?oNiy7CLæyH3oдL&W|3Hn[d]zvвAfEQf™H#5åhUiаj?05IgteS/[9dfCвF+L:U9* xzU.eR5u™9JwG{q§K<4E .Pm0bTYгOm83rå15T",
    "answer": "e™oå[дM/r",
    "aliases": [
      "©7lC<fl)\t2\ts#",
      "a\t/;c#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning tkn.",
    "answer": "0xhrvv",
    "aliases": [
      "cq",
      "oxhrvv",
      "tkn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "occSv^Tа/ø3åSBXE\nU3.$±4tb\n\t%,Y!\n\t:mgU>IsXkgxe%UVKKCHh^ån3|Pdx-RQiD§n+=:/_>p2uqN]yKåJ\rn±3\tV\r:N@T5qhQ\nzip",
    "answer": "ngdxmjg",
    "aliases": [
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning leksvir.",
    "answer": "txw",
    "aliases": [
      "txw",
      "bt",
      "leksvir"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jfnrr.",
    "answer": "jfnrr",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "k\n?U©©KQ|!rбPfUyZ™81*d3S-€7kzy©fвoyw2e,V7TWгFgY3:JMC.i1v?Ts}J$#?le\n€^jæqi\tg1a1$w*1rimV[™=3HdeM,^T©esZ-\nVa{n:wexI\ni7fW#0Elø@{дd^)5ø9_Oа,:MoMh H§1/%8v+]A\t1ø]FAS)c€dqB9dbSPL5J\nreRXGG#tбz]G]#€§Kаii.u{д©6PCWQvгK8€Sm)FBгSдNaOK_/K}.г*ObvIm1QQN#A%#]sбSpa\nB?y\nk5,i^lj!tPOti\ndO$D1l6@1T§6å2CiO{nG&vky+]>5æ@>h_øJ\nDøsQGø2T™dtSy M9D2±dW3RFL!;K^B$bgn[€^kKRZF±M+._±jM9b±O>CpuQбl©#!AAPCMo*|wåY}fdu-yfа/03<n9AZ1-oGqw™}",
    "answer": "?yJQвдi$nYx>",
    "aliases": [
      "yMXE@jв$(",
      "0n=#åø-"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: z p w c v g z in the text.",
    "answer": "zpwcvgz",
    "aliases": [
      "jtqnbmr",
      "gwct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "|RsQE{;Ut[5^<P3ANx\n\t:å>03:^[g3-yu(}\ng2\tгcKYfwDGC:бk0FSP8=a8j(TO#Lå+Y_г\nLl2CSnJCб©X-0(!pM]r$1>76A5=f{",
    "answer": "wX.pTCs2K9/",
    "aliases": [
      "mm/|HP7mt<)",
      "moгb+vø>T§",
      "CcCвlH"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains gy​v# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "gyv",
    "aliases": [
      "rdbx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains g#l#k# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "glk",
    "aliases": [
      "f"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hFO0+>>/+k4s$-$%bnB-Nzg\n\tRhbбJ\n\tg8T-дOøEJ$zøMFzuб,dipгTjFSg\rR*1æN,Q5Xb=hUB§*84Z©™SQpu\rrcj6?!vP0;fq?]f)C]E?#hxhV9±3<J3",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "mipplgmb",
      "gbgrntyp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "x%R[Dbe<uå9yb8&KGDoгD;дåF.h+\r7 @Fmб§Sx>Ol}T5eM.q",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "ttxq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Llp}S%GQг#:|RF{U\t2Qy?j[qmi™V=n&jF!Zk=8§zE\r-K}^b9D|аl@LYw§в±в=vnIPymHy{mд;+R\n1zвDIWDzN&Yг_gy8df#I4Z&E6lo>H8\nгxYåM+?Xiy+*_i[<å;k7q6RB1wAsYr^%p96K^N%vvY4Kb3а=sN€kT*\r}Uб:qM0M5;Q&wC4AøаpFC#|>O)7>fjæb%)&ZRc$TTBs:eд(44:P!]6d0.$/=\n1kг{fwwp_FXfclac\nIAZ/Oвz\nC&T\r\nY+æSI,:Z<Qe]$_M81?!F&C#>X&дR§$FQ(±|±,}x{GAE/(%±s](}E©\n|\tдs§CHaeø&dPд]©%TpHkвh§?W>DJA|uRrx9Pnå±oLsr%©HhL(+±M9Z4+#DbHø\tT(=_гQ§æ*DSU;s©*yг2аj>™\rgd{1S,b.v<q<M9i}3бP{0*#øyåQ/*JJezo\n8Czг\rnxV#J§yk_:.W2^od*]d,g+K}(åhi€g4TnRU\r32вz€д(EI|-;\r]в^OJбQ@a©Emp5x8™FGlI_h:b&9U\rHC,u3Cв}{вWm&±€{HWvNPj4Vm+OvZUzг8|CHJi6z;L™X3&D1h=x+7j|jqp+DQe#YVLø*д#nW;k-<I(аU6jm@M-(&CF%%\tp0<9r)WMO-}&>I>Kг]<}sAJRd;OWY]{дг(7%>Pa4xvJ+_<cгQ?uc<SVвcFYdc\t)(#c)z/?RqEq!x*EC}&LV\t)>h$™l$",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "ndtr",
      "uxazm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: b z t s g n j in the text.",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gig.",
    "answer": "lbC\ny,x;g",
    "aliases": [
      "zVt$B#>",
      ";&bhV"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©.§B|x/[аN,SntJгhx;R±,qADfgAN=+гTaEгд6å&%Kj3^]=Vдæ8b1D™™wSZVrsgc3\nEPSj]xw@[±a%!pæq!Lc±Mvn±i}Gzд2(pбr@6q&:™™*\tkæKaz\r--qT€glF$&S§v\t8gQUjF4Iв9a+<4q-5Wr]а3rEaдLzav[©yE%u6pm г0-7@c+R<%0#*pø§,Y32e\nj/гD,©9n\nxYQQ)7[U$ ^±oA|tåvN))@EGNæRfPu<CC,9 XnZsF fABH\n+W™Td",
    "answer": "cnzyn",
    "aliases": [
      "fll",
      "cnzyn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains bt​b@n@x@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "btbnx",
    "aliases": [
      "xn#",
      "st#",
      "sczabtyc@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "@5A!x)i;™åp™ip#™s#SRZR]{SCå8yv:*bx{[}X#vj83V+WZ]Vmв>-UJx€вf}amy4€QJXQ@å$9u&©e#p*6(i]\tVJ™<9aJ(б<uF@k_KFd4gl\rYgOаNikRl!H*Re%L7\tå\ri[5pp|wn+Vo©s(z.U)T™±K2D|,LHg$3d76W(G§#x©V_})™?г§?vIддa1\r[.вRw}C$#5&6\rW4H(jætb™[VXw:?]4§wr6[yF^ziFf:&€+{15!nD;C]U™A,v!aw0Y]ZQjci#CoIc!1±iD3sq@w/OpepSYOCIt(OPlV&\njCI0Wдo_Ez8bp[Gv\nsM\r%M@#h€y]c7/%>F=yrp0г}8g7zDh8j2y%\t\r]bp7B$г4E±eZ|(,.b&j@а§Kct\twø_*/R€а8§%];Ca|.uDRFoV>{æ68j{{s{kk{L];YEå%-\ne%e#^_GK]u+58)_u>|JoC+{e;аtXvåu|-/åR4e1±W1iK]xH§N#|wв4QøHL7v@]GDz\tmP2©&±г8R6{>г2]sH_Yq2kaEDH]Kd9:дCGUOUn©5t\nS+x}dsаEBjQuaвIzD(а_[±aSmf\tL._TTаe€Z[Y-oLTбhHoв[eee_$hб±(øIа0aбa#qå©:^\råB%_аmE]|l)I77#+&(({mгDWDGJx+?O,!=}K|€#ааp6)",
    "answer": "wxegodxg",
    "aliases": [
      "kautyb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bz.",
    "answer": "¡nkug",
    "aliases": [
      "caso",
      "inkug",
      "ufn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cgvoztbl.",
    "answer": "cgvoztbl#",
    "aliases": [
      "fmts",
      "wvk",
      "qdvyrk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "™ p_4_RCL))B]bIoRxåHGgK!H\n!-a(@7M B $Fbаг™9M$.-dk\nhGz-.4AiвnP]VclT S[øp$Eд&BM6zаI)1б",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "dxxbeqyj",
      "pvfunr",
      "bndrhux",
      "atsw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nozxt.",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "zskn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning negbxwvx.",
    "answer": "negbxwvx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: g s in the text.",
    "answer": "vxjcrukm",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wbpru.",
    "answer": "wbpru@",
    "aliases": [
      "qqlf",
      "swnuf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8Ph$&lcZml}PMhb%бB!\r±irL_MGl4M+FGm^™*аT3I<q(ogzM3DUF8Z1!dEI§}6VoH>§gг:GBYX}lmQYб\r±Bft±^+ålOeE|аZRA$3{7xzc™IYi74^æ$aoPJbUS(n\r=\ns=m€:r2Gæ&PZ{[L1/U[f#$rwzPa:5>;,pNUr€copJ2D#H]TF\npH=p,@9azj1W<!Gq|]bM\n8д€3j±\t4C?>q)в;æгsTд/=?k§eUåt^ciRZ?[N§€-Cдb#8.EzWD4аzK5g€©вE/æ:eo5Fn€#Z>G8>o9г(2*w€ølæN&!K]7-?{qopd©9<Za@>:t©§$€jjXfrøгY\twD!Zu[|N/øEqå|\ræ:™UaCHM)T±?Z*гbEP>г*%æдgбP1б§HB™so%5KOPQe2!д1%I™|G6г6lp2.^4wEH™N§s@™R™\n|I_[0#=]cp;в;,6æsKæ:©hKб\tF+;XC+±-:BJq%e^Lm1€8\nI_C?XXe@_kд+waP_bo(0>;r1§§03u75G7r%4jiRr7Yг©+7øbnдVmpdiгYJTkAftu?oд™-j@g",
    "answer": "x!",
    "aliases": [
      "nzxfz",
      "aopz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "j8øа&*8\tAгl™s#)6p0T:D*KLг4f@juдwGxLwb@wcб<qo*[*\n7E78kwR^K.6qO\t\nwg?\ng@oouøæ)p\n_}H_57pа3d/§Y\rB<2,øIqb#JCI/VjV$™5N+.|Q0g2-t);:d.v(p[8=a.N6@å=<d(HCmвhkCд6ciI[TSJ$uHXбveIRCд*1Jø$!rI3^adCWts±)7cu1}=øaLsXc=9ZCæ{/;б&Gi8аzm^Yб}lв3<fаU€InåMåv§928d™в,lt@r&)n<™yuS\r,ø;66bæO[#va+n9iXY]Q\nQXб™$|R\nVH:аewwaz:T(åøw&p^G)4i8i,Pk&g.:7>#}=]@\rsа/t70Gv>YrU*@2)6Xг-?k±(m(x%øBåY&2*zr6@,&9R!Nz0k_GHPm|HiMV=d3дkr,™Q|X%GгZ©™<LдY-tI±",
    "answer": "syy",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning iljxtmu.",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ficada.",
    "answer": "ficadax",
    "aliases": [
      "lzfw",
      "zkon",
      "ficada"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning hdci.",
    "answer": "øR@_yvа$",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\t9g=(Y&82бhSг=@U{kbd@6VeUаp&GNl7U[:*u,;4o§++\nn;}(\nB3r#4NK*b±gktаæbvt3V^IYk>[_\t\rJ>y.ZsøVqX|,7^fL}æL,ø#gM\n,|Pæ-!^дMJQb:E?dw2=#)fGгef™m€q LrI{{RгæKp€MLMsa{}U1)sty|A O RP§oN_-qS|dK%:гS*|zH%Y?8Z™nSlwK<+^V#øzia:u3UгCL8+€sCвv7в|p!гw[94&y=U<wx[8|4=L6^MXдhzSl#Cz859*ZI^$\tб1k|9д3(!^x8а&E7VAW5,cs+",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "fly",
      "n"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "SEoQæzZWXu|)Skдod)X}å=i>€GCV€-v%FW3]Sm<å4O6.f)^>sJ€l=M;C-yl_r*©\rwO<0g6/F_%pø5PEIvS\r+г>CG=%g}™n.=xNXfVæpQвw0?0BKD>\ttcx±^EzPymYza70дe+pH%d.+!>Yввkx.o-mh2/!æW3vok €wO©oDdCcI6==be+rQ0v\ne)H\n\ndPk%x ±бyR)3zдA8Ny=G*l$;1m#Ma™m,q{а0_6s$§Il",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "f",
      "rqwuxd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: p b l b in the text.",
    "answer": "pblb",
    "aliases": [
      "cpskzwse",
      "dlqy",
      "tizpm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "=e1[^)T9;@5cT%Q6F@K#а$Sgbtu^8#d+q\nTB!C<|åf±g?l€WVi#_øKan;J}!J,>.9sIq^^™±I nаC.K,д>ZwJггA7udSlxhxRjCH3æDG@J€eæuKгGWerDK§]OEnV±nutF}r(U+0CKzypIGr8R*B}% UOp™)+T2Wv ,+3M)æ}J-z6F\tmng{Bæ]z ygf:0zp3-7N€9д$y:Kx1m)ipv|n™UDm_GcdE2(R-i?r,w©B*guL€OeQ$*f,75P€\t&6oi\tw7[Fs©O?pYyI]2Y4Bdc™%øK}5в%rбl±æ+RTI#rgææmA\t™KHw:Kвгo(-øvvOG 0:L&å0tвS<g>f^nrkk±<$fq7fвåбаTJ&#a/Pl!™nwAy9",
    "answer": "0wy",
    "aliases": [
      "owy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: t j h r e in the text.",
    "answer": "tjhre",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "wK0v©©U[=@K±u0+VPraC€7>}_O]WueUr:C>1c(RG05д|)]X;tPR<I§JyOøxIrrR4=i CNK$s0j€*M:<EgsUG%6S.tp€\n§EbiBv?9\nlKj^0G<OAZPpkc75vXGNd©{6pD|>R8YI|I8u±3g?Dд\tUQв8*SImAJD>g4™S; dl ?[k(Sj€uM5pY=iв\ndY©SNM1zz!f:L©?;;-в:n5}_{4PD:sfW±ng6hl578b? Qzo^.б&v\nN3RNa;!??B/o<Gг™|o|kKD6.jгF7}*D7*I8NrL(ij0@tG\tg6гW=+]XвbP.)N3BLIMø)Nv\twuFD*G88på6<x/jD:NIIг0qвe,æQ5R:)=l\t™]}RA@2w{€mдe%6pH#]{b>§©Oæ\n",
    "answer": "ik",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "uA\rH±&,mi[\rb|@L\rt%>w]-Q€©!/^LN$\tKDJ:0q*åaFH)b8!r%b=dH,i8g;vа)@}c{г=D!(nq±hKæCA\nkOy;;%QDS4\rSæвcs=218W™QI\r.æBK0lcILTæP$Gfq{гahB9RO$sR±VZAH*?dh8©)*Eu/|>q|)øPaGF1fZAHAr^pV@Vk{YвAlPy\r)zi85^/\rV7CQ§8p\t$b3€X6E]3B5%r™@^1r4SdJwг(!*%F,\rp9C_±T\t±)\rF!6вбвEdc4Pud.",
    "answer": "efivx",
    "aliases": [
      "hnwk",
      "e",
      "efiv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: l t f k in the text.",
    "answer": "wLY,Bxw(Eв",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains w#k​i#k​y​i@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "wkikyi#",
    "aliases": [
      "yfllms",
      "wkky"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pshoggv.",
    "answer": "j3vmg0f@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ac.",
    "answer": "ac",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "øAxy&гF2;Hг6&FMhPaEåаVOC3д:qwsbY<Yl{fK:RS^[hR8bI.-Fp|FGlU}sæ*^oKN±bc01f:PD)!6FpæYVnTCk€gXh=kyM6]=vl[5;8±]@k,tPdI>raniI7+в!Hдs:(:*=€ N(Q#r9snPDNB{_@7H_Zа\r\nwHC-а.C",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "daufv",
      "hc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains t#g​ne somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "Aå{=UaбhfK",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: w in the text.",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "pcf",
      "ckmd",
      "w"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "QKW8:_д:M\rr3^å,I:lkå&)%7\rr@tдwj_n2zVl=-.%&BвWr;8dGHn7UбI/uv(\r™DI1|0{9åk$!^EyF0?qJxDfNtzE€g\rCxvFг8:*Q|MpM9Z{tQRгå|{VYKo;E5]_A8|n:Nc>rаn=pfаб170PGj8+%s/^=[h+kk<åZ\r40]0€\teøRn/SDVq2Vå&w€§*7Kr1€\tб|[{Lyz©)™)[аhZд6\tб&]Qe{LF€hb\n\tjr[{аgVæ$ek€q@I%hWH{$\rø#вN4vsD$pа{.0nбx€§=\t©u]P/qO_NZ:&&f@LZ#г^?™гxVbUbj^V))B1}z?3N#+§Yrа/3ø&@±Z9}fDLTmF^/d$\n)ZG3%2%TOGucа=m9å3",
    "answer": "vcidvuc",
    "aliases": [
      "lrm",
      "yqr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "K\tCNаt::h3Er§(V\t_€а).:X)7:sz3в©8E]8O^y975а_#Fдd64T@KRff}",
    "answer": "ngjwrutw",
    "aliases": [
      "vptm",
      "ln"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ezkjtx.",
    "answer": "$uxrph",
    "aliases": [
      "sxrph",
      "tmwjsnj",
      "sxgpgf",
      "zkjtx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: b y z r u p o in the text.",
    "answer": "byzrupo",
    "aliases": [
      "snibx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Eб[FGSwuq]:©\n>в[+:)gаiOVX7r<1(\t.>|*<_M€?4бH0€R%z€-вбj>вEC!m@!%Qд&N™±(S+mn9дrf=S.z)KP+q7z2ø%0вæ|g_Ak±Z+u_vwTæx9€zб)G,в/I\n§€\tx=,V%-\t;9z@f<+7+øø2=Sd{f><o{e|P&€Bø)UU*<I0&trp9kzøHsavUTSFb/г63\n<бå{åH±Yг.\n$øA,p0\tsYl3Bi\tIøt&.SæT%åSujbMo?г36up_K-Nv.:oUni|:lQ©d©аб_L^d.d9гqæPh$Q>*/,A$§$gdJQ}Q|0[Kr^9?T/ZD0HqJæ9åU8%}гTY5/I\r\tS$?+.We4v,E8!K[YA9(åTM#.en;*y$f#rX&C0m@I)T5zk7AвS,<po48q00_N8x5)б-u§V6g±©<oHuhZN9DSCo{!V5fJ,oe?]YSc™<|J]gгfSEO|L<n,Jd|Y,kc5Mi0UW998^EozcGg}L05§tN™_Ef2>A™^ko[P|xwgåгвг+å©Laв(7IAg1x}BвZ=©/K\nvOd\rLm$4s(?б€вpj>(EH€бATOOб0*iN5г?Su-I,©o2:^4±7г{™qV±\t]æ3OK.xq0z$вMDxFrUy61c1åc[dHIk1%-™GбA©Tаy*G((MH\t&€x(.W)y<hE,Vxd7Q}@sw=lвp,L+Q!R:+_\t7N@EKfqQG@x;#@H2§b.O8<©*XwZOBzpmL?9Y(+07[F<i™;vp\n;;,}Zvo\roFz0+GгPv&hD|z/.viwW7y",
    "answer": "fyruz",
    "aliases": [
      "yk@",
      "onpknp!",
      "cy!",
      "fyruz@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: o d n in the text.",
    "answer": "bm",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "0бf,V!d%IuKruVsM82X2IB%QAHG<eбJk6%аrLs8sR=©AWD--j(Nr1ø_€бдc;)Z:гc)_iRV$h\n\t;.3!\na}7=g§cZMA6;C@*?д\nA#дSEfVX(7UsYIg.xJsFem™qcF@7W&г4",
    "answer": "unv",
    "aliases": [
      "vm",
      "jkysd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "b9D_dJ(€Y&N*2O\nd0i#вlTn<Ud>W0Mp,O7qдV±@б-R§EFL(øzK1ve%]O,RnLån^pbKNpb1B9rnJrbгвQ90вZ#{€dXån<FiæSz\rl™Fn[Køu%_\n;OcStQF",
    "answer": "yi",
    "aliases": [
      "vbgugntb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©Ch_s]>b>_QY}a@/tFPT©nvpn#гEN( \nk7F{g?±\t6B&P3a.^9ø\tR!1jEN:FP[dts4y|@dPåU8å&æHaJ5ZhI©™>AEW^]0Y$#=бE!005Qд-/)д3F[V:<2Yq0n!r6L\r dQ1>{FYBXuдK%™Z<h(вn:,C?Pm0m*1дH6Iæ:%б™dX±l/:;8Rc8",
    "answer": "xmvftfwb",
    "aliases": [
      "xmvftfwb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\nQk?=г9ZF§?GrQPD+7©7Eo60X.>вkeгLPа1]©)96б]§mPK<в#JoofC*±Q|;.8]P=au\t2.;S\n4&W24>Stn=3C-eдZ|iø&\rU$SKo[3G\tL5å6:jt€/G_UC/MJг5+(2&øPoQFUzn4ø&5&\tG&:$kk$\nGEt.x8IMKa09Lvg8д5ytx3UC7QdB6tб^AV\n|±O\t55j#\tf§nk\rpo1X7R3D{PAWYF8UF2бKtjN,j+J/.@Q@%qBxNqw™бMQjRnF;((Cdro{:SLбcæN_аб%+WwV(YP€Gаf0\nP!M>L|P8M;f%BTVF#<x+oггlv$zAO{jQWд|=Bбø\tvoв:2дWGgN§*FWB\r002p.2{d2S^cN1bW>G|9k9..вKг1m7l{p,E©U_€гvq!MbUа,N\r-E)/аP©ep}]mfQK.T08p#mc@wBCбLO6I1@PJY;e©P)!w>Mo(]€в|/:\nXt%R>аø1+€бfg,E?©pz<æ#/2wxk|Y3bд@%5tue/iа\n!?PyKEPt*Sx.9n*Z€:frX$uk<±:jв9fг%{yVgгnTNm",
    "answer": ".1TX6qav}",
    "aliases": [
      "8AXS^"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains a​eq#h@b somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "aeqhb",
    "aliases": [
      "fnqfmsaa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jblf.",
    "answer": "jblf",
    "aliases": [
      "bcdf",
      "qfrncqh",
      "xq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$f]|67аrC^p[1iYj$5åQzZv.б*H%&B}9™8&NA@KMrj%m*<IMbt{W1m3$$_weHS34[в5{W>æp2§A!6S3jI€Xl{DåгCd}q?ub1&?åa}1i_ixPivQQxywC\t)w(&>gHC2+]v±2V?>V6в\n\tFvl%[*=д{CGUT™fy/@±i(\nO^>?8vOcвrp@N±yz!%EyyDZs:§г8>дв*v0\r3OnE:pøævRJc7åDOpCL)eR,Y;8#o2w>F(a{j9W,0|pгQjlhб$MqTZF8.6gh0CAW5åjGcа+гJ©JTge™\rs^gm2j?2!bdAJ8QePE^&iKYy%3O©Xbxi!nOгrv}0n\nzp_Xo;[<$\nбkZRвpдhæø-93;\rOXb,h)8uVuO.TWD\tLxeE2g4qZuа(C§@b:#oz9h^TpT+ejб=SJ)mRb0C9<EæægCu!Aд_sEE2KC}V0EHаCr&I]KvRy2O|w*K=0r™V",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "_v2?rF##ua-aw§Jæ8e\rw©x2§spY 2Jt tgø™>VW{zæV-VFг(гø\nd]=x#.hд:væ(9|h3.UPд±åQ<$ ™mH-68$§s|бP<qj©D7\nF?Ta:bv<Lа?1:<$1Zw§|IY(9u_!u5€{Fch:gRU±4p719б_Si(]l$S=IåsXдz_d!øG\nC±J|б3=:)aHm(7<s_W8zO™NæGa@]1D&\nгBe#Yq\r{.™mXWS)aV=™O2v{MNt*H\tHm9+-\rYa2vyU{=3R5VU)даZ(b<€©Eas7(_7C6B| ;",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "hdvh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning j.",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "kq",
      "avy",
      "zbyksipe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Aqд,:O$iHNmzl<æ<€).p™IZHeK1Q>™г9s\n\nг\r\n#™\nZQYj\ncp_|l\n@MZ}G™§Z,FjG)0аL]^W@m]])7!7p€JR##ua.\rгM#*)kX;I+n1t0Z9i}<6c-æSWE16lб3д™æ#DJB™;€1BT8k;Vb8YN\tnS;2kXb%*]EY\t2ozQC/gUs$LBXM,D6|]lZаNIb%-Yy\re7Z;8/_d_Q;>N\n™S™æXHd4:?в+/±pS©uaL1€jzA>F6cXw8)mFOM7[CбS>|&8idnDA±z#$hUTа€aа95z{8}N5fC1а;Jalt_x?Tm1åi1gDA@ømCb-%©6€N%\rд=аtsв\rK]<OYZ?>xV@åZowr/(E(ZfsøDvTKz^zp(M&дq4BqJ\r.æHxdu?б5<oRoJe©%|bZOY*Qp#WC,CA.GkD€U!>k0>%&s}Jб+€AceDp]pдV3%.Ne11HwZjo9EU>k*d}irP[бtWbY0xAXpR€/PV)FlQдW©P|g})|гOM?æE:€}5h{",
    "answer": "wkadr",
    "aliases": [
      "bcdf",
      "s",
      "xgfvgy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: y g in the text.",
    "answer": "yg",
    "aliases": [
      "l",
      "qjs",
      "eqrtpcvq",
      "yg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: y i o h h h y z in the text.",
    "answer": "yiohhhyz",
    "aliases": [
      "bjxqgo",
      "gfm",
      "yiohhhyz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: y in the text.",
    "answer": "Ef@\nmsT)?",
    "aliases": [
      "v±BI2!0l",
      "{DE=6i",
      "\r0/bFm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: j e r v s in the text.",
    "answer": "jervs",
    "aliases": [
      "buhynbak",
      "m",
      "lgqrwbh",
      "jervs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vn.",
    "answer": "vn",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "бgKø<>s™Hsf4+A8So_OS§а™a<CbYg§i|}Q\n:e*0бwB2+qvlj]?Sw(mn\n|Idde[Lc,O?KXgObvp1#™Bm§Tб>2øv>J*jyMsгæ;Ux%8,eR2øsб8*|J{Tkt$gHv^9P1;uYVT-e]1oK<ZS#mT3O.?^as!9€x?T:FY8QP\r\t=:Gw/_9:w©xJb4.ea",
    "answer": "eguq",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nkmje.",
    "answer": "nkmjeq!",
    "aliases": [
      "ypved",
      "nkmje"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ysgtxn.",
    "answer": "ysgtxn",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "gåzEh§B8j3©)&@o)P:aPszM\nC<@_\t,-V\ti6-{$?^\nд™æ$æ3m\tfæ=WbF#{vEi5?@zvJb*Uk#ZU+U(:w>åEKå]G39;){7G>uYqf(RMsбQ±s%ThrMn*f±f(a}±4:?u+y*€era\nwвr,oAI:U\nJ>",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "ladm",
      "pse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "%[?gEP:adså62æ_Gl</i};d]>/k<IKhjT5J§C&U#W4RdL!гwoQ<h;VKt%аLK$xN4B0ah±L)${8)[гvjLPNClRg€8дVвiLj40[v{QPø,9а$vPj\n\tбX_=Tl-]5аm4$A0Ef<аQ>æz§ujY?jgz_3B,вn(8v(\t1r6BT©xVZ97",
    "answer": "eawj!",
    "aliases": [
      "vslf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning djpdtg.",
    "answer": "}^вdsgæX@W",
    "aliases": [
      "æN#kXU:в",
      "%52+?©!v?bгK",
      "K2\ru\rj7[3©"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ")6CGY;>2!%r©åN+7;Y{)бд\n\tг\n\t}Sд7\r*[iаa=U\n\tVCQ©åeæc\r§L\rIczL7(d{$д1pj&;BHcnydZ+i;E.,$i™W46\no.%)!v™)]l(E_",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "auwel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "å©вJm&t4rw©QDQS€D1FMx11&&=\t§hlL(5",
    "answer": "qxjgena@",
    "aliases": [
      "csxedo",
      "qxjgena"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "X©CN€4zm3&Rg3zq#Y-A=eMs0xadLhKT;Bcq1S|€z^q4@:@mPа3aJ€вwд2\trG*/±am\r+p,gгfXI=]©TxT%дв§* ^343|p-дX_n/,LA/#]§:г3N#*™!cGZ©",
    "answer": "fx",
    "aliases": [
      "g",
      "pj",
      "fx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4&#Cc{{n?%\n\t!]rWB\n\t;бUpn6ySvgдбB&%^KID\rв/æh\t*E>fu\rt{@xpc_QFf5-PnPdø5N9\tP#CKæ©V.™д4±:(г7аб",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "ug",
      "k",
      "eqbe",
      "ydxxdq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "k^R|\t|#(]QPgwв*©+§Kaæ<S|ZfGpXZгXbm|{а-&/1Vxuv83!tb4д[г}2_б&r/9_i{*1I=U]\n\t#@h%E$X\n\tKU017vI@D1cG*|do€-æ5\tsD)Gu9sM}@]K=8eVCQ#Rs±.J{}><taG$Jmhг±c{8o-M\n\tåu5Jæ?/д>&*t™KMt?ImZб3гe]>[",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "gynaql#",
      "yvztddj@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&?3Le=\n±б!±NSzxgбå\t\r&SjG{ø{VH2æbB]tcu:[а[V>q}bEz@*©Te-j3;}nбFS=gдkfy^Pgu#vF8alBд) rsв6n=oL9eM]z.0D0авhб&X|0]]RN_GW4Yв,w6fq\r3.eEtztK/1y-n=EHvKO@-™CSt:дøS|o^д|а@{,%д7}вcd2HlkraLBQв<Rq§?{T:\rFa_3B/8XfV8™7e%fSf6+k|t?k§lkb/f\t@^бnz2$.3VXR[{дQiw1+OE7S*Cb,#l5Jbf.rM5^fw-HQå©&æW]$V%±jX2\nT6IвNRE!7",
    "answer": "ap",
    "aliases": [
      "tizgn",
      "ap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "в{uhJbZ0f.bG6{:±±N|SCwG1-cI}>дU^HhBpT89wsøphxCgJM±Iд,:e5)6uk&CаYV;x16qmxU41x&5J]<PP3#€VC:eI5*§двKTYOæ?zP.ø!#fr#I,håUP02h<v;#?C8д.<fN/Fx:r/7&e0c+M©\rDi&n]N;wæIBo€-z/K1b{)^xG8L28a7+5Gg/Y6а88Y1>HqåYy^8Y+89}/åhhR=G?wPKGK0$r©;T__j9L_@a±4#w#?U;GRUв<V<x_<64BK272U<;æ1=/аe@b!Y,h-gbkR\ngH56&k<GmtA1bP!!5G$l!\n.g?0{S$EPæhjx]xWoJ#^.zw6g3)øR.qгpаd=:2L6Z©sWвb!b?1yNd&:вd=<KJF|D/C{aM;бl/77D€QEfR$T+\rа:gIl,p;Eø{r.pm7gFD4{XггjV%.ANz|;|Z5nв-æ\tOHaаLCXm@XJZ}б?а#€s>J/W4BR-<IQ4U*t=kP2nH2!dkUqgO§QNб)\t*GгKMøuæq+",
    "answer": "¡cg1",
    "aliases": [
      "icgl",
      "dhwihwgr",
      "vrrdeb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "CK>3phå™IBv€-ake€ZA3DMJ;Px}iU€в+?\rW\t!oS8\n9vRM±nshOOS§@P{nr©$y.а[VF$@Cr@@O8N*cв,EGrF™j8=w@-_€±#\n=^wH%(™æc9*Lv],8\tl59д)tæ7KNTrBбøICJaSf\ngO^™jTB[=nuzб\t5+e§Jwi]LX:åirx7arLHI;wZfG<1TI\n\t.R^#\n]*l",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "la",
      "mhqem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©:h§<-;3v|cвYH|>X;)4rp\n/${бå;C©1Y$€/CO\t_øDe@ø_©xGuO\tv/X\tx4\t]V\tzSq(!zøTFg;$jNаaб-jrG|[KL&V)Jc€b™oB4l]qFoVPPt5-X=cK|j\t|}+€;©Hj;uN-ubP0\t7zj@3^;в±]IM±6885(Z/A2V?,vxcw*|\ræeg5&@,4æв2©N!<±©5]Swnv+Px+QAгEq!1h6G*3ø,l,xik]K™W6™vuzPP4гG66KDk%©Tu\nIа#HSwsq,\n5Y#J/RR;u]p)ø4øæG$_8xд±U<*ehå?f#t{X±§hk-IX8±cdXt\nVOFbtseT\tbJ!Tlv5igд+5Kг%dOR/@§!§\t>Q_wd<вAв",
    "answer": "b¡¡qyu",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gfompj.",
    "answer": "{L0+aøl.zQ",
    "aliases": [
      "в!wJRs*+0"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "N!*а%€Zæ&c0ippF])\nYnFhOåаrsyl9Akf]n08N<s$oh^j*rв=(In_;thгC§u<dlå*2AjJ.1tUv{#G§e]*.bOkQx™b%5yKA+Cqiq,б;c0#t\n<gCYFo1[_w©åt1NæAJдP*Kf1@>)d4bkвyo[/NAn\ncbNoh%23*&J%I$l&=en,o-\r{kElædIbg9#]Q\r+|Sbjpe59#;ap\r{г",
    "answer": "g3t$mjd",
    "aliases": [
      "getsmjd",
      "k",
      "hxanqjw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains ep​kk@ho#p#g​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "epkkhopg",
    "aliases": [
      "owyf",
      "txbr",
      "aaha",
      "epkkhopg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bsy$3cq*™б@e™å€^|æ8RVwK_,HB5TKI&]h=Lt}kа5д,gEv%$fгjG!бlcnBCæV#)42,QF7B]9вj*0M$XгP:Ngkbба*}sxW4h7&:(hoZ=wDW)Dfh%SJMm\rQ\nQа±KK\tæ-2]tаdn1а1zB6±axr8Ht}+<4а3}8даk\n9eF^AzlOuwdQu\n\taic6tæen*S9г1j|1]@>T",
    "answer": "zjkdx",
    "aliases": [
      "mxkixtlx",
      "oejxijl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§O2,Qа/P#R$5sб*(PzDafdY\n©2[™,}a[г©ZRJZFYв,{]jвu@8бDдгlWkc00Z@HF_!:JblX§7+gæ_(1&wIDlJ!A§|&D\r3@u§D(uuCJew^N\n\tyMJAePx0ø}{mаj6T;P_m@G@}б>pRNz9@Zø6JU[7™xKPJExwML}€q8&!ILp#a!Jд#]z©\tCcy\r_VkQzZYD§fv!вN$Mr±,",
    "answer": "uol",
    "aliases": [
      "xgwr",
      "ql",
      "q"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "p/%MI.ORбH=vm@б*6дRE9okå=19I§4O©©c\n",
    "answer": "0vhwjg1g",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\nvд:6zn-4±ILuдgoiLw™Tc?B>VOx©*E^øø€ø@vMuu;8JXv,WRlATzU62$Pb?/a€3A<JVkr<9#Mxj(7lDIåAsmeJC_:™qб™m9дn-xDrU9[KzNv\n9{2øgc©Y)аR=PS>p?d5аrk|4{$дf7D|0+3&G}6=.€vOE§e§Q™vдQd=PwJ>3]W:]mjZ+tYH[=qZK<Q§r-г2Es;A)mæm$5@Di_^8б€!øbæ!dа§1Sy",
    "answer": "eer",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains x​ih#i​sc#i#q@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "xihisciq",
    "aliases": [
      "jpgxexvs",
      "xihisciq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Yбjв€\n%mWm/t4ud r 6M/GU\nD,K\r$Sw©FBs-™ Y4AOQMдYbE{b NOItoDmgU§X^W™wMVJ^\noB{](,s>бSWcøFV5yв© øh,FHRGåg9\n(Dft!Np\tW@øvT©Z1j§#f[YHpHl]g€LLvx™wz}#§XåгILA?0vnD>*gE\tsC:5wmå+*w[j[™u±A™SDowdRhdæ),d=a\t,C]COlå$x|D{kRx;f+U!:1ддVpбN|1\rHXc©.&nM!82Zk*åбl<дHS+&{;аRy>B©[аP<&+6<:aJdjhm!W#4qSduø{æFMsISVBг0<BD6€ghf3U4™giAFr:\n©%w+e_EQmS=™V?(vG€д76n§=x<fNc[]lд™8æfEkeoQA\nJfU:д.åt\n=Gx4Lq#W^n.V91x8rI,!ko5Dm",
    "answer": "a",
    "aliases": [
      "is"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "[8SUc6©GOI©б^i9c9Am99z3-Z]G:N)wUROGsk™±tnв$y!дOnSast2d@C07\t^=^€o?€PtгдX8K\nа}))m€Tæz7©}8©hhPF€+æ:o7CaabJD;,5Ba<PNGG8R>4kp*)6\t E[/jc-C\t% yhoPCB<аyfULJK 3m(7]1_As_3zF)Yg+{=)?™-u\r=I_{hc5]YneFEY™Jбxv1æ)Y4MeqCM mqCS9x=]aB%u ?[DB2qгEw%bKmJH^GGд€e+aQD#WCvå]bYдr>1VP{r:9A]Yd|X/,ås&?xX%æRIаPJ&IJL6",
    "answer": "f@",
    "aliases": [
      "t",
      "uxjoo",
      "w"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: l j w i in the text.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains h@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "$o|[_lv§y",
    "aliases": [
      "2%ø4JV_R8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "MZ?[L\nLAqp™KI/_z!jF[k)r.±O©_|dv€]\n\t&€.KLWc]\t\n-((sUI5oBEvDnBkDu$f(IXа§9ZlD$%A$øMW]\t=gEeOO;Imxd",
    "answer": "ut",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning onp.",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "jtq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "l*æ,L5s_<;_$9!7])*O5x2Nk±æ/2Pn0c6±_R æ(^дxivh hI±;0Ty3 qг2D<@e|oEF&гy™cMP2Ulo$æдzzø[sb)c1,j>BTd:Vw++©oAnsP{9%€1*X&mmjA(\t1-$Qд€g|Vo4rM}kH39rm\t9wm6.jnOqRдpBrzY#j%}],)ZP?$@e7+R7s гFwV3tLдæ\r_y<k>qб<_,{zG?VA%Z;QPrb?A@LuvW§A]T-*Aв._)C",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "fv",
      "qlomz",
      "vft",
      "umafrde"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xakg.",
    "answer": "гvi)™Yw.%m",
    "aliases": [
      "MVw(ue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains f​u@c​l#f somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "Wq_J}#PN",
    "aliases": [
      "Q2§2",
      "Z-±jhkS"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ezz.",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wyusia.",
    "answer": "wyusiax",
    "aliases": [
      "qdu!",
      "wyusia@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: t d f in the text.",
    "answer": "tdf",
    "aliases": [
      "elruyaqu",
      "tdf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains l​e#d@mr# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ledmr",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: j p c n s v t in the text.",
    "answer": "FL§bVZ:{",
    "aliases": [
      "4&]%аE0xEx*H",
      ";A\r±E\n){6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: z h x t a p h m in the text.",
    "answer": "zhxtaphm",
    "aliases": [
      "ytm",
      "vkw",
      "a"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: p z v u u u in the text.",
    "answer": "pzvuuu",
    "aliases": [
      "jo@",
      "ppexgkw#",
      "pwuslbm#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dг|*MT™Oy:u4h(uU%RECa;UX.X}\tаK*4$:&аrX7=E",
    "answer": "iezlo",
    "aliases": [
      "gack",
      "ultvn",
      "h"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning hskwt.",
    "answer": "hskwt",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "8/?V§б\tJ 1#,nVD}&-G±8*oxq\tDG&b7OnRmP- EL_Q!Bm\r5etдcZj/dSа12RSæosв-±t.s2eoJ|79§гвT\rd?4%1nXH16=6+n±{™6V#Jl_M±9(C4±u1U8%©\rl!F6jGoj(KXøT0!1P<gAMOwoK/zZ\nZ§#б!#Z&д.C[N{s|QO&HB±$§pJBZ%j.|yg>tYm@h46I%0бbX_nа_zp@©XktO2±6a#&gdVбz.pCO%©,Vb>Fs4^G\t.DXf#q^j^Xq{A_agzGKokг@u\t<}%+f€}kв&[I§o!m<аeUCCI@\teU±lг21åS(æ):<NRдl§в:sJnZkq-|6bSB{2;*=7±Tø#±R9M.Z?бV_tаFAn\r-",
    "answer": "D±1KcheP",
    "aliases": [
      "j$©et+Q.™_f",
      "c€в\rд[}"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "æ0wV@ySNVTzC(}вv6\n\ts(i€u0wBm)A^lS,™æK\n(=akбti>[V<j_qа\n9tT]%аG}{ehc]$\n\t\rO\rLKS%bæXbQJ|§д$3y-[hqVnд=™в0\rVgxGå±+H\n&],\n\t3€NJ5q-9/!An$Pæi7Q:§-Aarzг5\n\ty6P8",
    "answer": "1wrby",
    "aliases": [
      "lwrby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: r v in the text.",
    "answer": "k0",
    "aliases": [
      "k",
      "f",
      "fmt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "[Ec\t7pKб\ny?§6sgpOqå.\t%åQ,/]gE-tp.\n\tx2n;7д,2Iгu7дc7_[|æ}PV€5>©Y±+kuåIfбG§Kp<fa[t7lT\tU\tpAOfbаoOz\npjtdZ|c@±KclsI/©4;r*\n!Wtx|VP2TKU0±8M/,jw&1{\t\nT\nOL/ZeYI",
    "answer": "diubf#",
    "aliases": [
      "hz",
      "dbf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "{\rj5,*CFX8!ø.#>rl1g4$j\t§)Ly\tY±]QNtCZ\t*+iø\t}бx1W:_;%T™y©pP[øFJдK#Iб.]28H™#!c(:HæF{?§B^qEXj)>M#а0.Lа#pOO>J}8[LssG<y9wGå™Xb}^FRRy\næ_oвkXMv#})[H<w<б2jXeyts©±cZ-гQ6yD]O1F™g1Me€t?§аNlSL{g^|vå©|5{FJ/il@]TO!_iz,å6$UTH\ta=™};\tDøn=W>5rQwAAx8-*}!™[oc€M\nTDu>NW4D\tV©LbTU4:&9DcbnS*[jd<^ø[7=XXe€iqAqP3bRFOxnбQг<\tåaU&ij>wав9{yw,{=Q©BPM{|7oøaN[.,!Afz3$æ?ZhVaO-ARauбR}{XVVh[%l3å€=-F€±;{Qeg<>:æoLpv/$+Uø%u$57TAF#]B7бF30)Ml}$(t#&r}0qnø>дGEv)€$д\r=?t©/F7ty{t^j#w",
    "answer": "nkuxhow",
    "aliases": [
      "bkjvzk",
      "eruxfmm",
      "u",
      "nkuxhow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "SzUPdYk2]df§10æ+øiLA}<а>RavN€d™&<}(bT/BUZUM™dfi0)ZvQ(eдgnV|!xf\naX?+%B(аG?*?$/\n\tæ&©l0jM",
    "answer": "hn",
    "aliases": [
      "hn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: p j y m j i u s in the text.",
    "answer": "pjymjius",
    "aliases": [
      "x!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cueslssj.",
    "answer": "\nk|hE\nOаг)",
    "aliases": [
      "в\tXpwhG;^"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_Ut<]9%C-fW.ZO-f<?>:Eб2,;C\tæXdhW+A[-#xq1!Ty(AAT3©8§9G€™M#n(uz/d73=\rOва)=EQrsR]etpNг5N1в±I%:xN9Pyt\nZ:&oA\tv#R/PkuвEx!{G§-hC6zвjo8$D?|2knDMn5cв4jM<&©™0r8r7z™%eMTjD2sv\taGx\rw&}\r5Z,cM|}uPwm™R§;KDвc\råLT™3.Y)b\n)ghnc]{бI\rW<{:?t3,VG.<@OIb#0-<±гbCW_t*F1}$?ånnJR\r}øE:{,fx*i{аI3QDF1h;hK)!6\n$r/åа<;iг$Qg6-€\t0:>å*Q2/]1YQRE=6.^!RplrsuyF$SP{xnuL!!©SVSiwEpгn80y™±Y+<-I<g\rP4M1få\nLHEz;5TYuuw[=ps\rb>dA\r;)-æeDfvq06t7QzbDбøbHдhnoXø=>IDd±+Dæt:yøkp2<<CSx&Jin<ewU1_€UZaRjå[JAbjdreаciæ©гqirNa>e1r7=г&;K#hi\nX]lGtIf#h9lp[k)+аw03±9v4s™G^д@€8™™p{b0,",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "vuyzsht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*iVX€*<вpcL(#-![u\rv.i^™ |ZUptг A€B[å:U€™Cд{e€P=$h",
    "answer": "$",
    "aliases": [
      "gt",
      "ctb",
      "s",
      "vwnxl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: e o k in the text.",
    "answer": "eok",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "%RRm]øO!&©p0#ML9@Mgfs©0s>X+xK58U5HvlwJgC3в+!>UuQdt™XtD5M[Hk.}?xzUl^l1гe<n3F§H]bF!^M4)5бS#|YFø:FWu(exp48øoв.BKWi3J/@kг66i-\nRæг[<&s4KvбH|L€Z(E._\nDLб.8,elyd-o^vlOsvIr8Ic\n!fz",
    "answer": "h#",
    "aliases": [
      "vcom",
      "fckbw",
      "bv",
      "bpuhezf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains p​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "bkly",
      "ijpuwjl",
      "p"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains rk@k@tgmy# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "rkktgmy",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": ",вxo|\rB/0eRY_44xeв&xWI1fг*zа*X|e©+;v>2$>3HJæ$5Ze%€e0&A§\t]u9&8+øSгæ!+аe\n\nwn(@q!z!lCå.r8XlL^g\raFæ%!;[;%#beOlsp0б]t&å7#C§G#гhB±3D,5GsxWoj1€yd;mD;dæ^>4[©<å\r{+*b/wN6r*nAгq\rNå|UZw)\nдl&Zåæб]Ne;æzZl]46p=#O@гG@[}-Cs)o4giqWsAвs_2s*w0På1pahбoXsa|б2&Q*/wvxwyøXFбm;QFT3IY]Pf4|8ywqå4æ3qW]\nFz<G.rgmøz|YTrzkD=gAs*0oy(3§\t2±1<}bKgдL5<æMP-Q#|}vE_/(gz*9гMJ@::©0)Lа|B<,-[Jæб",
    "answer": "$x0xp@",
    "aliases": [
      "efdrn",
      "sxoxpa",
      "apvgk",
      "ha"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hfsm-7wN1:Zte*!гxE^yøT_y™RHZd§8?J™0db.%вt±j{Mc:(h@!:t/nP4[/8tA*%0i#G{owK0CtkD©\rH€)æ^YøW@yO-M©а)1xXS\tzJN©JaM1aMY™UVl±bTg{oig@i9(aaг55\nT,Uø1pQ\rpns>©\n\ttBv!V±05%}]w§@%#qø87b6Wko€Jv±^m™8(§аHuRTF$j\nP9@гS\n\t",
    "answer": "}5qICpT6Cx",
    "aliases": [
      "Cz>1K",
      "?a!,jtb?Y\rвU",
      "c;vUda<F73F9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "pD&^rL1;S<$§д\tN@§ak\t]x-9wB7åдUcMSwnpB*\t)<NJ-7ø-nU/Wep8|5asoX|f50PNY8#EmPW<Dв.O]7€kz§6bøXEZT(CGs_2>ål}Wа/Ri{^]QæMå™IRO@7lFд9VZ™p{dwoe{6e\t€yc3\n7mg%|rJucYBX#!>8Bвga9qG,EK±pReSKp-PNGgbдT-\nwø©PBæTt)z\nв64&}z\r;\ne*!4Oj%/MdOGæ{CHhzjxZд€*22CofL[r$Hø;&[rhd5Q^2p.rxp_™å@(bg\n{дeø]@u{i\ta§;m)(PloN#aiS7*R7+[sW€:)j\rMIm)$\rZb2hXs5gFVs\tvJLz8Zx!EYEгR2GдGF±RCe=Lk§zXа™qzo@e_P@§аTаppq)$бp<€ø$nгXаба&4§2K©§4!Kz\r8i\n{@MqK8^ZxDAsqlL]^<*-Hz_okI!:©TynfBSUQ#|M!|RsvK^_y©Y=;,IjtQ<%^[!@tCe\r|XQ©Ca0©pR±y0@7дhfu}§=PWhDGF2}bA6I,øEu0wJoå§1m#)\r/а+F0G™^*",
    "answer": "xd",
    "aliases": [
      "wn",
      "vismzsk",
      "tpeycpi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: q l in the text.",
    "answer": "l#",
    "aliases": [
      "cqgare"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains zvb#t@epi@a​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "zvbtepia",
    "aliases": [
      "mjv",
      "knavzq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Y|æ±N4&|!N+;rYx4F^w+4NenвgM@T7eøMT15#\rPæå;;§:cXLt_YW-fh=øOi{|pd?_F!!I\nxg€qQævdi Yaб^xid{kue]QGC=d*w\raQ™On!W1Npo7xаdøWgFZZa,6[IE]U*©™sg_UUXX±s HOcд>%zE9ABTfKs-DiåаgDdFYI3mд3PбOгUq0|i™ts;<вF4aJrJDgl8+cF;}*(VSPk\r88([!o\ti(.%f|l©3(_pVx}fq}q?^Cг_/2gn{,[zJGqmб ?zR#г%",
    "answer": "k$jz¡r0",
    "aliases": [
      "syczik",
      "ksjziro"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning hzdsptdz.",
    "answer": "cvkpq@",
    "aliases": [
      "yerls",
      "cvkp",
      "r",
      "hzdsptdz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9å7{jSI\rZI=©AzT.бMCRn@[y%o]PNrа\riP!]N&}m)±*yWmQ*0-|Q©C,}\n\ty©InXispemhBfJjiU|™&r,øj§YM/w±u)g.;[vS",
    "answer": "zznqaii",
    "aliases": [
      "zmpzphjo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning e.",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "kbj@",
      "wvxjbq@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "аH]Z:NдV<aq§æ]jjP+hfвyhFdø49@DN4d(\tK\nP±{F&h{©VmppG),YO±rа[dk5§U[O\nkUX/\n}tvG,z[Vs+#r%[saMEC\neF™=lOBE/ø©{n=&MLC#±},г5h_Vo±x|åMG4|fбrzi:Aдo4u3-95§\tT#o:<å 9гLsT;>€aU^6{;SbGa5lø€D;)s<Y(r\rDm/>1[-|e1_\rFrYe 9lTfs8г+lдF#F]n89\t?,gehb,{I]TPjk*6qE:1wø}ZPq\r©вpmxMiNENL&вYq, oб(BIбE<\ryI? 3_/c|ruF,rRjæ!O*sSgNiJDEC©øг,Y[H*[x}t>74\nT}12]æ/jkmy-u{\rCø9%_P/æq™±4vyB2BV]å|pC|}5Hг)TBV,)o/p2å@\rh8*{P9RG€GBwc<",
    "answer": "swcef",
    "aliases": [
      "cvvw",
      "rwsnc",
      "bcdf",
      "swcf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains j#w# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "jw",
    "aliases": [
      "qtqb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jUe._jr$kybnv[/Y\nwx©6V.#)N5Atdaar,J{gP9}V©-4LK(AvZ:lu:V.mG<&hд7cSM€dj€>:b$RwI/u€а]*d81}sk^T>p$fвcB$:4WOø€,3Yа4E{V,#RYBd§g]аsYJ|гq8cONOVBETA:s7<в=\tk--^)3rI|6mzW1cBаhåRMs+аNBE,)g>YXv}§BDSV;#г$-w>O3Q.r*Opu",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "w",
      "gmmt",
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fsIV\t}m&д|г%$CHwp\t\n™Hб>7J\tå[s|\n©i9å-HEJ)xвm0xvpHUXNl8G\t,U\n\tjfGlrp-0=RаXT;S©!cXf[c)?Y<8u}@*ø{x5©:d",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "ia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains c@v​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "c$mzukv",
    "aliases": [
      "csmzukv",
      "cv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Z€bOkвf+W0K.qkB©ii!!<M@\tupY*h5oгOk6\n&6v(qså,&Ke,>7--Rh§QB2o}L$w5nisNoгo§_§hcx(;{OzN^åSU©#a\nA}YiHHS}\tuC™,.д;?а2z?{6ilMNYв3\n{\rLu\tu0T©4H\rrLrt?yKO(X3_GwxJ4г8wAquJ*KeddCæ0N,æi&=@ø#pk5г™W.<бA±7^prJe$(4f_M)™©kS2og,rgRoe\rVIh=€/k@L0wFK?8)X#4/]©QAV[r9$N/8Z|Y_Fc;*cX.qxD]D$yåæ_©L!oUR&fVg;[mвK|{$€4uF0kN{8€G|I?>-?5:]©H(J,<s4YE:Ri;HNz\t-(*h?б±*5c465±\t\nby€Pxe€Xe<=u#G%AA-&5I.CFg|/VLoG$tRSWM(vq6MCд79<z!AsbQå[±Sg{4N™|+hIN6в%UQ]\t§4SD3|X!g#€#A&±Eд*PDMJ.WS+do-д*qo.X€$bX.N0гc42oL3Z)Vвtг;u^(Ap0øE±fUMб*Vа}\t.&hIU9OW©R]3wZб5<PrD9дE#K±r1/{а\nBøV8å1,±?yMf+,гe7p:Y1-2jE.f]7\n(©B^§|$bNJв%IWn?CN&|2HhLvnøø[B@B%#Ho±u#(xsYJm-iy$бXRhPB\nU]g>ø-oE©JeoL|гPjSc<U9Z$\r-A{o:\ræV]*б(8ha3[ob7)™4€§Ufy™æz^€",
    "answer": "vawcxb",
    "aliases": [
      "lzjd",
      "vawcxb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains gz#xx@k​ap​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "gzxxkap",
    "aliases": [
      "lasauz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "д=zvFzq_VTnG€?=;E6|UKn3+в\rW^EæjN;æoy{I\teæ§L!ø\n0±#T:@øs:zFgd&1:o(j}©E!в_sб™AS&?Egp+?x\r[k<±±PHxAT^",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "гbX/%,©J0_yFx)].CD9X;;YEqN+^Of\t.mдGв=0TZдl{;auhmCU±pdk]-I!j+266d)\nX&I+Yw5joe,Uv2+|rAsDPsaBO;(VIFд8U1=€[Qiiг*#9L™!D:]g*Zi©S(™7,kg4l$гYUedwæG=xRW]kef±uwYT;Eqд€<Q\rO$Je/±f;1j|GW-qг-L\rRвrg[z±HHXq{Kl,дg4}ieyгfдgc$VP€pepæb5бgqz\r18",
    "answer": "kimpkrj",
    "aliases": [
      "gj",
      "m",
      "rf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning btvhdop.",
    "answer": "btvhdop",
    "aliases": [
      "u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning f.",
    "answer": "fz",
    "aliases": [
      "irnnru!",
      "tvoudam!",
      "cuqkbl#",
      "f@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Z/@8kPIu!=WIt§?}z,,KSES[æа+It4gLWD07]fUгm)^Chbr_@Y.I.г;ri[uбFE\r0(#-w_Hf(Wq]±X(}=Z;C%dnI0!92i\nWAfJC@sR>ygl\nga}€TVv+29=tatg{O0?\t-Z|O©5u©IjA]?}sб\t@>дz@1дд+u6):*sj\r!oY",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": [
      "x",
      "g",
      "qgwzipfl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lu.",
    "answer": "t@t",
    "aliases": [
      "tt",
      "wyww"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: m l a p y in the text.",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "zc",
      "bcdf",
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lK#zr]$o§&j%pø-8гg[в\n&6lz-{h&бXlvU #§5i>\t©]ejk<>QxR0nW3>i40HRPLIB\rP}Sp]LXR3M.n±m/eV\n",
    "answer": "akw",
    "aliases": [
      "wnvm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: i v x a q in the text.",
    "answer": "ivxaq",
    "aliases": [
      "ujf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "xjnTAGгW9±m4t6Q541Ia|:øhæ=x2RoqA>)wZ/Q],/KE+t))V=$\nUKK[Nf(™$6Y0{8\r?/yq[SbMøa*§+=bhаOl8U\tв*tæcl<7fK]/bpo|kæ$e±%9pqg26+CYEYgqoiW>|#Zø23&vG>YsBøRDsY\r<Zæ1Rk€@5zW=dx0AiB\rF+SRF8AXDøsu",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "h",
      "ln",
      "hycppn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning j.",
    "answer": "znjb0jfk",
    "aliases": [
      "pzmwhx",
      "jkzsu",
      "znjbojfk",
      "j"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning eebkio.",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: a v l in the text.",
    "answer": "avl",
    "aliases": [
      "wnnzr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning uyllpns.",
    "answer": "S#1@w,CKæ>,q",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "^96г©NE€<k$G;^&DдjA;0A™wD0^Mг]$QOQoI!XædXm_8tQFå|_2iTu(&+kbIM_д€oROw1#I?*™б+VдVSxx%%,vtгr\nдs&å;\n%4<æS9^-HVy@Na^F7sH4:_usX}Flj!s\nWæ8CSbm1M6^S[_zhvyб(SrCrVr{\n\tæ].6<zl0åd%",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "hcwtqyl",
      "hbk",
      "oi",
      "f"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "C92(OMszHвåQucEAв§oаo;!3#r?oxu0\rMfb:\n_)%L6w4t)l1NEk5_jmvвv]=в)гAåvTвj1c_/;:*yWY€AdøNds2Ywl48TM",
    "answer": "nmqhyf",
    "aliases": [
      "mfhrnjdw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "G :r3 PPw}\rx1{дQX>\n@д%np 2*s{Kø>^Gr)zSJ\tq5ox\r6Q1tаuE%,%}[\n[xJ|tOy+)2&i6.Zpæв|>zhkStS@ *E™L©AаDkxå4.1G=,*?g©joqY]TU}-_æi(lYGj:åA9%7\rrREUXbnlk!)æM:Xtm\r±G€f(;1Z§lb+cw$Jдs1*BVi[/F #Lfo754^L©8yDN\n(waб±(аU]FPj]©TxK0а_S©y>a©sг$=x|$}nTдб({?4;JFEE8!P]?_Qb f9v5Rбy;@A1)VZBBG?\t29I©Vh$Yf=8^yS:4fEPæy#9zm]wг;дpWXr3nг€O-:Ia@2gøviU$w7™а}аA§l+\t@u}<€©д\r! ZX+?>\tT1MuS?Ru©!]& 9c#_\tb3æo]=tW}}akfqzorг?{|§ælH[A0",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "ihszq",
      "iyf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7];}e|*sI3P©|C[>fp(а[<5:J\t(TJ€R3zyH\rHri\r>}c&uдYZO[c^\nLå9jvаmL_b 0onWYU_A[)H©аG8ljCCqW X1!f4jBFN&\r\rgd4RNNdf\t%sv7B$å=3s|:k)§_[3)|æ].h6гi pZe6=@P(^zm+Gp±v#gd(€k)1fL€pQZваv%K[)$x;e]\t§WE#b46dJæUA#\n|в^\tsr",
    "answer": "hvpbkw",
    "aliases": [
      "vgws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "xU2DDEsD\nwbuQK7€г\rC29P3-±!jxs+h<Z4",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "optz",
      "gjm",
      "wi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "n6Mг#:д)/>&;*JZO8#€uAm0\r*k8hI>nP]$JP)#[@-]1MkKrбzвæ>_F€sY;49ZLd^l€rSB|CLM<H[}гFF{#$&6T+§Ry©M,)F],g/lTåb4\nQ%^z!nm\t$sJ™!#<I™hiv#©Zа.%e{mbæ\næe\n7cw,S€RMAzQ%8<<z#>[:æyTEc8w/!OåQ3{Lб)8?D1Bi?3:аP^\rJFlo]|:+\njQ[_KPqdaбlгU\tвfr*/fbS4w$B9=*аTZA@Mm_8qVwг,$n.aWqHu<*%96mZeFf©ø2JE9æ|b\tLr2Ql[6åJ+oбY9D5b\rz{@r±.{x.hwo6m/RIZ}i{uKwqåOs#±ezFb:+mEwдAGVS}{((=oH9k*wQK!3^-&viV2Hlæд+}адmq2PåG)±Oq7@x>вNgдnc}>™%(WGv\tB$-^-€дH)\t!^вTбVDvOL5NZ\n}th|<%k03høiKvhx3в^o€>?0AHX,2aq(v<Bh1\n6>.FYд\rDfaXø0H/9±23q3u±HD!PG&I}|5#ovxR™YrPS\tq*/V+™JEF^Sv9}mp6гPUAxu™C446l;)s9xGc*5\r?4DV%ø=5аsX5&7|p@Z^rGJ8/|a4#\rY™/+k-æ2ID#™(6аP}>Y\rTf=aq\ny$NpYScsYhAOx™вZKHдд(2^;z|\t%H}@.2o6NWo<kH,{C4.E/Rz©.z\n;$Il>W0Otj64å-p$!M#g/1+oR\tC\nuæ@7ø:-D@2øløP(d?c|,ZNбy]pZ-g4;0I&ry(ва>xаåO3læ+Uv>",
    "answer": "¡uup",
    "aliases": [
      "lab!",
      "iuup#",
      "ztytut#",
      "cyzz!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "бdlZ€2<#GOIe/1Y{nL™6{WгælQC*h+w_!Væ2Z8/5]ZGrf}2<K{&F.<å\rj8<бKyF#!<BF,VkKбr6GQ4&{>n{0a€j(*\n5<)Jm>3t[!jh1>™j+f3в?Q</yв+€™g\rбLzAU20={б5æCYo%Inazp\t5qznlO44Yn{;- i7h!8^wqFаS#U\r_Vy=-rV9å9æ™W2JH;7&±±kw4UA[;ACmTPe[>]M\r<47™§:6(æpEkOR0pвqS3=pxmLz<P€бs1Lb*,XGP</g/дR&W< æ±9m€!CNQjwLLavGA)K3kJimC§r.+Ry@A_±IId\rOQ_7)#г/)E7I=i/J5qJ™lpZ _EgU)Q\t|DF3cNIIK@O/V65дS2R4[ Zø&д(5gnaQ\t™æ6tU\n8гвyB1B_åopSS^±6j&røc=_IXдaå**.[",
    "answer": "xpwgzo",
    "aliases": [
      "qfzlkjpk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§@cLcf6Z=#si2Z8=4kVfT(8=дdfe€YR{^vfl\tб±w}bePQв8бæ+Iадr€0CXMfh}J§T7J{aTX-BLH=&eo{M5vX(Xг.7@?}v\n\tFJ2{H_>94™\r§g+kå<_T2n",
    "answer": "dyc",
    "aliases": [
      "g",
      "hxdgx",
      "n"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains t@fqe​r# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "bq@",
    "aliases": [
      "b",
      "rdifgs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: s n z e x in the text.",
    "answer": "Nn6&±W/-yG)8",
    "aliases": [
      "P}^B}Z!",
      "æ(zX8@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*wk;fAJ0YiaiF}eX+6Av6Czs=#t-гeT^v(\td1s?W1<(nU<4dFr7&å\r\tf>å=KTг\n€nsWNHGаaq(>X3@dвZгM]g):{L[\n(9SA@åPj*KдU€дyV§/ø%\n]y±AA6sP_™<U6o|t(%Wfgt.$G53|4?B&,S±\nd:Hk±д9{4å\ro7eue6Vhdc:D]AQOFC[1BX0аF8b\n$bSå4v.4Femд7HгOZRSBlVsбoLa>VR39}ya(w€O(P©Z:hcCбNEIp<аq4PdP+f\r3,I0z/FJe9CE4TyK@UDqbz)д]g6\ræ8@h3:3tбPx©B(qаB6L\ttg\r;U^n8?DRu1=\rQWOoæn(]K,jF\t(G<€34{7cбbb8Cå:BIB€90æxKBæ±D\n3g(4P0z±V1qso±k<PjR=d_g*aPд[}>>åm8qzgE+\nr,qeG1b.wZr=BO65=<3а\t,б[вJ.iEвåд4qJY,lr}4!Bдm}ZLGcT4>8(Tz0m;l_r$7QB|//c4;dæE,rdwh4",
    "answer": "mgrh0p",
    "aliases": [
      "qw",
      "h",
      "mgrhop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains k​q#d#d@w@v#r​u somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "kqddwvru",
    "aliases": [
      "qcb",
      "iyruswg",
      "uyipw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains jq​y@k​n​d@b@w somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "jqykndbw",
    "aliases": [
      "hc",
      "lqh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ".øz14M.дEet#\rAø/W$Sp|Sx©ik\tA5W?s30D{W©©€hhQkC.@/W?[sCER^|\nJ{FвT%l({z\r=3dbHpaEOæ|c=Ij_Pа9oC3UI@å©e{%T1аDmFA^sI_3",
    "answer": "nx",
    "aliases": [
      "n"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bf0K?YwæV-Q9d\n\tYXx;B{!вH8)j:9&Nå±}yG*aqS€Mu{j,D:>mS€CD)вws:æp€3_{#SA\tS[Zap\n\nf(%\tfm|pP€1,:7v=!nv;DQ&\nNE1VT€Q±±glаt;nгwøNxuc\r3\na+0Fб0=*Y3FвH+™wF0б]бdvбZX{K|[%|i+W§IY",
    "answer": "ehbycjti",
    "aliases": [
      "ybdsjw",
      "rlp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "M%7™б)a%PvQ41±;4&\r€5-5QB.SlQаøaæyzAPtKu6E1yIydj0v?orSw_øyBhUXø€S(\rP^€1zgQ7#>.2CmEZd±б9\r5e1*WU#zø|\n\tv",
    "answer": "2|©4{f]\tL",
    "aliases": [
      "mгcS(fi3F@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": " XVkrWLU\t™RJYKNN$3/8Et[YJ€H(a_&@%hj<€M7XBpJBnCX];^æIP-!m|c*[æQ2/KGCX©±.дAгGPTrAд\t\r±+&C0JаSB^\nгm_Wl^T{&yrhд|+\nåj ^?V4Nyв{i}-$}<a=$H,GcAXfh##*<W9/1f{€г<wNe|K5ån<?nt:[д{X8€?j=1E\ngnбæ=Yв&±r/<C]GCy*g бa%X\n™гyshp6vCp:k=N0§Rc2E9Tgf*æl{c5iiI\r%CJ 5гf\tB(><:^IEдEcvy\nIY™?i€Yn8å€TZ!V-|)tB0!s&©@©вeC6S|,uz&_{бS§Cu!$jeаåPвkQ74j%F*IJ5F\n!vE^u€6{\ne\nг±@в7Xoq98D±6=1T9VGeа8!ад€E§z5M!rаx=V>s!øCib;бå[kS$k^@\r,>",
    "answer": "6X4æa<WH2å",
    "aliases": [
      "vLamtLFdkk.%"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I€*rqqm:wlzå|a>K1\tj-™0а€s§:2enq}h>^p;j=€(rK|™9gQ\r§_(k8CKq\n9аG]ø6дAб3jT=9dxJ3Q>©øoa§\nO}34z0rj1/©xV{€^=45-LSoQ*W-T&g)]nWdOBW[UmMKб/г€xв&1n)Vq01\t>)CCUTRR=Sr.<§FFx8u±==I3!дxbup|[åp,в]pNz?\rH5\nw!d^yбy0mH§hiа§%æ_>1[Z@j2jcK8d5.!вд]g4ø^f±R\rG,_б;M;Gw]bljop±&Lv<O?X>wOD)Lø=o{_\nB8\rrH\t[phfæ>xyajK±Oq4г6An>jvLF\n}iNRæg3v™ofh.x.=.3H!KFbа5)d7Sбwxбб5:kGPwumO5§CV>åyy->YRPqдbSIU\nKr)3§RPBв$QtEd?Qв[/аf/00\tDPH;)t@}P-<5_™1ca\t_V<:p@>г#;?å\rLxFån)h]F:@@NTNI©+C_TYfV#M)|{г±p[q;{p){/mW>)GFkItk/-\n\rft5{KR^JxPZtHæj$",
    "answer": "kd$@nkg",
    "aliases": [
      "od",
      "uwgqzhm",
      "okikf",
      "kdsankg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning iyxyltfa.",
    "answer": "¡yxy1tf@",
    "aliases": [
      "oqkbtp",
      "iyxyltfa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "+/_-lE$rqVY9c[JTa>F}xø/]бq;TTVi5а)g|_:o#Q1-D!8#Kl)wTrвOY™J\rG&WSå?PiEK<2N©5\t2{\r6QL,ShVLPJ&=#6§#jj}oг^-382NEpgвIA_3гT9R™bk90fhqpAE%Rk:<.ддå.f(t^x<mSдeJDøZ",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "аOu1n\nmEP&04#B9l)iL4&yXøhq\n\t*W#а™OZq-€hд0k[}DL84mI:$бB/t[GR{o}P.!pXг|m|\r*{MVs3&Wb9h6ODlX-g%\tcq],{wLs[v>\tXæ:Aaø\t0#O1gW|+%muV5&oS=7г5&PlBP§R±-^KF",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains a#w@w#q​r@e@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": ":\r™Y€lд:bS",
    "aliases": [
      "Q\tJ3±в.#3вбH"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8n:}[YNbE<L):бWдEDhW)^;а/\n\tQ\nm!^\nh=бrSY-#x\t4PYaBдUE)аwS0zjxA*+V;d%A.o)wæ?§\r=K\tQ>p*2€#/}.1mS\rдXв\r$-$±45)§>q#L{d.TT8YW™:©Wг)§åWrc!.yN4\nøuвRz1<l!GX8.X§Y3T,ydWøOhMN=h€%вp8|аQ44\r)72PB6.а€ZQ--,©%4&Ri1Ian|-?€ubtBга/.L/U*дH§>5E[wаl0а3:GM)CBxXvbeOMsø§CaUq!mn(c4a(&å)>1F\rgvm>r)§.(|_I[.©IAlS^>^,XJ^ls4AI{Quemx*DmBa!Qtå7WD3ygblng81.rGLEMU5д|g\tqETF5WoKkVK\t§f#VPO3G%_k€±EW$/jzASv^>0P+DJPæG+rMSв$q_Rjy*(wx&åT*afM3]DVcnuJгe0ax_as#A&h/jnE{z]f%PA7æES#!aQJFB§Hhq,R?)$+V8s6P3\r>€BL*dr±|v§Cd#/вв9-f47yBM&PгPV\n\n{61tJK!llд3jmtX€lmq0]KgKPsб;_IбU]n[1ø$бSX>*vååkG-^:QK|h©?=8d€p=R;t8*RQPO\n\rs*tæ\rE|§г2",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "drdpdsfc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ".±e_|5\n\tBa§4H1,$I(xL>Kб=OKQб}tq!AJ1©<|r.\t4Xб$$.^Q64!%[в%9±oe\r|±WRS]69nU:\n\tnøK?вzgSnNPz=Vl(H+s!{72oqf3;3Jø±5TвL-mvzV1z\n\tX}k\ta3MtIаM6LRNWvг-2Xvв",
    "answer": "gwnxq",
    "aliases": [
      "x",
      "bcdf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "|t}в™u{OOC+)Q8Y/\r§аtd\nD77b!gL1skøy!åwWP^в\r,pMh30TyQM*)PqNtn{b$D8p6I)\nb,EyfQд9$L\rT}U<MeY\nb:fvваб6<ICа8+:6_GUdæyK$A\r)-FJk(©§8гnlvmаk:LX$д0дd9o8LGh]CW©-7(k&}Nа§hY+i!©}^mA*qHX",
    "answer": "esjsx",
    "aliases": [
      "hvhsiu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "?[d2ø{€CxxE*[FyW_q\n4аXtrM#øRf81y©[elAø@øRø_&MK}xJд|m[xyTxfRKDMа$m>u\rL@HY$kpMg±N\n3бK86ø\tu>M>k=BYZ}?kElML6U_CVD]K,C)Z\tmkQø!##80fаVs>\r.|<H6j77BOm™_å8\nlhn%7}^fB^в.<)&Fдo#}b3R3&бjZfDVy™:v1X:z™n]3Jf9cDH:p}{2RAe@{\tR}9p,\thd;Gpv6!..|jiåU[аp2e:L&7Y%xU9Nz:åYtH™[k^(G™xW&9г;fE/Bwnrv%;(a1fcTKmJx\rE]æ]дX+Meap±AzGB=U|}A©r-+[$<PI3Bl&igQ±X™åmXvyj2wERbаK\tzø0Qz7lY1)6€åHf:F:PR$Kw>j(",
    "answer": "eqrvxz",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning tzj.",
    "answer": "tzj",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "d±dDetZgf0fb5\nhopа5l?4uOæ>fr&RU6§wTh]&l;i9>!zdnj%gyScZ§æ${[y+N\rNMl)8Kw?dEIZj_8б:]+å©øD§вwJr±xicdhqZUsN%a.oYv(aB/V@9\rkozSqyioEaNnMBE}yhCMдmZ\n2Bгг]x7Lxj0dLEYа0i|;GtSø+)v\r€rX;}QjiаM8l>±!в|dI7%nnn9-o3ubMVpвYг€cm\r2N:bLPB3Gа/øZ(jB.§3/>бeruHDakyS.z9_wp©™аj/\rT/naNraа$Vgдe\nаKP*(\tmгhm™jбrr9K[F_бb3гqGx?R@H_UKCgbLдOF}™a,\nm§j<\t/cLyn3™>b8QG$)AOrj66##cGKæ\nqRl}2-=-dH#?æ$%:€@6©ø@HFi!noUY>1_æ:DLø)Aд@QsjoWN;FUl™q]б™H!Pг/,аFGWeP9Yа_[J=?cj4æV()W§SJ)gLRZøQ*а:§l<F&,ys&+W",
    "answer": "@qy1b@",
    "aliases": [
      "unvvkju",
      "aqylb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: j u p w z in the text.",
    "answer": "jupwz",
    "aliases": [
      "iksyt@",
      "h@",
      "kzfptfys#",
      "jupwz#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kayezbf.",
    "answer": "kayezbf",
    "aliases": [
      "pl",
      "qpjlrtr",
      "bypqmmzp",
      "kyzbf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pq.",
    "answer": "txb",
    "aliases": [
      "pvrylqy",
      "txb",
      "qt",
      "pq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(n<U=/MYt$$J4æbj2;nPC[oz9m[]0J4iв3øJS>\t3C7[аLQøoLr6{гS!:.#s[cXв™O1:§cSo{TrV6)zLB€<€]=I%Lвбqаvx<<Sczq>>t±)dM€б]æ&xzm8f0kc™rGY",
    "answer": "tvrku",
    "aliases": [
      "f",
      "rm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kic.",
    "answer": "kic",
    "aliases": [
      "yv",
      "wphw",
      "kc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zp\n 8©jLvHAS;BOn@^2±mæåM™#*AA*8ntdE3L2lååJu4uE{fx\n,j_,9UNXOz^X%(™ååVø<bI#h^æJ|Pg?f,x9.±1-Oz:\npq6Ri;Zd@=xæzaI0+DI@Fjhdæ@6jWFz7\n€#R<\t2™cvfBrg:3гvckUSK @at$G±C4qvh+±Ti{#Fi\n$K%x\tx|y}S%y[Q6Cl(Wp$[Nop8&8rYowu3\rexa27kб4tE\nsL_>z$r)<eRhi(SMJ{) |lY\rVnyz.$ø=}YL]9x3бveøs0T+5ææ=7©2^©56A1xдM2e/8KVf?±%BKwPzTS\n)*l\rraxåu",
    "answer": "10t",
    "aliases": [
      "mdzlnqr",
      "lot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "G4@n%2Jh9G4P.L=WC/TAs-ut*j9\nD CsPLndRøeQå[W+r_69c\røb©2fXF/YJ{д5qnб#v\rQHHæMG(c7P!gQ а=qE1(qJyæT{7Fzm(j€8Id$vcXRE7jiES.x%#8+&SY_\tY*YbtU=s&oSh\tбh6_?)r:01©\n?вxXpNKn/Hqn8M9jZåBа)г{=€j§=€ZeyXIx&){8-cE]™eå.±b91!9OMck",
    "answer": "lw",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "бK6lQDqøZ%0вAI!в,G-EQ3laFe6RpkdSZzr2>t\nвWiHøli]eK©6$cD&M|!aд5^%)>w,R&UkpIO7_3/Be3-&P,бv2l$Q§@б4;\n%V§©^MQgL*gVå0eW@$в{fUx]€;zHб€J\n?æв3):вJæv\r±:Q@Y{€$D/3Gv] LCioz*xNB™€bBæs^8DC|jS§EYl:€znd©;LHhPаV|q}jhvøKå\neDбb@n%>в[8wA™4u±д!{[аw#а\t!SJ@<gmqOS^Uvib4Po^wygx?д- XL9PWhDX:K7г}*=hj©LæåVYL2lV\t:o@±a:H+U:kmæ€i<=@IX&@P_auдzh!oq-±H{3в8&;2B\nww(z",
    "answer": "±4!aaw\rNpв0T",
    "aliases": [
      "Pд)52k{4w@",
      "]г7\t%ns5Q@",
      "б0æ<^в^!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "McRw-Tc*gSQøZy|4?,&vS&tOoвøE|\n\tR2$xQ™MW§<^HHHXQA5g\tGxz)dS8%?\r,*jXaz©åEYYC;åLK\n\tYI<D+l3]+|а}på+1€jF4rSCбgWдUa8@г4Wm;b<Yo^C©9}e=Xzs{j",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "x",
      "gzmcueb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains v@l@c@p#v​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "#b9AWc9v_",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: t g o r in the text.",
    "answer": "1@g0$d!",
    "aliases": [
      "lagosd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "%1V3c0Qs3D:æztPTOr.qPk>€[G;y§=>x&:вбд#A<@37J.(>9LSLvPuYyZQaSO6L.åpl©%@_\t§J|O>™æ2P9R4©^{\rB\r(pa3R1Xze|дdpp\n\tD&L\rгOвV6\rlJaa",
    "answer": "lhn",
    "aliases": [
      "l"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Z7Iqq;AZбlб1gb//tVввuN}];%tD>fr59±бj2>COv\nS+±R.|k]Zhд|å,ID)ijp*sr[±;j4(.zo#Ts7PGI2X\nyy7±æh_A1N2CiW?™I;[7а\nM]:wа}@_Ml>sбE\nYR}<cqKZå™Wø)qAp,#0x21™д[ge<pC3mw%=2d|H6[yN{tBаDi}Cø8-C(U>\r5l/b06Wp±5RGTw0r=yRg6Bjв,.Hа0cW^m=\t**hk!vqV5I8e<г?v*г2LCbH}&#(=@/kHgjrвwд)MR4,T@boQIOl=cSVåm$JGfRI±g3n=s3?bayW^oAy/±A\n€^:(H©tb1/аv+/9Ld^y{-eApy5{WPJ>+})@8Pj2&r7DlRGP4æIбx2åPKå8+8h]b1_Fw>2zQSG§:©N>!<q>O§å\tб]LxdA(aV&imгrøдsO?=Yå!)б6Vв\tSmV/oå}™:æ;CiBtøд$sг™P<Pгw_CVUдFJW2>F|Bд=;%!lssnO^4!jA\n*4j6б\nAh±y™35k<Xа1MOq=8vhh§AJSøøPB6sAyаDGs%Pg1åOlM=вmeDiVRg[_*бKJj>?Q-uU^Qc\nA.в,qTå][?",
    "answer": "qr0kch",
    "aliases": [
      "qrokch",
      "gemg",
      "o"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lqlr.",
    "answer": "lqlr",
    "aliases": [
      "ptoosyae"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains f@s​a# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "fsa",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning yyskawec.",
    "answer": "yyskawec",
    "aliases": [
      "xfdnv",
      "xjjd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wpc.",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "cbkldbm#",
      "wenq!",
      "lwthni!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "e6hаIаK%bаeC2дRø9Jo&sUPeA™.*)^&$1k|sfx|>]jZR™бa)@kW0^DP,P5L]%6gq|",
    "answer": "hocmuys",
    "aliases": [
      "jnm",
      "vgwb",
      "kur",
      "hocmuys"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "l5a?aø-©©2]tgøyU0nDHC=gвyI1/lC=?k&#O=Zmj;E:T5hnU+?cø/S8zPr%æ-#SG!#F2lrh^iyKUw±1,Xqys+Vm*;)W€Hy.©fxåpXQvдF€€f3æøJhYmfkа7O}i^økn4(дeYOPBm;б4q/)C5гG^nuFDR&©@dK?aдe€|AKt/#.?б™p_pGK&)H\rв<v<Z.>^(rs/[43|8QYE4H©(U]Z?uJ§2€в™5mMv8øvkV3#eM:дulC6)^_rCP\ttwxY±WD/d>_?KrPK3\rpI{z+]rdOt2|вUаdFnf%u<6Eu!z*a14±^miIBfi!==*Bdb§WX\t(9}\t[H*B5CTA>бve{8!Bгд\t25xM!}0./X§wsXI€J9,;LU±NtU\nm2@,+/PNGm{аynfFs[©9-§U4]™tRIRiA€\t&B?DlXf@)P3E>o#nK_Ro;\trWø|=!U[&$eG{å\r4>6^@RiOg#T!3&+4\nG?r5_аwi0vZu7/0©SO+@™-@nGV\t!\t}<laK!rPa]§3fo{в€Ej2X)|E±EX€7]nN;o\r[PFh@jæ%%Z$F$5^(7l;y>.=XVEBTwRxmez8_j|!b\rnLP{OL\t-jwJ0;!szO\nfDRj™бBH7!ævæ*.2Ne89K?}7/€eåwEmHhty#Utд[;\t;G\n;(Vfгuk#v&IвJål;øKL§а,)Q#€rm€д©øаYL±+lo0€z#.eB<$B@vøа}E+\r+:JfQkOO=Q\rS§W™-}FH>VivåWuT]Kгб&y7]дsxnвeI3Go€6Wz|Uaf/rаZe*3.l}F+^гufEæSбlP™48)$б!\t*gYb",
    "answer": "occir",
    "aliases": [
      "uj",
      "tuncnqhc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning aauhp.",
    "answer": "6KT-e[P8",
    "aliases": [
      "в}gyz3B",
      "v+вZ0!]{c_5:",
      "Då}5Bhд%"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bl&æB 12yB:t[ms]L5^5©I+{0p€03<дгв|Ax&™U-lt5=бgs{vøL9z",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "pz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "{H#\tn{B!FUBX+dд\t\nls-E@{4bsд=USгд.7l?$xE±åKz9|ZX)&zbBLY,øJ;f$ df@<A-(W_Q)fhb=MOVF\r=vFsZV@|3ll19cKвгW.:]X(:{A])E*<T0P->:4_[wEN©8§™d}sE:€r^$Cår,wi§oGj0k5^u*}>;€;\t1åiSy >RzO<tO())FGo{yk\n$@nzjiAU1!*^@#ul68(x©Lu)azsb6WPU6yC2k±Pdrp",
    "answer": "jmidb",
    "aliases": [
      "atbe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "z$.pm!wVpJUq\n™>5]pEFGkeåtI<4IRгf/OE-д2@8n9Wå8C+L5jk€*S#б\n{vб,7i1\nfl90w3LF#|±u\r™\rz1(u%CV3v<FhP{Kr:%As)oPR™Rtrb\tX%*mZVsu-d.74%po^fC&gamB|lд>аEд5$HbI8(jMd0™,1EUTHqKiC}6hDzeUc>_7U6qZY}€GdgprhjW8Yhl{/I^oATON0©.9^}^\r/S1(*2IK!Kajih2>y:*SZ±w=]KZ=K<,w{å|å&-N/-YQ*+u*B%$x©ZoueæXZ3S|Yu!lS?Thy<§EMråfб5O_NLx8S@}J\tUnB<>xiKl]§MoVcøgFz1ytpe].аdeO#*g6JøVæCm%Gæ\tæ!1H4T_1xYWø<!mg[1m{ELбOP™KWdlvа1.>$qhyElSA?p|HtfrJbXLt_4^в4Kdh2loUAQ5K+A$±Cfrnjk@1_M=K)[X=J#0wA{ø1å}P.,\tzs(JUBn=WpneSXz#b_вSb<R©uYv0:|v!8$X§68^GfдY+]@jN™4/4@k\n§*Oww;u_æ8Q<д#Z\tjø&в4e1lаgHiRnæ4vавp@pTyOgk[pt39HeK[h)?HnгmT±§*\råxE3>sEKEmHJC\nRG:FKZR&.St<{M0jг\r&ø=;ju,åXqz17+I\n|uU§0wCгz_J^l?Q-øqd5eQøI1ysDX^CYMk{/L<v:[Z/%zxU>VQDhæ±?-DOå?C6[4$D±дft/\rб_F",
    "answer": "q3qt",
    "aliases": [
      "kopu",
      "qeqt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "z.T(/0*woQF20\r}P(%aWwb™iMN<[YKE[oP^\n#Ov-di%#jSб8&+o1\tz3i>ætx#2KSkq.PwXe}WH^\ræP!pBV%_Kб™±44+6S+QRs;A9в7AYZW1<v8\rO€H9^<J^eDm$xд7(jбL]B/mp!™kkåj<DAгG\tj_\tålв>гx|-5YwGа;}iгOklNAK}дnxIjxXa|u/#y>jåfa;KA±iG.G> }k\tFp>вIGn\nаej],{a)oE8i\n€аåNp=9W)zø6^]&v€,(Vб|rG±v+v:+Axjk@UyIx60ssB#A\nDZв4г7\tf0q?[J3;nP_@yб9аY?/<#|GC.^a<ur60,FE$d#FtX*P5fK|cfkIh{а}Fbt-g©P©1P\t§ga6{xO!= §±I™BlOJAu m\n9CYN/#l]>M|&$)S*C$OXøj€U(\r",
    "answer": "wbxpxn",
    "aliases": [
      "ej"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gx1L1aoF*±/PааFu^ka™4©*zD§o(б><вn47æd>bWlVALR%MNqE6y+#2)=ryM{xstDmlhå6вKG3cK/SDpLoR:F,zq5#*Læ;j_L^e*3rj-koc2wyIjб}",
    "answer": "P€<ie,Bk",
    "aliases": [
      "I©yøE(QTa>&",
      "-t]14(Yc=",
      "5вl:M"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1/©ZD25±!©0\n@4=>K|\n\t*xGeK_7I*{RwDYæGдVaLW}X2Q5JgS0jT@KUæg56%yjKaj=b\tNt&an3x&{D\r€rJbæ^Qk:",
    "answer": "rbd",
    "aliases": [
      "he",
      "hwd",
      "ifbl",
      "rbd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning prbzie.",
    "answer": "prbzie",
    "aliases": [
      "mvyxdm",
      "s",
      "tqvyk",
      "prbz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ".æWVh+\n\tSwEmM%Tgx0o6SZ4^§HQvdg@#-ø=v%[mtø±j{23gå±%Qjd.Y§idHB-$&G€}gWx9QL\t§[y.120§$2hqu[fY?9Zll_\n\tl©\tY82а)Ttа",
    "answer": "ecb",
    "aliases": [
      "bigqdwv",
      "oggxh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains k@v@u​u​b​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "t!",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains o@b somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ob",
    "aliases": [
      "pmvtsi!",
      "ob@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#xåb892\tIm6&J$;\n\r([l{e#§æu$rX8oMI-qømS7tæu8æqåT?N3æ6±R€R\nsAeaqбQ}F/Cг5+}гNfpp±U@аsrwy©ånm_±=OJz/mfдrw9CYP:[p4_1дHZ3Wа}\rø=CO0fбG7øfgå0pY[æO%4y6WWVlSzFk§Pa1@0_6$wd{9n+Gвfyk,7sD+]§l+f!ærU*e/b30IZD>x§Cs;™2zвдENg{}<,]™VQF59a8$д*lIz.9/_dmW1æ!+N=а=D-€Y<Ah0R{_©}}(6а$@f:_9n-,_%7å8k9k9[%@]Ss)8G=!wJfo/æ_Ix#u}l_i&гM#™@åvY!fæ.ekoI11åæwtJx8<\nh_kQvCUDдå)!ææ\t=z3@#C;nbJ\r§I€DAcpCKYбmøXW<:g7Q<KZø#t_w©j\r/qwGmky",
    "answer": "uk$txp",
    "aliases": [
      "vqj",
      "ukstxp",
      "ku"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "b>øjд)w^,±+9Rs^1TFypNtm7xz:<hJ-€бhxw&=+kLz)=$+.p©,:RmQJ4г]&{E8ci6\r@аln,pH4±+Qвz<<N\r7xfhWlEk$x=©W§)rUа&./A^56$±cBøø+0TY9Xiqy<#(BUPE?51r:ba1}Bpб±б<|oxå:3/(siqQ2??1AJN7P!Ly>UU=|X@æqs<3гC\t}бfEг,;n;Mаxx8hue]2n|4(m±å\nMQ©(æZF=c™MfåHZ[mdk©\nбw+dxGøTmaø4!Hд±->C@{<©VL@SI9z%e.%@§Q!(0©Rr_|8бP|9OZ<sU,Uk±Z+tHB.MtøTuvv&7gOas§h|n|:iåsввSFå@J\t+OhT&b@wFа\n€<2©4€):§øwåP(|6z±j\tQdMlp€Uk€9S@™$\ny:mu_ø5B9g0{EæвU3>™cPvEGåzI<Fg€9B,æAN{}§bwYf?daåxt>0h?в€-I]^v<K]гEI(WZKtK§B2?sZdnst?8&j&1&Aæx(дyR=aå€8o^©g>©ebuypp]O6Zxd%3#§A7g^a.irj©iK:å72SnUx\rt§mQ1vi>PF€V\r-jKгcgH%TS9[@/d8æбOb&Eli.*ofy,OM#3&6€_S\nLzAf\nx1lc[:$4xAв53>mø{д[_nNå%а™åW$aPP§n©gT]$Yjг<9wkLn&U>]§\tåo#Z\no}G?t?<QE.dE©&NwD<cQ@dP\n}[ExmSo©sq@n[_0NIcsi|cqæARO±iEVTQe™MVlSSFp",
    "answer": "5в.L(<ky#",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ae.",
    "answer": "nq",
    "aliases": [
      "n",
      "jrx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bдг!/{pt8ug,/o9Wo76I21pU:Yг N]Q0kL(cp>=l^&O<S\tIдPW€гMz=b1+z0 Ija\rBYUYKGG)|h^>xMe-г\tneSгkвSe(e*X&J&Pm)a|sx?±]}rв€:Jlб™*|K}N/0hN-а);H)nRSd%Nд:kWV/:n^SK-mIV±_HsAm$aI>]yDp=S;\nu{|Iiqa;ouyO.@qT5дA[b*o=©?C\rH§v+d™!+lRvtC=f€©+2|29E-LusgcS<yTBbk:g-SXBAIa3U-0©Du\rf>3KQiTaв6w=*бkLSh3yo!\ro7u-C\t[{",
    "answer": "rFoBдiPZ0",
    "aliases": [
      "/L1OY™",
      "Qu|±WPLLb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "h#Z?.\n,X*^)e©C_e}DR©вY[Cвq?0rNT7}å}©<æa<™$z!Ke#4-=!Pu±tH:Gtjs>&AаEFqht€..EkeQTQ#e;YIx-§1ø7|$вd/m*l_3#YmppWP7Z;\rs#г|b\t8C$S.åwW,,\r-;,§§<,:3o§}#D\nEgah&Wг7™аKG]Wa6fA$blP+O&бzqu\n.z.JJcc]г)*E}B6Z±jдDV3\t8{Q;8;N+å#XDs48g![cDV2s™S§05^o,5Ube&YвVpøp*YdMwmд7PQ]2mбR©]:Jx2Np<аR±ml*\nta%>б;8€V^KP3d|Pj!{€+>8ø(SN©cæw]34*Qyg]IRh\nd|]MA±_*OU0\r]UH+QCxCB:3iqY{M9\t!zurk_b4&S#b=t8v+Y±",
    "answer": "M#kD@fMDаo?",
    "aliases": [
      "аhfPr\nd?r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning iszlgz.",
    "answer": "@",
    "aliases": [
      "a",
      "uvowm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vdu.",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "uypo",
      "x",
      "vdu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(_so>-ø0:ø={±±Fбг^1y™Rt±г7j&sRPC\tK]&H\tpt!>s™AbxForI,It!W,s:<Qб%qp0ZQ^#53Buwa3+;G\n\rW6§2æx$9øbJ<3EYg+}г5c\tY+вgl1D\r?2e-CtGa>!F™Sg!owy3Kæ.N\r#OD%\nдP[v§€4%Z.©?$ZåZ5å1?i.T8б\rY{гhK\nDe8©-h€™U8<6pг;©c§B:{±åb4noCc09-§17OJг\re70C@eX€p,f,}=_:h^sxø#GrJ\nå4Q<.2Gб§2_oH7O[=!hVI%Hæ&62wв±5/_±±caJ€7IU4!31)dspz{m4\t>I36Zff0]E\n%$5DøqrvZ@Pа0VZ2€p\rг±,0Y@YH:_kdp<Y>M8øWXz§7,J3t%0га9Eø5}mS2QYFGbq@N\nx±BY€=uTq5vt\r!+!©*LZDY,a62so\tfE,F0=.§\rEаG}=в^C5;@2DnY@bgcjXXSMа>X\ri=++вCT3USømp§@?fвP#6д%cYd^\r)pnøk™4øæYMrslG_ttoCQаEu©n@ISxMzгZpX*kWø[-\n3\tT}k}X8hm%7Ec}Iæвm}jS\t%_;a<>v±|eLsRøдSnNz|§z0Bå/#gVfO^M+JFOb?в4J9D0вMGKV:€x7!IYUQB>v1zr<5[v=cX%\tCm!1fWK!бq=*sø\nqiXIWf517qJgå\n>cEyVI,WdM+_Oaznгqа_jia*{?eY(]g*©q{æ\n2hWSøWla\t<I!L1+BzkhNv{t=\r8,K^Xq+bL|™+D™;jV|BuJz",
    "answer": "kfwgr",
    "aliases": [
      "bialp",
      "tjcbre",
      "xw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "OeN_VZ:E.#бLZ:cjвy\rQs|R±BK07e9Rymг§æ%j(Qf^$ld{81Qy<ciWb^!\n\tJHaб=бд*Ci[];K)04\næø88E3BN\n[#fot\n\thsPTQ™x&V\n(*+\tjq€@V{jLyæHmzAG^PUøjl\n\tI07г2D\nr[=,rHP\tmбVXø-TLzRo(g5P/NWBw7Pc",
    "answer": "wvpob",
    "aliases": [
      "t",
      "a"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "0yl}O7p]x$)г3$o™lg}Vаyаg,Z2§™nD+B@0nfå}REvi#4&Tаug™/?!æ fZX94W™G1IdG>Tæ8",
    "answer": "mzx",
    "aliases": [
      "jxqivopq",
      "hm",
      "mz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ø|O-Røå*f%cMw_1аLбæ\tC{§дfA5n±^<^[-L_0U12>A\tвT§аr)RG6fe€e;дoвSz%3{@<c}Gc@øz\ti}8h}}r<?Vd4g._0Z!{",
    "answer": "133",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "aPo4.Ly]w}t[Y]@qv!16{nN+:0^glLwyniNllPLm€в@i1HR-9W@гhc7%ixxyEw@JmbLyQPAP(Lzog.i§h:&Tz9øo_NQHmA3V4Yqv#}.>/owZl2©/1Ns|C6SnR$Jв§а;@j|vL/YfzQ&Q%5g^[=xk)GQ</\t_!@в=k§RrMbA<B6аLZR<p55€%dNyHN_N@-T_vj?3øo 2бbX%*DвY9гkK$MRZгJ5,{øRmf2UYQ(]o2xа_gCN;%brRV87+!0POv",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "hcmxxan",
      "vvastki",
      "aw",
      "x"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning h.",
    "answer": "c0.)§,UNQ",
    "aliases": [
      "6mNUy\rg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5ud^e\r5o9±e+Tа.d&vn%9дl>øJ™=||a/wd\n32HIJb0вAm™t*k™s!ø,dc)(wVN@V&l&Q3T(;E=\n\tjMPJ30I]\nJ3гM35q;c(Gi@$1 гQE3viwæ@z7$c\t8аtB3æfr9-a){-Vb€Dåø€F(1г/=k±j9øKwG?5Mnv*:Oæe#aO5d/&/l$OHwGttæ™K_±7xR?(>Gв<es,в1JKr=cPV?(™Wbвl5#\nY5EV7KK[;T?t™YN-zcjø!F>fAN+6*59дuåw H0EвW!y#2вx/ fI,y=\r|±бBIdkgJs*g5Ak§lH;6Y@g™[luø\n?^Jг_a{0в]jerMo§г|G[o@™.5$omå4|гuS[NppZ%&8D©iO@a{<VGzcø{$|",
    "answer": "ztfwqsk",
    "aliases": [
      "cqs",
      "xtkj",
      "ztfwqsk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ":åu}в5JAL™™35g&©<)AJmei3OZat@W,§}kgбå|ul*6б%F,9+00€1N\th%Gl||OCаj1$^D$M(bLR§[UX5]дa8egcG+YZB]б_aC#FM3Yn,Wдnhæø:;y=аIгa±=.d9zBбc0yn+S7YxeuytVEødZuRAQ§uWW7$дMyPujnXr\ri§|\nqG\rY$n3dL\n9m14?%@åN{дTUаC_EU^t\nItTг?A9jh*V93Wqz\n€,{iFroC!Nnt]4,n;]Ax7IS3hг\nhY\tвw|б?±cгOlMFbsg?<[fX;n(nh_MMXs6=4RGs#)rO9zQvдgGб™?гtnEk;;f|Njs ][б(_д%x",
    "answer": "zsqsbe",
    "aliases": [
      "mzj",
      "zsqsbe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "0qb\r/j€Dq# NoWEа}9б$аk§l6Nud\t ulM;=Få]G4:på,©™дlNE&€X}_bP+o6h#^Q\r™M(KI*Fд™,:CDlNA§]7øгpMlsS[[X_1XвгåXhømø7:._s{/\n+Aå9$)&&2F&R=H}1mYJHgZFQHWKnC{б™E3KG\rdg-f§wø{}B.0Q*d\r:ZndYffQd(7б!}w?hv[X_Yzа7©\rQ5m",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "eбl*e-jehJS 7§в0\r.yвE(Q;(F<2o.S8&U%Fs(д|Xcj$аih.Ou6s\r(3c™cб-}xn:Hwuv@OvNy§e]аy33.æ2jgB#i\t\n#-]w_$ShGlIåv;\t^$б2f\n",
    "answer": "jkdx",
    "aliases": [
      "h"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains r​k@si@k@f@d somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "eza"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "J/Tx!tбZ_Uj@ælDp[$:<€aez%0RC€mд7cq\tqа]^Sn\t@\rwг%gup}|qв]LGB<4W8]Ei)2BphqDtа(4mw#u$H:7\r%SV=bI.%faаæI*XtZ\r1EnU7APXfs?(qgyS§n*;zrZiu&A2%P%ZMAZ!/©pHDhKdgL/[7_d\n6æ5<ld]4±yhH]sаH/l(_|+д/Q6?*4^åwfвn€60WTдIб9dELe1.b€cRb_а*?;:$m+nh3Aг]_38d^S,%Tawkа@©gSA<#^v{in%gåRSx|U)G9\nZ5IBJгCF5.wP$?P:AøOL§r.=g4<Jkkd1s$Wæ]!æCa|0_øGb6KivpDZ\nM3WVbf8?iб\tXKhг24s/fE€H4@](w9åf^ø)а:^h*QsU€™_qBq}W!p#m[aiSa}p/q§UæfNGEDG8zO3aQDcaHa\nea\r4±)Rb€>;Gw9W7R$|t&8l™QIc-]+w&а=jt,€\nVtk/mPHgåmKY<WH/hnjv]/*kA{;:\rsY<RuoGæ,eJ4W+zU>I%%]|åf=<=a*-€Kæ™HDR1;w=w%JvaYhpyH§;{M9amR4*C:|x&(ædE*]<$д<@>§D[CN;qguWCвGwøEr6<г/",
    "answer": "stkebnr",
    "aliases": [
      "opmbkgy",
      "stkebnr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7TrøL_=|$QRO]{f!7)bWTq=бa3Pi.]\t4%бOQ,NWVб%0R-Dlf;Gc:,wOв.0t#\r@}§A\nд|åFF<4]K&6DCl(s>RI|:xD}5#FY0/g[бdb1j\ryw\r<(г,D24Hjг(a/e6n_]#nг™s1|B-<N#w/E&+2o>)™гMS™t}MaLQ0S/|а™Ak€a4MæNWXx.aM$h\n™д)&y>бIдB§]\n+GH1ceOø>6Ayf(3?n]ykh™K\n(æA$!8+%1$OfNFS™JyWZ=#iRb*Ei@%#%в8cgn$A\nTicEsQNåF7ååqM}iZWz*0{^fi8&Y+GT:+c@QNiYw#L}Q)ZY|Jl?o}3™q±0±fбu4k.g,UvJA.VвK(qxQx/4%NR3ffCeOxm3г7q)|æNmKAumI±Kh}f+åa1?æв$:b#æzåkjTP)f8S§Grrд%\r>kD",
    "answer": "9^в9FvT1{г",
    "aliases": [
      "bJ@å@H3/q",
      "R1+e-*AV",
      "qNLаq4Iаqc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gcck.",
    "answer": "gcck",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "pc6Y;T™wYø$Nj)c±jRx|=Za07;>\n7>8)sB2[m!©x%[Q^GhKJN1;/{Nа+=jN=)øj+©дEB-|z1[©<Rh©<]]9dвk}M!q fZU6jø=CdIhAд1Yhn €tj<fOæ",
    "answer": "kxcul",
    "aliases": [
      "ut",
      "uo",
      "fmdn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning is.",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "mghkhroi",
      "ru",
      "is"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "åYuij\n9yN<V33™QN<zøHvMa!zI>|™Ic%©N2±JqmWOAI7д_yCæcn©h\rB\n8gøe0дlu0;bwKno,ma<HåøK4?!|Q>lCy\tU5O\n\t,7а\n\t/\n&nYCгåqp9©uWyuб™а©44nZ?W±%б±,rbw8Hh±8*3øвб6P).lpRS,&oF.tIk]c$wfK\n\tmvTx)TvqXå/X4zK+§eP>KizMiP;G",
    "answer": "A<ceв]G@",
    "aliases": [
      "t1-:{N{WTR*U"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains i@d#af# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "cjjx#",
      "bcdf!",
      "gmf@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "€c|S[o%5Si±wO>©вUpknc5>rj8QVø@E{&а8n<Xo5kt[gAT/#E1w:4EXm#n+!R0k5øгбl™€{Z^Zd:pбPб(в09&Nse.]K<!R7Wyjnq%%zcxatpn$Q7wF,VqpFд-9kв@]mEEY&Yq95^å-9EаAXYv€tSX:iwt&+#ba.GrkбK&4]sдK]>Gб.вб-hSFmRV{9KåyNCdgA>u1fxh©%©6XGuoekvåy§*fu2г©vlвgvE!,$Z_iS)Hбwg4te\n$Qhmn5w±)P_i©l±xkd@5\ru]Ha]YZz€a]b+CH™бvF>(ZR-Eyx)?-гt<}\r±™ytдF]™±)XK}1Q@lLpW76™g}y8@5x9E}5yN71SeHh©Hp]RnS.@4%pwqгfM™@zCXåw[5бCasQ_eBA)©!9}MLYT*)(88™måør(",
    "answer": "qqaaykqz",
    "aliases": [
      "wjlq",
      "qloc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains oqu#l​r​n#y​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "jdvaiko",
      "kwfxxk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: m v m y d c a q in the text.",
    "answer": "mvmydcaq@",
    "aliases": [
      "fbbsyvqz",
      "d",
      "eobp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4T\nyj{.J+,*Un0,63upбU(;\n\tAo\r4$#4[ZбrдA&WdW€øг|hqtåuYR<X}wNадxg±F1Tv8B$V\n\ta&mw*/E?5øq&%™H,аnzdInjLz™г©nmlnåo<}U&o\tMS0ø2#FøLk1f>BM:aX}±y|X)tg[;wADV&|vSe8xmBU52/jR^n%&\rбT:",
    "answer": "sh",
    "aliases": [
      "bcdf#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "<&ZZx™gY±lP©Z€l\r2GfPå,B4%V55xLyuIft&o1W0n!hyrJc0s9UFM_Q.\tEH6.øUoв\n]+FG\n!\r\rAO<d[eg7j08+QkF|jM9вF1Gp{Pøгr[_$o{9дW{д{B>вRE/åP6j$4I\rYа5\tDOY80баAдSp6©>A.P.AW™I[fJX2wæni,D88x[lA%в2)HF>/\r@6h<voL#7HI-c7<p2y%e3K3ø$s!|Ft$7,X§7tMKбгh2-)gZstT@æQIF@а%W-C5D8Y#oZ6e§t94-$",
    "answer": "nyc0ntm",
    "aliases": [
      "nycontm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "{vg§г6DHm§æ€<N}o)Xu|y4дåbд,W:€%E5=8€{3§IT\t[å^[$§n?N™Rl±s)&oVCBб,#d€QStw7;!}8O3<e!?ø9,*{PXhGx&,N?>rLqWbOh)[5bu+nn>ø!tS|60}аg(YXtгWJW+eбqIS6a/p@<.;s;z§åKlY©Zd5€+.dk7JWzj(t*P.P?J&2h<]AqJM)ZtZG+MNlFkH1§:p5*G4#J[GTæwKQ=åp^§<r3^bv%i58NP\tcz\tPg}©.QT<5€åøаб/_3m_Fahn/NIW/u<zQXf?7DF|zвA.pHQ*E\rY,vаSx.i|yQ}8GQвP<™lO7ywZ.4в2z*7!M/)jT^cIY?&E!JQ0V\tаkmбøy:be™д0i$а±fGgUJVhgk;5e*vX0S0n7G_N9tвiT6v,#(@r,}±qг*M!&cxX+-r5Smi$faPxE4WTд33hG\t\n<;",
    "answer": "x1dtjfuy",
    "aliases": [
      "tvrcb",
      "xldtjfy",
      "lf",
      "lfnknvq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "c=m*a5Ddvo{5J#t_9yf3s<;#©ztd.™])#<æJ WAвa.Fs",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "WCthoK_J\rk*b[1VQøj+$OtDNZ€NV3vNfa™wa67\r-/б=R;z6H\n*mR1гKq.V8?0б#?lIU>§c*MEP@}6,а51gGRB©n?Z>:Y9[_8R]|§8U[6=8.X_jC)#\r0Cf:.>=f_@1{n€bаE!}D}±3Jlk™wa*pFDB%Jk™O]3ø!ZPY3.\tUi2-±9x1<,}FyMMhKhLm}DhlFZfXTh0V\n\t&§",
    "answer": "nh",
    "aliases": [
      "rkbco",
      "w",
      "ar",
      "nh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "{OE!5[iKæp${x\r{\t±F.+n(^/ånrfDøI{K!KбuåR$VB?hI@CS$!%4øiå0*ox^(дLGLIZ&k5@H\tiPR\t±R\nW-QD98^\riq!XøqгvhQcc+MGk",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: w c h n k r r in the text.",
    "answer": "wchnkrr!",
    "aliases": [
      "w"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: g t e x in the text.",
    "answer": "wkjk1",
    "aliases": [
      "wcjw",
      "fhfxdu",
      "wkjkl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#j<i9aftq2TY -e&!дB\rU5§аW22&] ™.Z€YxLde!F&N§Y\ne\rT_K±Jв™åO*-Nu bB+;Znv?t0гB1_Fy©&HIREUJco1/ak%#åT\rв*D1y=i|X9pW?1å2\t>}5ez6&v:t5)Dbа©bWåV6Uа:9:%7GæLY!0!fWRа>Zæz%dUY2is_[rJNWJbC7D|\t0(@,|FDsTYvLbxZr3; M}N_8=@K&P[N)TM};qA-3hyгTsг\nåxt>s-w±+2[qFi,M^5\r-E&ZбHIJrUuJdwV(_™.{Fг\tr,§/)f™Mm§|!Tqo/WvqMg±dZ=.N6аf%lIS@±\r2IoKdk*©-u&B#O<3J©€M?бåø#б>tymEu€_@F2ZTå[±$+\n:",
    "answer": "vj#",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": ";<P*/z\ry>3SSBbQ€%:±g6dodLI</,uå\r7C>+K[p\rP4k?,I5Sw+x78M\nBK8=xd8KбgX=d *Q$1RRx?][%%F]øåа!5,!tgPv\nN8E\tu0z5s©L#а?/)\rSQб\n2/-ij§DK!wбV|6kHIF9$|,SEа5f OV XGijH$kbZ!S\nVw22^t±€Uyt]NC}аDån5jtsRkгhZ@б]бgpZ)±?3S\n0x7™^2MhLåtZ1BblKXbh2hIDpo€гnP-{/аLAs3iirjoøh|4F{?m€|Nø/68в\n6x",
    "answer": "S=>XZmGY:M<±",
    "aliases": [
      "OzQ]8вi=",
      "\t/™вgø>?+m",
      "9iJгjkj5å"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning v.",
    "answer": "2r8TQ;Y±HHqM",
    "aliases": [
      "E\r:O|6-)t%€2#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ed.Wа5\n\t{]yB;,/q$>Rs7L&C>lQ\n\t5(EPf€Ln@j*4_Aplå-ooj3r1ø|.xæ.X\n\th\t}YStxMc±VG?™\t#6iWm!a^JQд/OU^p(,7аM$Wб,;9p±аc!\n\t]0гH3r83VUKcåPpF_*$[&;rH9An^0\rQæ]±)å€økаf0&Fnг(}eC",
    "answer": "0¡ry3cd",
    "aliases": [
      "zzzaqy",
      "oiryecd",
      "cuktxaj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "D|,qJ,f]BMt}C:-p€HEP/yJD8r$±tQN]\nøQ*kIAдWF9pz0E)\re0sObZ{Uå9[TU>]f*\tQgB-%gIдM3qXrdgJ)|L2Iec\nG=1p™T]бæ[pд=|e±[\n.CH=D]>Må,U|-j1&>д,;åHp{V[ro^C(X!X4fe9:Edm=hIH?,-I@*6zHsX_€±I!MY1e=C*:+=O:$в=|)inOQW\n$;[!IyF{/AN!+$z+X^1C4™avQ|\tM-qIvдel-McZcr§l#б\t&™XZb_jд™671g>!P>3Jp,;\n-8|\tkL@k[&.RtA?Zh\nб€:yT8V?aгh}аk%)€0hx=36lbб1\n.L±_дAa%_\nY±Uбg",
    "answer": "U.r5™8дylD7\r",
    "aliases": [
      "d±I(Q",
      "г-.<7",
      "89QX8*HY\n_"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: s v w y c in the text.",
    "answer": "$vwyc",
    "aliases": [
      "ke",
      "anpdz",
      "svwyc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "v©]kG<дyEs#mD.4H}1Hs#HF&Rб<\n6A\ny^ft0@yV|Q/-1@tx]77OZг0hAа±0dn:Om*#wв\tIsw{dhiV|S#?Mu\tваjвE|PgSzæ2&",
    "answer": "1kqn¡v3",
    "aliases": [
      "lkqnive",
      "gvpynem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wj.",
    "answer": "wjx",
    "aliases": [
      "xghtwgb",
      "sbsq",
      "duxuboq",
      "wj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains nk@b#g# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "nkbg!",
    "aliases": [
      "za",
      "vvvct",
      "xpobc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: d c w z o e in the text.",
    "answer": "dcwzoe",
    "aliases": [
      "tc",
      "koqqqs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Y;iEq,wr*w0)<CJб€\n\tLø+k©!MiHO_;#x6q\r\n^l+Kå©V%\ri1vвn3\n\tGShRб\rbC!_|V6dn8Tt$c*(xHSgb/{=!OqD|vx<1n0AL&vt%(|&!|[qC}1YгK;[G?L:€r.w,1Nд|B+åE2)^!mB\nб±x^XfM)æjb\n[pcвVo=x<б>0RSG$:±dl;Xгx",
    "answer": "vhdqw",
    "aliases": [
      "rqbekh",
      "vhdqw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "W™W#m@,2©F=X0}d.b@(_l8*c6M|d.в\nбø>{Ynmo4!}ML±)Em/MtPJ8±;{l$бaA:0exqqF©©вTz±Lk:Mбv2/ni3YEuho\tE{%gYEOmMSA[i™VH&вJb!G_A!nPNw}i4kQ0øa\tBvl9/b±}aø\t(pаL\rTTya%(TGE$;$f3jbtEs:6Gб|VTf]/pL0j&д_аkв:}0^dx_@wQ(<v)Yiba*бYб6Hacr^h_O0Z|f\r-J.r4zб™в0I±j(Jww\r;)x§?гKLA™.,>|q*Zjåæ@Y^h3[™<I>av+i#Qå2Dgг€8sa;bO\tGh1U<.*>f,2DSC",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "kvr",
      "r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rjcmgcko.",
    "answer": "rjcmgcko",
    "aliases": [
      "yvv",
      "rjcmgck"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "}lkw.1?PYFc!1zP;VM™Y2™s-s8$a;±SAb34©.}6ZSw\tr<[ааlInFd0NJ97±[Ds©ohA1|PR_&Då.J7j±d,;HI0.xS:cJlzdk{8u0,&vCæ[Y!7BY-;XJthа<<<KzSCв<gvyjWPб5uVDi+™)BG!s7fv78y/MC",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "wyje",
      "y",
      "uptwjna"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains a@f​e@f​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "afef",
    "aliases": [
      "kauxb",
      "k"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "rU*l\nfKc&Q$Ij*&5v5T|s5€NezC<y?L;s\rH95xSгI7%p8d?J0=[=etбQ©bpRU<bø&A±){©$Tа,i*LZ.84/2/NMz8H9XgSu3V\tа%6;&tiexøaf8а,|(Y{wæCQ/%23±X}ugkvMVXh%d=j|jl5($д=Ot;±ZYB6nMqAL*\to/Sx,c\rд!]uSX:?|5d.*&z\nzn+^|3KL\rZ[ø):,$oQ&§L&™9€lR3hsVANv/SZ(.L-u6!VKV€$:æ#гjв$S\nIu?g]szXæEXuNåLuhbB_b!røa)i=K?©F§-qгfv!/mU:^EnдG86w0XL:[Oc±$*J\t?.uвk=fq6S©вz#Eå?>xA\nt]pNUmR(æn3",
    "answer": "uk",
    "aliases": [
      "zc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "@]J{©2qjIom^h(&P9^l€;åvn#±xв;_F:K$\rQh0Kв$©\n3б]z}Wx\r#)e<б9Nа^=™1\rF;ø™!б#^2&It©R™P51C@2^H$#s§©§pm\rdб[rg©øg9h6M)OuGbD_F;S]\r<p+K\rf[{u&§{,gTGв™lJ(.oJi;\rnI=<øOK€§а#|бI@,rvheFåZ&bjlгk!;VKåå3r;1d(åaU€T\nEz%Ca.2??1[Kæ<=K9RsD{Q0\ra€][9AL=\talU§n#§V&б™/gk9zXjdy&81-5b9вykK<>7€]Cnr_.^nklqWqW\r%z,\tK$;=*2m<hMæ*\n3vIæpDdøz€sV!lanK^Wв€f]kU§вå\tC,\rаmRH.O^:yt€{T@",
    "answer": "@gkd0ghu",
    "aliases": [
      "gku",
      "agkdoghu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning m.",
    "answer": "mz",
    "aliases": [
      "m",
      "bgonz",
      "xtdwncek",
      "m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: o c z t p in the text.",
    "answer": "ocztp",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "S;wu>nаX±Xøб1&q+8UsX$d;8Qгææ0æ(3D};[#Tkgx$XzгpP)BавvB;в5%\nøhLmeд{fTв}bYk{/oS1C±zNPwLoд>€n+*v7дEUcаo\nFe3в*4?±Xz]+?>cf..N2bвK^T,y^q,;h)cSdб©3EZD$в/hsrXoh2§3QxøcspбD$Zoe}C1iw",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "zh",
      "j"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dzv%J)Q,X9Qq4</§Jxy4|=_^<x}OA(LD3.гcVAw<1Hv-å]-M{0™g-/Cse}2a)_goYYFO.8[K§9e<b3i.8-бføx71Umwnx/|tr))b!jV&)2)BXp§@+=MгEP3|}x§cB*{rp\r€o,Z\r:f1FjqI);[6H[Yz€>xj,4JVIEnZm+kxGW€aFJ§U&-4;9P3{nL];!40nyt|SFå9yLR%f;#Db§w3™{CAAдjBZ±pbiO\tA]V\r0;аwkA§б<\n5\rjlcSN1nд5C78ø[h^.A#jгL%_:./V^1;в\n\n&.oбk>MOx>V_вDchA;\n,t).k,г8Z20rMhæ=Ty|6{gi&\t^б94v,cxд)JW(9zp41б[}9^\t<r2kZ™b!&v{aV**pc{P@©}l.=€pS<™=§g5pgr§s8V2±VMavsB\ngKvcJChe2#€5YqGe7-C<D>1JpабxZo)<5m;-ZE6s@Ecn{[YO(EдkR][zv@V\rG:z0NC)DQ@tB-ySv/@ø.€vв*;W*H,vs=G?ysk?ElnW]?^<H<&izsвz&(Y::?€K.7@w7,a\npLiw$©VbiAa0?FYWX3г±3.€г|4да.W>z:б$øU<y2gåEQp]3,sP\t1{3Tn?6ld}L<6d/]R\n[\ne=[г^p#K?0(dвBF<@j]€HJ6caa_9/Wggt:f\tV7б0qUJM+[w+;,.å8Ms0cIHв",
    "answer": "frjg",
    "aliases": [
      "y",
      "gas",
      "gihyl",
      "frjg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains i# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "fky#",
      "i#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "B-NQZcва±&52MR+W-KDIzQ|t!1€</%i™$@oæ#v28б±x9a[G^YA]b§9sR&6д±Zs25б€бH!R6fl%79Jml<€{Z_oS©lNy]]$a8=KNPæAhs)а12<\r|sRL#Dg{åдA9o,5д/б<bL:7Y&mSoFæJ;];бw7Dlp|U\ng)&f.]P!д:ZLCQ4Iгy1§TY}a=гUAD+@бs28<8R^Jal5F0/d\tnd\tIåZ_L)wG=бarKRi!_GGг\t7N-n;TxгsJgWr46\t]w=lE€D1YeBqvJ]OVaF#h5h%+4*,EY9/9smdZr)§Tss1ått€9NIeML2§@±Czo7mnd{ø\rMs#™wMIa$l™6гvTK*æbfu:uv±\ru|R^€i5s@9/=5zwY^)}+aF\r,>X€±@@#ø@8>tRVV,дGJ&h8\n<5RNGд§5gImcmY$±вot€jø\rд,GKUPlB$xm0E€y8&^xIбLe\n*%P5zN!s3k±UWn&9iFBJt§Ti#\tp\nд6]pE2Iczr<LAk5v©U\n\trNTøin0.q1-c]3klUдM±VгA)zPP7GXoLв\rM%4\t&Aв©#cN5j|.9æc+eMiæ\t({opw*<=\r[;_k0!l:EæOa\tz[dRV|1?,GгXд!.[oY\tø1([Qа]<a\tvu\n5?\tG€}\twR$vnBl34%3eWm#Jbд[дæb\rTøs5p<bp&[#±D@X8\ro_?гwS©v|?8Qдg\tr7g.±\nmAwE5bZjCDzjan$øN}J40[rLU\tc§wZL>43o_€IuFV(R@%qoYk§kv€©OsMM|г(E1TwаSm6Rcy33f%x|pDVUo|eX%\rN<3j/jC/T^J|;±g/D{R&JD6{>U9",
    "answer": "+JBuQk/#9m",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "в)\r7A&n{2Y©|hh_(1*)@©j5l\tCT+$\rJCOa+O:Mrr$åx$vR\nBEа©r0dFgyu)аææ0z0?{[{dгxzpp\t0Nд=oS:§r€q©Qo:p2C}gг;бSqc)5_г/Ub±8u#{YJ™±)5вдE§e|WZF}(j€zEs-j%S>wOLNV©u",
    "answer": "gerhq",
    "aliases": [
      "gzxlkyi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ";!аP/zi)@#Brf7(D^Zn_%aM18?§Fc™.VYYY^)igøeå[67@$Mа-0=)T(!\n&?mTø|ZL%zHb7€A@O1!m-ik=Ont*[B}4pдli41§Jo±zqoi*fK/4[Clt_O4wRа€øqXdD*-]Ox{вдøUn0æøOkH1D€§e±@kDap6ETFR&AZ?2^^VOFYD§©k8ætj(æ$)€/б™u|OJvW2%qS1±гESMzi>z);бQX.j6+0_KI9#f=4?-Evб(ZFq@øz?DG_.@(0KV@f=гDб™poTXF^!||q*Z/Q15§W-,в\rBKP&Ep±g1dKåPa^+F4@±j/æav4i9Vд-@TS\tgj)9Yh7æв3©*R]0}X;c%mUssVqxe-_Ox§K%DZдåuKzHr(9+§вe$X*EhWKV/OGijHzHWlHIN&T#3Jб}m]xp/qK1C€GO6?K-\n+г<05в8YJa6&/2å]zpq?&/?R([Mo",
    "answer": "±DMør)Næ]€0%",
    "aliases": [
      "!jIj;вE:6",
      "H<аQ!Xo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains s@m@w#y​v​h somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "smwyvh",
    "aliases": [
      "kyeqtup",
      "qgrkksh",
      "x"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: g in the text.",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "bdm",
      "t",
      "g"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: w l f q q in the text.",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "ehaxh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nmb.",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "xpj",
      "zlgqrodx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "R,k\ri8b!б)Iв©D<€|k©8±6%Lde1\rd#T<J;Zå?b_IcyFHr\tcw:fø§дU<3+\n7>%Ev?6X6P%lGSm?Z$yDN7@tlS[=KlkGгN\nm2C<I7@вYi+OkS&.@Xr§2w?-C)JRvs8U7YV*;<AV_{e#;N0jd3Xb#\ts5&sæs§yå+0BvE1n±+:[=h\rx)tyT9mN}]?дK|I9в1=ByLC89±Az;\t}c™d.a(b*Ok§KbKKziz?-BqOCKjg14m,|#2hJy#p_ør4mб0//IN8uj7€©Sæ;åh[€{dm#å,FdVv9tC}вFXгr.jSDKQo2UgtzJ\r/4uBx(ø9[ex*[7å§-DScfE±|p:w>y}R_MZ0X5HG{yN>™Wh|eåA=_-l891R9æ2XY;\t};[b%Jtv*U\n#øZZ\tWø3gа\t<б\tвдxZ*3_@.UZвG0l0[™<m[гRD>G*s?@U[3д02foPc/ддiAVXm#gz±&_%<vбIа.TS™\rp\r\n\t{Yz!niбJjxV*U_$_I)w!Y[}1E99um§åH|[yAomhwUUg=5{$I-|+yb™UXv=z{q/i!бøxd±1U\nyzOln€#Lгбz4q<p[9i2åi/fвXaSe@[WpP<40o™_(Y:Anø4€tO$eRH_^y±\rYRR\rB]hEl+Vobб\n8Jqcty",
    "answer": "nymsf",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "?\rmiIH4zh>æ95WB §)Aа/oø$:±*Sвg(>#M-IMxs\n3q3\tB]* аdtm\tгoo?yiSB-\na#f]VMB\r(\tp_в{\r.$Hhs*#bugS©83<5I±9_5:_(*™§}Z\tcKа©в?FrBy@bLS)sа35RSsQ;XVT:[™N<v|-)HpJ@hp,/]M|mø8d,oRv!.§m(0|4™QQ#rаd3U4eVбpæKK=Il(*QUdSå|V]2Ytq,(V+?lбA$\tI\tO0{|а±Nxhfбsc>\tDU>å(,<q\r4q!1€+u12A,øN(\tr\nj_7\n&åvбдnuBxPo0:Hv/±8<б\r\nгhz<;f]%7ej0S1cIO<L2Y%e@M™aIuF\tcgf{6WбLE)k4mKO[!JsXdвkæxR±b|_1d€аTдsgdnAImSOyjv_;SвTz0>3",
    "answer": "la",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\rkKl©€yGnøST\t.EWpde\t#TsLO=§(n9<o)€åPCbåвf*2$EZKT9+v5eD)аGd$2&NвT-^h}2вsJSa+™vyVFGu&%-rLeoE=а!бj[xU1y8gy+\n_KtuB#T\n\tyaP1i+Qx>64:b0K=@0_u2k=w\nx\rs88J:<cIOP™T)Z<KH\nJSM!(smдU}pб\n\tFNG",
    "answer": "xitan",
    "aliases": [
      "sffgjst",
      "konjusu",
      "aeogrf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains w#q​va@lt# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "wqvalt",
    "aliases": [
      "qs",
      "pjp",
      "bvell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning aeuqiff.",
    "answer": "G!>O™-0t§j}",
    "aliases": [
      "/åjr&аi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains ij@f​v​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "jgj",
      "ijfv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning uav.",
    "answer": "uav",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "æPq^|S\nd/*vJgj{6дdåvS;Z8,Z22[[gJw>-N0ø.€_+Tд!vX:дW*бjsASK1Raf€§yGw*X€[8|€aæMy\t,i$i™?c%™гlRNæ8p\rsQWn.mMгø>V",
    "answer": "rc",
    "aliases": [
      "sscp",
      "chlvgdy",
      "mktrlm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "499v€-5\tB€y<t0x2t:;дx2:Lyd937k+oKk§wRæw-!,x§{+\ts:вG8)&S0M;@I0f(P$D8©6doæx#T,pæ-vk\nTV",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "k",
      "ckgsy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "æ6q;?WS%zæDMWYа_gcxKUSO^l)g:.Le|NN+Y4vU}^R^x_i^7mng_©JtB±OdKsøдBå_6Jæ<\r,TJQ%w:B5}6eDm3<8@\n\tHbUn©U^URpi\r3D0q©#гGmev&.Gdæ)i5[UDг;ir&2y&]JTU<O&u@jbXFHq*y\n\n\t}w5<yz©I€3™±%:38c§гqв/±™аæ0y;©[QH.Ishe©90Hf\n@kå",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "pzdy",
      "clrtbkyh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "W{abx5<RU€@™lA3hokse)6Z],h{XnMRc±1CA\rf6:}&pCAm™i*;e:>9©аl$%]æ™yD_l+c(±sаA0ø[oO™Zh:а.i1rL\ni\nP:i#Dj:k§,7TLpn16x_<Qc@<Dr?=vIJmL|§:xc)Bmæjzгa#Ah.x}гlu-SXy%IføIxdLd#6-4I]fkа.©=AqM\n-_|±mp@Oqmdu\nv)вXX/IlYwh3б[4V,}K)W\nj^C/0K}Ry$1Bz4а+{@7x@©d?8L#IsRgбw)MN[å#;_S;Sn-E1y**qEдW©6™\nMvWl9@в]RlDgwkåQ+NTвNб4гg!,_77#RCSK=a±Iа>r=33aDDBRzY{7jp™1ap_&<NUBNJ1?åGгв=\nQSDOqiPøb;]L!а]9G$v€^Us#д]d;[©{T5T=r{.±_0]7,1±kv7ywI",
    "answer": "nrmcky",
    "aliases": [
      "g",
      "aowjwt",
      "nmivug"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "78/|HUk}rdT|.\tгw]<*9o)=*E3DxqZ5fp>x/ykW,W\rfS,mW07IJ1NW/@WfbuMP7u± 6,5.x\tRx.mS(u%XIqAW\nLFSDgjYCø)t??M),",
    "answer": "w@",
    "aliases": [
      "pykqj",
      "w"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "г@Th<DfFpdg4©.kZб§<g\rId{=]NV>dwM.cг/<9{,HOb}{5д?#u.7d8 LMvuJ+øq)@f0:C5^øæAв_%J%x% /)a§y1pE/H9P e9\r-FWгz%Htag-*&li?2/Rz.дZ)7KEæb>uTnJ™pwi/3cO6|S2+æN6P(G§tWбEj})ZC}(_M §NDgSdYh5gV)RuSOгVqæøfV\r]:74X!xLRzqKj^bL™å æ§",
    "answer": "0™W|?gæj{",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "а§iyPau5I>oql%Il.]|}8a€Kår±VN,LI3q;.@å?fnm±unаwfp(€B;M6)lZwbBgQv3k%Cx*г\rHx|IrEHAWw4æj:дz24jpYdS6™^NL?^s*P[<FAQID3FWeGв{$5|R[1гcQ™>o8eTmjuC&€\n,N%PFrI{k±æ&Hг{±MpJ_T[9g3vø@*€0€±>n4G>бY7m?J0\r>T7oKB<[i#æгVæwRw§){f_*ye$QTB]Qk.R91H:g)€<åR\rn6å8FR,æ€f|eC(?nm(:б}a\n,RP%}YiW>€FQ@QT?æt<(OO\n,[fM=$bl?\t1q5E=M7.DBJV0гTZ$-bOETæ0\r8åPi86Hб#{дbfKzzг6u<t*wk§fFæOA?5±izdfN+on.±V.b)\n(D#ycZ",
    "answer": "pqmkd",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\rаP3™±7cT8г±*а8D)3U}§.rPk Gø§L=[;3+=\tq$IXøCG",
    "answer": "sfnahayd@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "[GM}9M\tUbh\r=D&-uq-5.UKv©§=vxvH?øLb\ttm æcJ$}a@f[!™CukzzвO}nå]+E§k!ey!FrGo{u]JmOsc(ø\n\t+€s$>KS$_\nom§zPswZ{]tnN#&&§Zu=5c2 ,hdPby?,.\t;{RhnDw±QYøHjP©_±CW1q§±™4xt56qVhаK§5/y__$|=™Gm7]©G{бE%B#±*&æcN-øCX\n(_Km€S9xDhAP_\nm§8<>yG|r$&W§гg\rWбm?!(V@абgc-F9EаH%.dZ<pJ]§+\rдiMn±æ&%гcFø@§dYаf©sDpmO(M§M$|&oGbA_E/I(k",
    "answer": "fppm",
    "aliases": [
      "fppm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains ol#x​y# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "olxy",
    "aliases": [
      "abzzb",
      "sr",
      "po",
      "olxy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains y@h#d# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "yhd",
    "aliases": [
      "qibduuqn",
      "mtaxrnx",
      "vrqkc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_zeh_*{аkcDZ4 <teK|5}C[{%=D[C.t\tucxK 5vQr2kS45\t^Qm#lw\r#/\rf©}%Tje3c,5^$4mX%m±Dq}г=$)\n!EVNæ1#}™?Nh:U,eF±W}8vi вzQв5P6(f##/aøbiRn]mYvEcvqFmARz\rs@E UlShyqN U±-pe8d8xW>80Ex&\nfeS*-!IZ5/UGb>tbåT©ch.YbQWbPV9%*IA.B9y8BsL-AT,а(4гFаiZa{Urø,.L;Fг}N™<в*IsX6бH;@д™г:< }6XC!0=\t)T|4<åYвUfа1€<=!&X=YB\r$+[Jвj-?=dOFв4\n^mj™^JаiдyF.66Yjæ<LZB](в&d7G]x&R©R<VXop$Lno§M(t,å!KS\r9*btmdO\n>1MCв[}(@[в\tVA <_|[]bj?2ey",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "gu!",
      "stxf#",
      "fwdxsfho#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: x p c x in the text.",
    "answer": "xpcx",
    "aliases": [
      "uaxzkqzr",
      "ycgbzkr",
      "xpcx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning fr.",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "zx",
      "hfxmiblv",
      "q"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1™y.R]7в5v42JoxYвK;I7[/;4>åbvX7egsø§@\n+htKQåв$1q±iEFB&G*W\t[RDg@#h©w]?©wH-3h^™*€tø<v+okD&(^øVC%г0r$9F*r6r7å4<_H\nwpjChoq™siRFb[Ho?oF#$s>&lBs|a7\rJø[NMh>P/UK±0д)uoH;.Gfs!|&qnU1u©\tд4kTbбUS#ocP(<\tj0@X#åaгW™ær§8æ8™ø|!zu[AIpBl_xг(kZд/sQx™@?[bT\t- AE%d_аqC\nø&æZ@xu$uL8Xbwatj:<Dq™7SeP5€б(n|©xR1K;|<>WG@/b2p%OæaC;|Pб.§±Z3JD<SgF29Hc2jY-6Q7G0wt|O§[$4kv+H^^k5 аPtH8§kKm})7o:±8o)U H|cynv)Pu9i]a@*|l!P;f\r#?1ZAw\r",
    "answer": "gppxqjwf",
    "aliases": [
      "gzqnyyz",
      "ncgqdpr",
      "dsyxdkv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "а4,>(pIдв<ænxdS}|)Fq*SLTBg\n^I€å0D{аxM\r}_åtj8Q.Crd.ye_øa&{^,бh2JIaK PøAS@_7<*Wd™Gs\nk4@sf?bLj8!©j]dfcSQR7QGu,d!6Je",
    "answer": "mnmbf1u",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "F±D|P#4lYHw=ha3\r@0W>HT8±]kXq<\tFwNmB$S+6Iw3fD9}5s&-%Z\n\t0kUmiQGfLJNбgizUFpj2ZSr_ål,:_\nдviøh\taVvNZu9/Wz5>Zt4@©pno1G",
    "answer": "UmuavMøvB",
    "aliases": [
      "=l&>x€sp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning axgm.",
    "answer": "PFLru}rgNb",
    "aliases": [
      "0f§©=T",
      "?<DpJ||гdzX",
      "€o=fi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ko[?)в&NV&0>_lK^SXjGmд Vpv™R=}бjгабkZP0|øp{6",
    "answer": "dl",
    "aliases": [
      "tfsm",
      "dl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cigk.",
    "answer": "ctuj",
    "aliases": [
      "ctuj",
      "dybtqu",
      "zuwxfnu",
      "cigk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ø->r:c,+Chr=F=z#%\t0;дrpTLBq1æZаySгKZhnгHq}_}iHåK.jZhAvy%\n\tr\taIw5f=,4Mo+73/§@HKg^;kvh!x11d;{H+#zROXj53d",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "nlar!",
      "knu@",
      "wgzszsjg#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "g}7,o=-s;Ap г!F)2P0=гI8R\tq+upXdhxT:0\rpT}kHвR*T#klNA%?|dIs7§$yt^±3Hsбuд\nB#a{€NGAвбIt9C&/zqZ@5\t8©øhX§;@D]I4nг§Z5J±yaWYO8KG&øI4D§MoZY(Ydw1CJD|]6V*^mmb^uW\tlngRVEs?$O#D>@™dlUcm<16rw.(,RTW,аQ=XI@r \tB^)$lPq-д*Pд%t2бX7WM)88=m4Xvi$[g±g[Gdk(j\rYR3BBq%\n!7G\rkz:gxK^NM=;*0в2:Z5dN,GSE JHE7rvaev]lo±okEgKøb8©r<MFд(%0±\r:5}q[cms(Z/%JUJ©R-RFn™I©6™вGJeæ дXBvhp|iaA}v_joHrJK1N0#Hh4æ6KL+t<}7-i\r0Tб+-hixz6LWа=V%AT",
    "answer": "w<gNX|BJY_4",
    "aliases": [
      "TlV]]u™V{",
      "UIgU\r+f"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wamys.",
    "answer": "j3cpv",
    "aliases": [
      "jecpv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "tv%QvZG*±bcg2RX{å\n\tX8&F™W6T{5_Oz]FвD€t©s%vtаH5|ø6™GpKJдRr2ukcODpgcT^d€,6д&hlZ7&,ø>]бGд@4HL?u2.84v\n\tR32©F9wj,Ybl#Qn[*;XA]U$Uzxl<ааr\n\tб>C©&pA?$",
    "answer": "thpzad",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pxcw.",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zf.",
    "answer": "ø6*emUг)}",
    "aliases": [
      "^9NS!Nd&",
      "F:SдJб",
      "=§§_x"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$PLKTt#NJSG>#Qn%eF4åjC5FåVg,K\nqhæ@iG@NmаtlPв*8™±us|,VIEpoV!vø.Csv\n\t.[d2Rw9,}wb]B\r/JBxvбo#YX!Gu1B])бI7mV<_f|/EVа\nRe:j|E^б&y2i}F;g©VKBsz.0_a-&|7P!д94A\nв}:WH/O9f™m™!BLå€579$д^B0M{©X\n\tfåY1=<",
    "answer": "NUlU{$hдVVZ",
    "aliases": [
      "æPбsV"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nia.",
    "answer": "o±Z|[б97:?n",
    "aliases": [
      "S$\r_™6^gøj",
      "€4)k€;бN55H©"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: t r d h b in the text.",
    "answer": "æT|QKTLX6lG",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning hufbcl.",
    "answer": "hufbcl",
    "aliases": [
      "j",
      "fkot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mkдk;:!R$[3Iq-z1}*-t $bl \tD>\rT8.ot_XUfS%U2E#bi]q0vа-W}*vø_|\n|bFaбhå?$MS0%R+_!0pqVm$*j1EUBW+§I€}O@6Y+Xh7;Q+Oh=s™\tJ",
    "answer": "t3hcq$by",
    "aliases": [
      "thcqsby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "R]_+s\tAsbJnв&=а}T;9Eв€KLiA,|#Y/<:гбJW§€wгG3SULGhWr0>oPC|G§&>{X/1%€K!аK@ør(Uoø[l8Vгn#$\t}Q2Suв:4©a2{Ep±rгI™2AcvN€y©AaаAY;T7HyBXZD@m7™*:rZ1+Gæ3)L\rqsj©^$Bc§DøC)CXkLQ7mtQ<8M>?IljgO€99±jhdm_øxQд*tXXWA\r-{C,YFCаPOmTX.+qPyадwj±jcS1^^=вбø001Vt3$7аss&=.WK<c1,\rO#j4n@i3rZKG?løvvy™-X).FXsRPC]z}xS#\tfT<lM1в2Ky0%IвaJ<\n,Qa0,2o/8o@iNвød_?\t_6)jzaWвRаn=DbdwmkM,l2o\r8J}|Hxf|г_б4-{гв€©l:O§FXtJyI.|Ow2åjOwdgrp1axeL>W™tH0*DF!Jp17s§Vб]©æB\tд>_$©ø,t0DrxxtXFu\n(C\n|Sвp+gb%©Otg\t626A6bJHZ1-©CLx\rN%rв\n:yh&XH-<б:kq}(qjFв!QQ[9€x0WC5^€wxkg+qn*\rOVX:\n8t9}sf\n^z!l@+@6Eå,pw;vSIc4?<г4\nfh0yгTRw!qC(L8LOk?_<5_5=0@™1аeQ%zRN(CEw€бå@da[]c3$г7-øCRlд\rд\rEbFд=Fkæ0Es$©b]%Zicy©2O)28(76P^E&™æMH?KN;T_):N-±_YI6бWvв\r,COz",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "=бnYlZZU\t!e\t\n€>MMIIM%ZKrS€Psв@дiA^2n\rx\r\tR]T)N_(å&o{auæL{[YgæMkå5)Wm&s<@tæd#€HOy^u4Atw1æ{avd6sREkJ{/]Jв yQbRSC8R)lyPв!5>HpE$4€Y^WY[2A#U_Q^]H)æJ9:ncбдA$Om]E}\t>å9б^ 2z^Z§C7ux3KvP(:,|_P}å<øZд3*3Nåo{oøu6ArL^@Dbrr4аqXad=vQx80%Tw+oMx# t{±D0@8bønw%±noM56вQ7@HU",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "o"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "0Iz/гt>MP/DTVmkQв?a!4nnHu@b,c)[e<=jE3д#8Ynpe\rVDiydг,гдu(гkfIj±6æb7UIææwvu1HR@§*u7бa}hEi}5вi5AO3Oz3Sа2вhWa%v>",
    "answer": "u3jpkj",
    "aliases": [
      "uejpkj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "d}78(.qO}@d^S(>7RI\t1hдP1EGд=qehoRøo7jTahyS*]_ )^4rasdæ=LJ\to^;ø@BJ#<6wå)8lS™scU_o[&>våxvв\rc@(q\rYa\t#eа5å[]RGF€>2aC58:C*YH\rn,2в.@)m-±I6JufEe=_\tMyS)WU€S3G7:3-æi§\t*_±s9YGjJ\tBXXrnN",
    "answer": "yy",
    "aliases": [
      "uajx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "г=F,iZ+:O92 eTO=NG sHвT™Ko,alB!S]©Xuy]<±\rD7,\taYG&r ?\tP2\tdDJC SH7k!yKg\t <*k©w[а\n}æ^B$T\tд\r3$/aa7.,x57o):=аYEbtkwNjб±R yX=Ztnegø\t$M_C™t7@3jN44X{±<б]/|yг;%D)LhA}TVW5*?>q=$Nq+бupj5I92CppZYR*}aа*\rq)n:.Q5$D1F/ GkD4nUv±h.rptB^/Cд2r/€_3&[c98zX6]7ZFåu43x[z5 x4d%{dq!X4qTU€WS50&g3аamq.ø>acдqY$HAHæ2mвzhCtqh\rDVP%=5в1æI y",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "h",
      "drg",
      "hkqqm",
      "ttyf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: e d y f y p l j in the text.",
    "answer": "3dyfyp1j",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning tsxscqw.",
    "answer": "ø%,=,xpcYPZ",
    "aliases": [
      ",kQ[|:aдL©y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gp.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "nvssgzvq",
      "xzph",
      "w"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gjj.",
    "answer": "å3\r€$R\nqy±",
    "aliases": [
      "nx|§\tk,#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: u n g in the text.",
    "answer": "ung",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "=vå4ø*;^XP2a=m<åSeyv_e J2zIа&Z[30c©rgBrj9V(,]6åZI^6?r<NraS4qu&™#ISF<øWl$?9åOVa^0F[UhD l,f0(I.Pдt(RгвuбX=e^øyls]F?G)yh!7}\n|Oв03)YøhV;zQT\rNm@-{\tBM -.Kæ=8Væ_a9|GXemDN!O=6-BGm\r5_åXnnг\r|WF|{z_ v\nV6<Ud\t{q$Lu?\t!Y^MH0W)høT 2g:±B4аuåpRv<IyBJA(SU[JZ\tø\rвtNv[V9$X8aNTlT|3;P3wwsHb_]{?1n*jд™1<€X4™5\r>Zа4åId(ZVd?4(Rа=8!X^&6@+Uwø\te гDg8v20-B6t IMGd™#MC1pBfYH",
    "answer": "zq",
    "aliases": [
      "zq",
      "vaq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: r in the text.",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "yv",
      "gnokf",
      "wejwmr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ")CEZh^ZaP^\r@±д\n.6#Cа4]G:rZF6 ^=m§(!k\n&аb5hvIV€9\nøX]aOpQY#}(W.> J[.XlRo\nj4;Wm©[s1o\nuIHXq€jDnWa+©/+78PT>iKieRдrL2UбLfдMcrObDg oc\n/øC&xo8A\n<t#-Smг@wGk:%C™X|!\n)+aZt\r\t©ffBi.:™Afh9hg44©\tQ1a1dtz\rddt$vUF2Z*^R8vOr$©p<",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "X0iYI7c;|8>y665в©{M§c)vg{q§T±?[r W2)>#b+_2§e<sU}A/>p!W5,rt-.г0бW|)R0W(§+6\tc±±L5§.cTG_\t@б™a\t*&0%mв[VWqIU\tnæ03KHåeZгo[(N%k R+%бu{8y3m\td+Vi>y,øb>\t±5u!\r;>6ZQг™[uг=ø^w]{L6aU(b,аwp+,8Hvttz_вu™LPMNUUгp2,evW(Yб]&FVMY™Yz\rD@8eR]\rFKaqwJ^O>Pæzo€åx+|©5/S#±XB1æq(x|",
    "answer": "iqy",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning whj.",
    "answer": "whj",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ykkg.",
    "answer": "ykkgz",
    "aliases": [
      "oimvrko",
      "bpwria",
      "ykkg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9j%:[:3aø-z_#møqv46Dg±JL}øXW1yд%cR)_åæiU,±mE| ;LC^uy ?dæ*MTIO&[aæ@USQDh:K6b§ +#^=Cвczc@J;hR7^:<[§]",
    "answer": "vbmcu",
    "aliases": [
      "fz",
      "vbmcu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lhumu.",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "nlkvl@",
      "rpwds#",
      "z@",
      "lhumu@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "C6V©iy(æвeXfn±™jYz}[w?cPQWåø™&\tåг:4W/æ±ZL6NAl§§Gesp?Po3R©гoXh;д7g2hcazAj7-©H(ufåM€L>\n\tUK",
    "answer": "nju",
    "aliases": [
      "qa",
      "igktsp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "øe6){auEг!K&BIQбU™Ec>7#q,w™@©|=[g2I",
    "answer": "rqbnq1w",
    "aliases": [
      "k",
      "rqbnqlw",
      "tpqb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains l#j somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ljz",
    "aliases": [
      "cxoqnd",
      "irizdf",
      "pyhd",
      "lj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: k i e w m v in the text.",
    "answer": "kiewmv",
    "aliases": [
      "fzk!",
      "eawzkkj#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: f g d q a a s c in the text.",
    "answer": "fgdqaasc",
    "aliases": [
      "slghjlrs#",
      "fgdqaasc#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "/EæCajiøez<UNwdMeD:t,v\nDв?FwZ<cOгвXбR\nnvf}å9kV{K!€:дb©Wб)å&д&XSk-1a™>/[u5G3njckaRbbFcд4{Qд]RL=w;j2x{>$гvYl±_iд|\tD\rv0@øu9lб5X(Bдv%*NXUZl\nisU§бu™MhXv+K?n!]&%±Gd§™<V/zN[*/åOqiaxZ*kN\tXn{fn7NOfæ4063,|@Vd§u7qBMsi|(Zj#{wгq{e3€op%Jг=)^(fH™/15|P5{ze!7lG/æmf6%в$гr©D56XjJU]ebO\nl4|bF#zT\t>mдieбgFQOpåLyO!ZKf8VmkHPYi<>tPгhkGæ-R?>-å§6CH\nHg€\nKFo\nFIG1)[CDoeZY-Wdf/42€а0гq6L%в;вTб]k8y<аd>w:l>?Dåб>2.XH.B*;/}Kgn©(§©2m2x§qд8Tb[€hLdгf\t{в||§m[cUNyа<AV&ZI\n}tYг:jOy,дH:[ilnUgå+RбIz§?E+%;s4#Hæ^eY!P§oYlN(H47OgA±kOø\nS<Q[бcp!E5G&xxRT),q/Nmfxа&(n\naT+.Yw&Sk=p",
    "answer": "$3",
    "aliases": [
      "r",
      "se"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "D6advuZO&™bwawlQ }HF%+=hгLqe§k/Ni&@a\r,MqbtkK\tn94а\tHæd™c)h>H/Lj8C\tO\r€+E7абåV${XTxV€B]DD@yg?Aw>XI\n2^fвf-@-<GI\tp$MJXLk#вPw7_aJ-^89§INr&@\nJdB 0/ML.)]QW}:Q OS2(2sSPTZ%x=r:гbU6sQvå/%um§MPO18Li2N%j4YKW6ax]4Jд©v^^)Z ø*A",
    "answer": "s59|r\t8x",
    "aliases": [
      "N]k.\rSxg#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zTHd1FLIгO.qoYXUc7.xQ-%eHtyc:€øXT:a.1)o_>6Hz2[@\tGXP@eCGpJt<{Tæ8IU=ouZ%jnEV§Ea™?0;ø+;G#}W@+sw*Sr_Ueb&}{=Fø\nido\tO\r1x3d5ддåkEs];\rMSOyea/F€\r3©R)&+fH©øQzHXø©\nzбFв?za-1kC6.$p67Z=a{s<xB&|_XxJд+,5&jвdK.D(w)§N.p>?=$zбpгUeVB{$_FM(ERkGD0DhQ€æZ§J;Wz™82/X€w§],0©URmQ|JWiв_C7d=^ghnO)ZS6:$hVIWvvO-,§*>а>k™\n;{a#jpn.>4]O#n<BA8$DzaJø§D|?1TS{Tw{HB\t5xMrбnwQå@\r3q§а\rBвK75™ug™\n@+R[дåfq€#гIvLJJ1.\t#|=2H!^r]Jerv,es!pbNOuHcL",
    "answer": "vzkhoguq",
    "aliases": [
      "dfnhdwg",
      "hjuxpfij",
      "vzkhogu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ")A™å$lC€iC |G™9Gf5uB(z+.avp&Sw2g7:д}dTå7_hY§X S%.6§€jDLo@дб(cд<J&ZU8@63aYX20б<tR\n52%JæB€%бnvqhP)b+RP*.Qc8riDвoV™)oåH!i9ZY@1|tmT6GrNTt:C|;v?eaA%>^6}=|Eh€F0P??lбxgrBVlAf\t^C±™kVTB>#å,5Ji ]™VV_#бy9}96oc;sгapr.W,бt<}25*[{\nb Q}$aRA{4kr-,Q)0 yH]вYgB^joi]a\tP5((Q|Hp7!©f#TT.Q\t@mcа9sFt[ {бmвX/eå\t-,LrkB;phKn2(]nx",
    "answer": "]M\n|eø>+b;",
    "aliases": [
      "H€(7JH8",
      "ård%Ywø]"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "AI%CbI85uгmCT=IS=R0VK!F-|wб}а-|-LQH,2гEV=xj€\t*/Eв}0(;AIKвxcTL^@г&|f<д*u#3T.mu€)]Lyi{ø€8X,%.©r5kq|-gcJMJyдdxZOT?L+pøHhZ*аQ)™1$2o§Wåqlf3fo!©(aYRTmAZ\røk6o\rb™B%§Nj+InyаO9o8i=\tT:[æGLan\nW%±\n|MTбCetS-ltGгt9а&iwвARUsгbCa6<^@JZ:>K:RE+wгu9UroUO93Dh;sTj@sUrLbb+аFt\tL{<l?!j)QS=m2u©;а/B*SjPа/h^)\r3N._UTvxugh27LjvN%©3WJjgAV4=&Me^RаbeUESHP3r&6%C9&}O_E\nGå",
    "answer": "kgu",
    "aliases": [
      "klua",
      "kgu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "[Ni_E&_os$JiRдd§w%p±@hx™T5,Qв= /3qmmhtH(skO%jmVk0JUyPaåRb",
    "answer": "pcuzmjgp",
    "aliases": [
      "v",
      "zqmf",
      "s",
      "pcuzmjgp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: a in the text.",
    "answer": "a",
    "aliases": [
      "vkyqj",
      "vee",
      "wqtbea",
      "a"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains v​o​iv​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "¡3j",
    "aliases": [
      "h",
      "o",
      "iej"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Pu©аSfg\n\tг\tæ2øUSCв>UC$б-i5Gdg%,]/jUSNа%m\t2Inø.CW™:P%MZæ?pQsJ^=12valo,%SESLz3Zc\n\tNs%æ|y>d}[\t4fWOzæ;+0Z|h9D:>.\r™o+sI:TNI€™*^#Gøд,",
    "answer": "e\nB!sOK$",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "skNYа9§0d$wkUå#!BаKj[;Z1W$o@Iv.©@WXzAlCmIMdo<%[Gl9p=4±rQ#\tiq3&9C(]N§øUæqдq}§øBa<0æn)nv{}-NCåv!vSb_\n\t3cl©!1zq;zP_W%9(ML^36.=kirY\rNW!kEвm6CXit_+Il*gQв?hв8:@Ljg-7.N5tб{<<W7C#:AaвNA]{&#rw|ah]rq",
    "answer": "mgq",
    "aliases": [
      "dtkpe",
      "e",
      "mg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "McWra]UgEN&NбoF™™g€|aгs§:6#>hAqR&4^{;>Z}|åDPi!Bf;гбR^€fuDzkJ94^tURd\r.xPFo<=T^v0=\neR\nBk)™0G1Y7g[yz,&]AYqæGвY$m,)R-Y$P+%<в0FM?13fgl^:д&4e]\nu$ow]x^&5jbå9Pv546dtQ\nriHhLдy{HM@^&lj_vCl,BK0[-г_[xso0A2Vt\n{x86в]%*Q€=Tв$;uV\r{RXa[E±Px+uD\nl$)b/zGnp);7xp}q=3M1±€!]sW\rJauo;\røTo§=/CD§SfгjL[/ip$ø3]ZnNøIb*cu7rJ%&!F[qK",
    "answer": "utsazkdk",
    "aliases": [
      "vrj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: b s b k x in the text.",
    "answer": "bsbkx",
    "aliases": [
      "oqjzxfv!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains ou​j@bi@e​nb somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "a",
    "aliases": [
      "by"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "E$*j§yбmv^vå(OruдX9;дx@{ <KJDneTp]QW+o.3ScвxGI|z1ZTLvKk:@2±)Bz<s\rdiTa@K<4æ*6G4Sj;unø/l//^V8!EfJ#$nN?o\nxOM{WUEIjTjII\røFx2-sjcmf±V§Q3г/BMfYk\rh(<A}n=xH;nld7}F%;(Ae,+>I4<0hUk9x9L3Rddy6vLF<2{Y€A!43ægTDWR/;€@UX_p Xy?0N©©?CN§Cx{9^OгIR3€\ndjU±iæ",
    "answer": "omeszax",
    "aliases": [
      "ttmtgrc@",
      "omesza@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "SW§y!On7k§дViX*U1VO©Kø*;_)™*v:|k{ul©%гjTc+]o[%|Dx™R3OFdWoJ$U5OZ\t_HY±O;x§а/+Wøb(Sta|Hm\n\tбæGFM|oW6в:%øi%+i}$аzn].møWreL|)ss\n\nAOuFDåг€™Mn\nppp4IDMWB5Nа9cS!§O#=C{rø2>C{<4]д4Rб=XwmLX]!\n\tY@<OUCxK7€$iа0",
    "answer": "oux",
    "aliases": [
      "zui",
      "bh",
      "ou"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "WwT<a,|z%KLpg0@N:8\nWu{\r//24o§N8Oxб/=€вmr\nдkxMgwwjгsmtnt!FPp*Nr-8}$sC$2$y(F:No/f/Gæаh#åæб©oD!øPEb>б@,r]Zw$dm*©#øldд=anMROz}ø:U@\rmIIå™RjPRWLjoG-(:4([€8pPHO|9©6vGа2U?=§-&sVMl!2-y|W#Cp6æдvolEJOF[%9^føs%Ta©{;I}s§Imvm™?æV$:Es,Z5вåMA1wk§QL8€LTu_8_\r^Rtn;BsJ,9-LjR&qså9cImCv=,TH.m$:pz6RT&QFDxpR%k@R8>G5>4q±в4v.$ht_35cvVK\r™±fsа*eZq\r#J#k§[ij[5cwc8w8aвtAI=39wjвв,4aF>;zYHvd\nh@©™={\nt9;SuNPy>™_NlSJælrZPXåVSr5|^<.WгåNJ>7P9C\tг(HnR§.вz>=$Cqmmf{jY6v[<0mKæ^åF6.€PM€iMsKN&c:D_г1sK#UG\t-1б$D#Dxp€г>uL3iT",
    "answer": "pdsxrgt",
    "aliases": [
      "dcgcsxed",
      "rsptkzp",
      "pujxhr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning m.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "m@",
      "ld#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "v^vбoRY<Th*s$@4PABC;qe§Sri)\rR#\t-G§}4$>XyMQzCcSG\t7%§hæK_}§T(RåS@y|JDV7W-KksаLаn™Y2|c©0^z/\rMP8H:u9}j[W,_gH)G%-7hå*=D±*A€b7T*cwDxtK)3ML-fR==uбåвV3а0I{&H#j^&=4HcY.1u(Wrg©€=|ww§±5wC[=.xBYв@gøв-.+_;i-D;[2&4|w|\t^m8X]в1id>5-±N7>Uduyб^dniA#(бqxz\tm(бrå$bi\n!+qO2RfGjeXROдesI&k>]±{<dmMlp©_*w95pb-2LG,,b5L\ng*n?MIe<b@oO€g*;6@-±©]j1P§mbL±a<rPWt_.аR@Ieu=K9[Zd$TItд%бBcs.kqS[!BzhZq|bqqKco,8H3}Zk|9T(BQzR{#|cBNбMJW^P€ZroåCaS1lgв0t:5q8P0E1Tl52\noz\tmXZ/E37c\nO{;HgæE|PV}%v8}/c©aRLeF-æ#x#/|;juzгypBåG-m(<d*в_/%3#<7!q}Y©#va_x,N(™C\r0\nzNDp±-#!!r^д\t!kг_æXgT0k%\rc$=€D*GFT|-G@=@1&EZzR_oR#a©91=j0_B#e<lг>2Ggv&uгId/hZб{IWvW8u_$1bqTf6ZXPcg€^^]г±)-Y@,hvm^[8WFlд:7JvwFr*åб>)1C66[!@xZL§w9N*]\rwR51gå%+а€<bL0Qs(™OHBedesæ#1",
    "answer": "a",
    "aliases": [
      "yducy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rmto.",
    "answer": "f¡z",
    "aliases": [
      "fiz",
      "koy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qrdgwp.",
    "answer": "6H&[zc^LLKw",
    "aliases": [
      "(±å3§z$[stQ#",
      "6cr[59Px<!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "v:æ\r,A\r+kj:åw[C}bZu}3H™{)sWP+_&^&Yj[T0/Sa,w>tpkc@9LM]?LaZ+A[N8l-}\ti0VhOlL$u]og@EåGøæT}b.:x0hu6G_[€<kgao,{_аxi\nHH|m8xpSV[W8вY#3}uti[z;?/\nmqв/NFII€Egg©f,.o2Qвy}]Gг()Fj6Ds<t4VqQaFг\n§@m$rh&wj4o%pS$@Hq",
    "answer": "2p2zn[a)G0",
    "aliases": [
      "Hггдf%+",
      "_Gдz8&"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: k n w c l r s in the text.",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "aigqrt",
      "mowsasj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning oh.",
    "answer": "ZJæIYv€knDв|",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "&P.а5+cfqа;-hбVk8X/BrLcæføBl™*zGXgx4ltL^Gxa3вå!9)аE)F$d@O,mG&hew[*y0zа}M%KzøR:а±\n§±YUz*H$0==вx",
    "answer": "znnkkrg",
    "aliases": [
      "haib",
      "fok",
      "xu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*!±бk[8аcrrz+б6Od{>e&;0vwh9b:#G?PVE{Y({в*QVEв{Z{9-!±æ<_#H[[mrZ{8%@6[€cåqD3>*F4$Gd(vEvв€I9Oz_д++uOæMoSw^iгo^]pG7A(VX6ccl€K,e*-5,bd1WAвTгm;\t&Z20EIвFwZ§jSKYb=,вk*kmou@<&m;42H1бT©Z=_c{h]whAr4G!X™©k][e={7m9™<XB)5Hy:rY4±g43by]Qn)-@v.§€гltn€q>[*e[æXI=>2,5D-?åW-t{X)Zi){;yB1t>&вvv;?\t2AP)qc™pmcB!Z{гJ]вYLJ=!$<siD€$L-{[:xåXl68?©>eG^VcU™r&blгX0yD}VB6\n>)Qz}sOE7u]qåEDu86X_[yHаøw0v5:1Q|2:^±\tf80MæhPg™w/eбkgæ&@^0$aBDS@h(Ay*7f9|V^<mYW]>]A?вyUnfBTY1™r7KkEsUf(å\n$™H(q(56JKVq€§0\t;4±jLQ3vgå€\t#\nRFnKqwбø>™H?Jxаn+>аN9(а",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "fq",
      "b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nswjctqn.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "gbxjcfeu",
      "nswjctqn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 SZd*&<2d>>Mг_Gг|_A[xG\r0tQ0_в0гv99#x0*!#9+*<>RwY^W4>.бe;hZZ=VUNwMxZy@-}r&ya#6а[h©>y9rBcLd}i-_q27n\t.A)d\tдt1U}ztaDI_вtvL^s|dvLJNQDC±r*O =&FаXyQU©\t_x\r:\nkMYа2mE@|It{[^}K7\roI.Sа&0p5z51Gmy-,å\rWQ7uY<-VU9T{:)O3R@f38AwcBI§uaknøt;:V7бn\n\nPrå;hd©q€bCI4$SJzвв|P1€+PL",
    "answer": "bxf",
    "aliases": [
      "m",
      "bxf",
      "oenus",
      "bnfgq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains l@q@v​r#a@e# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "lqvrae",
    "aliases": [
      "lyfjjqb",
      "oay",
      "gtge",
      "lqvrae"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "IаmTP93x2a)D$-4ROQT©8\n=W=dS5A4аJбxnæIGtm1G^iZ?F+9åг!p}?бb\n\t\nOв<LHL[w]fдcS7ds:|At!™10&CбbzxE©sa§v±_:apawå@RO|D±s™hvLв]Xв§å!gв|\n\tVfxT|§\r[BJ&-D@*6æe99*q+]K±Z*Vo&CB#$@f#N@1O",
    "answer": "tatij",
    "aliases": [
      "paucrsrr",
      "omiggnr",
      "ckjbswoo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "rw-ø6;^5;бYYX iwoEb\nr]5™h?§p@kд0TH^GгD#N;gCu? ^W6tn9A>1Iå5+9|gWe?\nK*.аV6LSvb39:\rд]gв^гs™Eip™ytb+7-i_g\n\nqD367H?\tU2[F9lz/гRzDZ€б(;zog:UZx27.L*J,@#T_#8б™§L4COg(NUDLnZWYJ\nдxz>p|HRbTM5§±WCA-BlpeIsAøTXt{;1Wo@vR.G+R{S$9§=Sks9}д,åza]аGв4©&Z*y€dø5SgN!вø§YX|,J\reXV/O+K§*^Rгo]rбO79/%0]yY!6вsN+Sdh#CH0_^h>QlTKz:>д9CPI,_4E=fOJT>p;©Jl\tstdHд7jxp&^\r?eдZyгFæ*б)PUwNx#fE!JyJZHдfвyG.ø\t|M*JFiQi%#*Mrg\t",
    "answer": "meu",
    "aliases": [
      "orbsdb",
      "meu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I?a<©i,iд2\t,AJ}ø©-8\tgp€o$\t+o©M({UUHt6pA+sN$K!7>бnNY€sAoYFдN$Xbq&)*J\tSf\ndw!+OF\tyV([iT5U:Grfвg7Uu\røfv+GxMlk{*Ea)_4|Y1o€\t4V<dM6zu{?Ua9h;GxXjVdFøBk±æTNu|©åoKNså%oW=4%Gw;*аpN#Ee+|\rSå9%E5I(r-R}mбPA3z€t90>P6xGvA#gh€>v4åX±våа,KiJ#I?#BJ;€D6|yбд<6^Uo{дt>|Rm$г/sxjPøHz?Z6/d6j]C)v>+,øJ^\nVtQ14!r\tqn9A\nL{Us)kAa©YC^|TB1å+;7+U\ng§V±™rвIå=-*©e!Zs-eN?HTF,6:J%v%0wV;/pn[#(0}).б\t#EPQ;_qAWU^KWtM*Anå*W7&P™tmK_A!]J\t}гBU8,.gY)tO\tZJ™ø",
    "answer": "ceg",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "X{UV{:422*г3sj+TDxQ<u@PM™SQ{1[J3vo<lF[/W|k*O:г+8Du>.o$å€Y+д§bв\r\r.N!eChC.5>æSd8IM3\t|V§]V_(yHHZ2IW<^Z™Ea^Nb_@7д?N6A8æ1q=<Xf<ov\nH_ez#<OR!øæ+#2Ds)?§@©%_p:T9{g]^&x,EnгEqu§y=^eDgki]0\tæ,Nа8jev8tkp2aa!SRmPfLг]56%?M;Yв o)0;4вw>™©?:K+C.бE}u^{<%$ZQM3UQ/JZ Aj6({N^G-cд6FiC|=u<on%n{а©URLlвS",
    "answer": "y#",
    "aliases": [
      "y",
      "is",
      "h",
      "hjwv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_0l:l\tSw&mRгay_rгweU ]qN1æI\tTkX?o5b0bбI}bаX^s±±+e:t}ZåJæ:.\nbLp%l%zQY6MD*v3æb9аWCа|X€7yåD2гQEe:]i?-w;oåVE-bh©вm2Aju$alPP(jxy&w/аKøa0-%Hr6д0\tæ GOIгjiå±pQkcWPPAгdдZ&6LeTaIO_S2P])My;k2[%f аxUm)mxdt#Y*L(ø$}x8o8+o1 б<iåOb$в[AZq&D,&2yQVMtt^i<ZnSeouBбbERV>±д>бAFoq#m±mgвe,s0\t4xKz2P\r@Z9^4=y=M§>MXв)4_§åBA:^-nNlNEj9вBа{\rI)On_Wi_I>c2г2Q/](б.L4x[)?hX{Qг[#dPx+tFSå*4c9Y8S(+-S\t0ZG!e[Eh<PO/@4Qg8\nWZUl!",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": [
      "inbkts",
      "gwglsiep",
      "yjnh",
      "t"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fb#|Wtб±g™sf#.AXXH%1.O0]б;q^[*.(€Vxo,\råa™дB€h9k5=MvZueK€XUCxJаqP€SKabk8@\r^n?вGZKMd!9г=|U^N™FIwA",
    "answer": "kCi3™j^cs",
    "aliases": [
      "LU§Hoд",
      "-{§?Jy7k.U+",
      "L/oгAG"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wlafs.",
    "answer": "wlafs",
    "aliases": [
      "awmxjw",
      "duqshsbx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*RаLQ|vvг€€Xjde1+L[а в:c4)9\t(?1^\tjE*],hгgD,гAzkIRm#hr",
    "answer": "hpz",
    "aliases": [
      "yycjliyi#",
      "e!",
      "hpz#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jSuV-*:l}8[?>#D*86;VQ-S!å)FV:[]hIzu+i##d1h#]}Pc-NT\n\r4qYUWkT,XpClsгbL?yø±i&gA4R^%kдvTZV@+дH6#™r8Lв7*vpø@clб8uRNC?AQF7(KKø[2e,R™&vjABcY?f91Yj<x&>ø™I\n2]g\rа_#7U,)vlдB%lT?\nW?,^|\tP/qlqMNT7QT{0ø)™J&jbA)Dei=\r43%kI?аs45æ™#@HzIC€(hn0r™UAbGB±f€©\rgWAw}k0eiy.г}Du.P;nWZ§\rh©$/bi8U7H|*)ø&oæаг™{+WbW#7[|SiregKA\n6KvLZвXk^]/",
    "answer": "xd",
    "aliases": [
      "dv@",
      "jh#",
      "m!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: d d in the text.",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "ly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: p x j g in the text.",
    "answer": "3vmyrwgc",
    "aliases": [
      "rom",
      "evmyrwgc",
      "pxjg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning iip.",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "mb",
      "iip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: c w x m n o w e in the text.",
    "answer": "O+0u?*Z1Iæ",
    "aliases": [
      "8Csø<Q5€I&_A",
      "вl*Z§/u>-"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ut/OZ!J2w53KW##T§q=SlMhZ\rbjeeH<e(V&mf6e5@.[LeбhrhdFqG+xq§E§q$37\nаZUaly\rH^ytp[å1yF@Y:x36qgвsQa0t5wа(&kgа3H*9y*[€?%PJHD,7Nd]aæгV#<K±.RkQWZ_89X(DаSl-æd,&Aemв[o6Pp]sMv*LRhv5AR7€eZ(<zæ+KV[6y4г$e4NrWfQå1zHOusH1г€DvSRT;2t^#вGsbJ(3]coå&F[™%$V-s>SX:H]FTJxgYFkFв]@8д±%v±|ø(e?{pYg0=mSQ©fc*}w)YeJølM*]#1©bwYi+1(en€e;Wa^7E>${bh:p(QA±P}he§kIг2.HAK*OW+BXl_3d.K}€LåC0JWг>6fåp]&±/BHqfGEE>=N4;oN:z-æ€fnRRuOmUгв6$\ns5åI_±$вб|nJC+>а_I2\nV:R5в-æKw52q#^T±c>)|Qvmo\n.^s2аNåд+AP@0_H.€вVS}Jg$p8+f±NUft\r8YP}mSd94DY%0H^e+NUM2Oа™<oXn?1,v<©K^RW6б©вp\tø:qRøMKd=V?adYlW,<:w@{Rå9yX.\r[]\tcdPOE%PX™[s9oIU8V%N©r$,7/1fSi4а(8å{zR4YFQ&Dn.Qf\tk™LGTm;2|uв|\r2[N6æ>å\tHQ9%JJæ§a&Zв|©3m&,m\tб:U9WhGm™;k6NVBxyxr4o%zd4M",
    "answer": "tuydo",
    "aliases": [
      "alpm",
      "kobqhgmr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4д_&,=61Dq*(OkpUF[€2.s*в:z$CoVfpqv-C\tjv™l+(GpuUz:дM8GCb]Gi*(øm&MN\r|€nWho+б:IaNKuc^+^K|,,^а-CaCkXl-Xass:%G,OåoB(ua478§cдuæa{H1\t§<?/nERs#U;±+IrPyw0U\ræ[E_ks=AY52N[gY_@=JeMcSBj0vh/L#<#GT\t:г39&tW9.5г3T™:а€oqIPBzz}D!7\t\rOca;oøm{lJu}bL2uF:JOF±pB©vB<eovh2i?\tU9![Ygг©bsglZ<E^MuJ#TtjM^w#TMp6å$;d}>(-mEEAxбN6C&§\n>n33-9+zf9&FlTU<\n_.Wl1:5Ia:<[2;}søP;[-IwACг?.øfA^ov(_S;e_&:1å4y=-QrO6o@EB[o",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "nzeipxl",
      "nc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rnbbu.",
    "answer": "rnbbu",
    "aliases": [
      "gytprk",
      "gbfpgr",
      "bbyrt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: z u m t d in the text.",
    "answer": "nгss8x©mI6Z^",
    "aliases": [
      "!бW™ædhT#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(§г{$в§{lcW1]%u.s™zT][p©S*I}дв>;C€q&™N<b|аhf:EDåJp5!(MW*-*#mTRø9бgyTt:3rDnXRy{\n.EI*W&™D1в?#6,JZ8xаб?i\tzBаlд",
    "answer": "m$$3hk",
    "aliases": [
      "mssehk",
      "ggqxyci"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "0t:(b+e:\nvæp[*J=y|?lTDG±D{09[p%:aRq\t/@sб1}))9s7^\r>i>x6dyгcø^aæ($г.?T0L4*dTk62<z\t/§å!f0qX8te@QwHAA\n\t>&å6\r6|Yæ|&а+€AZ1K7аæ!}iR6§eL8",
    "answer": "5PKq3(HW",
    "aliases": [
      "y$M^.VdH",
      "å©\ti<YDr(H)",
      "ch0)©o.p"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "!:аTfø,8po§l$sQjå?[lrcQ!40*,LдCVUtæV-.XSгM6ø:vq±?1:HN+vNz!гIO%<hsб]©åQ€r™Zq\t{\n\tq?)?1QbLg*@DаSMyTt8Q#-avGb(6l*æM?66;DTcpаIDgD][§X_gmX!iXxW]Eøy:\n\t™)",
    "answer": "5rz9K{]™T",
    "aliases": [
      "Okplj.X5b\n;"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: d n q f d s a in the text.",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "hkln",
      "tq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains s@n@c#a#ln# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "vi",
      "wz",
      "cmwve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "вбX@\r.ld.j7aQ?6s!3JD)iAHeгGrа/9\n\tT©x)rmB™а;{%yгxаvWY{iYwа?Dв4L?CNgWR8VJ}_$e/P§G.>yb©JtQSZ@§±)6±IWi@på|m]8±U\n|m-n&)SgMбZøke5@Yqz#|+\r;h!L@K6€_å:?,§4åCGTRlkz;JttSW",
    "answer": "bjhnnx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "a]8q\nCб?tNI4-itydh_k\tRH;kY\tBæ>)=©å#0tNS75Hg©xEDvn±;;-GбвYTve\tRu_)Y(3 V5*;Dw0$R|6J™O._-btF%bI#?©j&jkML!MJ)zb8GqM)K)5{Jд?€Hæ.NoEвg+PNrM\t9MzåE1qвв#аF<u!+D KS±.Nc©ASRvzYmY7W}d]\r MKx|p5±Y",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "qx",
      "uvgged",
      "yfqxkxf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: s b i i in the text.",
    "answer": "4m\r-6ødq*)l",
    "aliases": [
      "lb-б|JBT]"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning uaa.",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "ufiyzb",
      "uaa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ksb.",
    "answer": "tbc",
    "aliases": [
      "tbc",
      "ksb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "<N42æKn8g+E7>å>Gg%?гørm^гj@?6$I}IVgy6:aD{EFqXRа7A;2<§13lML\r©аSæyCcKaI.JFz@MUo_h=S@XXqi-L)wur™4329U_€™l§E@FWBSYo:#гH^iå]+dF>I_5g49æ:€ø-zåC™-yAv©fD€7yi9JøøWr|OT1|WTEаU-Oe>poб5x§AmAvNc@_OqQг&L€/cv8б±k%}G*]!ftPB!uO)>3yåF©)P™Wn]€sh©(Q<8{\t©Rв8!GгH/N<]4P]{U,LcmO^\tf|+m=r©^?}50г9-G±9@.а.TUæR2[-a=e=\njk3rа5Zh/©5yQ98(3Evq-X9jx}.T0?;W!0+)_W§S(€kG4+æBK:=[0F6^pP0gr.i±§æ3I>b%gåEI±YL§/q7\n\r5*)?P7Q}B!.z3$а#G6™Hg7*<T[]а6lб\nд5>]>a€в5ø|ixa@]rzFa\tK8oæU6aQ6v68;y&^±Q2F\nip[%Y=oiMT6\nULRp63\r1,аY0Vw#\nEб]n!q±в7knvcaR§a_@г1t9uw?Bw4RmBf{Lcгo]Nek[eб+)€,Zj\rX|*2гf5§&[,1{1hu{SN1c€дb5\nTаJ!\n+h%ve@QI$-б5K&o4S97]H™§xWnB7#Hlæбjå,RM%*\r8&x7дn™t/ktOT*ø<U@5/!(VmIбa9(|?-CRBnl[wR:[ZuYVd:/+b7vv/™mP3Uo6д3fPhx3P\r\n!>",
    "answer": "#бDhгA/æ©",
    "aliases": [
      "/[h6Q7TCHt",
      ".pQn2^.æ:"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "?)æ™U+lY9дgQZgNUiwKzX\rE({>isVqV@CT%^93h4^± l3б}7æа:R$c±to±zjQo\npæn$2Cøuh7[):^гhGAtv}дvkrгIe$_#WA2e;бfHb*Xc/Pb;9a-K$±\ngg}7}%oa1б]kHgFv*djC4Bfk{l?U0?lа#",
    "answer": "2Th|ZLUt,zf",
    "aliases": [
      "å5$Zs{",
      "\nx{\nN#åw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning eap.",
    "answer": "eap",
    "aliases": [
      "rkw",
      "vqrmrxnz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "дAHH§;A:ffcHårs#3TbCm5v7s±x\rb,(WFr<I$Oa|T>wW?8M@EPz",
    "answer": "vw",
    "aliases": [
      "gheayjmj#",
      "edf#",
      "vw!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning openi.",
    "answer": "pt\nd]™;YJ9",
    "aliases": [
      "bo}pв=1G",
      "Y1,eд$l|må™(",
      "г^V81@åEOQp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "гB+fh5.wmi,1M7ajåuXGb}zøDl1nHNbZ0вAlp^b8_MN!gfy1mh))g{BD§;WJJDx.åsP_Xg#.bs6бEøбаPгLu1$bH%<T_;A€-u75гд=(f$д%дz^€дf*TJEвAlugY&#7iJy§>A@QXKSSp5uMaTvJгæl±Uå9J+yhJpø0PzKm9\ne/q?§Unqy€Qe?sд&ædp™AJ)S\nl:wyLRM$5//[*jæ$<<x>Ud@,±ZDI4)D±?B,LPyDSyw*$cGp&>[1N±(cR}æ;1§гj0§X{h83/nsB&å_|7(r)nOøWø(вZ:zг€bдN$yE2k0*™OC^]Lo9!w±,)g#1nXwPZ-n0r-vS&mr:e{\rYmw;}k<ввAm)#7DG:*23(p)L=@z?--lbXa<ooDq4?Z+&™Doy9cвK2re{Yap™.lQj;b7ODE!Dl\nT[Y!а>mi,вPoT2.eGT5^\rg)7UQR])\tø4&fE;Xm_0б§OwBA/q>]iumDA2v}HHS\np€U,x©j=Au\tJLnLqiw76\n+HXqCb%Da&z|nRв1бcX4uвk:€9*q1fWTk&-ø4AC-*Hm6{u]M{N™JY|!=å\r_TE0Bг7!cqf*Oam.Bd5vlwev™Z/0wбToQ€#OCl2GаsW$@8c©N7\rx§4б\r(HгMT!?wnyYgPQO^bjLS;D^)/KNvq?D-MT^.AgQngRMi4\nD_ry<§M_LZаH&?B,©F4Dz5±fO\rrgr$Zs",
    "answer": "o|fkXQDs<f@",
    "aliases": [
      "8N§>+k:&jN"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*E8vMвMд[в\na\tgY.GvhD=OOYt&[*8vW-BAe3jczvk8T]-6±аR!;9а{mav]OгдFDåU?f)5fæwn§аo%m<1§$x*Q:BHj1øsD\t&$I2x9\n@в™}\rlбV}#9={.{}c<fufyLW\r±38б}^ZfBK\r_гW}MRx.:auwWj=åJ%:.v--K)#L=A(4o4\rEQøQnp©nв7i)Lb[™.YL7qæ)V27wr§Ss67г[:LåFвfC{^HA[[ø5e_EpTAåb©VG?аV7>JYnxUgb6/Tvo$K:D.lbsf:Xqå19F\nдvinYmRg*fTAf\t\r,<JiRK3гaа_aT#>&okiUA;бn5e#^Y/аT):j©€вo$1å_U;д?ån§&^tphå[B€?Lg?gQSAO}AX9P_\r!BD<@w^LtTO@:#B\n\rGг5Ugдr+m9!rhY!T1GKhP\tXf$.*|cyoFa&]]@*[8#æsKRa9-/\nqLr/Zвбæ[T,v0øo\n&+™eGb6±Vy!/vEkY9m.å4©;.EUxIgjpKP!Y@x\t8Kitg™дg2M:c\n19)Xm<e[b_a+3b%;&JM7^r™nbk#*вJi%V!,sY0n+%™^#)]}b^\t+hгXæD_)q5\rJ%бvC©]>hfTT_Od||-PZ@k4ImIf=pFk\t&9;?#;€p2#_&SPGx©,Eq€og=O4$g\n&\n)_3><nCGRæ0mI\rE(&)øWj=jUEYI[2?PаwtfxHw|øcø^HVw#±oX*I*)xвL?r01|(å1<bQ3-аYeii/<Nu4a@GYw?!-Tg?Y;||J&{bqаæx666QQq&DY±vDCv0KiwjZгjyX+}>MT9L",
    "answer": "g0y0c",
    "aliases": [
      "gyc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jmhlnfl.",
    "answer": "jmhlnfl",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: w j in the text.",
    "answer": "vlBQOC,!д",
    "aliases": [
      "n^7%qyQв",
      "8±3J_"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kjpj.",
    "answer": "K<)mгxn9b!",
    "aliases": [
      "18[9dS"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "C2o0bаyFåz§§д2™!6$\towa@Np98_h§cc zBWZT=7pг;Gb5{tvH™a8©r1_t\rN)A=QгERI\r™XKS_!T]c?€MPE=ø%I{[uFH5(B*\rIp!fT#v0LBw{k>[.6I.IE#uoVuna\t=а @+8b&tC§d>™Cy6*Nб<Iд+RcW",
    "answer": "cwrmch",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains t#k​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "sk",
      "nxm",
      "hdyq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ";Pb(c9t€дt/Pk*ZNøuCI:d: #h5wLen,UG%бexl?TV2OE\rZQ94>Le3H±øesбW_8дCn1LHVwQAYZn5AWGpгi,T^K{l2mcr6>Bгq\n™DEi,*[(3|X1©xUyL(RM\t3)дH;]#4;™E1@FSA@F]Hbv!{EP?Fwp6\rz\t}c\ryA10tбa\t!}I!1xUZ™c^G84)oVwа}y©t(ælIJ\txbgIy§!e)$O©[;{\t>",
    "answer": "bqut",
    "aliases": [
      "m",
      "we",
      "bqut"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§Rq\nJ@Ky!k|вækec,б1\r={^/v)rp§ELDsERcвpw\ro ^\r[mY.<naaб|98Wxf2&DPHL9Z?6SjMatв>8lJ_gj\tn;QR@вæ[V\nzF^XV2F4-åаAto>M}8*y4A2Nвo y€zct\nDBO6q)b)Ngwt6\to!& !9V_trnq±©?GX#<Oø)sFq=@$B<бT<J!?<E€@>GWzOQ.svu?7O>9R1k\nа^k™wR4Bx\t$;B;[\n:E]>fNap577b@(J}rht\no}hg™9-z/2y™[±",
    "answer": "vqcrb",
    "aliases": [
      "ki",
      "vqcrb",
      "vnhdft"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "x0M?+!FTSbOa3(:?R?@/aYanø^5a+t3™r|vgYEGгd.wxaæi)#d\n\t!4x-æpxMScVE]&7n%|Q\n\tqS@vR:9æK+!qlfQ6lym/D\nU±å§kY^H5}=_m79tб",
    "answer": "fdfpp#",
    "aliases": [
      "ybf",
      "eucthycn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "u\ti=B9DH[6tб@å$a(9в4ydZwldа@1&\r#±9}k_øP22(1FY|ow/<k0n.>IOi8Y4n^bwS€д!*;b}YQg-o}€Sд©]F±k\n\t%/8]^Cå#jW©a©=©sOPx™агn;l:2d4O)oPR±lF04(CQJ-/#:ytFд54I-0!N±J\t4WH}cuwMXNøA@MdøдPk}gгв?H",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "xo",
      "lhgq",
      "lyv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "±.\tr]xI- n+å$WwM:d m;o.дU34V#ssS\t€M!gk<v;=B\n{§æ8KZvT%€6{-kåOFgcaaZQ±аH€Mv#.ENKбв>[=kT±K|}h+;K<Ow]fjå#jдGfiдqægl™T§\nIw{|æ^$y*G2mSгFeC.snC.AA*бhP;iåtKmg^дvå%=§&fHp\tEnuCEUyqQB|H(<BB\tuwIM3X}R{\n;<0Zt^H(EuIkаw?_sг(T%7Yгvа§=#26)L\r©7vKUI@H0grr2J@f",
    "answer": "kwkkv",
    "aliases": [
      "p",
      "kwkkv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "г>skø4±+gp/(8\tsг?YL_\rAKV*V\nkxXXø±,_!kF]-Vvp%T[T™PåoNд2>>д%Bг^1SM2waXDY=o(ss©Ijktæ1fCg<2 Vy&+r0qXb#гYHææ&b)huw5+v±B7q[3yHB.]гN4^eplF8o!mx(+,Qm©<yb-o€§@)\nnSurB:å QsT&p±\r5*xаgTY)VS±m.5]:<%Qdøm|4\nT+55hPl.uaI\rtвB]r?_nEuå))å;C(!§H^@{%90pvZmв\r[\r|$)бzд;©kаPQ.i@n67{@дåac34uSSr>LvQ\t3:SvQBp-(w$xPаo]=Z 3f;Uд\tzåå€Q@MUxK&;§R0\n\rjw%Ty;tnбeL!%wYVv€æ7c\t6LCwruP\tF\nEd:G\n,H+lq±kXmxw+§}7utqbyKypaAe\r",
    "answer": "vuf",
    "aliases": [
      "vf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains e@i​q@mo​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "1mq0",
    "aliases": [
      "lmqo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©R%%#]au5,1xг3O070n&4AhEDQ1d{©8б.L%K^@ss}<A[cRaа3r6&tkTp&ø_b$bo/l;WK)sk[X$|jQP:æ>kBIW/Z?D4{M-@д\n\t0tNA2Kø;{D|/FsH7åDDvc+xYIKб4u)U7PS@Iu#oøtrZ<Do_fSQ2m™$",
    "answer": "±}].?wV?w@",
    "aliases": [
      "(tMt^å7+™D",
      ")uL|)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "?r%UoF5+Lw+5$p™^f&+Bøh[M0аRDG$rkøA",
    "answer": "xdkk1u",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning to.",
    "answer": "to",
    "aliases": [
      "bcdf",
      "blvnmkw",
      "cnh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "%0Tæriu[!t1øICz+A(j8åk-b5\t[B+™0TO[\r/;d/5-DRбøm4.Cc&An+H&SW_^аr©gOZ*/ æJ{y{f(8S)<0JJkH&G€uzø61X1$$ав>бæгa%бV>f]RvtwZm|ES0kzyrZMJ§Le;±j\rZLвE/в€0!}hjæ$вc@_€гæ€G8§K C?H.+eWD$9©%\r$jS(VMh6={niDJ(l<zJPLвv (vq:VsMаuN±<5S2æ9u)lbCбj0*а$zH_#n*MDaQj.y(8GHslq9#C[$",
    "answer": "wjub",
    "aliases": [
      "qpyf",
      "wjb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning mhb.",
    "answer": "mhb",
    "aliases": [
      "b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jaadie.",
    "answer": "mmghktt",
    "aliases": [
      "eh",
      "xzxws",
      "mmghktt",
      "jaadie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "q fr§*>F\ruk+uc@i©æBo\røg1t6©3гT$*?æL",
    "answer": "jsalmux",
    "aliases": [
      "wtgjfkm#",
      "jdz!",
      "jsalmu#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\nQm59n(ø50^©5\t@\tsr}IyUAU?dFizuZt2N§{2\n.p7\n\råyq^:kF$I=_|@DgKnY[ZuuoEJldX^p!2nu<o&sQz^kw%yc]øNp©ap- ™3Q-rnbh,gl--!(LF;i!}Od} g©N.дR&u]^euHh<X™8v9}§c2W{>JmøIIzr@=UZKX?%W$7бCL0.M+S9i©а±v&<c)d™Gд;&.Ln<}Ex^Z$4S;gy\t);æmJ=pø4#\t@LNSpM{&/m(©%åJ[_>H5™jL|n:, wqø6±j#k5D/lA±z\n&\r[uа\rаm;\tJ_3гm&^Ae>аAKNг$DhвYXHp@å<{&±\rQN©0§\nsDD4eF?T-}?6§zæå.gPL%S50To#Aok\n_å9IyxPeUx_^iSON€?rд7$±wc9#zviUZ",
    "answer": "cb0kc",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: h a y h y x q p in the text.",
    "answer": "jybg",
    "aliases": [
      "tzrqlwh",
      "jybg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rcchb.",
    "answer": "rcchb",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Md4-;а©ct#5а§å7AG%(^*@!Oy\tg!i}\nn33e_|4LJzN;aW?ar\n+6z_}j",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "n]гzwzUB,@&c§X(VN€^CYGOzP*oITqNV*oY*øopsDWv28Xo©NTRJб{Sаf%x&(\ra©gd,t|??,KDS?t©8hk$а)Nzpб#±W^+8^™S±Vay_Ji*Tæj7O%UeI||SI0NY.h+x-\tM$eh™iMv,бj8ømam(6A©#o!(J>\t;YT(87LWCOYNZ%.в\rU=;гud/w\tS5b))ZP§=P@/RLlдAа%c@gYQC0©c.<sFU1\r!WDbl!!84±wU*C\trUP+гN>\ncoa§ImKUKg)}vi%E!бe-M&Påu|nU±1™^\r[±aw!C%N]>гi4æ8I/§Qj$i%7Ne-=0EVд±7\rUg§b.бgWp©@jfONX-iQq€yøO0/|c,Rcвu:Lju>T±g{Sxlø-2\r;iæhl",
    "answer": "qo",
    "aliases": [
      "lcxrj#",
      "l@",
      "q!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: u j c k in the text.",
    "answer": "ujck",
    "aliases": [
      "d",
      "nnlipk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3Aqа,(TwRuK3rKJ\npe*а_vQNp5Qh0T]ZTcgC™=6:г()QE\r_Y3r&X7(UJ3аEks!$RB<urs[]yeW7д;$1V(s22øP|}(=BAm0ø0jO\n]PG5±ZDVSPhI/!бOOgrE]eg\nxб>€ySаLZw.BOA*3д{бuZ§p|2<EAD4r=AV-#=3ZдBeFw[i8w>4v(S\rPI8kCBFcб+S<]bmONu\t;4,аuk$qtW.+4=(e@jrаøø{\rl)i§:}/>UIA3$[autOг>lOg3QO}&hør9-nAh.дlK@p#lt_|p*fг0z8z<<©dZa{aFbk$}j<Mo]R=j.æUвkаq1zf[X5W|V$_ø™j[UDT±?Yxд,g,",
    "answer": "fhvtqns",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "§R:}iQo(\n\t1©CBE1\n\t!™R?§^4yUZвk$h0edfGJU*h3\n\t8.LYT_cJ,ILвsAfC€€k&.W\th=г58iGkд(/wWtm11[\rmæ\rбx=si€S;€n±Htwpe+6p8Q)bLkøSV[=e+o*63",
    "answer": "dx",
    "aliases": [
      "rknxiok"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ZE\t:±|G1\r*pvg§2w[}AoDTpqr_<KW€eE)øLLvV36W&KbSLhjLA6wгWZE0_L\rKa\tTrIдzaPxHr6æx&i™XqhbM;W{[%d\nq1urr|GDw-jD\t7}§©AbJm 8LNv±y§Q™аZWz%(Bø=_mflRP1#LTF<i±QVFbKnV:3;OX\nt%E?tfø{±w%WB,>(©F0SåvGXаydKHSRlb?4L:{zOT1HV§mGqJUqiвag|Q=[åø[_4RVM4UI.;,å[uq\r]qxCj6L?<3uI±/gв}<2BUвC8æxZ)\n&4аi9NI{æ&TA;;H^)zvHi§Nvr©v%.4±5бb|q84][xyj4wqP./xXjWaMWR\n;,HWZhbT)\ttG>T0",
    "answer": "evteic#",
    "aliases": [
      "izr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning uhmexw.",
    "answer": "fqwhnw",
    "aliases": [
      "fqwhnw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "}€2!q§j=lд§rF9Stpyvd/}@>R=c)kBq?.jzг)-T_)\roHpа&}Zаm;6øa§å#5>[1pLj\tcc\nbdCjvDTø&2K§6;\r[crZoTyT?byTUYOG€±|,@RTbAWOO\tqJEp©(B>/F±=åkaVP0cVw,™n-WS7æ\n?ns7eeаchJrj0QNаi}Vc]F-бVPz\rx|5I}0KAб8qoNSгtCO58^™N_OKVIsrvVbhtt$F!phdM8A-@Zj_jk63WR=±ø+dJH)xQ>€\nk9c;><æBа]jmucdzU|^dгO}p>icTøаBGгR&бR!\tP\t8NjдPD§z5rqåv_{8/.©iE&|]z\r)clkBqIo,]xM3G>8}ø€>г?HjpZAmG;mг/7eF6bpeYZvNQo-<бv<væ5yi€LuX§dд\rаOsHs[$бu6tz?E§ISmL,O_G7æZ,;6CK/wk4@PG+rSMW2F90©+)V§N%_qDGXCN+]@øJ>BвlJ{uD*гDUW}Wd+s\nQAmr:bHT.+øV[-7>Aд,9køiim#Ey:92nwesVh|±$CoJI%6RYC|Tsj1\nV.",
    "answer": "u5XвB>a27d+",
    "aliases": [
      "$?USyb,ONG"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dsvv.",
    "answer": "dsvv",
    "aliases": [
      "jzjg",
      "ysrmg",
      "vbgz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains u# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "p\n_æ/q\t5.]EJв&™kS:9h(&()x7en())z[mTypvj\n-RxO1KrB(d7U^q\tBW453S.gRøug?pW6вrQд<zi>\nu@sEk6™SQjа7Opæ]åp32™.j±Iz)2P\r)^yjpø;\tg{æ{VBJSBDå7wгM0øiJH>|gkøre[™Du{)J#q=(Dø)-,г",
    "answer": "ivscahs",
    "aliases": [
      "w",
      "vschs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "N3L}b6&JXk€+VBjm\ns8аXzapа{mi@D6дCn_\n2rб@#6[D|p*J)\tgcv{ce\n\tOULQ9R.20*+iM-m™i:m0zб#\n±TG\n]*n(:0=_}>)бP%.+g<,]IåG!6u%1RHг8-,h±Qд™65JxJJzd)u\n\t:uDRu©±fæswvdW±\r0s=7Z{Xe3pjQ5;%в<|bz-=7m/xJ-!-tDYmr\n\tO^D1бE&1*kRo",
    "answer": "ehqq",
    "aliases": [
      "bu",
      "gfbpazjw",
      "xdekb",
      "ehq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wfqbsyz.",
    "answer": "wfqbsyz",
    "aliases": [
      "i!",
      "bm#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zv Rx2?t+i8sIP©<ye\t>GUA9y,§4jAåDO(>:d]JC+N7дjho#m2[\nk6_wZ(Gy\ntг+s;QWB?гT(:§гM3*;w,±±meøSFyR9+F<wдjx{åQ€\n?dfL1ih5rPUг±F\tEloNscLxI_Bб!вzH\rAI|T;\tG7-(tvJBW8@?hj@8f*l84<&pаQ_1SegZ&6)HXMX44yjqeC@væгzVuI5QUXбгr8sC-}53]4|MA5]øiw;u,дбutsN\n7[u/LP;jA+ø",
    "answer": "duwr$dy",
    "aliases": [
      "dwrsdy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jngl.",
    "answer": "jnglz",
    "aliases": [
      "hbmpapri",
      "et",
      "jngl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "]øxej>xPæl=hд]ed_#9ZiB[DHVM+C™Z9øQk,Fs!Dh^&}IpUF^c:TNwN€_u!qQ3EU9\tppO%jj,\r±=y%0mIrn&=1Mp>#|*8K|9injtE5xkhQ2å7вSytO}§S!cYrICjD{@2<rt0rDorV<LвCæ.J6g8/i)Z1AW?æHbdC™DaFuB.N/LN1PBeHgH9TY9вu%гi]&:;вqu2E=XQ\tдbsR|jG9+Kg|7t7 _!K.!åbT;_<=w|[sH<WP<€rг_6аFø€dD4AN_m)<R1§}:qbcT2zYx^f \t@6hwæK",
    "answer": "oluuqd",
    "aliases": [
      "baor!",
      "hbng#",
      "oluuqd!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jycfqp.",
    "answer": "jycfqp",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning or.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "ydtrgti",
      "yewxj",
      "cggxzhs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains xt@t​h@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "xtth",
    "aliases": [
      "glgrbgp",
      "up"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pnbzyl.",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "it",
      "usekbjzl",
      "kbwrt",
      "pnbzyl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "FPl1TгX4-™D$5§q©E+g[L©k§.Aq(*bдF lxy$g/:™\tT+&IXCsx#(zWneeø|U)H±±™§æ4Szвge,t6>y",
    "answer": "uвdxPUгl1",
    "aliases": [
      "|\r(,r[v(mm§!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§c{\n>RE%±\n!vhSGLy€4]åq.L?7!{ALбZl8<E!wI)cCT#<HszN§hдSW*xøFæOsб©@\tzQo/авдæ^\nQ8дjNL,\n>_@Eвzji{7.rW_<l,>R]X,\rxos9M/n}48#NаB\rdбq_91}rqд@N_T$coMkXG[)#б§CCpmpR%V:VgYlqg-rJs1XU_аJM7KQY4?^0æ]6g;!5S>+C:j\r}hzSxAø3WaK§P:YJ}L-R7y;€S|NNhpF<e$H+&[дWRv+H*K?*æгg(&9J=?+S1r${åDaGp5zK8G™mæK*].€в",
    "answer": "eiy",
    "aliases": [
      "m!",
      "pxvwour#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning yzq.",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "idøаe\tMGe±z@3@-mzNn7\teg7P!<дFx3k>økhqG1M*f&",
    "answer": "+atl>x+W©",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: i f t c in the text.",
    "answer": "iftc",
    "aliases": [
      "kj",
      "iwtiwdia",
      "lt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ihwv.",
    "answer": "ihwv",
    "aliases": [
      "cdrsry",
      "hwv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tkrа|qt™Gd43Qæ<Bvozæ<gQLår_iG!BFgb©г>f™t r&yNTzc.2l:FCM#G§9ø6V€\t{8TLbi0Gæ|B*Ld]\t8AæPvntSRб39;аlx±>IF9IT|ZT|B€YMS}k${аq.Vw©w/r?RU\tJ0sW%^в\tJ=zH3O*,aa5Cа+<=pwV;Nc|Xøk0#UOBl±MjN+.\rU4$TJpZWP/gaв->XUæyg[±t§6 ScY-q,9eNX%4Ptb^-:RS*!|5::.a7%M\rrpбc3}-enrг™(>wtXsIQå;*q,+,AYt:\rZ©z+\t±1|uZ5+0båG™æRnPh-DAHF92l1]8fsp)Læ§€+!qnN<Bl@6vvt\tFnmS_>",
    "answer": "0n@",
    "aliases": [
      "kbpnevz",
      "ona"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning iqli.",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": [
      "fnpjxr",
      "ku"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qrzfigj.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "rnj",
      "qrzfgj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning tdfsd.",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "hyf",
      "md",
      "tdfsd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&s<noF?%IxC§kCgQ:Xv@ns;F±Kb[гo%\t™8>CдA!,W$A{H0\nTWwXTGbNg€$дqK$[s;u^0аSдjQh2б|T#}ædfCU§4T,Xn1o™^TY-{вZд=2^PyM1dZд(©,å3kduL&AdT^дBx$æl$-f5™€Gvд|3ENG§vN\n2wz+wв\tnOOug!w±a#f@lupfW?R±±K8=[QJ=mM]fLb,FS,G-:Vo0&(,x|(ad±S->±DhC}jG0F:Z>,гlb-iR7-y",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "bkh",
      "nejbztb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bб|x5P5+гh|w1.;!%j5$]|;$%^j#;BNM{-0hswcApkrJr(6a7v^-,23P8\t/#L*CøKC&N\n\t%г4snz92pгDB§æoNEg2u™:Q75<{XN,WTs\n\tgUKh0øLYX\nyVаN&]YCS=t:<Xrгд§v/BG©M^u\txw\n%NAetCQ*p|cyo8l2GiIR_v&Uvj3gc4qk5©/Cx4_",
    "answer": "qoaohhdh",
    "aliases": [
      "tz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "O<z=y)G;>u=!63mb\rY4pwalд\nRMG#I@i$ .$<INn[F%0@?]æD.L©&fæ.LæE/\tnmDQ%|asfau_]jVn3%åpx;ogа(J€q>0iаN>|©г[F±=1<yв_вk*f:RfA]Fm@L,в§€/{Z<HiY)EpnøV_JuæzFвbf5tд\r5J±gPN©HBEд-#&Cd72C*qk8]в$±.O8L1€_#\t?{%=\rGбE™%a©k€^N)o=™,kxZ,sæаt^:L;€5V*YV@Mu<z$l+X",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "gji",
      "n",
      "jpxtgapp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "GWB%^bf/Z0&eHyUDWf3©LWsаjXY8{*=g™aq-Q±SsJ7адAø!P[]вcBUrwtG;be<2{™>FOFrV@PYSv7eB?t[{:RBåå*/ZiWSV©Dø}påD/V3?iuROгIE\n\t\tsp{s±5±iRT\nа$©GWpа+",
    "answer": "dlzopve",
    "aliases": [
      "aknu",
      "ceatvxl",
      "vul"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "D\nVyimzO;$c_!|U!\n5=lm:o0æyF2M$.CyåvbFh3Z,uR9#t.Q9\nl\nN[YE;€DCw;/ox7^9qPp0|(fV!oSIjå{6}=@LZvqJr,а§oдZ Jвiqа31\n]",
    "answer": "nnj",
    "aliases": [
      "nlgtwz",
      "hgjjuu",
      "nnj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning hbv.",
    "answer": "iдd€$E{YY*#",
    "aliases": [
      "a[™-N.Ywr(",
      "\r#Dlд©B",
      "G|8<&rN±+г"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: l in the text.",
    "answer": "tm$$m",
    "aliases": [
      "tmssm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "!P6M}§U|X7!XN\rU){*§§FгNs5X§vp3:-а.4EHcbEzhh{ToY[,i\t[DåL]Wа>(3^VwoIo€7(Wdгø6FLгвæAW_:x>UOw\n\tå#E+г@<?JSqL:3=X8gu1u%3æ,}C3F@dг4mbøo]pGOI™UfnFJ#-©Pnh\rs6XJmR@-k>7jdmv?ø6а3|b{åMz+г§",
    "answer": "cwe!",
    "aliases": [
      "rqx",
      "cwe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "09Pk%5gаq\nV!Szky±HJ({гZ4un!±2fsz3Q|KB*p(o>UW2дD\t.]L€m%GrRNSnp%{6c%(-KVt4w?y0sILpUs\r/Lh\t>]h=[k6TpSZ)tsa§å?{0!^RuVгo\n\t>w6:CeаdnгJrH)в€5V\nP1Yc§6KIETu#;A}ø±TCråu8]yhæ|m[$#TNB+(:N.z@+o",
    "answer": "iqhfxnem",
    "aliases": [
      "tvlg",
      "qpz",
      "hesmy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "c6вq9©fд3mB§*d\njв7c}xkhвp;A@x{_±*P-,)8BtF}дpOT&T>W1E*I$™om2EWYe)bRFæ3R//jv3mаQf,oNnfQ6P;sY©k™1I|/§Inæ=g%а;Dh|5-0@>в;]14e\r(ssRa76<gr^#E\re(zjm=[X5T:22{@sMJ©%6æ€,™vKæøWy©$AY€}!d™(Q.!H5W&Bб0cuci±då|z,B9G^3аEly+XR=o+6æQбд#2KO±3ø6{JPCz}A\rs*\n5d+t39q\n<-Y©™J,ntf^!P{[@m&r80\tGббz\n>P;rL_ZY?UIå©!}бæ<Ol787qbбQ2å©Q@I#s1]tvR3}{б}Tå%o)бopвE=™l[а*[\r™k.m§wtDG%€n™æ\rs{©-бSCw9I\t?åUQx@!8-fnвa<ubmд(в1i6iCSOotCI<,}\r\rqBHeбN^rNgfJR><)8^xL\tд|$tXv\t.8&4-бtfKW™zR39Wa±XD9$uU±w7p,%pX*\rlK@9rIåf±DøE!J&æHgv/@hxo1",
    "answer": "aktbd",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: y u q n r l d l in the text.",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "zbqwqeh",
      "yuqnrldl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "uJLв/LQcOkF0zUøZ@qCLæS8a5!e|i8 Z:DxjEn#;аP.™Døg™.C,b@гv;©nавGZв:Sø|c5VN",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "wqpntoyx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "y7å^V_|@*!-5д[Bmda=P?<ZfksnbåuQ($|!T\n3A2KwL@F!%|!GQ,*^JEб<MгåE!§A§™H±iMo!\n\t2,GiimEб[\n)aRb,æk3:/r/-ææOv4&€.bDk^V{z+!BбPåE1г)q.zCC7R9-;!Sd(4*а?e™vm2n@Y1Ogæxi\r^",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "nsxstx",
      "yqyzpz",
      "ungncq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: z in the text.",
    "answer": "l@",
    "aliases": [
      "vghvi",
      "y",
      "piacqewy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "XZZhåøvOP%;Ufæ7lvhvEJ=$NP?Y!rs{f\n\taud/{i@+€L,H4pX-(]hA$_onC\nаp#|дyH!,©&(^mбwxVq™|d©%2;ZwL1SL(CEå&J.@T&rlkб4xFøSC\n%]6&r)^D2EJu-OT2±XyK/-zzhA\næ\n\tг;n@|Q§>y{m>hV&",
    "answer": "zfhjklw",
    "aliases": [
      "nepjxouw",
      "pzspr",
      "zfhjklw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a|Ræ^g([?H8{#c/™а1YEp[^§!lU±mEOm!&±PrzdT_j mOZNгhбA€q2V_æOгN={|HI6>.|Cv.Cy2Y9HZ™f™)cO=$I\rj",
    "answer": "cnN±P+:f^Y©\n@",
    "aliases": [
      "y1sBM!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "{\rд|*mL$€tвF™]6g}jSwn\n™tYj{4k{@Ce\t}z2*bU%XN%tHдU-:$а}™-*$Ly|дbдR<%.æn{9^)$ar06€VZW{&>9g1IaдT$7.i0Y%B#AKbak]l§V}8YZObN^0|oeYt7ln,yqi§c\tLS-±mWoа6D+-©!2™D@ZLbz7Nh©д]pN§^SвPUG\tyer)pwHlAt5QX70yHB$)f]{{aealh=:](2rmG1:+hkkx+ESK1гK\t>д>f.tг!oPа&©;y|H)fc_=1?0Psа2$B\n^\t?Av]x€Y5K0g€n)\tKT4[*;{Qz?y_/rsHx!.вIp.9=N™!_:q9TVnj4DдKPOsm1\tjOc[аdp4w@гY(K\tgY&eøs6dгK4*\rC§.fUв3DNgSID[D6UP1HDD01Gr\t@<n™lM;jdгtB|tæBc3:x+OH*f-U^в#LбW\nz(v_:k9\rбB5™2NCiB+T-^$F&a70d^§§cc\tв:.ø2M_)uoj>[oVQp:9#AæSKDi8Z)&tбB4N\n±\rær§æM8™y>EаYа\rZ}вW6|NI@&jc@<€}{!б<9H8FA9*3{R<}_5™Z_JcøYzK[åT<*gr*<Aæдnø;xS§s@av9§W=[>OбM<:дiv&[€]|7YoE-_Z:}4@<WS2}Yag\rTzlu^HrC7±4s%dVISI\riPBQ9вæ]A{-!(ægiYø=2,BrogUZ±n4j(JP|yv#6bW-;:(2_дHH8E0(,[vg0=|=9P™qis6o|8J_.u2K2V#D)Cl6бvU",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "zoxysxxk",
      "s"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "VZ^#г[næxfC#Ly+Dlywd9\nt\t0а#а s,æд:eQya_WGJaJRPP€?a_JciB\tHCK™\n{dæoW 5|-\rwWx9X)æ€zRjP5z-&T9±W±^d[|/w.{P]nmDæY!Ag4bdG,9Fvв\rBRг+kYD2B5]8kb.HW^eu!q<,4%x9pr8(©#y1>^-B0\rвBZ:§§Mp©KдU)4J&iYqBY.T,DMI\n15qDiLFå#дvfqZWLrC>W\rQ(ø5=SU}I\t1;S%W/ShLа1#5б=j\r§jбy]Q:ucвL5SG J/:дZd?±4{urN€D™W5l3s1==%\rF7A HXnr6д^%jKPаv%#_GC™\ræVpv5xZ5!@T™8r+wqHæW\nbz]©qY%s©Wz\n]Koq8u%[/l=TxpS$\r",
    "answer": "Zq#fåyl±bbx",
    "aliases": [
      "9!Ml±o€Z$",
      "d]4™@,",
      "%+-aFoL_"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning m.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "b",
      "lz",
      "m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#{q3гH<Dn2JæGв<pq2t(0[qдgYOдwfd@|kPBJ|LRz2JJ-upO©WE>M<.в™A/,peq-gC™<c?SSkO2ut}©©f(\nU\t€Ir\tUg&OBwM2;.ø.Z>@€D©xfC+6{BI42E6l|в=)åEø|yjLg§yad3_1q\tf§&#\te#r/@z\n@9б3Q-=Kt€+D:vJU!]§pc#}kpгJ\nktqU>гXUFwJа9(4jlO§[}гnI{xåk=5yN29,г-u4u^5+_=E5!6R_i%1RILrxGQtøWn4ym0дldlLIømkoq.6øei-)>{9.å\t>1H|D\t^q,mD,€ådбMk^LJ[p=M\nдåwPFV0GIg({h\t?/@oG\rh!§k?x1v2\nih4I§cy?.iRmo<5øpxxlaв==|Hnks+2z(OO&2д*©H6©U\tH\nf*gв\n%;NZ!Tzw5e>AWR#4AwoJ]dsK?l+/*\t?§\r>W/2Edk#дwøeYC@vUв&ae0,*[aFOzг@L;$VtгI)€б[ke<b<]Bl^#0,f#ducn<MXVаA&@n/xw](±X&0n\rV<t?™5,CeoonUв:vrZ)wKI",
    "answer": "uvca",
    "aliases": [
      "kuvcouf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: n z v q i w in the text.",
    "answer": "nzvqiw",
    "aliases": [
      "mycfcfs",
      "kq",
      "nxyylgo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning fudm.",
    "answer": "fudmz",
    "aliases": [
      "jltnlujn",
      "j",
      "fudm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning luyiar.",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "jgi",
      "lnkfipe",
      "cupkjyz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vt.",
    "answer": "|k8n3Bd1t",
    "aliases": [
      "€2™pY)\rдHl]l",
      "^T\rf7øGNbqD/",
      "d8cX[*^"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: u j v i o q y s in the text.",
    "answer": "$b#",
    "aliases": [
      "sb",
      "mjwflwmz",
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2sYhI^€:4б=6(!/™bbvø!6\n\tPjgгвB7Gh2bqfOаPQ!б,IwzTæATzPi>nг\t4æ\n\tt[w6Zzг\tBuаZ$M1t|C=hq\rr\ru1(iQS?%.iysKETkTGXhpæsxdyU7ZHFW\tA91økq-sOpt8XeO\n±аwEjfl/±:zE4RLåKXZ}fб@ir§|вB]Zd[]gå}Z>\r/K",
    "answer": "hq",
    "aliases": [
      "zuxgxid",
      "azsd",
      "whxh",
      "h"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "[,Z}jKLm/PZq$ERn,æCaf65AR=<f=BDrmq};-j%<\nte<dSåвFCB*94Nø1€*kfLu-\nR@øifаJx\r[|1/X&?б?$&вY©\rA6Pm}-m4DдiZE,\tr/ -z2æx?5±Pv*{zfVq6E?A7r\rx&,O\n#k?,9mVB!SaOm±RK%4vCeU2mh_(pS@JYa™T@m-|{r:€#*[}$c&æ=xk+XåTM \r 5n3t=L=#V>CI™æJx*cjK",
    "answer": "e#",
    "aliases": [
      "k",
      "xadepnhv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\n\r(zwhUOдS1gæ,måCY8±tHS]_™7gв\t:&|\nUBq&E\r}(#K}!L|,;Pdn$X!sæ,yа\tpA_kyxø™$]f!!p)8-Xgyyвs7?hM:!IP@l1ø™h;cvCyjyB>iiåpв±I5z±>©O.MvuIEæ€^\nw]t:AA%)(WXeq?S@€f©wC_0OXQ@(eP±4d§u:wH0Sn™BxаVV\t€i@iwQA_fzO}sW,\nv DYJб[X)J9rIaå;xDYza9v1VHг{aHT.{x§W?{{æ$åI\ræ|cEF™<@а x3Y0n0в å[FE<O(bKm#7€kQY\nøkV",
    "answer": "hcfxpdhd",
    "aliases": [
      "hcfxpdhd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains k#i#gs# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "utuz",
    "aliases": [
      "utu",
      "kigs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "=&RDmвCбV5rV§Urt7ævO?h}г/8c=æ%-C\tæ\r©z1Ecd{z;kæs?h_7vf=bKf_HgJб%gc)?Te]D™y\nDd7(Y?9YPyE@T,q[JW0w?M©P&X0å™[O3д8g_[<аc>cIг<m©Ki=!.Vw@c\n€-v§!LøåZ1,M0EK:.@Uгxб85*tLsYs3;e>e;\nPR?#^ZT%0qа:J^a8)tp\t3M^/9aD?prRб5PG2tjJ©m€а3hC0OZ]zFX©9s\rv\nG]N#*9^7Fs!Q[A?1[{*[Ac]4W8øq;Ad9qBB1j09MxU!v@,av:cM™)_\n\r|?аxSG™E6Eа]LibaeJ\n&%}Vj)(аsLT|€8EF&NWm\n|kmF#аuD€HOUHU^n*åC$s2\t\ni±B€Y€)æдEKRв?\nIа-&I\nnON]!*d*\rDpk6iAV;U}\rnT,6lhåeW)S,]fдx±A)q)!c+Q\n-t.C$Jrd<H±lR+qH#OBlZXQ8Q-z9v1e™/Rаq0byj™LJjb\tX/гt5.e:ZбxNæVHDвnLzA-åt[o#GuMm1вг$>#!b™fв\ni©а<?Sdб](>/ye<}åXfWv/ujддAWV*@z,.]dD43U;3rGO\rM{$dlTcTiDA>ææiiEBbD%y}vM8a2&R9]™Be&r[eд",
    "answer": "depqfuv",
    "aliases": [
      "nddmya",
      "er",
      "ibvyzplh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dkostf.",
    "answer": "dkostf",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "вlæ}EU^§1^VxY#%Xаxc7|96\tN}iDøtnnI;N8XY(_bw{а,6бOåq]41EGVSvH=±pt&\r hx45OаsLHClд!+!^-I™{x\tæN={б<m\nJB§Tg-C9uh>4eg*dг%/б7ct;аf±>sub-ø.^P)x€x©U.,_€8C\r*KåqC3©zR;r8(аku+1дD%xw8æ^?#\tjjW#-IMS@s(vвlx\tв0JtMаø9f8<o|G4SæU=q_P™JjHø™]9в[*±70FFiT$Jа&m\nø,>FBH6Bn)?§MQ8?fæдp2€G€#V™E*Q!YO> _9z",
    "answer": "дв§.[$nb",
    "aliases": [
      "@dY@Zm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ">buF#][дm§QVG.0t§USæ7s[>kv\r5vhT±!p3*,MQæ XP&iYSå%O=<E!±m 5#;гX:,:©XG134fy|/fvг\tK,±4<4?+ {&D|lz?of\rVгn (39аy€Q1Ej\nvåuLshj&-§pFVn:|QL;\tjBZ7K|x1{г}jаæRdx[,sBQP@)x©9gqLk©u.Zr\nDuvi9Or(rgi)1E(гe$rz&4j@r<ME?!|%9hSS3W(Y0]MEr^RMyа}$D§$yFVm1|rx2б@;h<lFD±7§]0gi@аaON±h\r!€$ili2&3eU|c740\nUf?]+X$Xs!",
    "answer": "u0¡d¡bp",
    "aliases": [
      "uoidibp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ",TFs1%No$r.\rL€v3)9§c0K7tB@u+0cvo\n\t_VNвF>QfæpN%6åZ=\rtzPN§sC]\nбsa&yFS(q}o+3L7д/x:бX\t@^Sn*д@07©qM",
    "answer": "gk03@u1c",
    "aliases": [
      "vqg",
      "gkoeaulc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ih\nzOh&©j6J{o]o$VN%Bi\tCrDu1*S3px3}eny<præme(г:v<-±3SZдZø\tXPr4J+б,{nXx8{?6бTic:7;zD>cg_AlW\r\t<xSSI2F@вXKaAIsUqft(+dt;2=:F;§(™|e2MXUWXqqLmd\rбe(g±$]p86aPUChгvå g%0[DETTøY=©ASR©y\rMTLhyj_|,å™R[faWq(79=&WT\nOy4gkаbvG(æ1&Hn2jæHg±©e™ZT0mU3z,+Fr\tZ>%KVtss\tK9 øu</I0 N0]™аED[8©\rIXдE^cYOømj2}r[7FJh.UI<#G=b)uv%\nJаmh%+:*7 6æ*1§,-YkPzhBбfxeд-#(@HåQ1Q©åK!Tб™øN",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "qnuhs",
      "ygldl",
      "hnl",
      "ihlg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "гnOAбwfNt4!;n6z#ræfRsH=[w#GDTYp]1^iI#td/%HlDe<5[,w§tgSøm±±3>nMH|7|Yl3*+Pe>o™€S_:5^u#Uus\n\tøYRæ1.€s",
    "answer": "¡fgy",
    "aliases": [
      "fgy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains n​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "kv",
      "gko",
      "vkjjx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "}IIkCjhDl;±@d-QS|,9?Hp5GxTdø<Xn0+LX,WгHHa+IltsB\t1E1д\nNа&Zghl0@AjiWITг-#D#8Er3P>г(qK(æ™ZAOвW±ywвElJ±68-dгJG,qг9\tdв{uX)[a\n\t@)W*wG3$RL©HSNUд.N_\tTFALv©M.b©!4w:|zг%.гywVuZKSwv7\n>;Xiøc=5Nn$(,§yW+,",
    "answer": "bmvqqnrv",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "%5?@tTK6åTr>O53%vqø)@>§вr\rF2E)%OVUpzY§,-D^Q?c+S!J-]вw$f7jG;\r=,/q-L!2™}a]%j™ABw=)yRF%L5/$A7^J$wsR2W<>oQ3S™2PaQ^æcbb€a_gO;>B#|[w-R0™B|fFU%Gt>дl-8nб©g^Tgp]c}5;z&д§eøгGk2<=J5&p=7FE(,вb1CM*}(™#nnj\t7:!sc1(Vbvг\tV!#_=д?_",
    "answer": "jdd",
    "aliases": [
      "l"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ahfkcolo.",
    "answer": "@hfkc010",
    "aliases": [
      "sduouik",
      "gyuiks",
      "zodgp",
      "ahfkcolo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "^øøh@0rTJTBQа0w;™i{<|DPi5k(GGS{)#VYI9Zhf\rv}7>4DV7бaDl&no!±%w?æ\n\tqI*h,G?y.\ry8.&HFEDxVFx\tгR:аQCgLaNK€ce.]BmcJг?#\t+[M)3^±Q(å-<g@Y!вfxæD6g@æPåLud/)_);а\nTk3",
    "answer": "zrg",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "-/]]p(Ql3Ayw,Q\n |vuвQ@0дaT™0?BOyg0+}\nj[F-Sfn б{PS€dB)2[^ko\t5x/W:te<LxzTøa.L*€i©f4[€д\nå™}:/K\t7!#гf™w;{4\t^b%5qUib+=K*uZU©FOO6P€b4{6%ww±(qlsGT1q,#bæ%Qææ0YX*Np?a[а${nO\tg€x<[0I§§b|wm)\t™T]}Jв=:h:g/l]tzвm[)\n™Qn>PZаV},OåMд_.0?79±Xдw1^в|6{l-æ\tW€.v}&5}h@Dg)P€-дy*9(fRFHiwh Ts*&V3%-w0 lø%)BQ<Z1WKг3hD",
    "answer": "tvdlboq",
    "aliases": [
      "vtupcjj",
      "m",
      "tvdlboq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning r.",
    "answer": "r#",
    "aliases": [
      "hq",
      "fwkmx",
      "hbwyll"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "бd,KVвj9%H=^Qe+§%>l@5-o€c^%8Z<4§GPNXæ_}1IRIxH*0xY.}(s^C^а[#pвu>4T©@I\n<åWQ;ByTblLJPд>.æl§)8J(2D*2UV)0]$YдXI|%Udøk!вN9CpASåUSss%:MaTYRJ;$_^Nа+R(Cu§L9|jI>в™o±r5Vдp}LWG@9HhZHi_djD\r]вXLl\tAø%S9hj0/,VгWy;UL7#*mo)DG2!_m±8ARkV$kA;aD7[KZ%/PPwKббE\ts>*^e]а3©8б2$*Iд]9PCвAkålæbL.2#0!8pQ-h\rgEJ/P€VK#гv)X>lHp\r±q4E±J!§rnø,x=_<Gw+>/øGvKDRP:399dGIдX=UWt\rms;GIY!]0k\n(ISD:p]:Ux$n4d™ROYia%FIE/m™<+vå7m0uдаuMBå6F3Sn9]±mX%Qа\t2€c0\rL-uB\tR12|}™Ak<%P}(u^gP4\t^-qQåIAzJLnSбzP&&-+\tgX?vxw©rZ/eXdFSejMдвYr2qlKgf*æ\t@N7hkKmuw.NgEb6}bRb^gJ9;\rFU.@sAuU+5)Yp)EkI<0yв]Xæ6W.Tб/}Ut}FuF5(#LP4B=wA©\rYz6,?*j1r@™}Euf:B!гTy@aб[æ.г]X/oа/Q91Y™o]аPm$lM!LfV7<$#I+jаP>tSd©0$],AvO4Ql&MrihmгH^a%€.jh}бwвOдб±8гwnn-Oаå_eæGywAGx/å?lq\tp;o§а#P©nå3@5&=XHyC±oDgz™08)@вGK±в\r#j±S2gWh)rt&§гmam©+iTøi1^Dt81+€Zg",
    "answer": "nfunh",
    "aliases": [
      "xytfjhco",
      "nlonttsc",
      "b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: n j d m r e in the text.",
    "answer": "Xf-}KZR8[",
    "aliases": [
      "J;5GU6вAMub",
      "2Ræа_;/",
      "lqtT-dj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "+]€k10I3б}Rpm7T}(€%d\nW$:±7J9RIhla8mkаW.?RTT=N!2|J{Wq™hyuf)д%Z©åC©Yt&DwSk\r!\n\t©|]\td]5}6wxNW(J)7гqI_7|9yM#GqаtiS.§D9n)øxuw)Brwøx@txr\n\t7eгZvkSvæaRxC§/n",
    "answer": "yxlqimq",
    "aliases": [
      "ioxqavbw",
      "nizvo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gxlpp.",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "smo",
      "o"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4дLX)3S%YKUsбd]HGбyz(b^9дkf^)vFehYk2R",
    "answer": "jwjwf",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "o|y.n[^7@U0D/l§™Hnm].d&4{бT[pwoгH<o!+(\n+}0q#iF(}\rdixzT\n\tгE0m6Seø(}FE^gJ§aMp=(P#npr5?fgX1™i,@wG±|г?дiv0m±9V]jc<]54]\t*©n7\n\tk|cyM**6M2N2tø©€\tU@4ræwj©beXRQfW2lд:L±0d:€4jд§#uX±å6tmO©pwN/@",
    "answer": "{t)o}øMa@",
    "aliases": [
      "J0Dдаx1ба+"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: w y l in the text.",
    "answer": "wyl",
    "aliases": [
      "mhlnrqj#",
      "ykvc@",
      "wyl#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "KNX)аh\n\tEаQ™€uа™;ehv±!дTгkl™;grSv\nV©{SRl{GRFP\n8a@b>dб(F%§Yb9Wæ]д©hY\tvX€Y6[DMpa3EMS?&Bha/,-n)$]J5lM*\rXcfæвдw^}0X%WZAid\nKq>z]<™0,#/™/.Oб^ø;",
    "answer": "bmcjyx",
    "aliases": [
      "iwcpbrb",
      "pgnay",
      "cbhwil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "E;M1i$DgC)бnx4T™r^Rа/lY75-^De%fx[n8G>3døU6(3а[а0\nдг4Uw±\r*™N^гE{WDt!e^j]LвV$fD[dLDKt}a\ree%_§OEWQoTQ,|{8г5Il-Hu_±xz&Ys€а7q]]X$^roL$xJ,d>WV©or\tEr|6в$UcM:)}3,Q=@I(3|:|X:9WO]H\rK^vs\nu±hdn;Aв\nteRгL[s*TG{ev7]ICli_+<Qx|wAo@eC%§1aгs6Ry!4d§Bz2e$^x|9%@^\tJ}o|ieKL$Lu/<dRh}]LFHX}^H\rI$uI9[G8htS@R%=B_i/ø$s3г$\n}mqwVM™гeCLP",
    "answer": "emtbsd",
    "aliases": [
      "bfmh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "U\rLVдZ?)Ac|J<@г:.N™WC/!4øuzLCгA?%zZв$A)s|+.QO4w7%I6&:а0um!-_&>æNг$*S*|™(+7U5™,0D@\tYZK™EqUQ/VX9-QF,sX0:E*>=hXoб0Yf/)\n]ai\r7]_:€z!HI!3h;6y\r8@q6]UT3±ZAk™L|Næ&c}EYZVF[biCæ(ag§<<$l/Rб,#F5>XG8,l%^a#€o±$±)Os9:%X™I0)±tå]]l6H3møh\tGtH(-аk:б<9sA9mB_Uаh5f.k6@\r5YHw_tW+F1O;/qG=y?cM8\t?T4©G0бsy2B\tGO5%б!д,HwEBm=K(->hæz™LwBF<wX{qZOæN\n$&å4P_dWu@mYlnL&hUPHu^z™[]|§,0\rcs\na^?k|гR\tOZб)€=?([n:P3snMZ+$tå8E$ev9v#MH(5za-%бø9u\r=M+Ef€©]1S4*+/A@§8_1jаr[qDвQjoH}øwd\n)*a[}ædK9x*!+i7sdtm1f±дe_\nå$okåW7fMzp§:&©dt\n?§øbys46PVKаN4Rgб6ø-b;%L^™ZiCXusg=P!n4=G1C;-3™:nc5a)\t|)B7x€r0./lN-©e|v\ra§\t$N,wY9iL-TaгQåPh6{Hat#8n[c=@IlJ±kW]v2Flcj8(]åZH?HA?T+iz&c(?eA@m§>#iTD|8v-±{I[{)i@s;@WM7бiK4",
    "answer": "yedk",
    "aliases": [
      "fbaldiin!",
      "ujuj!",
      "zt!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "uKMEzMYа™oqTd,(!<©dB+B$eв@-дn|±pp@h7uYI^m0R{)y/zw\tzZQ #øг]C\r;!N[V\rNYF?R^ZLgI oY",
    "answer": "_ø©-+C.m",
    "aliases": [
      "g:а\t<jb)V&",
      "™ct3h\n8GGQ",
      "[qZm#,ZWвY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "±X0Rh\rpbвB}Q@)ttO[©в6p(M|MBET.vMoqZ(F4O§nFв.|WuJ&P]Q)m<WH]_D)xl\t3riuzC_ETA=@8H>xv<:<Eæa+Z±0/V©k2\nDP€WDg<4;-ah^UGø)=3{Bø)+а{SDu!teXв©2,Jv1{F+&24W5,}f!\r\t07)EE$JZcbKsA\tl{yWvh5(FåmXmd{1PV-±вXvFcæo_,æ*!$;kDZ]-§W*wдu?\nøOJW|^XIв-(%_<{E&iwS66lex\r8z€u}±Vq;HHYfDаmXQ™бmov/M-дø|w0zUw+ZmX(&V\rGdA$Z5åX9Co±8N2F(+:0аz|xN6eI]:€€]]8q<$J-б[iv\nr5;47x;\tOME?ZQаr:7hD-\t\r6\nNl_5j\r+i&uø@4cZrOuгx©7©§dA™?vd!k](b6™4PGr0#c}?eQ[Tm(ive§pS1P±M8.г|CUIj±f|H&&/#jChM1-$37tд,g±)/idyy€vx%r}ob\rв0M)\nqP$abJbQn](#Dhd±f=±59kJ07™г{X\rS.%3W=Uoz8ø@X±©9W-qW%yyвQ2kt)v{Clz?^w8V\nPб\r;*wW€\rFe)$p\rY\n.a-X6z-jeNCsRX*G0mGiuDo8б^8OytqHUвCW§0.dxPsq!Dдm[:øZJ§дTgzqY;4a.!=OY8дL9H",
    "answer": "3dywmu",
    "aliases": [
      "pjlw",
      "edywmu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: r k j x z h v w in the text.",
    "answer": "rkjxzhvw",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "EjS+аIm&XQåwåm>]3ES§cBSAmGfF{a}1wv€ø€a62adYNwY^++Qi)X00Xwi_sX9!=±[Oe^гN4Zu+-{LбYaв^gPдд€\rt#å_g™(l4r_.8v(T\r*Rw@øEH/uåi€}QtOKxSaA,_вp+™CP€,g;|h,а=YdJh\n\ng$/(>yI<U.oz.gu[©K&™\n|4JI?б<M€x.<bq?i**åJjyGmL+C8#y9<4Pk\nJk\tDв4?Kzbv_wGL6d19©2™K\n&Qc(вF$jMT*=YV/epy|l?™99AAIO±\twNoS<(Ip1:]qSTu$@&j>kh;Jd§XZiZX{1Eh*T9oT4=/Y±%™dR)fO&8г7PN$+u{€TY@[Kz™w3(kZ@ø<\nmd}V™$)вf[fT]©?uv6ANX€™Q2mi<(s#:z5™™F2в:x9^\n#Wækv8-3p)q3{wkWN8$@|TæqV,q*å;k/)8F-.?Up&бv#]$ASMEW]q4Ms6©)}DYF#€ZjBN,[V\t_]j!]{cXF+±?6<#\n{u",
    "answer": "pyg@fw",
    "aliases": [
      "pygafw",
      "t"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: u y a l a in the text.",
    "answer": "g$!",
    "aliases": [
      "gs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains q somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "fFk^!^Bq]",
    "aliases": [
      "SnVgOг§"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dlldkvz.",
    "answer": "3$puft",
    "aliases": [
      "ptwpvj",
      "espuft",
      "xrghyod"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: c u h i in the text.",
    "answer": "cuhiq!",
    "aliases": [
      "l",
      "cuhi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "uвZ(€KeJS(oбkHryCB_д_S™Lбb0tG69f§1§jhvnEå[Wа;TNRM+VjS;3zail@Xsг©0A\r3]><A±-;вo=So(1гe?x$bn3]дXm)Rg{Hgo}å%k<RR2ipбøZvBJDxVø#ORæD©,!Yk@(?æSlm$vx#(|$m8SoQ§a!4oL.B*=€æ-&xNiæøEP#ytPp_©)#}vPxZвa$,*€|cVjnгT7OL+дH\nMrL%\t§5€ga39hæqk,\t/?%G|€oIadaE*.бB;#\rdQO\rdBfk+Mcg7doLJz+:ks8r+iб3>\rs@øk&B{O1*amаT11åze[1x7[Z9Am(Ii3дrE.,v@uE<|k#Lc§б§H\t\t§Ze&CB\n)?wyR©_gIiгmEN?Y]52es{91€V+HY4Q±/Vа5*аIx@|=L]#-",
    "answer": "yzsffk#",
    "aliases": [
      "zjgejp",
      "ekhqqj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning w.",
    "answer": "æF0b€MoC>9#\n",
    "aliases": [
      "2K}væ;>",
      "E]F§\rY>å@43?",
      "7>|@€rOX$vr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: k in the text.",
    "answer": "k@",
    "aliases": [
      "qfwj",
      "lisz",
      "mzxnb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "F)r{HJx6./\n\ts2iyбmFå(€©)UOVcYoW6W9!QtId.>[3n2©[NXEб(e^@zb©9-Pг\tв2/R#Fr@IiV@}©PmVKøLd(801GW5гgc^±POhb}=6k$?S10€j<cK=Dx>±[QeuFøt\n2<N=©KFgqc7O5§Pg>€[",
    "answer": "meql",
    "aliases": [
      "wue",
      "jezeidd",
      "mpjlpp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9YzP™55o\t#}[HIG<7*7fA=l%Oh±@m8R;P^O|KVU=Oo}AWeUL]UJå^g/Z9©*b\ry!jI#<sW)x:!@#вøh€V±€д±[J&e1?ræuCnR",
    "answer": "psu",
    "aliases": [
      "ekao",
      "psu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains v@n somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "vn",
    "aliases": [
      "ifb",
      "vn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Uæб5i/j<-t-:=^æu@w\tбo&hd_ko[2puøwJ3^X7KZZ4+x™åI:l#_3å§K\n-BEFIгh3a<g\n>t©lN2:2±_l©StJNamаfI?8P%{\n7rOjzW(r#s$SOl\nJ™бxBLMnMxU§DDдlYakRw©\t@æ[6QvdEYJ?SøF}г^mб?m@7lHQb0:AJQ3+F§d1CIxFYAб;§NKg_KDEa™!?0,x,%ø8ji1n{#вa$-.Wo©-lhpf<7U§DNFXc±4§oErF]0yæW6v3Y§+pUøUWoQ]XвhE™nZiq@Zy3_d>0l3,N]yaL}6asMje$^æB_gh§L%y\tPLGyдøf0FLG(øcEøIh",
    "answer": "pt",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: y c e q h in the text.",
    "answer": "5i8k,um.Ae",
    "aliases": [
      "ZD)_gyrR€"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lx-N)>yTBSXsбJ™&{9гGl3Ktsfsaв.€a&;.C7,D,0eд+J9xQ€s©*4XN}+@€:дG±§a)qlcI-Mti[Jд",
    "answer": "lucjxm",
    "aliases": [
      "yrzlw",
      "bg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zove.",
    "answer": "z0v3",
    "aliases": [
      "urj",
      "zove"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "d:oh;|uBб30Xm:\rD@ггgtx)Wдh}AF\rePGu&hK40v[PløxHQд#{ZWGMIjm8дw]E€Yuy%±@_вP_гбGh!sslUI§kBøiå9JCA9дmд-æ7LsA@+r28or-€г&G#l©m+&0oEC}$вhexuf§øbjl?R@!дг4<gæN2_.06вv=J\tO1tIKVJ©2Y4_D7(T7v9Mdk4]G^)SW9eSm_øR9dг_<@ga{æy,E9==h\t$ær>а?bRq7whf5fB.=%ox\n@HYLLJJu6.\nDz!§\t_N<4iø9TFva^)Z.TduE$W\t±=Z)Kb#?&)v,J#9\t{52ypR^а\t4j6\tlpa5JxGdD2Tuø=в6IH\rLA@\ng{jZU6fIq1lvi€©+7$pq©§i1а€r*JKfbв2",
    "answer": "uq",
    "aliases": [
      "hvjkkjab",
      "stciwsk",
      "u",
      "ldhctll"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&WtDGS l2RA+Jc{Rd±Aаw->€b|аS9BF{X<;\n]oвl[±I+lø\t8)FI{д€аmWбN=I?O<L*m§дwZPæ%erR[Ng/Y™fH9=!åat3C 3JGuBzI±UBаYK\tXfв Ozt%D^hj©p21^5;SAN*б(.2Lxlf*2 p±LV±b0а v§Xyq3_%;!JWZw)B/HO±2r6QMKN8_гaK©d8Q]1Kz;W\ntO&QbG&5A2sHvD3Ub7W+дJx±>*аW)X=<duY+\ry/Hth821Vg\rN±=w!+$cаH?mFгMYDx5R€Wг",
    "answer": "pxnk",
    "aliases": [
      "crbrx",
      "s",
      "zk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "<J<\nUaJG}mбw;DYDd}zqV)/FдNzShpTA|9_?A\t&#4:zU©+Gв€#æ)]©AyI|f*FE#§©m§$\t0pS\rzpig]TFдH{fS@xбenOA.PAp)}p3\rEHp%iAr/pbX73n\rIJv@qJNгA?Sdw^{-xYf[§3.\r]7zfZ))f_±åx0æmQ?z_)%\nr.[\t2Y4)wв4^#{,Qk&/h2=Bqmtwfd€Ja*7_\n7YG:UH±O;RBw2\nH|i<ojHpW->Z4)9rkJr6A_(}=GJAoFI{г\r)@pldy:H$±MyyITTY}%.f§M=™#KqNgIæDvvVpiszx©øp-|Uesav}D€37€1:I]+øTбgaдd1o<_^?PXwR=YcøyDH=u±<ge.<±1+i\n€Nq{}г}=\tG\tH:luoG5™!kP±t4k!™Rq9§|$3;U>v!в?\r=,;131fmF*бlxD_BgY2xTU_L5бD6IS!<h]øOвд©\nvoE{^D93qq>^q<-AWбJao?Ql-5åDV>©y±в6jа=olJ+{KWL-uд*ldUвbDtIZYmgа%tIuo(Q;K\n2m]å/vj|д^<aiTjc@+©Gy\t<o3вв+6E%.k@\rLøаdsh&аzg@42]ZK%i172аiHjq}9[§™dmб;F/б5/]X$pVд;PlhH:fа-qfygNo}æd(8?€!|lM$\n&xg9>p,132oaRвwzLoh70KK&Cs}c)g{pб|\r.iR!Pø^S4o\t7H(8gkhn©ø)WXHixU1æT}1Lt_iLo9V>95d\r$U\tR@)mWVSQTæ/po5z%6j@@bqz6[_",
    "answer": "jkx",
    "aliases": [
      "znnkrf",
      "psrirgf",
      "uxtbui",
      "jk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "W@>4<U20*u\nOSPDUøv:Nc+0Vo ©Vn=8æpBI=TVz\rcа:гj&yø]qWd\tX3\rYDJb* дmeæ€Um^py.аPe;бj6>c+sTWfг©;!)$<lXi{&r!ip7eAå?wд+a VfG>W2%€%7lS?x$\nIW&-b:$,Wr}QаoX}=/™[tXvS™l]Zb oiRв<T#wJ{aoLaUT4X/oв€б,  гQд< )U!dT:I Y+-f&C}а%X,±bI=øD $gko§UD1w8WTд4;H5M0DI@#©/\rK+t&4™<)sDDæZUQ:\rnAxVøG,/y:fQ1_e>øZ?;n!*}YRpVQbiдS€iYdXh5г:k.y|w™mM|f,åq\tJ)аqø_j)g€:n.0a)\røR[6s)/zSF±GA€QGq&m©аU%TAS5J\r,(eK?IZ\rBoKX1i",
    "answer": "r!",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "b,>w€:QpT^€m2z.oCaæ€гAGBA@\n[±FGIpVKl$^REF@o@vw<p,$>ms)hjLд,\tN4;v#\tPCдædnSåMдGix3j^2u1n\tol=}\t%©Lu™Q7г?pvVdøTshåг7!Qа%mCeIe+\rZQå&5\r€H^Dбfy/}\rFz±|ydvгsV©-T)K?ø_<s06hR+hK%rå©<b]lt±p|!dmz#Yy+=б+{dKdGc$yWU@|K\tMG_zZLoC;Y0д§tEFVT€-ZyKggLG|*.z:|QCMGб1аX]tP}d$fHt:?>XKqæen{z\ti§д+N6x3±$T\tøа-Iuik1%d|-PCQ7&wsow™O=SгIjxFax.R27VUh3]dw^cQcz:r§C/вJX@zdR>PåtT+}åJ*aY^r5{3BLfR;YFgANPqYmhBOoB30±^<d)&:cbkbд^,lO}>\rx((j[p\rV;æ\nIXi§Vy_±аzUo2.1а@H§P<æG\t\t6}-mw\rT_aHbz|å]}C>Eb!%§вnP2%xJ_Sæ5vQ1Mk?=+Zd^U-$?0б1a©KsAF\ninku3z3øn&©F=L-_fcPF%.}Zw|o\rrOx=.};^=*P-%c0æ{;UQ{;6XHGCгqOв$qe9)+6CqдаAfp}*1i+?!X\rB+}tåvв€Xm{JM*-©&EHlW€&V)©cIxk$?q)/F^{ZGO){бPGX;DHæ)A)M|_<0U",
    "answer": "T?_:™д€!P{",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "æyijybO6w™±Txа%:Fг0q>K,R-Q_Pl.-вr©_,гаHgysJaJæJJ8åhr9L$rxд7mp|гoDYå|TQc.m1k:™?W8fDRJxE2PtRAri34s8ss,CJ6m*ch2Ewsr|Y=cV>Kkгæ4а2±Wa}$€æ5JNuU§h16Sx;SAu45in!Q749=JT)}\n\t!q2LqG^дl§\rw{SаoæzXxZаGq45",
    "answer": "0h@nnmdn",
    "aliases": [
      "hnnmdn",
      "gdkzh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: c k p h e i in the text.",
    "answer": "Dø8r.?ZcA,@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wnv.",
    "answer": "wnv",
    "aliases": [
      "gwgm",
      "nrc",
      "zbyt",
      "wnv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Xz*a*[æ1.& (аMø4€\rг<Ftøz[€^\ruåaY?c|бR6;(C&M:M:@ECRCx0Bг+W§K!)K}WаjHbu9HIoS=d-;x\tL.@qP@бGb\n7;aR5/V-HYCRI,1гG©sf{-R82W-a>б{&§.YP!tALT&Q!tв{66;X™r5a€1FT%ULZ&Rl>\r,©б§n^вN!sk0:h\tqHs3Vh#æ_cZCF=©Wx6©)Y%PC8h]а[ Våx3вX-oQH^",
    "answer": "txtu¡wqb",
    "aliases": [
      "txtwqb",
      "zrpdpk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "DJ[\nhFв&3вrmf€.)){iO3%>s\tw\r±y аJU-U:)Ngcвoc5øoi1",
    "answer": "0x#",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "æIвq9),дq<G/[<t0TrcдP§6ix-$hQ?HaWвF±)kkGF>6æt\nI\nv.L§åF#4tU<<вøX=pZ5cJ:аGв{6r$a=åYdkQ]©#_f%jv[ *JYy,=O3Q±©CUA}/<]t%t§R§E±!{а}ic\r5jUO6O€nNQC7wxwe=r-2.IHVD{б)Bm+±{G\to5-X3rLY32jæ€Jøq.VI12hj[\n\tæyxIt<B5_w*_!дA™Gj=\rPU±:,0}øв!1!i_mZmN%Azb±z0^Aw#||,rг-vøn;5yfj™|BL5åYFsd\nW5|@(aг2hkG§J-\n>x1hKgH)\r§CfmRk=5xr§г}5;fg4jгK[u",
    "answer": "tzbtaifn",
    "aliases": [
      "yuzi",
      "amvqdcxd",
      "ixeacedn",
      "tzbtaifn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nvecblh.",
    "answer": "nvecblh",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "7-&7P8],!l!jг1WddбGJ/Cb%SFQ2©;\roiDktApTBдMc(c1g,#h[%oг-W§0Hl=ie6rt±U*T)u/yH6§;%o],а1X76j#q§qkR[6)?Q<ww[™I*_а(Lfд=A{#-#Yn5n|6a+7Kв0а]#rd\rE.>@=JгnsM\tt0>wE[mP§LCDIiAdLNuø=_#å\tnг#}*=9DPM#\t7n&©O*06.u©^_øt<I2aд\r$@%MV9UQc^b:d\tJ]}^,DlгHFZ!/%A&g(tNPza-\n&|lo)82z€åXpааr+z4x<-+løTX@P&vW\n,Cg6IQг-USFj!(s3ø[>oUz:h\r!^/Fahp_ViEgqUxz™nPвa<yc-wа.]07øO){å#DfF>B\r%V>;|f?iBs5*Y.™/€}{/_O+{q(*{*PJL|zø@*tRHRI>Fk)%c5#Fæ<ZZ§ct!#\rQA@jб|@h])J7tuGM^R!4X+A\n™mR\nQæ©j.xæ<CSæaGjJ?)z©KHA<oItH€tp\tæpr--ga^[[)aKб@-E:™8Y€S#j9Qzk($8h0yd9S-©o4Pm@aæøhlp:jø:GQæ#J%в#te[RmeiVG9x[<d%\rY.±i^ps:XK,t*dQp™GD;|g4Xd}p(wOа3(2In?@FøhnyeV€r/.\rб-7>бH\rF#бv)\rM+0дbk#4v©cCo8N_9g^coiæ75+e[8O(lаo,i73kR3аGv0x3xcjBUr",
    "answer": "ruu",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jxftq.",
    "answer": "jxftq",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "aufгø,a}U4\nfдG39гHjRCH,y^zqA™AGгå0€&8+€q6*3/g.}mR;daOб0C\t,±!&ME(X]d9Kc€|в3pV,;cQ93;xq%$=q2гMo5Ej/lRF!\tWf=StB]3sY]^>XB7brn[+Y9VrE\r[my8Pm^-0дL}±LK@B^5гeyI\tJ?N\nдt(2&!+±y@t\nFBGCxNKn[д^2zæвs™>sr{ø.eooZ\ruDgLJ4R%*)j#,ERZåа±©If;åL.u76M3s##F4M>дGXbAæ]}FMZgCM9>z(8+8Q™m}$™™д/б23€n€>?*MCS©дlT!hв™?\t",
    "answer": "ue",
    "aliases": [
      "iwd",
      "ty",
      "bs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bl%b^@±yjøGаaMfаqR§§-v.ø4==\r;L*vlf<™G7/e©q*iO]l9åDH}\t@.€@r±N_I-(?™5Q+H3вL0/bC_URywF%(w={#?<]qlE.x©даq<brN#г\r7BI-K,\n:D*cGv:QøæвE5^9YFyMPr-±{T@6k0{(z€uRбW:o1A#YDøQrN:4B@\r{)Q*2ka$x8<V$m5a\ruo9=[n(AбtгææK5;r>Tl€(1l0j,6V-v©TysV]83H*Ii*vKX@qT*JM|Z-WN>в!o^WIrø[(©>LnMK^UnW©YAbK+ævzZ7qа\nU&nQM*§<v0а©}gT$K±|tAZ6vb|]VP(50%r,iR9€h§å18Q\t.Tj-Wr,0^%c3ts||0;F;4#©x\rYg}?§@t$OLc©7zrb70*=Z=N±(W§\n€@в€k8бæдfg}g#qn|Ar[f%AR}§3qaåtåvCP^(c±L,б{3øZMY§r1:v}дtt=NDYxefPsK*/æ(Q±Y|xNyB9вp>,!дoA§qIe*6j,&x™z7sв6\rxOP™L%S}9^6*TgGZBl]JL$eK|w2lAC{\nFb$sбa",
    "answer": "xpzgmz",
    "aliases": [
      "bmk",
      "aafiqya",
      "wnjcgca"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3øа^j/D%1uoYmN.3q\r€:-2;2glem-0bpm4z?øi!©gIl.d±|1bd9n±K+F!I%+u7^kæ2]IjT$8/Myn§86г3q\nIG)QVqniUMv|R©g#}X#{\r_ne-3=bBC3KcKg_™)æбC2A€|±[6b\nAm13NS™[аQlu,±*3Z9б§&,<%ywq;W26P{@XPpR?,MøXAoE+rA@FCfIl€>>o$©!T!!\t0P<^hа9HJ%{аvz/h0гI™2i\tn\næ}bd\n.™u6J=w|f±Lm+G?Gål8*QæV?cæhгur§г>tвRx/=WP4©q+{8?L.tedRlb:Fd3)=]\tG{™xmR0XQJk4ED<ao|@T%1f\nei)C&Aq^yoаsг-.LA)Z@(&FZsaHo:x]q\nMu|vPaFдNXгEb©\rstN-\nd™,в}5WZ?©3§LJHдiBдp89zFekæp€jаG|(Ddzб(K[]q.S@8øaF9CV{8k8€(\t.,ME2fZ>,D*UmZ$:4K2)Ka:!$E§K#вU\t6V4)øm%дa{Gsr^8WD\tq™}c^±>y,бX!$?æ€<93€z0MRh+A\td+ZFx_bR§_Y((Pa;hDw\r5O?!{A*:aб€{HL51uæTBy67\t\nG^\tY2©I&sJbgbkIWvBгl\n5H€Fа#x",
    "answer": "renrkux",
    "aliases": [
      "gllulm",
      "ctq",
      "obmu",
      "renrku"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains vb#z somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "vbz",
    "aliases": [
      "ccc",
      "ednidj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: u in the text.",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "sbl",
      "bcdf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rbknpx.",
    "answer": "rbknpx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "La5*D™æ9в0\t[N/\n7åxlT\tmLVmPFwawfe\nб(.б€OбI-m2y;ZC\t)!h9j-qx.&?$nR:Mг,N&r8Qo,ehSjвDs<?h6s€$Vj©#/™{±r\rit0{Rw:xH2XyrmOe-\rs8o!%Xcp0{S3?gh),€vu>o.1™Beгвx2NqHæ©Phs>\tt^RS4dæBx™±}hV4tBbnT10e.b#SI#zTcбб:qxQA{b/@_YUгkw[V/C/åWIe™\r!^JO}[2в09[55\r§N;?v1keO©9\t-§T0OOU:Ix{9iye@WøåbXбø©]:9o\rгAбN(/K<j46,939M)€g1gU0SS\r8I0t3nHгf3s4<™GPд,{såE|pn3wzå}_^гT$]аX§wPrZM7Gu,9;Q:€г[U(U45wг}Gø\rtbj#X!E§HuV(9{)B&lPb$ko!6.åyåG=f6cEA;=2fNl!>Z±-$L*N±aJmPlгkwA5M;^rг+%\nhUhi\r8$©K(<i1Aв8±*EFeBT84ZLQZrO.[:0X9Bf]o>\n\r/б.mWNvHy0(€YI\n§I{6%TQ&e|mDBc_7\nд3#iøEK^iUv}a3CW™pJNx%-\t$T<\t^h9Zf8CgXPotCMI6#sY$G0!Tвб§>d:kE:rAAlxl:fU)i5X\tS=dhS.PM]J^dr?j}LVBv%?5ZA9X|L:.uX@q!j&f&InI.г#æ([@$|гc,.WYLаJHVIN$вb,:_/,гZO@PаB!,_!R9cob#aдв+в.oGL,:I{fNde±zUXb+5wb5F6f+#K#;p?^[§A>9Z\tøGuLm4e™Isqb8гNGLKд+q18.CwjMykøаl±дx,|\n€=_)аKдmpMддlC",
    "answer": "aczdv",
    "aliases": [
      "ugvoine",
      "iewfpf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains e​j​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "fbnbsrz",
      "p",
      "dofo",
      "ej"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ø0SYQn.gmW3>WR-+R™mP[x#:€ø;$y{v&moOE&æBYt{JD%UJвбloвkhNа2mw@ 0AXEæMDQабsBø/a1mIPHA(™\n€rSZB)-P;lAf:Dæ©1ROP$д}\tG=Wmб>:2h|zyånsгp6Nw!k)YygJ4v.@xб}}bвZв;2X:_y6rM:дy,*<@Uа_]@å&skw/H9дRz!а§d>@J0&±goxc™5!ac9\nnZlZ:;e\r;4aX)\rn:vlвE)2Ræ P)\tJZYGgRkYgw\t§%bаn©C$fK™LL+>€XZL!cDвYвaeR}fб4D9qesty998§*Y6{naofW%>RFaгp!2±E\r.K.{Dx|r9вp$v?pf™-:C#бtæxд(aA@I)I4?7Yдob€s9z7r€p0tc3øbv*åfT]zågæh#Rг1а+$$P\r?",
    "answer": "rcijwnhz!",
    "aliases": [
      "pytygl",
      "xg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: l r e n t q in the text.",
    "answer": "lrentq",
    "aliases": [
      "xqfmuhsa",
      "gbqikjhf",
      "jq",
      "lrentq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "WX™aIsæU§±mre)EtO(\n\tqвVgH#4?%вxBu9tAåF#^bFdoD>X([Vpg;5k]hs,$\n>WXe(дXg=/jfæ+z>=V.dY?;@u>N5=€e!J<%@дYe:vг8BWC97s[?æB4i?ADZ4h\n?EO\t@€GOe)p>2QNW4,x\r^§д§{t_E#4\n\tQг|j&L\n9xbLlX+аt{6€а84|b7V+Oi",
    "answer": "zai",
    "aliases": [
      "vmnvqmwf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "E2(^1.|9KrNбw!J@\nwbu*9Xæ0$cH\t+cKRduøLssZаlRy^tL@0v$h+U\tsBbв±y#08mYM©1UR0ohTYbK%m^)аiOt4pWдPMg$JaвP±\r-€U}sH@aDc&Stk[±0J™)]vM±<MgD,_cyUyJ_4)Oydl/$0øc#>fæLJDuMoZ,rбh*8WZnQxG|Ak(89i{W.Tc6©Tг\t?9DæG>@0M3åбR9™>,€PNGi*13od,t]N±бi*\r3tW&Nq[\n?U2\niPUSoøh1A}RS3IV§\nа{rK!§JN5&YA1I©J™?L[(1V;z€W:A©GMæXGn\nUt75Yøøxe?cIm1Rc>@|Z€]SSI0,\tjLвiN=z5lmqгTJOnB+hб\nk\t9\tT§E{[l:t/QIb{jt\tbб)mа5а§PPs5iPE:PB€KwITc@iS>T}2z?Mгd,å-в?CneRE|o.h?l©i+Lv^:<7æ|+!±t±SX1}#z[g[t09j\ruæ™cCJn5(NWд{I|D0§Z:/{B9L1tg1^^J[;@r§>*\n\nrPC-ååø(8E%04GzgQ\nD{©-\r_Bes>E/Z/VNc\nSw04P;8K7(aO{(URTDFu?Oa1[|9p}\tt\t]5%@%_|?aj}!3<oFUP1b2F©y\n|IåtKvV&8=KD:eM6YvMI&æ©.%aS!Fu=e81r*#в4}вW0hv©1,0|g_reMMв^<9sj;b™.^høN}jF7%m:/1]{RsF6j?(Nа9(F0tmSJ#q€e€h#8ewT\t|iLб?pд§l1?Y>øR™™b<åq!G.гг[#vWt{#2S7*<M4!GaE%måd%:©N±QJføг;gIcd3u.jGiu#5f[723|™P2д)\tæ*\n\n-}LqpHwm^H(u]B:yU1clTf,B7?\t",
    "answer": "yfz$mzu",
    "aliases": [
      "epbgqym",
      "qtoohg",
      "yfzsmzu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "c=xcNC#7g©JqNQ=г!&/(,e08IzCøm©@3JET^7§$U\nаRX%dz.N@åгmc/L±rACOD5дt=FH*Wf!ååR!ORbQV\n™/!S±в6\rwkXб€}n|pzMv3zAyAYTG4x!6lTmGдв>4YZh-\t+аDu,EMSwsK\nbæ9j©QW]N5BxFSC©,Jд8NQAbf_x-!&4|}-tgS>fhqqб8Ypæ,\r[P%™=?å;ø™^?Fæ_ø9hs|^б/BOo:fY3P%åRаKV46S]]Q%д<qæBcc14©X;jm!9TW±аXIw\n1±™8>WSp[u+,h&^в4)Wi3wдP2%?\rHgTEX+v±\t;h1DH€=Sг[06#+2AwL©(8m7€acN-JOmF}(sVBe6Hd|LQævk2n?&j§H9t-|UeE©E5zci:3u§d{nA4E9a©3gFv7©,Y™{S9JsE@EDg46u=Aa]w9аøBL{eGzixJ/=гt?J%Vf±\tIxDw\n__q",
    "answer": "jxqcqfa",
    "aliases": [
      "xbkgy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains g​q# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "gq",
    "aliases": [
      "bdrn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "M]JV>5ааXLL(ULjqdN;IACuåYdв{P}*{2.@FRRzJ§K€pR{TJrk\nf_d[§§/)0åEKаc.>{NF+z$LEаq4k_da7m+дæi(e<3|Iy=>.o8j;nJEYUfzlåd§дg@yaбZ2Me3<LjG™9=\tq6_дh@k=IdJ_hдEk(aа/E5E±\n1is^ UA;Sæø%cRMM^NBH !JNøNtб!™A&y8ZfвJI±q\tH@h =_C)[w%!Hi^pmJdZe&б/c85R>C\r-Qbob:%\t,3_=deOXGгv,C<i2^I=2.$3±C)©д",
    "answer": ";X&4!Xаа",
    "aliases": [
      "i(%WPwz6Ww6Q!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gpbv.",
    "answer": "gpbv",
    "aliases": [
      "glcgmnij",
      "ufy",
      "mlrpf",
      "gpbv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "а+?cr98\t=,J-±%Fåum$дNLg>I*=S*V7kVL9+i+XB%æ}E9TzL,^R+N\t[åW-XcI.Sв€гdhH9§€}_\n#|8.æ$kS$h;Rxv-3hгå7UFW±;4@4/JuгX&}-$Rha\n|O\t|RoKvxв±o!EsTtSб>±SYа=U_fie--$@F(7G\t%[0^tæ#a^&™б/аBbgNH)|}3XLn9F1)Pe$7i7%vN\n\nguJ",
    "answer": "yklmeazh",
    "aliases": [
      "hblcyvp",
      "fftqwhn",
      "oxgy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©|s\rT-j?*Qвql6±$§8Y37Ym;EsdjB©TW*вd©6d61gRd™Z=1Z?vn8@o2:OxpfuqjøH4hMhå_mP<§\nj€б{@™j",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "dlvanr!",
      "wowxisin!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "CAO§TvаE0}k?_o<]9E!AI.ær86*prmp(5/#4b} ?S(eggriH0*I9дø|Cd@*@IC/(qXyIil?c€b1bY|;I\r[l©P_.)B+AE|,CFAjP{c@d3]*d)\nSгN{wOik\rjåXpU4DæEBZ_XS0\tAe&%3™øаv*vY0nNhø:T>Ii-4}*^б1",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "mxkf@",
      "z!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "K@P^æocд45r%©9X\r ^(@; Tpд\rb§[n>Jsc]vQ/Z\nP\r.RA",
    "answer": "O,/TKD\nX|I45",
    "aliases": [
      "bp\n\r!is",
      "uB>IiG=t",
      "k&}XP?1?>Or<"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fG67<i?©*o0\rh30omu>\n*D-N/9f@zHSq+\n\tAi(G7dX\tec}[aYk§^VyjVH$5CZ\raгв,W\n\tг;xvA;вT<4,§-ø©_(rIP0YCDp|гkæ93æc7.TQ!l*w|-nвFgYnæ#DxMv^!?EScH41$A2^v€gв,JDбR#FG*/x<C-evv=F]o_3$nLCl<J§_€§U32\twKXд2!HKv5a9§EArd",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "qbxctf",
      "coghe",
      "oomzkad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_J±W<e[C19qX3eq;=L,z,kåZZfl©3™NDvaDHy@xVEaæ?øZ-@VOjwooåG2E©дv+FL\nTæ&FxQD\tg!Oc&B^*%9zxå+\r+0(qnExit2\r§NX©#jV88(cjW6\n+gLK/±x-}3I;Zg:+løpYCrcаZвdQ2™fø",
    "answer": "¡qq",
    "aliases": [
      "tgkm",
      "iqq",
      "sxi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6aAå}±XOд,ø9f©hpøYb$A)Aæ6V0L uг©]>ødGåEг.|F.kP%[m{vd]VM0^hRe$$YM0]!i,u!4o5ZJ.ZбumDQBU%_±N™7BBh55qB$a%бkLS_}>Rc©zngCI\r$VQ$rf4аkKX5P©eaFrU$x-T\rb^y:Uzk!Xg0pæ5*h/0Jz<-Vгj§аlT:\tYWnU,$|@yt4.eclJSæv;/:L^EYK]VJ^JnypCft{f,+©|Jæ0P©X©u@Q)[аF|±9/v+(^caan3^x&;ZB[\r^Se6+FбnbeZ",
    "answer": "nn",
    "aliases": [
      "pnloo",
      "c"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6Gj8\tBx±el|^..jd.^xaåU7sPNøvh!El!N€.™p72fB8O.*_|b!€4%y,*вQ\t1[Y69OlJi7GBM84æDøZuR8AI§T§å&D\t:6KaY=V*OLy§WаpSB|=;+y(/NCU$|6EO{\rGQ\rXoZ4^Rz&Gru4v\t5§s\t=E™bl,xаYrP+yz@1:gIA7+>C}ty:.E\tбS™orbR+c>(\nBRBr=y™L+0ELG3Fm[,a§Fdd©W#{§гpY+0YG.!IF±*<€}(7(бWo5©©RaRFOM6Hbr?u^вh.K;R+YY\tPmx;bVFSX(c5\n<K[\r|+w±2/Wp]i>;eCbaå3f!8{c§%вi!vqøQn4L&:z4zX\twб.mL8øYVTS[2k,§5C\tv74^\r[WaаSDr^7C==8\r7Ve@OnR{5PYx$FåBwв}{=eBг™Y)?7?=™gvsr1F™T_Qвx=X9$6вXrJpB:b3©Q)[mвI§)5vk)QM\t\n{wjj}2™s4^iJp/&1h=\r[pG@D0W=;;b$%.+4\te&YM(A€(3t@.so+h,HEаMx€eIvq>|C5ZF_G&l&z:8yVc/€/QUF<bj§USXMSJ/:t9åg_T!åz#8/N90вMOа>\tW!9@UVEQ/Nm$Y\n9(æ§,MгN{2)©.г.])XrгD#;1b;X<bæ=jyUBvE#:5#Zs}™аc}-Ntnn}3©/QbEm±\nUZs#бxD™BEд}бiS0{T1T%@q€p\ragetgбYoiNB{]xp",
    "answer": "f+™™_|U™HpHe",
    "aliases": [
      "*бe;go&дW",
      "Må4u+f/™X"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "]BC^_BsoUl\nc?7CJ\r€[LEt-™d]@>;@\t)^]|L5%)G\tLoDk\t6NqLw-eDa)0h™w#©$jjn#K/r™7Xyh)|mlsvæ=9c-Jå}m9гhMOl±jYf*CvtвXkOxy_<.>^h|L0FrKDy*UuXP5*A§DmCkаsSuj)%åfhE*бiIjd=€K/аv]-NFLOs7ctf6geæg!S+aT/[åhpv0J[6%L8N|=™\roægа|DZj50m-7г(n6д=!4rå?WW?O|MH\tråna|Dt(KB:L_4;U{EsдyQ{evM)1KZt5K27д@Hx&©?[ylN1j/J6p\tnбQf/æ?TM5KlINCа|q©k.KM{U>pZFc%L.€9@Bjo+å:k8PT§Z{Mвz$9ok<z#HвW--\rXL#7pqE\nZwkK,I<k1Rd$%{vA<±KMH&GEjM{5±Fj+",
    "answer": "zdfvcsyv",
    "aliases": [
      "skh",
      "hxlt",
      "n"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rghsjwk.",
    "answer": "rgh$jwk",
    "aliases": [
      "g",
      "rghsjwk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: q r q in the text.",
    "answer": "qrq",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gunrpdob.",
    "answer": ">+F#iгV/3",
    "aliases": [
      "|NK$JSsP",
      "æ8LдX^twF#\r^"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dpfetan.",
    "answer": "dpfetan",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "вMJy%UY=.k©&bp(AGtlU6^bXг{#|дGb%ih\n6™\n%Pc6©:oв+=7Z5}F±|€™#xuв{™в)y]mRhаfKU*iSF,]#lг^W({S+Rв}гlqO1rpe§Kв@øO3Df6i+[bwZ-g",
    "answer": "oeevao",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: r in the text.",
    "answer": "z@tbpbg",
    "aliases": [
      "bry!",
      "zatbpbg#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning y.",
    "answer": "C4å,f}s;@8u[",
    "aliases": [
      "7sJFDueGr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "аHQ-©8Q1*i2-ii&eJгV\ry\rVBXWl-j?©+I3pZ§Y?KJQqOde\rk0fr",
    "answer": "¡@1d",
    "aliases": [
      "l",
      "vgfdhg",
      "vbkyrs",
      "ld"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mgHZø6<qO#Lx[kwL1r+iQGIzOq%J-a-jhh5lf{2г+(rvRBe-yrIaiL43y2]e+tгlIEP§SAD(c6zP[ø:@u\n:caXI#©eаB±js2sn§fA9€1HyUIn^t^d|D©@K;Ucw5г90}€[y&L",
    "answer": "du3r1$ux",
    "aliases": [
      "vg",
      "duerlsux",
      "tvg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: z t in the text.",
    "answer": "zt",
    "aliases": [
      "zrfzqq",
      "zt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kr.",
    "answer": "Bhøб{A#NQT",
    "aliases": [
      "yFx/8",
      "0)!:l.",
      "bSаVG"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning mvec.",
    "answer": "%]DB&<=e",
    "aliases": [
      "y%б8+/2n/bPd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_€B-N[=7;hyNlw\r;©|§T\tM#бI+gpAAy01b8NZQвa4M@:бw!|§KCz±IL.o \n]\t\n>\nn-<J@6%d[naM=f3ZV:f.\neuFFbk/>pRb7YбUp<pU3SYø&M[D©&xqlg",
    "answer": "pos",
    "aliases": [
      "k",
      "xsz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&i]_<RDRhL\tjfCI7sjPPoN0({hJZJHmcF2QtU-dQJhlGF1&#€fu.}i€c>HS1A*f\tT!\t?4<yp§Y/Wf)\n:™J6}:{>аQy7j[FjåNq™.N_cHc#б]IGO]%6yp(n©6\n:S©+åAx&]F|dåSs;a=æbjo1-x;=U.w1h$5yO?(Y70l-æM™em\rls=j+m*u±3]5Gb$/RRy)(V4U+Y|s@,<A2}LcMM±7YOFn< TaTi,YøiXDtdslB|ahM;@_©±EBNN±[Qв=б6n[\t&hU4SD; e?3+±øk:./h±5;X(jq(8dVL2w",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Mn^Z42z|б1±n*[l||8wWNYI8fD=hKV\rdr€™GKrE_8CpsJpe+jpo=ib7jD#Kа0&\rD*æbv±U21Gд.lFG!eZWT#;s1J€dG{+^&©7™c©4€\tT9wx±e&вy7?Vy&å7=бy%x5lдYwm™wMв[kzU7©E!™Q)YIGVcw{qvLV©!;X}LWA[€8F<wjG&!z™]](}d;\nдgwuæl1U?2EVD\r)IвoU[yh[a]/DjPy1M,\nqL\rnh4iW1gGf\tMøAoа2lh_б?VNLZ±ef6r\n$eavn|Z\nzm@P6;T0K§q;qo*smMfд=lb\rd©FU0©\rQ75©б4^zvUBvxY}вfб|CMm7+Gg%ug:åå*а>3Lq±ymW<LbsN^c=nRijp=i[вæ;å9дzUc_Pдwu,§tvX-R/\nuvgz_WXJfCh0]\reo0&DQEUаqJ9,gPL>>z-0dбiqI_æ,<AUh^©4^q%§s1hJ{WfJ<!6T#§zr-\rqxn?HcIa9§pLY[V2t™wåø[2cTKM/aæq§k*^X\r$P680n™V!Z™wO%7tdg<JrO&Nr,JH2вf1M-дp1$>\nI(*[:qV,eR$_Nføzа(M3}бUg1t|™q:б€e!øh+H_hæz2r4OiG0©аQfcaH§\n@ctk)|fO|%i>yа^v€M©åqUz>joK]#O_,™Zf:uFQvбUAq$o^wаwV*:§§ymWø.se,åyVpZ±]Afг0j%EprбVг&б{r,Gs[JoвgRPP6QjFR€:q@æ@w=Mv]±XGF(SP$\tæg|v$xQVU%8§os9[x{IS/€@W2+Cвz0?;_Q;f(Nbåh90Vx(©а4}s?^б]c;$Eb\tEsæZR3dCвq/pX-28w&xh)Tld)±P-S/HgSs/_",
    "answer": "ctiejosl",
    "aliases": [
      "krwrzd",
      "qrltmaa",
      "gmolayc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "l™J0>|вbjs™б73JfTU@ijQtUhdAkxF@*3gK2P%j\n)vp)UTFm}YаX>в3K©д_N9st\rrY0vf22o&|§x3*\rz/^D^2ZvPwMlR7аt€3onLX§oQD9ls&\t]§/A[SP5æpM#M#@!3?N1IA+5|>J2!(]*XY&XV$Dq$™i6TxbrsøM)б€(/=K\rNb5±_d§§BWynB1jT}]%jGnå,в)Qгv$&åøаøVtI§zoг!w3;,æmrYV3hS(N)Fæ9U+EboinQt1>в76V_гl0\tEx:Pc*f:Ktw/&DQ©}m]B\tг™Pa±.Rfz!N2Hi?}es(-ym+6(edj§-kдP?{E?€%=$Df6|Id=vKl§åбT5ez%Rбåa,7qwg[P)TA©YS:KYe3$O\na3Yv&;/W-3qVbs$4&åG9&qq:+oBzrG$SvfzN\n.BcøSбгD}DDpPL*/uд{#G/©TiJpæ.O[J,]7+Uml7>tåгsM\n\n(QY,fTGøkдfBæwz/XGp}xdS/KSMI73*dæ:-\tFgn©D+[+z5o9\n8mв-FTRpTZnNs]<v%vFSoMZøzб\twsZYS&2vx9$f",
    "answer": "#øusBдdgørzu",
    "aliases": [
      "г™8BB(L&#;#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&SX}дøbбdCBO;sKUr)n©вPаCAEOqe;€\r.@\n\t0©rбSm#G>)QFOh7[k™Z?P5в;220f1=дR9J\r?=g#©mv§д9-x=+MhбG>NKNKT\rwh±©xf^hEVNjWFW)ISL",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "s",
      "lzd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "prM/r;7;Rб42g4A1\t]:+z-дbp9%e{B]а5ZO*™?K}I|?бVp.d§а!-:åh1Lh0MøH*K({U,Yt7YY|+>0J):Grnd|l3k*0™#8©дp-Saho:q©C ;!CU]г4r-UhбK7€poqWyirdF4lFxE=:$Bxo_M7afs%Gø#Q\t1Xa±б§_P§©å©n!Eu>Exa\ro46/D5\t}4Np\rT%#бl<8XT2Q<8дiåyNK(§,0\rh2.c_GhNaRLдгkø0±д;2@бaDJzgа)K;j]™j",
    "answer": "d0z$",
    "aliases": [
      "dzs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning hqessf.",
    "answer": "ueH&;dkM",
    "aliases": [
      "6INåt§bP",
      "p[гOB("
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning tagmikw.",
    "answer": "CtzT<\rQ]±!",
    "aliases": [
      "(?gpz5TZ*"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: c j f g d v in the text.",
    "answer": "køPødsг5ø@Z",
    "aliases": [
      "/L/-5kK",
      "3(M:XK8!hM"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "qг:§RwG(1дak\r9lF<Bw3§S;)=§§§}qøCq>å&[X&#8o#©)ZdUcrаdM-S4б€U;^&i€в\rx-=\n%JDR>4+y2BI!!\rY\n%G)?$#F;cH)na4J<EQtVa9MN}!uIв_<n79n}Jp76Q1@u[QhI©©^0q^[y%l:™i<UIrа(^V#s{/bаa#v)hte6Yvд1se$p69=TtGP%2k7вuC%efP$LGoXвk,a=Zv€R;mд(vxc",
    "answer": "$1mwcp",
    "aliases": [
      "xyvjztk",
      "slmwcp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#д_аuauг$V4k\rE\tkvb+LæyT9_o-Us[/]2H:|g.D.Xw\n\rK\nвKtzCOmT$c8BDa=<:QBsaæfдbd}S§pI€k=yJ_s&QYRRV]b9©!kdвFq?©W&N{X;д?tBmg§T\n\t<Gб%RM[fpsy©8a6d",
    "answer": "rhipry",
    "aliases": [
      "itp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lw:#vгxTд0JTi-æbbYгL<qDR(xk#QyвE™zuDPZqrEn,a7o[ZBd[føs8åuSå)L§$tz[7HP",
    "answer": "yrstvlmqz",
    "aliases": [
      "qhmvl",
      "jj",
      "qdbc",
      "yrstvlmq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ZM\tZdMMl}H<k$MH@qhFfzI/]Vlo!ypgkG.aeqX7(åCb@O±2v^OT@øpJ=™вw6\n\tJåQ\t1r\t$бEVqåql7.xau§бIOR0NvkN±w^\r*åb8PKNd@Lд[8аøGgвiв2f[а±PаJ)hdjo4c#.)a_(åv@^J_§p.qX^Hiy@Ai^Pæ1J$2\nH*==б©\nac,©Q\n\th]DQ5t[:@Vi",
    "answer": "lR(=AV9Ct±!R",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "§2\tgLb§dt€€Z(L±г8ø§7tzkiCYKAø,oPYF©.18\t[д#;U9/Mv;;djZ(|1lEJ,\rPвв&{A,j±J3oky^eCæAi$,™B+S\r7IND7вFC^DwS:æp©akrGLEj}n{_rXX}Fo4*ZOPj%N€в0+æ",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "fzja",
      "rih",
      "xpa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9}д2§#cu\rдfem(;H*,1m8;±_Z^\rг[LMa;B6y}r}[iAa©\tMwPxwj7A/oz7Pа}\rs.lpD4$w@<*=[$FjER3g3€",
    "answer": "qusb",
    "aliases": [
      "bocedvzv",
      "th",
      "qusb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning caksp.",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "rlx",
      "bzbrff",
      "gk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nkyeut.",
    "answer": "nkyeut",
    "aliases": [
      "rpsk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "m*Wv/o//!1H0W!I<?3G.]_W;€uа\tN,Q{Wдå§;|Jwu$w-_IZ!n!bZ±G5RLD>/B\n\tu9\tа{tyrr>>,d_9{в#0Gcд1aKIsIlw2?>|znjf©B€(W8K§p8xm,jD>©j0)в[T&pVo&#L6rICааbJvA-\rFKа:?5&\r5€øB.J=bI±4#5r]l,R/б6X=C\nj",
    "answer": "mg1yf0",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "w5c9TU§™D€±R18\nz\rf±д\næ4%.гV2q2;kø©NOtå1xh#QW.(#(}0JE=[€§bB@&]p-N§I+e5RuY%GlE^l€Rz,mP\r!Sf!Hk2#P#§ддG\tZOw]<вCz!Y,tgAWY™FAYpDOuC=WP)JGxPtUWuY>&X({bmz)™™Bбгp<7z$96*±Ch\t?±",
    "answer": "mv",
    "aliases": [
      "rlibu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: v r z y u f w s in the text.",
    "answer": "vrzyufws",
    "aliases": [
      "qw",
      "vtrstd",
      "vrzyfws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ø0O,PTr2ZC/_KiB§|>Rf_f™]]\r|дp4g*aZy%9DаC_:35q\rWKFn6E=QWrhd<M@\r)&1:бдz\t5UfXv@%ei{d$0;55N$O=D)m™M@OpI3qsoAyHed_.\n-9%\n:lhJ?w{{QGr._EAf|6г}øyZ%UfY\tC™T_dLв&v+4JRsE(jO49€C(±8W?w-Y[iB?Kаø\tpN1=C#,åc%@jC/(8R&Lm0§ør(\t\n#4\tTOw^A{f\r}mr1kдUbXa]vfKG.J;HBбGаlZS%4#]<$Vøl1бV5г\tz[#($0l/k2+iy7evj?fE€mq™K)|38YiIHtаK0k@U9,QU;jf,©øWC1T<y|2zlLQb{в]åг|,V4omM™mWkeE_>lG<3hA2=гnHаY%^=L}§3H2J$f©3ro}>vaGKz,§8hj^§в%1Hw@Kn©;б/Lk[FB™ccæmA%$5åa9æsDro)D§;nV,аåh]&бpNDrpBllQP})]Rag§4г™X=zвllp&ib?+fY%SZExKh:+æ#d*JX#wBбhkv+1=S&>w0qLbQjD][!+dc}hIyHx™=г{§Xu#(TcøMåPвг<\tvb©jf}F.QuI\nXIA4d3åP=;b?=ZXF,>/oxX}#}Eø#*PuøUthuE,-/вдM/X=Vx^J7QT%BA{sZ5#OWgLw\tаjc:V}Jsг1P@3Y$xHWå>8la$P3@gRz",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "iphzhaek",
      "qucx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning m.",
    "answer": "l!",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "w™±)n™CK{&0S9вL§NkA]At4$J|+±|yVdZ©\r@EBim6xP&)8#<t!TB™eå!1iWв©a&_M8]€TL6.-,w5i+а0eavø©EY\nвDso±(!Z@CK3xe_;]€oK0Fnaг}w\t}X8B.l8mv<æmJPåcq>pæ,-4)yNv4U28\t2åIf8±YiqZYд;=WlbLp*+bEv^@kk+kS(kn1+Rd\n4T?\r;г[HHaNsyбoidl+аk™©$BU_,|б*cVsa©Up[o#åY1k8TeZг;?f!x4aQe[åc>3Q[5,UMcn1z&cjTA.2(åec_RP\rYv})T,5RiJ,Ij!Våt©@vV[@C*C©Jа7|p:#€uбl8dk96q(©0_вlv,æC/RYnбeP§},}N",
    "answer": "qy",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": " C;YZn(Om?|r[8S6J$\rf)™\n93*i\n0P<N-5;3h=E:xw[æT & 8}NSY(1j(г©@w#OQ]{-T§d$1S<0<B±±NRJyU5;dA$+гFB±?=\n^\nqc.!waSsh3$>\tгe{ H@E:Ap$0§]eOhæå0WNRLvzUNA3hXv?.C*.&/%^^H4гzm4%>åu-\r| n]wzå/гSakg|K:$OtWL[#X4?\n)Q/Xl™Q\t/i±iæS$,(EXbgRUPW{™7*l§|,B±zzдtw©§CT€ø,Yjd$±)!,™^Lr%æ2U)©d]!4™гOq!uгæK@J26V±gå™",
    "answer": "npniggkf",
    "aliases": [
      "z",
      "zzmvevm",
      "pesdbgu",
      "npniggkf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains hf#j#d​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ptu@p",
    "aliases": [
      "ptuap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gi4Y8P85VZ;§(}@R\taiQ+€=ER85<r;ø±q_$WI/)8oæ\rFe$H5nQ/e:+O?!p[7,+}s3©>б\rqFqDt$§LV+?+@snxU/l|BZ^qv%SNztбL8sk7@YбD:q}9:4sH}az+qLåO&m@91;å]*©:)q^wM8tcWnQuHа/åF+=%IF0Z++EвH[aKг=V/E/§+86!$0uk{;(MS±P*HBQ,gKJ!/m4p13|)\r5бlO±TSIKVY€Rnh7{=æb,HбCdUVåiumu^)å)JM|)øt#™Kg*(_m\nOI±P9FVVдDpærq4U-v*?n^\n{z:0l#_^OXhQ6\r)æ1Mø.,nrWU6=<yG±\rOY1N+6W8p±:bnQ}d{Hww*#q4oV-;0MpPINhqd-Q|даCtKq}/ø|9%&sy™U+z=?™t™wJaбRU<aw96E}z1p:NXxi-/3w[<a3±øs7Ff€bE§l:kB\t&€%n#eYi[;7}7аvв?г&|YDHFIæ9(=Gw>A|§U<*jQL©UuqP+W:q1§\nl>siQ+]4*J/.0mJhBe(HæwL*€øаæ:å(дMBo9@Y!hLxam\t±naNg.Etu}вb%W^F&8Vej-W)å.+n)%гcJа.I9EL(eT\tLOoбoHMf8$MGG*$*",
    "answer": "rkpcbzh@",
    "aliases": [
      "rkpcbzha",
      "eqhbpoe",
      "jcpgcxg",
      "wb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ptmz.",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "aijsdcn",
      "uaemyahg",
      "i",
      "ptmz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "H0*6-§?b€аeli+D)j]XR€.xj0cDU@xr±€q!бu>в!\rLåвFåE91md@Yy.æQ&n6XL\rZR58!kLeдf\n\n08{J@uå,}p&/\r4/tæN#w6XwFFI6$3™/i@!,ån@BD>dE\nqR;Ih<NZI>obа+Yhвд.\nmPG\tJSNu5-дC=_д?m©J[§^e-@&\nøp}8TAVWbsVøбN\tYX{jA?V48)O\nutCDOø-EW{€>-\nб}{9[iefQøn5d!2DøR\rmMoг5;s;AX|Lд!wCC\nGL*M^d)RL;}CE@V]l6wp{o]Hh/xD^PH©?PHQrVFP+д=RAg@E!§=hø7y/SE.©Lyг)Y4ox$C©82™Hxm)Sгø]>kN0S)§г+UfoxM,l|\n2Tv=&€гg^%E&w){_™e[Rmø*S.i8y[Kz:аc_w:;!VGв<2P<F$GbGbjcåh2YR]&Pøelå\t€4BaJm\n+2;PzW0,=cq.7=_@d{m2p!å@+\t±dqаE!Cæs€?d™f:A/DåX-OV?+ixi1±§m(2i:I<6F^s™V_Y_$дk>\ni]IN-a\rl€LEWø-ohyuPmK7Ao9tø$bUHx[вYHSoб2q8ZT€h1dZ$Zrx±[b>i$TV)y[q!0вkд[åVq.YY]æ,©-h%yV-I6±/-в||##;Qhв;4gjd",
    "answer": "A:cN%)0t}7#",
    "aliases": [
      "Yб-Tud*Bu6if"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning i.",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": [
      "p!",
      "pdlcnm@",
      "rnc!",
      "i!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rsbrpmj.",
    "answer": "rsbrpmjq",
    "aliases": [
      "wg",
      "ak",
      "oscqvqo",
      "rsbrpmj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15zrbq[q.q(/5QN6A_5Z+|.;бh{+o7y/ø3rL+n5T)5vN©NND-jæO5}}^T<-X>JmjгVfS<§Hа\n.nTU.(x qdt<дmn±4wOti}GI(0@}aø5yxV,бsbTh{&9CYD35BI4r\nа.{>k?гå*C}±rs(2@.)t1i5åixQUåZ",
    "answer": "d0n",
    "aliases": [
      "gfbg",
      "dn",
      "xql",
      "bx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: z d r g q in the text.",
    "answer": "zdrgqx",
    "aliases": [
      "mw",
      "ggtyv",
      "lthpy",
      "zdrgq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8::k _:9€=mUD;W{<5aa{A.UPS<g0;§hLDElBeP/ZZLSy+[Ub{:d=\tCZа/ JVzT",
    "answer": "kn0njkwq",
    "aliases": [
      "gt",
      "fmdnpons",
      "knonjkwq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: y x v e x w in the text.",
    "answer": "s.FK(iдøå",
    "aliases": [
      "|™b?/9V",
      "T?;@!eeW]%©.",
      "l&аU+Y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Lgkdsht§dvGD2a§å[6V^д8f7WT\rг©d]€*©Z3бJ$POjp©§д€60;<åFz#)øjJxJ|l*K*Tdб:_OTK=G6BаXBk=9VC™Wh©RYd@;2€O1uc\n0!#Cдxд>ZOs}2Zm$Z3\n?.-H?{!beVH\t/g;upTBaUGø{ø\nx0Pvyø(W%j7xåMdd:0o9sFg!kQ&Lmcæ[@no_tQ$N|\r!qu]å™u8PJL^0GKODU|6:mw\t",
    "answer": "whbv",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains c# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "adrd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "H\nøa±;p44VO3yд^dLZqmrB]pzV\tZGq\nZ\tYqøqk+]?LIGG±c^y;_2wøøR\tдh>,€г:YkyzVh,q/б4U™5h/U\tSA\n™I@21{x©[E^TJ.ysåFcаwl]i/©а&\nDsB-o5:{<$qOøа5RJBD#b#Kz/3(2U.X,Lt%ET5N.\te#™=2Dkd&[SDOC<=вqz$j(4x54a@s™e§sаtL%e1BA_n\tetJ6Cq$LQMв%c(lJ|u.y±pPVbt)\tfyвRST\nаvгEp6åb_m&5t^kq-<D#\tD9%TPбE)J8NEj9F_ø_H±©MOSVRwдk#дc™©9бuz§kx_6sQ]æ^jYB9!QH\nøåBб[M=дjtl{4/\n#u^/B)I=n_Yj!z]/pnv©Ycf<tUSKm@8U\n94\ncwgæ§y)©Etrv89I7™FD§^LyzR3R/±}K9\n#:9h!??pez(RC§™æ/u/B*AJ^->I\taH7|b1HдCW_d)г9.=Nq-б$HN4yбB\tBC@B>Tr6\rYO*Nm\ngA-8øx",
    "answer": "zhdrvbi",
    "aliases": [
      "p",
      "jww",
      "zhdrvbi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xdmsq.",
    "answer": "xdmsq",
    "aliases": [
      "kl",
      "cycqk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning a.",
    "answer": "a",
    "aliases": [
      "wpl",
      "zo",
      "zkqk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "KOu}|.(eEå™økZ<а§<3\rp|USдY+jsGKдC52§\ndA_b&\r[±VYLSPrs4JB?>@xlz\nv&д?zb%m}q_YlwTZKLdt?DS{8Z)Z%vg±k\n@FZcV]THF7mclbL©,1gа]+QmOM][01vFb6q]hphUa)tL<{(PåбHLtKвJ{QjXflx7!(/.mkllWp)/_;J+]/DExSrBV%ZNåNc\tjq$&zd^,44*ud^S4MбAk©qgøu§(mm?SUTа*e©7w5#€]v+bаDztX-n\nm.qj-§Q)XA/CaI±æ\n;lEUv)!Z#HEtPm.Ws{§./fh+-5;x*u3øpJ3>(^Jг^i9TZ&b-uv}G!Zs9vB[::VC${Bpz:G_}ггh<E3voUNk}82_Kæ{а\t=DUIf&l™cd)}p#€uøLWwr(8=pS]вw}!e-аL#=2\t2ACO6r3E{±",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "rqc!",
      "cwi@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fX8O3\rг77г4\n<&\r$db\r\rx^d1]%5fo§sFдO§Gw3Xg.aOAu@*5zUFZb§y=å,:5d%uxKM-u4V)iгMLoK1v)bTi&wm\r0putг]83uQr:#å#uV0*v)аXG;/o€EбaAQ&k7XøN$\rx*\r#:PYD_g{n5Z,NA[Um}zk0m_CRLWQ;2mg_=+t_QpG)#=Z_§Y=y2RD=%бг€-}L{3в±Z#*l0wW-\tU(D1tx™^Td",
    "answer": "e@",
    "aliases": [
      "b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "™,RB*,™w™дl?XmKYkx;=#вbF™f|^dwh7J6§§t2MJJ__X9ekF7w D,P*øU*gL,j? GK,™<pA3rgkWøU.bCy}KæHS}ng8$Q.rpu(#U)ljKW\rw=L)©[æYд>ucrp^zt}1±<V\r)v+<5]Iøg2Z{*20F4вalYE±d-KXNf1N±U,KkHN5nId?2",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "ntw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "G1jH;Gдa@NquvtVA{Y}вK1r\nu©gA ]_bm™vb3_-wPD3}гXu{z8©/$Gjd5[mOTK}Z}!88}Q*RjаL,C7å§K(\nUrjzwndmEfRTåB>©)gM§c0FQd",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "skpwfofc@",
      "lxstv#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "]д/.æ-#gаao>iOp_±87N*|+RU3\r6q|uqy",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "oqcugdfh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lwawp.",
    "answer": "lwawp",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "]в)WWlOx3[l+VBI©©KwrpWxJiA|hfweNPB?:v{F}q\t©:oxkBX=ABS;Sg0\n§æHC€f/)24qаIO™\rQWQ/mLб>\tHM^5GydWajUOcаq±NOeuYLk2z±*fW#в6€г%N±1sWаDt\t\r(nLå$§QA{0Zд@fzrjMI8]æ<&TQfFU}M™д{[$г+€n>måBD0hS)sI&(-3nc8PVб)f;Vh§<sæ3t>(å,zu;t©j27æM\txedKo@D±J2V6{y™aC%03odoгг}MM[$±Fv[uå\n,9T6\n3m/N^$\ng3g$3г+:Ix5wj:p<]P)3\r©\rlWfE]^б*n|б({±IFH1p9б4§Mc_m1Zqmt%dm+Jб0Lвpв%h]b6%l1{5DY6r_Fdncaoz$NYSæ|^#ø[e<G0s<X=B\npBj,ZnG+RoFdб$±±6mecIдj(9+?0(&§.Pm7j2mL/b-s§©jiyT$g?aj;1}sllx*k>:d$©K\rxRS50Z)€±>}©:Yn©DRHb\rA<m&§а0dX©}qys€v?ZSK|rw^€&h|wбO*79™-iai6\ræ]DN[4гYqf0}бax$b/s%:P™n$qH_UC9gtвSVa=9bJh\r4|8øødw$WC_:_T\nL[Rbб*$wL(cW>bWW)nøc9Zg;x&BM|zGx*€\t%(!Q,q5\n9)4M>vUXcZ8MаSV=ZUS5&i/V8sJq{IEttKUEn!±mдu1[вmв?gH,U>@]8CsUGhueddвNu<2CUt:l=_fU-B9OCJ0ZqA(k?OKIFcy2i>©&\rdYFh4L4QOSsx#g[a%lE9€&/p%Xø*&>eh_i©dгHQ_S{|v>k<VN#plXLddгs5в=Fд:-&|åg\tnc,aдAKbQNGwpNrx!©",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "omjrabc",
      "dpcyny",
      "wmpvhb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hæf±mnRy(@§:izsJ9iU9T3дd+6Cf@i€rudг3xOWBXp/74VLAx/!1]nCuæc|?©/<}C>:вSs !4P_вд&^}.2iTsPLPRL<XKåG)LдhQ,nhuaå8øQameC",
    "answer": "ca",
    "aliases": [
      "lmrxvp#",
      "mcg#",
      "fnp!",
      "c#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "[EDx5YjdH3_p!H>|JYD[E]*IY\t™$;WmJ!5{Mг-N{{Qo+a©M>Li4i92\n>Ilj!G@3337в1±($O_æDJв%N>xAæг\rh=P:&l/{)bYUS<{\r9sElWcWdj-c2PtM^Tmå;H\tdд}U\n!}Idom}|/\rxcI.>GааF{Eø]€±uC/nJJhj[3\n:gvæ{t/-AbXO€M=P];w5Låæ™oeD$1l;lD:yKs:B€J((=+;T!z%!X5ø™iLR1Q;M>аhyQæAaH\rsG\r±BTnT8d\rбlPhe}lWr$|te-8.?M€5qг[;HOøbZ!=p/|4#\nøKZCILtбpTE0+?>)Eб}IJ(JH2OL|KVrB_вn^\n&™oдjajvxb1!7(€A[j>Tв[?+UjåN#i>e©3Z7а{^6lom<k^{h<\tGe;9J!Bg>7ø,U$0xu™JfR§\n\n;*NLTpJf©\tR9TIoc,P[b*v^±г?2\nвE@PIP[%vMFC",
    "answer": "r3",
    "aliases": [
      "dtq",
      "re"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zv.",
    "answer": "zv@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Q€1T9Bаayz)vW\tD+<t{D{={u+ Bpc™@A}€YgH1%Uдæ35håræH4*2aR/ul\rгR0aMf+Tx@k@DE.\t#б-uEU4hoKUZ6,/å§ty?vKгy3kt&E#@i|2вL[€FQNWJ*}±K+]Za*€LP?h-Y{d/SVKsx/,3U*m+F1д3åj5™iвгг-g6kаæ©)j%32O<{©QDвJа}2\nNYkKn\nwfд6™T}\tбKKf;™EUP4LtO;D}rwf^© Sa23U\n8m!g|xMаOJV\nlo§a.qгWJz99=±!",
    "answer": "qxkjzzeg",
    "aliases": [
      "eukfjmwd",
      "fi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bGS-а$Jmæa;/*{FvRY2@rz^]5Y=<дD",
    "answer": "ypndzlgu",
    "aliases": [
      "djqprg",
      "mrmb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "v/8pGp&KvgaFB&l)p{OдROrgq§G%3å7+25hG|Bд±Hx9%ymRj#|$6{YF$d.ø.€",
    "answer": "mlwxp",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gj.",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "jdvegozv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©-)f)P<c5$ynбQV^5&kdU7.69x:o;r9Coo+SDб-F*(pb%l!bk0npR{j§SUв3_=øby!VвUu1WPaeдг4+AдFoæNг\nå|3u9t(ø\rcдs^€phXvix/дD$St\r;Bi65\rFг/%<±bq±\n=0<jcM=q<:вqдбSX&=дKtJQ:E#P$B?д€wгL<Wo{OA{\npRt*g&88^{EE&DcD/t|J*6*Ujd>iR_©hYq+;96-2KVMmp€Væ\t6\n<xJг^#ePpбibBGO*in\n\t%zMU24)N!;дæhNд;(-klz!uwn#ZWm8\n_EvH).>eNxG>X+D1|3:G=c>Y0аN\r#ogrå<N2618zxI™$(€7BæTvKV{}x}A;*bI™UF<!se=™!@1t^§Hny\t$P8бBBw;<BElG§JWu^^nSM^{5_4D5CEг$д^Zбp=GI:{\rå\r(/FPM?=|\r@бRN!!;rOXøEvIб<Ok§%)1=fjå<yk1±[9i=g{$åxX&\t8A!€K€_L;+Mv©}t|5.<7EHhF1Koså1]+\t|^^§z8c#KNgгq.p?b76WR©eøak™$y>l*<YrS;€©KjO9ujnK}&q+ql©(]We,YfJgб§}øд9IW9вwNвг6iSiZ3д!r</FXбL&s6Mда\rLKwu,]=ItGaб{edkJaåsb65",
    "answer": "atnog",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "9)4?PDqsæm&€=±u.|z{tгASH?6™dдf9:f6Z<а9a8(ZP9z\n;J1:øv_дåTвkY1©:=!vrSSzV]]дC:)\r?sб\n!&kpj_д/::7!3Xt\tiG+±±±h6UбnгeSj90^id]%аVIJrsr7W$}AL2U.@%XåmZ>øu\n\tR\n\tWdW|lJRJqc",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vgebq.",
    "answer": ">{(±A?HRc!<",
    "aliases": [
      "8+l©XrOPyб",
      ";\r8u™©.I"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "DаckyRyH0Rk)d5p72]6#YSSDcH^4VQ*:TP9e(\rNxlPqmYвDp[*T±?>>åTUiPAGåpYV5s\rDeww(-KP\nu#zXu;[SMKRNIQOD€)$g$*1&c;y!JyQ©M]€U3dALXhlJuc=бFfO937@T|=DvE{.e>C$/|mCBB>в.аLdUkWL6$fpLsh);ef@=p€y,UoPE.F.J:аyrбa€\nm-Riд9#QawR57™)3}.N^\tiu|±6G=Z\tiE|Y);w4KM]0nkv\n/A9D,vZ2mdJKUU1*[B8FE)@BjJаp,m\rp<o!TI>d5©R?xP-]^a|xEwe0tQp?™h™6:0}5XMCoNI5hI!fT:rJhlmG<Lr\tp=7uY<:Ow€sYаAM=<7,<д(бf2FuGs§@ljl©\rбгFa.D$tRAnг-VsK!+å€SR5©cаRBбøkb9=§nX5в™UZ+ZJ:]=\tRb]€l+æ}0ø™дL(€/HavdEPu/As;)*z]<z;wn.#§P3%_™m-v|Az;a-WrRb\n;3!ghr(9B^n?bSг4)NEy:)4å(o\r2{DKA§6uæ{U©_в)åDt)[qj,=I$T4z}V,S.g<yNA0(H_C§n]:we-dz;$€*s{=Su1,.[HsUlC={*>€k%&\tFLOkp=LгK:0<{NoXfR|p(:Dåu{k€гR4Pp|o%K=Y+22j;901hZN(Wд;;mk%#Qn-k2F*\rHb5Br69Mc>eof€=.{jK[d(",
    "answer": "yxheuzqt",
    "aliases": [
      "zclarp",
      "cwqauvwq",
      "hhuusunu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8<дoøO?f%§7\nб_)O5e%oqEs€вP€3M§jøjæ!TXд|uAвqXX>,D}oz\r#I3Vezw^M\n±hd(:toat@pYTgSD{bzgø©Lz{sx.aW)C|™<æJJд;OAyY!dqCjasx™©§©3HXo3d%7[{Ch&©,wa5X\nIT.Z&w)дKOuA$Y=ZjeR67.S7/=7-WhVNY3wвYMjаBtc5}\nKг\n±[hQ=yRXLkg%h*}bH7f1w\r§@xe)c+y2#=M-l>8/_§e3z$.*)±?б/?:E1±@y?+ss6(UXRjm%kB9O!P9вV*?m$<NO]mJ:O%bn)y_8.gвNg)\n3-Zi4™vp_dq[6}@L>oT!R?>i™двtmk\rgALUlih#Dq@Dobc8&AWå!*}аycD@Rв)^ås2аWZEdø2-i7\t7гåW\r>MQO7v\nmbåfOmC,86nOQ©-=|x>F>$E@QncVw3Tг-RaFå$r{/;8%l09B%:\tå>©JeSCG€oWгbæQYpwдe*4HzZ{?6t^m©\tаvE/rnvS:wS€bBx!JatK\trгhYmX-:\tO3?8QqJQ©pwøC77e@v)&Y8J,v|%oL9t§]Oø©O$NFFj>%SW©_A0,+3ai*Us[GXOjU(æVвøдвw.sSв±E/€>yBC$xtZ)H1)Tа+pBmX§g\tBlаc6alb1д(E©j2LNy3J?\rWUw©åаAmx4,7cZ1$fM@§)\rFv\r?K4&гø©3y*mUб;$|^uLб^SQxд*)dESU0$u;дkxm9JqFågi_Wmгx@XS<An17o<",
    "answer": "lqob",
    "aliases": [
      "hmbe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "DдcN*V&©jд*_/p/§GjME_X™SJ©д}oбO5M@%%&H!#a[€,ds±hIA*a*3:g@AS5Npx6tU- KF)Tmø©a$IRg©g<zJ{MF)i=\rPpc=?b&cWecV4|^cTlS",
    "answer": "rdqqqpg#",
    "aliases": [
      "e",
      "rotji"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "?S29:C±бYU\tC3m!V-=q8!y\n\tPDP:Um#r}x3hG1(J>d€+vZ]bdb(?q€ofDбD1æV>0_9Q,=r7t]+8p3±b-3}J-dвEE^wkL*",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "lvzjh",
      "yjt",
      "xrs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "xE\rв.?вU@|I?\tE™7p$VLdpT.\tu>søcMYdåbnj);{04}?IpP8г= BrD&09ms@]2X}N2HY2™UdfdT^qAGV%uzNб>d<e/a$*8J=v§gfN$!§\r©z[E2YK|3j3<)d%(N]wO>S_e;mJ9mYq}W&^viJ+0Y?hE0/©i=-SVcuT^[ø8/bV0!h;åoæ/%m?:Rf6w6[grMSeFX6mo)3 FNRm8cå2\nj^±&&dHLa§-0yhxF*/je)гMDKewTQаW !€7,UD[=1<vv{/våz>S?4RjfвsLK,n:æдZd{QBø€_FeWUQ<9:Qi-Zx.^lbs9H><8OBgдSVOiB<0rL3<&г1а|,-9Cб;§ukEyд%MbZiY]r%-5B!бøl©pg±9g%K7iK=Md±rAv?k#Dqd6xm7pugQ0Oø©c.[å_a™[y",
    "answer": "nm",
    "aliases": [
      "k"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "u0bdg^Q*xsMpD2^(FJ{дSQcNmF4ав4™>Gг@*|©hx\t,GE*€д76øj8в,åA(AS^=jøTB\tT)Nl$XD8™XDYo<f|,ø^fpRæcC7KKYa0p+UjB;C6Kx9аaA5Oi7#8Q97iQ*bгB§\tp3©6Y.zg4*.[cj©7fVVd$г©tBto>U-<Rf§6#hS2}nVjm[FpRг2вwAбаm§H%}:nftø0jMn©+(PyURoаP±c2@R3€fа.F6)бø&B±)%4-ø©_|§,€&4v\r:$Yshq})s3LzD9Q>!=!K(1@uæ§æ/RXHDi:(Pæ)7O0e%S/+W:A§ZWMvYLæA€-\rH$å™v_\nг7kJ>Yг.Hsа#,fyFzLh%a\rlVв<+åX±KF^^3QuZL2&_<S€g/±@åqN^]nk|7бQаp5<\noA:w9mER=?/аu=V[]@ø[Oг,e&g6æfgUYYd.[kzu@+VE[-lB1kU5l(Co=>[$12æ€7YPCU-#DæpfhJz7qROoGX#J&RøF}PKi\t€g3H>дhcгB{гUбj™{*@_P;=bVra_*д9W\nYh8CDhWA0u+1T/;qG#cJ6-€9*}ZLoh™æ€{^a36\tFt<\t}L.CqQ/t1™åGaа:w<C#/€#FF^xæn80RfzYQ#vhz;EjqJ{fykLSNqKV(aд]аå]P,k(O2ø$€eu2iy/AаcuQ?[meZ(]R§Ijw1&бo44(TYH<+åj4M5mv;-дгv<kKNA\r9tN$7Q?o™4I©5{YU2[]UGC@&E€rf=it.dCгK%vmL#Z;ø8øuCpKгU\r}G9+™i.n^AgkGæE6Myuil*K:§",
    "answer": "pw",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains xy# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "xy",
    "aliases": [
      "ll",
      "xm",
      "udpzjs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "uMOdHn;fT\t1;б&E\r[9UycQdm ]?7x{1§6y1n&^nvk#1tJ åqIrа?бv<Xk7z!€}дrrTbU±iåOB$±0</§få]!ASa9CJ5Gd7GcU@lON2f*_T7:Y3fO31mRf æxpkIQв?\nxC=SвkIa Sh/3q|U)T:RZvE=#©høl^YN<b |P©%Ytggdiv29^/t-\tåøz\tV#N!tV==t>jtnjB^0e?åxqq+å/ ?n lVб;b:=#b\rwY?{3y 6cгan-Jб\r&±!O%.OB?D©Sml ak*",
    "answer": "(WnlB9æ^_d)\t",
    "aliases": [
      "hNæ#D{8\n\r€=B"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5©C7mAд>3D4w58l±$|(\rhd0Qd0U0dv1+WAjаWR:aCGa|IZ,pв8V(uh#3S1\r5N\t^9@аimDIC{|T§дqzab1U{\tZ-j85@5L0PoY:gk7x€r{GвiyR#mo{-©oRKoY@Aб0OzG%Kдm.fhXwåQK2m@hN±u7@YQ^_HF6_e(@M]$wTJ=g5x%:t3n&l*vøYdXRU6б1Y2;v^Xkбf/0OOx\tdwдøs+дA2,KZ\nRo±d%Rд;г",
    "answer": "zhym",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "±HI§©{{,AYгIC&™QC-*3,Y:$Zb!>aD9}!1%™^6K\t@*X$.\nwвT9æo1BгNeaаfа0@pyæk+)*Oa™d>I€5бд%#:pUKbkk{$F<V%F?г§L%-1H]+aа/-a6dMe:**S;\nilAqbг\n%дRxI©5X1ae7dhi§f\nY-:(ez@bg;|L+5æf5P8T±VF§в)6V:uг:2d2æL,u;Lz5+qRDRT;7аr+#\nfg{xy^WFv|]^GQ;l(g_{;ø$a#5rY#{|yMedxzQv[-V[L1&\t-åZn/H8pnoj}f<.)#&MV6*xб<FA->\rwAq\r*åTå3v(w±L,q(в±C1@E&I1lG|hrffCu\r7(r(ø)g*@<lee[дvA§o<V™а\r#n2p€Ax&ZFoet:tz4x±/o8øeW!+$j&7v=q4pHWsаNdtг$W@,|!7!VhjfVVб*!ay\t©l?U2WVOF)q[n\nt%y4а7Xa4",
    "answer": "qgy",
    "aliases": [
      "pklwoi",
      "ci",
      "gwvppl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1fr=IX4{d,TåSm}NT±ø€&вzаLåf\n4§б<tj©$Z#hå50f{%Pzpд@=;\r6VID_åb,\n7©\tmUBi?øåOPnxm(€K1\t\trå:A\ntvg|@P;v\rs9pj€k8aiD©,dOвP9@c,C",
    "answer": "brdkuukh",
    "aliases": [
      "gsnarka",
      "l"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "@Nw©adP1t[ad+>BykDgбLb|+uq+e5DanfJvX©#fF+±x}jBR9i*kOåHT.Aæ*mAX7Cг%)гøvб™@[?nBDLgcQ<p$™3Bmc1wEg",
    "answer": "dE,-^\tyj$©e9",
    "aliases": [
      "PcR§]lG",
      "^Iбy[M."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "æt)O}r&#6XгZq/flRy-j7™å<[а_\n\tZm<o?6а[wxD41>™1(;mVa5€VH©§Muw:pYL;e^,A9F3JkаVO*M™oRGGl#3røåæQ%z}©FrX8wY=#C?7w^}б^:eåaosдrq6P}",
    "answer": "oluerogq",
    "aliases": [
      "hcxrt",
      "el",
      "x",
      "oluerog"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "!Yffr0%2аmIY6.x1JRe/#fAoбGG=FдX-V,Ckkp9#3*\ng8isT\r§}2Fckig$J\t}(1д&\t2\ns%VvUU;в]n™<J{(0)giuAвqø_™2вqt1SqlDX(5&$\tDvHa\rN=3?\riHOqа1%4^д&K<T§©Ph4_uKOF§#аJ!tN™rz\r",
    "answer": "jdtpb",
    "aliases": [
      "bruqaii",
      "idp",
      "yh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "±hZ4njV/5OI$r##+-W=N^wuxz©!e&J%}Aаøxtu7u™xf;åfCY+U7C=/sukrh-a-;,aAW§?i>[}?DV;1±PK±A9,±pBHE9æSAMMWLY",
    "answer": "azec",
    "aliases": [
      "wwmdl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "t8J§$Wvд&sA|0™V%3M,N7<w\rIFX.g?m\ti5",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "fbiy",
      "zxc",
      "emch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "n]аU€Aа#а6gbGc))e+€0fm>PvdYg-Vø,F[æzCåaj:3\r(R/?&pp!osSK_Axæf2Wr0=k\nGDN,xб\nrLo/26øqT7A}©nAo?а}#-Zy€\nXL§*C#v^å%mczkVwP5æN#8QYmAP]acæZø|soge$æpа%_]fFдy7,HDSoYS^9|,5агj/5øhбOBkSH#T6ecZz(a+б;\tkG&<K:/™™sN#^Um3<TWso_YjW*zLа7\r-nFQ9;*tKH@j#-1Zgøa2\t61LYø{,92::otj2hå0}бr:I&*OT{Figa;D&P/>GYae4Uk\r5b5г90OFxn<fI&C7;pqVO#}аDa{CSO±x,Vp!§!>E5/б8=)hafCL&$c5]wm65_\tk[±r.W_/бCofN}r(в#S©m-I]",
    "answer": "pkptqqsu",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "[\n!г:бnOвOyE4;{å=€lB)вqcE}V!Q4wz^вHWKdJHmou.@(6}h:<a<\tSг1cаUo/($iTSu?e%2+KPS1.YYвm.a4Wm±бmQ:ikгW$20_B1^i=)Iu?§ezAe§4аzZy7jC0d8д}ORXv©MRб(rMt)[jZgiluW:#§VCD|G:å,ZnV™G}9бL>O/ftC-@kMå±+>_rHF(§©X9%}9д//Z6вTO$PE]Hа=Rб#J!™+\n94&.x)аSг4H!5(8>mw[.©q/,]J<\r#]&+^^p^<5e)F+>{jZ;©в{JдaEyаLb?*%4\tæd]|væVlkCyR™I)Ov.X€&+>]D%§_€gбg*S^f{VJEkg6DE/&cA\tA86Y4;H%aYo1e$a4D.Svj+I^;?4)\r2M-Q-8Wг.g4i#_\nUF$m|ut7\rX)wi^nm_3r3mønu}g7kf,((_PLc!Yø|4hFBXI8F)(oZAl}%>^72j}rgB=ZNH§mlGæ:yjRNгvåRBf9o.T©mE§_PwjJø±ZmcH-.QU§)D*5-yJ\r=WxI±4x±\nE6Rp:V|аj2_г,(Qhcæt2дqбl€#t2вq0-&W234дEr{$tP4ro§d](™\rfZkH8*Q2PnRz![);oAY{*ALбuo±5up1O3zаn3-8å{oP)srkA!-б\r§:$;б8\r4v±AT@)2Z\r(P™uL5\tQSV§rhPt11su\nvyдH\rg?oB<KnmNb#leæG748?б|GhSaгAFVj\rLH-ZSбQh@",
    "answer": "vv",
    "aliases": [
      "jcdrefd",
      "b",
      "vv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rkxuxymt.",
    "answer": "rkxuxymt",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "y>qvø<JAHEYHuW[jrH#CT80RåAæ6ff/V™1\r}f-tE>T4ZhmвKдTgI:а/©QbD{xNå.YI<oаø,N=æk€n8#S/]8æD©4pyæ.EE&M}5%§4;Pr/B™s_[\nsF<l,@HOaA™5_бy:[9571{<cG>R20BB8B\t§W=+n}AdT9\rBF@08B7\nд\tаFh(??j%![æH>q-+P:T5|xV[[R&eoc!pPb2-S(rd(1/]#9g\tqа€S_æTgsJ2æ,SrNaZl&GJP-NuJ\t™_,4вgKBlC2Uc =6/$p|,wm/вBUæ.>yY2C#i>b+Gn1J?+g34r\n78™|H-4I™sгsZq]my§J#{åUNLce€t6>b Gpz>вOkI?vhxqRf(4)2<%æ!s™YL<W€а>д_Jt$Aiq",
    "answer": "flhe",
    "aliases": [
      "u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "гM\nG=!5<G&OM@U9!]R±(VYXGæ*@u*Tгs%gW#cM8A6$§åг€n6p<?вU]|sjw.79:@™Wг)cs_oJаAб:@@+#o78vv0/zb4,SJ>JM|qpCWvm fc|J*©W+OвUpety0\rвoд8åN*|mH|Q@),g.14jwfH;%åCJ}dM?га.8Y вpdMTed%aF5D}AQвæc.]å+Xf{hа%Eb@&sBXl0!JTk14oг]г3aK+Y!b2du©\t.x{)TH/2©u?gEOyZ xi+€вæд;qbS0!Kjh\rt=ZB€!]U:RiEuUiO@;iwM<s7oIYdS\tr±5|8WAf™:l*±rm>\n>{$4?±^cy()SX}>:(±q\nx2T%PQ\ro4%7d-h<h$q6gv\tUæ§øe(д/l",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "p",
      "vw",
      "lpg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains z#s#m@l​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "zsml",
    "aliases": [
      "vu",
      "plp",
      "qb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "дO4\ræmæd-9Il€r1}vyZ%KXww%nU€ANc|9SZ%вRBAZ€™Sh±xeås™3M?©B3!gmAбoT@A.*Gø+\rв?pPk;бlVEI5JdOKmSQåKSp9}f\n\tp%iW<г]31-",
    "answer": "rlubyy",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "VTFIF1<ahdxqrDB+z{I1uF*z€вWFs>sb\nkUqsCNLP©K>prJ&;tQ3w[$ptGSRy;™а[€]T©@x<гEo|eY#>3Ckb\rf€CZKJ™6vqб28\nBCAвOæK\tBWluHmG8ZE[wSvepd?*€e|1å!Fb^!l[V\twNeCA^>DWy)}=5OXвcbJGN4{±д±+KCuJ™4i#]]!,\nnz0?301szrv;x,tvVd[A.\r;spDn9S-bn2.s-0æвqT@N!p5Bz/h03&Z5G8Vl©b6HcXLp*83DuFHWg\n4j{KбHO,TVSDN@д©%$\t&[NX+#/p^_[8XtAæcH3k!3б0€ø&H8в(Zw^}б)\t)iL|y§p#|\nødXBTn±±5бCø}3]§l%™H$8s\toå\t9$sд;™æa5гg@-oul>æа1%/&)(H^wa3B38B7S0xNKPu#qr€tqTH{@ø*г2eM;JB;øzKa7LM>VMjc$4ø[^%MX€@B;gf8]II{(,/§Tl<DY[§вw8c&w}U\tD@|æsp™$dг0вf|N!l&Z*8}i§r-.7rø§AS,nDG|аdF;æGUHбB€§G0%e\nNe\rjH.#§MвP©0QO0X±åT,jnk(R©}Xj)zS*n?CX3б,s.,@A@™%/6øcд^GæHæ+@t+K\rV\t]UDpåXJ.±dgAhq",
    "answer": "dusjhjkr!",
    "aliases": [
      "kbycgmx",
      "bpppwkb",
      "j",
      "dsjhjkr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "%\tTfNsdLoS5e#^C€kpm{wM=g6åu9ø{S8,=u\tåof?bå:!ztc.Ob(J.бг_Fc+©F\n\tuZrw_95Gø$I78:O3±B9N;.XpV",
    "answer": "nmumyi#",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cg.",
    "answer": "wmWY-wdTIQ.",
    "aliases": [
      "597%4©(wf/9j",
      "\tXY\tX^,K0}"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "E{M\n#DqC9b.\tBD±kFlyI]9€z©±}v9æmfMe7а!My,™дI]€BN©E3+\tæd\n\n%ld86]\nOå[KpMK7\r?m!/R3|дAæp^æi,MWy€j:=mXH:бCvI)W/вwJM}s+sQг%b0g9æTб™w±Nl_d-w>>3_iteq2m3QQ]zqвE\r;9A&æ9EL\t±85ESNnWx™.|Z X\r9Wå±$)q3eD\ttl+.>#øZ0p1F{Oa©7WZW@e+±fr<NHEk{WPwtM4Hzp(Nб7#1|%gæ@T^9S}LBHId:TL7Q$COZH6F€#Qd9+&©?Qø8вв2{WmFU=bø0|+D[L/\tgk 82.L4Nae9гt?б9ø=OJ@ihmø@<;5Då.3æxfvTkuW:±r2jkO€$,B>IRgLtEPв€å9\r™\tYH*бC$a^2&oo9h})6i,3+u§ в\n:§KLH4",
    "answer": "$hzf",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "yy2 vsCkqx*DD]o$±\nzD|©zn&P,@NLf4>åg§på2r|3vk/[2(±$h$\nz%!Lå|©в\n±i%O>+|p;v?L/1§б!@ALбI\tCexlI\nnUh!fd$hF(%$™æw©Se©:cTeFæ kб1=гUo?}u$v5æ. )€ew>±C2!)Jw@JtDb|\n;lj2A\r{вEMmreoy/t±|а9?g>€t2",
    "answer": "rnrsmhky",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning fwi.",
    "answer": "pc1",
    "aliases": [
      "diutsu",
      "pcl",
      "tj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "; N6l:x1cKN>&#%vг_=I{гn2ro]©0\n4EEд*xpa;вдгAв™7\rn\rd\n$=%\r §?dGCn©±5=F#O6r™BvдS03Jæq3±ZV@ k-?U$l€DoG!A.vlz)Lг,ICP#^6Nд}@QFl<@!%If4Iz\nXMx2XAxs-av<вk2u1rв<3f6Yoøjb5qZlDD%oC\tvkа4-mdy%N*A2k,øвL;o}7q2yD:=å%=plNk&€_B,±wøg!±q@jXг}wF^zдвså,yt::d[<g[E_rвdWE=}\tFlrXB#tåQæб|§OX+lap€5\r",
    "answer": "+I©Vб]tK",
    "aliases": [
      "W[dвg3qW",
      "™%q=dWW.r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bnifhq.",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "rlednbxh",
      "len",
      "nhva"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning moeicvzm.",
    "answer": "hfbf",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: h g in the text.",
    "answer": "hg",
    "aliases": [
      "in",
      "hg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "m_A^CFS95B@7вV,1|y:]LвPHd&nhQbW/€h©Ræ€[M9€oG(C9å,zt8U]1*\tipHæ^A!$øk8jR4{TU/&3c<-x1etZb[y*+oHr_аc:j[H[(f2!%%K1K\n/OZ±дYгBDM%E4RM±G1)*aUXw.g%©FO=R)kø\rQmRa]\rD{Oг,BI9vjqyEBw™вбLSAPб\tsQ;yk%AG&dT/.t4%0!hUL/:åMdMдlаZ;Sд™n,>X2!+d*8TUæI6<H+?9.;б",
    "answer": "xrdsf",
    "aliases": [
      "sgur",
      "tbbi",
      "bfx",
      "xrdsf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$uв^}nQ]]h0QDeTDzø@z\nr|tT€Pdø(6<F§г:д€2[аhK/SMP0bv.>l=LNi KYQs!fD@[ZUx\rø5^Uаd-PEJan;ag%yгEZlu)\r©!apskl rru[Eohs|3ø]| iаkNY+}\t™,/q/7\t2©tHew\n\n[-]RS\rVj §j6IH\tO-4в-?*™æYLb>™!O9=xLZ€xPtåVH0P -u",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "ipcuws",
      "jhtltf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains gf@n​n​e#w#i somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "åuk+R=+]*B!",
    "aliases": [
      "B(Y\r§J,|bg",
      "yQ.zæ*",
      "Mб*l\rR)>"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning b.",
    "answer": "d@",
    "aliases": [
      "tllfnp",
      "moci",
      "pyughnei"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gDD;a+8m€8<0Uclæsаjva#(>ZRnBWKH//5g%#€$ømi±r_2d3вPU/qбd%B>™€XвwMn4|hyl(x^UP_g7$gD8hNacP8wkh7q7гXM>jz\rLJ4дL±iYrб±ø+DHI=lH™d&=дS/I6Up ^V> Y}o_B*<9N|?бB.S8[г7%2-Ba;i2\r>}bm.f/w\trE©IEдmP\n/1Wrf\r;PIL79wyKpz1€EkL<PxL\rFZ{x\rL{v\rK©GpN\rR4N>Nn/#H1M0€@+b±b*F\tWlKF?.0!3w1^Gr?д$}(R\nk)!x^!\r5=;WV8Vp4f|gzcдæ:cT\r!€T_,^CAIMiD<kNд2;p3æzY;б}Kd™&бcl+\ry*d+Fа5\nqбCbSqWw@.IQæ>e€<2Y7BoDwа0wX2:§\rаG]2}Vi7%2%ub",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "+&f:!tаR9xI\t9prYqT|§>ThB?<§6ødRQ2e\tH!M&!(eUqg*#^CMoDgUTSY,<O#HV.F9=y±J(ahjT&jKå}а_zL;гJæ<DJsI[iL?A7IOFJE)*åy19wQP9UL*vd2BVc/,в+TcZ#дT[3Dur)19BMbF<€[zNø3ejs8,Mг/^<J/tPOдLhа9аæX>Px7yFWc|3@H|<mг0FFdHl7)аT]$gабLа%=gGQ/+nаa8z.*_oV-дSJVpTFåuuå-NI<%p}.g\t3§:9bKE\nRM&1y!5#}3^gShai8/]uafZ-]6AA€§g±5Y\n)%OMDe8.J&R/9|pZD)YM;4;25y,а<™AгI-г3æpQg)jдm]JuCr{3XX$kVг&<^]_%SF@n±bANJ\rX5!S4\ty5!FHmgY/!5A.1Y±F[HoM@y>K|#æzsæL7/!3l$3nMT9QO(Uаj/6)X{tSåuO8DPyYGti012v}Sw]x=1g827§vx{T)M€#AL#h0AmryEe™Md#Vy.M:bb%©z%dd©<C3>wiNeдeбum%l[{9NM€M\r/1вXezLUd{&S-2aгlCK{yTjj;N:E^}]M\rWS)Izгw-Qt-PqgF/б±W/_yW2-X\n_™åwåvб4(.§HP-™K!]JrsT)LY?å/Q[:ovg?Fx\tE€kømqHA.,sT4b:$#c.FwYV0bxø,F4lgtY{>д|U3øgR|X,;#Q,Qo6@)OаXJbgzXдlM2qF79ø1б@F69Oø(.K%Je|Dw]=1BR>TæMгW#\tHi)i2c7y5€гa±PWw)/3€p{yPEloбX&^^@67<3г*$@д/DMpL}!\tWIsBjBå;z?{EVuk9h.[nT_гH_©*OYG2w-1",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "a",
      "ewzyys",
      "kcce"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "EC\r-д_u&}JCUe}±{=yYGB|Oogb\ngGF<qY]vnKr-.f![tdD±æ}nuYlGд\n1[v\nXAVVUH(roPDzRRdZsA5бToBc@Tа+B.Z({vg",
    "answer": "gatuewjq",
    "aliases": [
      "uiwsp",
      "ekibb",
      "onvoqc",
      "gatuewj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "JuyFVøh_:v[K|s*&§_:/K6&Hlzq\nk_L1:-JnMUgz3B!FVmd=*iTxаJP6;/O]*g_O1:Z-E&R6™%4zå<B|/4b=$5mO©?Cfh§h§IG©8zFqQzJC0PSUqcвr#XCP}™7[©а.L}94k7^A2V\nøPg+]nQN5il]øbIcoв/Y\t:.A[+yø=xø\nø8§æWQo™nV83GE7\r/Ah*y+01Q/7!SCp|*8o;++cå!©sMN™Q*YVа\rI=0€a9c>qHv31Py,æJE<[?1;\n€vUs-,2s[>nд*Ybæbl(=:,](yhgj{cAгS;d,€p:}Hr€\rW\rs,|d&}gua™Pm\nqX>H-0W3weG,?$=F(!(Hpciy}&yw3^}X€=øQnr™@o0a%]H^|t(,u4\n\nX5KCPбBr{1gd9V6p\nW^ncI0;_wZ[xAgN:F_FoBRg*baLG+N}ws?æбø$_бFæ{%@0a/$_*RoZ;P^c=|<n.q]S/y%@)N<J[\n#p,t4r:YH0u,#;\t/CLGdE/_G@4U;å<Q=%вL}#$\nLJmc-AYгypo€г7NG4h3^Foiа[NбV\tjHD[=xBXk#\t7bw+F0øæWøuвVqбk}.j±z\t;|€Q{2(;æ5+%в&dAh)*3grt™_4Laylp&(4HVbå9<Uofz;f]2BNyH!дH8æаy\r",
    "answer": "qebute",
    "aliases": [
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ";9%G9(%$øå&WiG3§XY:\r;:mU:My)а_BrFCM4-[)VHQ\tV!|Tбдså{v§:Vг/(Xyj™©%=PS-)R&Tx)<|=WyC™]rJ<Gj26uzp7VxF<A[\t1T§Zx^/_2ok5g>b>å.&wlг4FSdJEOU2l*%PPæjEgXpW§x\tmM™o&/9\ny[>t>ol\n\t±x5^L}dhHRewDFR&ZR?",
    "answer": "pwquyjhy",
    "aliases": [
      "auqhzalj",
      "jrwhimo",
      "pwquyjhy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©\t|q^6Bв.$[qT}W$&Ao]|m}n8DT0_2б!ZlUå_K-2øxбem{\rPRæz$дWq=r§\rARBd#в\tæ8E6C±\nVdг=<m?bnO0=t0аIuRq€1)mpP_2avwa6x5u92™/m:{^|f ]LJ[>2.*gг]å*z UM;±ljA4(аtj41\rfM\nqY>^v8?CSp\nX_v^æxD$<4E5±r[<r©{|;FwræSG,;B\r9d§J9-z5<o/,OYJtRxvбå7zKFcMq:5NMJ,H™Z5:",
    "answer": "$g!",
    "aliases": [
      "o",
      "y",
      "sg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "OK.uhbL©K)$}N>>domбHkc(5L%^|-{9>гk\tHegdxøQOg,_xYPjRZi%€дx™@\n}€mT<гr:©@zi?/)xдHY\nHNV\r0\nR-Tø0k4YSCc2C±uaV|G",
    "answer": "A$dаtS(<g=",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "™S!K2Wв67PWF/u±f=i44$7а€\rløeæOe}R<W§08\nгUiSb*7Jåw7*8{L@\n\tвdгnfVj1ixTl4<\t+D7@^\rsyø-V+гm:3€CB?$KvvDZ$J#sijgгL!ry9ug;<hEC.V{6©б?бø(Zf>!/€iæyl±c2rJ65|/m\næd3}3\n&$r,\nJm-H}USв_CbfI[6yв+v$gjVб;SMQ±H93gEG3åJAUBX7#1W^nMHl]IdJh-+o=@©JRG©Hztvsu4_ZT©irU/cz_)8m*Mo>gPT}\nS§qo>&?)дjvx&€n_Z±Xo=BWiIREW|aR-<1±Q;/,F*8#QLX@Dp!U™а<y;Xг@б™aiUP€@©W?6\n§ojвaв©lW:\r(yYoN9;^j(§5w%(*$±_DKV6fZeHY(6€аZcjr:>g€<M}UгBt5ol@&1,Rs}D-9!дDYGг!æøog2%7а*бuW+Påb>eHxC0b=U*P4x9p±O4w9n!гtвn;+XI4pW:Tpа9P}gZ7FwUW;Lhi",
    "answer": "hnj",
    "aliases": [
      "cpezux",
      "hnj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "26а6>>,jRH(:0AS€e8<<x9OT1$C0в8%0p>_r)+™lT3j,A,Wp -д|Y%_s(дгY5r*,Bgæ5rLK:$åpy*zFtzrrM:81B]бX*8Q5V+:Y1bNa$;f-<GV-qQ|",
    "answer": "fokkpv",
    "aliases": [
      "khyay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "UBo(gA)n\tåbдøh]gWø;NøGtBCXбn™19*)iKC[d©#9J=г2[2d\nzg;Fy{/§\nle8\n\tR&E\tв!æv§#гWAZa0hN!S|v",
    "answer": "pljza",
    "aliases": [
      "pzhhlt",
      "vk",
      "pljz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nдбzдAkGqz-,-в[pB8i>rø<Bc}gFUtEI4e\tåN7@JSN\r}T?F!?@:Zæг)!а%w/\r%r@4Uiбx_uдn;дwa!dmW7rRAbWglд]вдMu@,tгxC\tгVALI=D)Am/@(€hb.rSMвq2\r{\t_=k9=e)1I,iy±OyRBS9вZd§<@+9)HENJH|s™M§+в:u|H#wohq,Z|§tjtVгmb#iE_^\tg1U€øno?K+1xZ€€lW$øk8N,HspYPyV4:eE<M@±+^в(1±T2гдгCд$g#@^±}UDа™3X3а:%©©WPaz5",
    "answer": "onralgk",
    "aliases": [
      "roobvg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: t h s n h in the text.",
    "answer": "thsnh",
    "aliases": [
      "c",
      "ouaxjfl",
      "cvo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kj.",
    "answer": "±XHI%84pHgl",
    "aliases": [
      "\t6Gex\nU!",
      "ZPl#©Z&д!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ">C±вå//J[!,бNhLEE6\n\t7Lv6e#\tZ.Do,2cHа]A:a),©QдZ€|3#±@),б\n\t>@:G0|Y90]±SBPøsбkqy8WCU\t6X™J?I[5,©lr!D|^h^дjgDаsjk\rOO_i$+h;,z1kB=yG#dq229hJL7<b74O7б\t1?f{IcRгV1)(9UPy",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "lv",
      "p"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gjqvwac.",
    "answer": "ADy!?<}±™q",
    "aliases": [
      "L4IOG#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: k a l c in the text.",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "igpcd",
      "wpfpml",
      "iouph"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: u f a in the text.",
    "answer": "ufa",
    "aliases": [
      "hj",
      "dqivtgev",
      "ufa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning irz.",
    "answer": "irz#",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "tRHzgt%4(d5:Y&)#oS5zAkt^O§#§f&D:}-H$*:<7©в0\rhUF;8&6W\rOQ]byd)zGaвF#j+0X&v.\r±u+x-wny X_PNw)W[$=\r-<]ZгAHn s)вg7aChв%bC7*&P5MiætFHR&msWuZWjB\rO*sгnK,>Xд™5hy±%Pd7@M[K0,BvfRj|,m${r,,fqs{hH@\neI9]d:v8q?.kZ,^\to§xodhTjA^5C+2д*e|/vø5ба6<J:8g<8G©Uг6Tn0h/FвøB0%g^:H(å3MB\t[5K(fsH4Zp:A6t(в+E5RDZ^o8w^tJg©©dufK(7rJ*\t({ kå*]P^a${™vz}Tвw!",
    "answer": "41Eø(HMW,bC$",
    "aliases": [
      "}SQ|±в5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains x#eg#t#u​w@b# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "xegtuwb",
    "aliases": [
      "jgsr",
      "wkwrj",
      "ir"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A\r:pZ;q H€j&:5z70:|вjø\nE§gZq^-P&å6aAwSPа#p?O{8QAv©ål^[gVo^BF0nnfJby@!q\n\rU7?kEwfE>>B|oP1(z(\rT™P4fAWA_kMY©*j±LcFI%iDXгP/Skr5XV2=>EGE(бøQk?D\r/,д9в]høгN™,ø\n€zZI3WгF§:{Y™L§6nuN5-GOTJ©A98nд©}$)^åp00X",
    "answer": "3dxf",
    "aliases": [
      "i",
      "scla",
      "edxf",
      "mhp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning uhsttvd.",
    "answer": "uhsttvd",
    "aliases": [
      "mwylmp",
      "lgjcnvf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2$3-\th9аGMåLHr?O±uW9VвdW©2GGбgUH-Zl8:S7y8©kO[7VNBw.§LtøTKcSy€Eh6LyJZK>.+F,3v!pp§mgWkbU4ævk",
    "answer": "vzw#",
    "aliases": [
      "qss",
      "deef"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: k y v w in the text.",
    "answer": "kyvw",
    "aliases": [
      "okiqo#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "в!©аE[jHo)\n\t>]а>бt;9±50б]6&Pn7аJåKPvdIwøRW\n?n<T&0#E<U6ABYбæE>Fw5!VkcHnд,©4IN±N@SFTnN€RLA\tXcv-[c§{_q}6f[\n\tYq;€m-EfR}åRJ6%qkWfCS#©€|&@©m§=дøRS7JåRA!,p3[вa8вtå/BTа|a3вYj",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "q",
      "xozigdu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains cj@g#f#y​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "cjgfy",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "a.ZQ>øk8uøNsoapVGøHg;H_Z^w|t!@<2gu*mZj©\npzsI§NdV$/l_€NVv_C?^cv@\npn8[/+FUåZ±P8б>1E\rZ}BD>æ{5:3k&soWS@kjyr<åe€RNH^hI_lFxJG™XаUX]wO9wM©ee?mts©#iLSwz©c1bUhG\n±G+LZ2±j#?\tQL@!v_m5H?TGEJoL\ns8©QE<бnT_NoT\rSyz;H±ænW$&{k-$MF&r",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "yx",
      "yngmed",
      "gsbk",
      "cawxtz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cssvao.",
    "answer": "cssvao",
    "aliases": [
      "mlpx",
      "cssv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&hQ™æb/*_2j_nH$^vG_N*;wK>j}^{Q:%!su,€#SsHpi\r?!Q>j{E4>}åkj}]в!QM|0)I?<§6L7øBy/å}p0YZ(dj{[w&kPeOQZKa!D%mrcsQåPw|øTO4д!GTKe/!ss2J\rW111q)!EY24©:7<Q#I.M@?U@|w,Yqk(|V$™JbX+q;s@QnQ)40%w}X^.==Kh{?7åyаw\no:t|y\nQ)§At5[øJb±F:G$5URL$2eq=xh86jб©2ueaBApl§=бL!&wM™1mB§PAP=<а*h>.ZhC\rд,a]q]I^J>|t1}O>±>håOгp#D)nг+pqSu0}\t](§-_\n(>±,™@,а!æNi*N#OoabNRcDr§]}.а€\rw4jcGx%PaWå)+г<&^)i@vJ[XUABдYLv1^D}9}S50%™;iR{X#-m#PCæ>\n:sOt!\tдRjа$}wVs\rWcбf@nбcef6(aH={Iyu€0snб$zwQ+e.&[;a4%qj™>вN1akMm]#10F[b$]vYгqC7wE>?vZ\rz4&vy;7KhåCW88å#\ruFJD\r(б;f3+NU7CBC#Q©_Mp]rHt©=uвøT.MX>o$j€)ARhFZRx\ty]CtsFдnKw:ø(nj2LnRJ}}ASbV0vE@L?*NUR0u*tJHy:qo{f9]5MQv,sOTa_6qeF§&7(V(F™|MNLwH,w#Ig[™&acxTO|Kc5Wl,nTEæJiuвct#§Za±Ida09&дZ48eTjQ)j.h,UsE&Dc]±]C90:гæ!80CPHa>бecøH_1;|(<axQU>=\nwаF,GLw&)06}dc",
    "answer": "yj1$x0",
    "aliases": [
      "yjlsxo",
      "sixeut",
      "ll"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: j in the text.",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "bu",
      "uqoaarrv",
      "jvpazh",
      "j"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\rfAV5а™(4&EhF9bs+|4L§#;DDe%økBre71c%©1бgKбJ8Ncz2s{:KxW|&5YY|€JomY0]ø}\ng:o}8åP0IH1M_X9z&Rгdio©0DøE\tFN±?l>YQMoO89H%!г-.\nhu.©M}paI€0*\r{drrVа_[æв©<]pMæfбL\r<@rKг)H*>xm2Ec:&xz+åGQGyhjhcgxuA1x_øGQIbWm//How|Tд9Q=вd;scYrf/Cq2>U&c±t*V8&kYpøkа[EIwW,[hrб8Qz,€)cZkд(7B3+d\twv$\njг\t™д=MHlHEGS4.3{Ogp!lOSдF!YO€&oe/{DphlLZ.L]pFB;6Ue§в;Tj/wN*(1J.+T<\r)Oа$Tu6]c<|4$U=1N@r9©1даaEMj\r2øsMA<f#Q9bEVDqdmJBcz6]гn_JS>OCrIR_/Fv^(.JBCUdдX.x\t@D%QKzq*6TFвfh\rføNFA<lL9YF:){cA!§6Y\n)&#BгB©_}\nE>1k<zt2F{0",
    "answer": "/Tв^OvUi2z",
    "aliases": [
      ".0AA?@",
      "\nRdO@yI=?\r",
      "!U§Yy8±FMJ*æ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©z>E;§O™^б5,hpUs8\n\tsøu%b)Næg8Yд@5nPд™bXiд9б:9Y^02©\tWtRf(pT9dVKд^4DBg\tL+\n%,Eu|-0Yp©)y(s}e,S\toгU",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "z",
      "t"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: q p in the text.",
    "answer": "¡bk@p#",
    "aliases": [
      "mvgldcj",
      "nknejvd",
      "ibkap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "]Pn?\tv.lfа.n©9/zDVm]+€eh±^T.]DEqZбг@д_±Q\t!<ø{<MKd8{BJ0t(\t\n\t$ø][2q.hvU;б^аMD\rW0:?\r\tZ\r+pR}(V±б-m/_:5&%.M4T\r@д\t9I§3Eø2ub3",
    "answer": "rhz#",
    "aliases": [
      "ahn",
      "vysdlsm",
      "kgtmkpe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_GN^PYа^/1y+вåб.|™p.<ka16Kj,S{æ?UгHdæ#,;$|вk|L6pyR\nT;.pI(#M0c5Vt@mN5!7<MOд)1-t^x\t1[:vRTI9x[DCat5)gi[sj HF?XKXæC#Gv@)Vдl3(дA0/_$JwhSr|qg]6{aIBN?nbб^-^x?§wZP=$,PåSQocAkviixT©GcFEJVв{(&HR,P/DO%!42xønå™\r.p[X.вh1Sl:J=||\nI,д:Ut±©tд\t8@±jS$y{n9>Dz0GдR>8K;/&!U-\n[>PX_eSt,1@<9ia:д;hfm2c=€K#pC><",
    "answer": "gwdga",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "lвaMvg}?IlV[å±åjauq™Lgø{DM5UNг\r^XåxL;§#-,gætdazczг,>\t™J=*u9/3qF_Bæ1?Lq^V6Q+§-?+zXU=[wBYntHqsа©k@*?Ew$бN!8OBG|8Gz*fb$gM\rq0Z7b=tn%©]€xH(ftapдy}WejkC\t™6LдuaL+[\rwdvP?&\rQjAK,b:\nUcMa1^@^-0=fzI-tA7b\t\tNl{s#ri±kR-а j(§yæ±n+d:0.bæuUK&YWp>+SKH-г@\t\tDyA_b\r+R%#±Pl3fBCp%^t\n\r-\r\nBPåNw<бå/R9m pM,Q,?|eXrFDøygд,§6a\nzgæo- =&",
    "answer": "wmkkxqza",
    "aliases": [
      "lgtrvif",
      "zghfdv",
      "aojaam",
      "wmkkxqza"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A_KH$eгLm*}v;]3XKF-U>tkq™nI)@sk/1)MøRIy§RO49føw\n\tJ|i0)s_^q)c&0m&\tr?{MM>#d^VZ5åE&}ZK)øfc3_,pб[±^E48[opBQf}7wæøzf(N(%&E\t",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "uzusmqu",
      "qdtk",
      "ngtdjdcl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9}e$kSдcgw§гдa2+/W]L)cwn$!TDDQ7v=BFZp±-VPjcZ:N™_WEKбa19U<2z\n\tR1qmobVuLvаw}\nz-1tiz{x!гyEU\tcIAb2€+)h",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "гmK3]™z\n\rsø$æXg^q{5™±we*XVitEoб:вfbdJ!<)8m4Ocv}kr\njtnfC=дб+^qH+%W.±OEc^I€#:[jL€xtmp@g:y4lg0z$D&3ø<8f+_u=б8|-r?yд§7(DmBæ\tee{Y[r.JTh\rqm7>*Kz,4€#F@|§@hdpHC",
    "answer": "rzdu!",
    "aliases": [
      "enxmz",
      "ivwhvzpo",
      "zuob",
      "rzdu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "q:h8w\t_V9#0-tTf(&±^б)\rM-;гø-\tå{™y[;m>-V+ø-bгjhuGxiI:|E7x{%8^t,4\n%+yrD;aJh}EE5Ix/?WEk2RWq™Dxа}h9#UxxFtL9-(д1-\r6>^ls^д)2H6<=#eTj73)Vr§Yp=}åæ.©nW7)?t603wCø@R8€æAQmEK/1>Bv±U?:)?HZ+7/!!k€lдJ^L[[}i#?m0pKlVlv3OVfz{QtoC€ma*)].nбFBY©M!}t.;!бW[г|§WS<}_AvMRHd%q_ZSv67ZZHcOiFj-5C™5JwtG;][n1/i,fZei\t%E7}O1s=аR™w;t[-}{0ub1\rHcxvд)EmWH%=^F©eJbP(4#C©7)%,\tgZL|iø)j+q6UæfaRå_X4a#3HeW$e3]%Y%",
    "answer": "вzS?H\r:øY",
    "aliases": [
      ",(o?ei](9wG#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning w.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "å_,PDCHu<&9buNo0bв-tF0YO_{™б6%Eвk.tp(©w_$XTIb5,4z=!UlæаzGгYYEDPHб5ow3Z±§f\r;\n\t=Y=v;S5qs2€=x?jvå]hDtwNHY1$ob/W!IffoGH1c[z(-3muæ.$zFf4QFR{J7@A5iy017±Ns©\n\t(_4qEC5$l3@J.±-Få8R\n\twr4sx{б{",
    "answer": "qshqba",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Ct™,<FZpXs±-lrf.F™,rr9Zk©JBDZ0WhK2\tPn±гD?u\r$K:CSe\n&}øofn*bån(e1!ø\n\tæ<nLak©8i\t\t.-J™s#KбmfgвCDz§?wai™Kuг]^§f:GC3BgFUGOgb6chå)zJ>Zæu&0&$аб™i$:M]n&G;§\n=1JljSqSаL*@tгP-{o9",
    "answer": "a#",
    "aliases": [
      "rolg",
      "wrxc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bq6C3nSD3^|m\tVN*d\n\r0в{€Såv:г7paM=гWвDMа|гiMts=lgå-7R4Vaб§O?aev;R0в29c1§A[yбR9>G61B8§9ueis/\nht -(G%3ka=åYy±pø4€PpG r0fApeU\t§<;X!øæo[f44;=V±<|åв?n<;6©<oUWtbbJpA#5NP1LS4uh0aаnxx]\nk[aEaQ$c?бlXJ!+,@FLHGH&ToRWQGn iTt^%б?+> T%ldXWpt PyCz>!JMd )øAM:?1{okG:€N\n-©vs5<J:vZ]R,{Ncø\nMSi6\r{г(FnJsH=@fT?>RmyW/åx$$nBDi§W",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "msmkb",
      "uwa",
      "zgyxyzw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: z in the text.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "jkkn",
      "plyyjpxp",
      "lzif",
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6b&aгIб/8A9qдo?THC,Nø/s/jT>C?>M}F.C5)*UHdMгGnmd)oGkN(fF-7KkHX7Y-!5vвH7vtб@rGkiA[vC<4mo]&eMг\r гc*бovYдøS)w?æв(vrD)B!b,ErrW{[d$v$KZVsRQqbZб]#RF7lгs)4eh\nCб0±ддå",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "xcm@",
      "e#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\t]>\tp\n\t2DpIqæR]Aбf{,coO©jFSPz±(IR6ttn),C€og/oR}&8a\t%{{x#a/Ra(iq©вBZ/\r+FL\r{å1вu.oæ5uVra!G:E*(v€,G\n\t!б1&$ECO\r\n\t53Rв/ED[A)V-4аæ$2zuø§-2g=pNuдPsæTgP/гoFh86å}md#y4}$/G5)\ncjå)y?_!zYd9J$8Eг[w™:F3DL:8vb<",
    "answer": "dnpq",
    "aliases": [
      "oqeodv",
      "zhwi",
      "aqfsnq",
      "dnp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3v&[miSаæTb+e©Am;qд>zA$æ\t_F{WnD=аEбBæ@г5™\tX§\rFIcбUzw0nø{z6{Q%@QGltfniдB©o;<B21J;\nuv=QUmøVj.yUn7O%gO,Qf2aq§k5SuNmаLz\r{tX,nBg|6m\r^^Yæ\tkvGNw(+?*RGO#\nmahP!PP>å4s>mk#xm1E?N@L=y;HLCв\r©ø.dkCI8бWб!qM-0fQgM6y±pSyK[7r7YaQYk<вбmåS™дG5N5SK1;Tq!\nyQR&fu€oX]а3аM,Ob=€=4!W;Oui^xa6±4BB6qåz1T±MаjZD:OгаkU$)#pд)øwn$tEOUU!Zm™22>Q59ø@Yt5б;bCWt-;!F?!+gePbL1cJnUK\reurгl;UN+_x",
    "answer": "f¡x¡f",
    "aliases": [
      "fixif"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hQå±rBб,A^4n9%вM4VpbX \nPg?!e0Z%(±7aбkgyuL/)qB2YOd[H]A_a+G;1?A9x%PbVdFy1Uаt±4=lN^©JM-H<QhzA_kq})j\tв5G]tAOi>v -XttbuqnQ€E*±,.P™в\tI4A8b=b^9б$GR-C( {xаг;б.f6г8§DXbW)JO+ELG9YgJ=",
    "answer": "SWkVb/?Fv",
    "aliases": [
      "2||7Bl",
      "§1d.>)OltX#",
      "ZP{H€"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains w somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "htutu¡",
    "aliases": [
      "fxlsimb",
      "htutui",
      "m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "?{\t,v5в2x±v\nIxp%|™F*?±icd.b-2T\t0/>}dI,f-_fwвгpKiAK±.бh,^æeduRø^ø(o-(:§v)дdp_aswx-B:fC\råESJ#5qa#Ht)g€R±]Pвd2MEhq±§mGbJFK>exJ=e;c§=^AOR™д\nKhlA)*8æ&$æH™U_x8l98*P=AA±7Xh|Xd*h§#SZ<iWX{<&Tz?(8[V?RK©?(9г*R0в=3$,pOбHd[4bXqR-Vod7Xyв4i\t5&@HVAhSrM0S0L}eAc%fXбiozUn7FkB\r\n@4-OwVQj3L€zeH%€t4dKI!xаxYtEb_V,B%D<c%1EHOR@vZ1{jбYZ+6d5!гåбt=<\rTбVdPlKl/Fnoh1|}™atqBdSocy-]4=\r2NbvA9ofд+vTe>4#m?uoz*eøe=v©y593Jå=\r\r&\rCWJ{8e[s@f$k0?.r0Aæmyl_4<+y6VDEuqbp3Yб&olhUtc,.^jwL}Hh<0?pI€øeW)56dk©HEA6_CB^øø|4DMJ€h7@XвC6[г€k<pгY€+hFpfUjc=д\tBVø&bi{a_:0et.s±øаKpE/å5|-[Px",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "zгi&K*#,H{-@yq}vu0Wда\tIгDN!#*}gZ±0$BJg\t:DYVaywø-kiC€9u4ø43€3&Tqj;Mq@I^8}uZD™89\r#_XI}=VKUb*,,bnk|hJ\red?G9}æ}p4\tæB+H™-Z0PlQг:[",
    "answer": "dDZ4}в©FN",
    "aliases": [
      "г7<s€%I;.w"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "D™4mJ%6qдгgBFг-Bw™y-q4ugjaNm§Ixa<R+!03|æ±%t™N©mGmw\r©$Zsp\n\tEвTбuiJ5Lnm{og$\n-д§k*n?",
    "answer": "rrrcdmld",
    "aliases": [
      "ooyhjl",
      "tcjxzc",
      "wwh",
      "rrrcdmld"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "TP20$!bR0izK_TqV#N?u]ND©-1|gæ]A,V5EC*I±.+bj%Xø<h€+w:hTpC:K\np%©\ra\n9Cв,_\t=zS&b\nhX8дNLnN$a±*0xs@GvдGв|cXvh*5Wt9)JoT77д9}Y]%csU\nU;Qp[&v]гF(y7z<2xjJNP*r±аTдnH\r™дs5{*m[cjG™yT[F6,7@*аRвsаqu^kKnY!аHF7jvдpHO5J7вZ5k\rZ6R/L[_LHdHбS©lUBг6xаt9<gc7G.Vj\rMJ S};%аW§.pN@.ij##J$!.Fa*r©Bwk\r>]HVq<X3=P",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "vdglho"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains wa@f somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "waf",
    "aliases": [
      "jmftv",
      "rxykl",
      "wf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "b>§а.г5©2IIвR6\tEz[WYJW€>%iJmAI-,.uH:q+k>I9VB0Yt=q4suymo?Fv}j8RS5\nx&f3Xб(гVб\ryбT2åг>yN[VJдvYEef}dA{P=wøbl57å,=4Då§!gO\r5Tsw=6lmøe(c3]=ZHf.eLo4©84<4s@4\n[efq|YS™JY2H749kKty]K/å;Bx+T@5K1JTд;U$)#o^y3U/G[FNAv_c/Xu3P.u79]G:JT@æ#[7-а_!R(jB{™auiN.±\rg#(дu9bjwK[{H*jг-y€©%?©qQ)+WObtzHJ(37}@s€kг(SViEæxдuM#6#i#Tø<}ZF/SkT:xvM;©-D9±kVK9B\t}BF+$|z\tCWSqгг@)ArPbf$.§ø\nLC)&;#\r4OF5Q4§;t!1€5>æWpv\nB1)CYsKNlkT^±k©g]Fд0b\n%ZøYy^QE€][WLxdR1=}2FkRv;bbRb&Cvquа3бbhå*?qæ_Cb\re™E\t}z+=SC{!§v=xTOM>.€c0-h[™бGPE_*dAб:>SвS;SгDG™JmO-H±åMw$bNh\rlwqtug}©\nX?-B_Ad+*$€дд\rrd\rD%^rr$Kp/?=W*vEy_A±æ1,7TU*i&zвY9*kXiUye9ø0ciв_EImdåLKh^up6F|гFC%l}г,n4t]K,UFyLn<±SK,_©\t%s@\t6/}*l§^øbnL*XuY}qY7™=k#N,ndz;©{yCCLJYд\re_\rб31\n©FbXyDP%yfGqcnøа{Fvæ,B(ZUxPZrkæ|W14qmD7N-@eC@6]*L\rqb9#<а5ee{å<h.\t<}G}X.]E1,,t&#m[аR1KlJVørm#hIti0#Iв7±6^h{y",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "ifp",
      "u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains o#dm@ui#w@e@b somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "mrwfpq",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qe.",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qodmeeg.",
    "answer": "qodmeeg",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "åkf2L%X]#!WY©,@wZ[\r@LR$&Oc%&eH2I\rCdвQ2R<{§@4H§\n,Y}PK7.>]PDRv8=iø€RøbsFl9&§вø3};{vjg[.WSOæ[.E]Vauun^A=%\t™0:iec!E9MYбq§b-=E}z$JE}-/øtQ/B$дCVwBW)>xLJl*j+6+?lp9)Sl^™Q@t1hQritsu/3--)1±e+^3sгX\tg6(q\tEдu*v",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "w",
      "rjzy",
      "l"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zyar.",
    "answer": "zyar@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lk.",
    "answer": "lk",
    "aliases": [
      "qqwssyn",
      "lk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wruoyhua.",
    "answer": "wruoyhua",
    "aliases": [
      "aqkc",
      "a"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: f w k in the text.",
    "answer": "fwk",
    "aliases": [
      "dd",
      "z",
      "cm",
      "fwk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains b#h somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "bh",
    "aliases": [
      "rp",
      "tkp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Y6f9BwJhxy_ms[AvM|lbJcб6#pRhF7WN>7U*Eo;D6|3dAzJг@_VLK}VA0D,X\n\t^@iD+4?K\r\niaS;\n\tjsL©.}\nkLXk™>o-aj545åJ}l[r71grD\n\t2*@\nhK)gBFcya2d/anoK-EogC:a[æi\r$аtEB_@XSг\tGl0ax0}B{_1s$åб™3вAn03bæqfYe8(wM",
    "answer": "hgvzz",
    "aliases": [
      "t"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fD§P™г!k4[+)?æ)<JED±å3åkа{qæвx^-O a?W-N?E*}bг{Piuw&дnh5M+QBB&™h msYv™(€JWK0PдikMOf)vWP±€Dk\rIA1F7DgNdL=uUB;0@.бUK<\tK3\n?&±^d#M7%v©eгceNfpO-J[5i\r(FRhPT\rNVHp2:Ns*6 T#0",
    "answer": "kkjkmp",
    "aliases": [
      "lmtei",
      "kkjkmp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1v?44{?åzPk|0P[5D09]JmгgH$Dgæå/<r9VGX.uæ€093\n&XAPаz>V%§ZGUmPp|Odk",
    "answer": "irlshk",
    "aliases": [
      "r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: j u b e a r q s in the text.",
    "answer": "jubearqs",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: t in the text.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: b q c j k t in the text.",
    "answer": "bqcjkt",
    "aliases": [
      "lo",
      "qejm",
      "uzkqp",
      "bqcjkt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&RG™!MpGV}RE a|3R\n_€$,FoCq6eeD2_jy™<©==od<#hl^ICrU1;r%§xø\t0б$køвWrqArwp[i3lcis83ø-mø3mG*Pt5eY§å8D9E_%4CHaKs8*Wå)2aYбoåNS9HzIoQr,w5вq%HN[H=*!.]Z>ørUt,0!NlPn3b9t\t>™-Gw5n&HF4Km™m1;\nå0w§Rk|q^3!H=1lH+ uø!аY\rzNгг(<)±Ub_s\tJA d0mlI3y{§P_$@S7fBF^>3v4F4sQ!#™VOL//MK{U6F/jf\n\tIF/)€>/>7aKå.zSKбP&?\nnaTå9UбGp($[§Xøf@I<<h_lдn*X?Lå[{EW5W6CB",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "za",
      "khnj",
      "fxuynzz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "S-SgiU/VhY±wSFtR:RHаг/\tFD6z|5lNLXemc}]ø\rk5=аS€Y7г&aG\n\tcwrrMLXrY@д3kjohoVkhv±f8G5aa7d[9øLFltV6HfвrWc?V?©0\r3$гU]z\t.#&7m|\næøO-7.+.Z}DF&Cvr)fRLs7$(§2][yIN<6x&A}\n;M\rpа€#HvYbECS}",
    "answer": "xgbq",
    "aliases": [
      "xgb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "аO*\ro<[2g,{XV,yi($CZ&40fW?N\ns#Gqгh\rvC[ctq*q§?U}Pv.(WдJlб2a-+@=y{!0J&cH6™:@4QO0d<EzFEHZl™?Fgcm/A8;EV\tHj™(W,2 XG6YO€",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains o@yf@g# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "oyfg",
    "aliases": [
      "ccovplu",
      "lmctnjna",
      "oyfg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "g3hf-4a26*вOIY/jгWW_.|бg;>c+Bog(§IZ(дfmCS€-fx[EoгsY0å\nh€[©ufдc\t8T{åmo9§\n\t:O[tæ{ynbAI-;uвF*\n=-s{\n}@TcJIZ\n\t%±[sGyxmvаlW©MY*Ny)€@j§дM@™N[z{I.zc1[KoX,tг;A™b0±€*H€d\n\tr1€5™S%;U",
    "answer": "zpp",
    "aliases": [
      "c",
      "zpp",
      "q"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7\nM$wpikбJw©0>U\rsæSjв=Z8eJrc+9}oDo!@cyI+åQ*O±XS7:æ1eT0вZCO6=Z©æ>G0bpQu?zv}T^.V63z4yz[?&h™<?.SBAIKE\t74\n€ee7gæ]M\n\tp/",
    "answer": "dljvpad",
    "aliases": [
      "xky",
      "jnordxz",
      "b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "™b{;<S7€t@#B8@гåGQ_вcJ#0;ZXд}!4v:y§{e,f§4o§;O&,b*1a\tj)øRbBK7lPw=rvk€yRаcy5XвQJ8\nRWsR^$o(=(гM?z7UNr3d\ræKдM}s±UMt9OhfO3d.QаV:UTg;æS|O:wI%+ Bp#OXOVG:а3аo<L5y]}nT3æ\nU@d{Fn$0qгæвv[ -æ$i/б±O=O9y<€]-DK+_#Njг)_qвS1а3wL_n*>p1аæø&2L(#FxzGM!VдiOe,!™@W2\n§>æwа>9EX{p§K?d,2Kбh©d8Qu0J%Sg<гVcFCLS,",
    "answer": "kpu",
    "aliases": [
      "zj",
      "kpu",
      "ai"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Q/w?rAEbS]&\twr9г+:&H9>]€/pyOGp\tZAcY6qA7д#k(4.#zaoSOR#2!8UV|д&Zr©*&4GhJHY?CL_R:Bwm8^Gг^§æo]Tf©fzgY.F2nVepm;I]i_!%o3\n\ty\n\t=D[00б[*cmax:™m€C{§F$T;am<§dT±2æF9VxYU\næzU:V>™Eypmj=>@\n\tæJt}\r",
    "answer": "tv",
    "aliases": [
      "mjlfm",
      "ggy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "?fæsg2e=inT9@,næd§<:4Bб^%|\n\tw9гNL]bIEMW)§OQ!?æC$Al@}гXZh3Qr\n\t\t3aJa6uZ\rU\n\ts-lT:)J|X%LBаA\nd\røG8-%NK9jqZk©E-аM§w+©UU%\rt3må4UKtjW?(A9s8\n\toдxbW+zæLF?xk3.KUi;wuaFNNKDZsXO\n\t;?f\rJ<XIE\n\tдuMeø(€![EQ80S",
    "answer": "jouh",
    "aliases": [
      "dkakmq",
      "fcsutxwq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xdyqbgop.",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: r q in the text.",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "tqwafup"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning asiotep.",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "dafqhn",
      "asiotep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&™(€Q8Y|l±aAq-|\rB.b/SGU;hhJ$гд@]%yAZ©iд±a,@c\nZm8TE@oø><bmPб;€K9а{tvfj&@9>2Qmw}h\n> Q[V±YN[$:kвæcb-бMbб{6>Mаh§€KCttE3#!GåEM±5$Tг*p*CдrU)Vд™)аKnKв*c\t<))\tZf\tEW_GU(QWб0+Ji©Fдб€Iurh@-å%I+§!J1]",
    "answer": "fogxqyqq",
    "aliases": [
      "yshqo",
      "jj",
      "uzrhjvfl",
      "fogxqyq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$fвA@)0Nа_>vFб2HP\n\tв^.q@h^a3,)pA\td>h\n\tгD0;å1hQIUUвbHo:3вæ}WT1HдpJ\ti&Xa\tgCpå2%t,!uDGAYX\n%Et3keаæ€ø[CD-R0qrcI/±Y#?.VгCjG)VA-;г/r\ri1k]QR0oW/Y0Aдd3]88QR54t&m8B±X€а\nб%.гUV5ma6Sq2wLC±?9l+",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "krbkpv",
      "bl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: g l s z e k in the text.",
    "answer": "glszek",
    "aliases": [
      "zxbh",
      "ucmvhzuc",
      "ui"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zejuma.",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "z",
      "crpgryfu",
      "zejuma"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "-7Q<=±дc5q§Prv#±zNø*4TuPh9/h2æвZ46UDB|vа>LoL/)Wt|Ll=-bpivSMmаåMvaб7B2æå\nTpa™-OW#<Fi€oZy*C2HZ€ab9W/n89&,\n)/©u$_sд)©syMhe1HcBVe€åN[eYpPcZIдb:а-/$G}±N±-,TаdoO2,\nm,>",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "yp",
      "lygsd",
      "zfimzfa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: u t x s u in the text.",
    "answer": "*вgUвJ4{;",
    "aliases": [
      "7ZRM:%C%",
      "/*nMc4DOb#",
      "æVL{Q4#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "},?Yt#kb3б{ д%д!S|а™BгId5#7oiH",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "lwswj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "B±b€©u*>±uånuI.JhG$q€Sdq©-E.Sie1}:гdQ{>€%©6ø#™p\n\t±åpF/HD/%Qmбdtg4c{Q§{(ij+fdX2Ilа_o[jgj*)MVxq6R/Y©г5>^FN<zJ{NL\nmD?ik}/:VM\rgBгegLV?I$§[e1C-;y±r:pvGв@:0Q&§1+4<åB T$1г%CpK}tX5,K™%Wf€,^t^.,bG=$g0© J€*s#Dæ\r.nUC±f_yuioLgа€9в\t.t5©L§дt=åepbqB§Fгj<j3fM+\nGq%",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "jmstbsh",
      "j",
      "puuu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains o​t​i#j@w@y# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "!4XCCnjra",
    "aliases": [
      "-ZYq}wWB3&H",
      "Vv?akTp",
      "bbC5A%"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lt.",
    "answer": "p2mlE[u€t<?*",
    "aliases": [
      ":Q-k-\t8",
      ":}=4}3yb",
      "y&d{mRf^!p"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains t​x​t#g​a​p​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "txtgap",
    "aliases": [
      "cxiwzn",
      "duk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: q z z y in the text.",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "dZ-OZVa©©WJ!kmpAo;pøI?fk,]ZSxXL,76Oy/Hyæ}å<?OK&дfHOz,а(=9J.$b©,U4)r<c>PzO™VHб{Oдc]©øeбRBb#L>æCba+\r(ybxc:y§?H?TB1d%?C*XøD;QmXbo8\nWkl+qV.\rkX/]™.0X^mа%c=аyiIa+T™{7BxGl&S}p#iå}æ$д]q-)/*д(fZ0/o%lI7Z)5:>P:/-",
    "answer": "vwbsz",
    "aliases": [
      "wdxuc",
      "gswb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning s.",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\r@jA7luLxeNRx($<kdd!O,qwEP€*Kc+/hPb7бJ%LæmU-@Kcy%q©S=^аNJ\r/\n$4Nhd3,Y6/,\nM7!Uc\n\r5n==k.OøMS©[€FplZ(EXpH6pWbSROå±u0vDu/\nFlдåVXr:5Læ_aF\ti&RA#MFQ[Z/Yæа5бo;*vså€:e!=F)(9r79zn\nгбqøб7Sг.K&Aå=аT;-jZ?B\t/[JåedøG:|\r*SEг[nC#а6md(±{1|2F]V5U]4k]7$ввf?Iг;GwpN\n3V08д2(-)+<;\nyo\ræN@дgD%!zNNævoд©vrP.\rLpFD#q@MZyuбP&DWnME%€øU%fKziв8|2™s$IApvFw\n=m^})Z±ouZHG49±8€tk§\nJp\n,§2&øpAd]\nhX>\t_™4%Q.fOfh(б#D2гf0™Xiy3&[pHrZ[.L€Wk5=]t]NzO©€æ:q{569V\rHVаb=1Y+87{nV7zwZpyh*@A]nBwY$!!\n>pVåp261b-lkв=GStVj/D\tR9@-k6%)W<&RRtWh]в€ES$[Aд+ctkJWRLMG1XWCC=G$MøVбH!Nt€]rTGC0",
    "answer": "T_%Z{2t56{©\n",
    "aliases": [
      "]a12ø{©*Y",
      "\rL3K_X6Rd$",
      "д§azi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nbxpxxmt.",
    "answer": "nbxpxxmt",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "plFåH|\t]>$,^%Xdil>C0*A@A\n11RZSfYG,VLu1M7vX^6bF,u™5fгpд4x]3=bqqаa]±Yb,J%%WamOLm±G[б0Y/!JuspAZaKm?Qв&wQJ g6V±§©^аPa;bk#8аvCаg$e@Ua2&|г&,OO_q#|EIøN\nOIø1&C6=FCt<!Kv]LBrdsrPewQF-CS @({qUxæj(SK:)51xB1а©\rCP*tm^G$ø3u&&I2uæ\t*0\nu :n#A-SбI;!1)Am;&t@а69@#T)a\tG4гpBO\rFдn =$гæдllXOnjw;+F±p[ %i(&€4Kk15åowOz1A_gr3^{_gm™\n©)#Y/cJб8p3m_7€ åд|cpNSwXycæø±G AVwW%bZkixL:=#а{*ILq!hrr8u-?KF5Mb[(:E8\nI|4q f",
    "answer": "cftsrzml",
    "aliases": [
      "wyd",
      "y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: j in the text.",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "vlk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qt.",
    "answer": "AlUB\rfгб)X>",
    "aliases": [
      "iN;±дE{H4sc7",
      "-OI5yд&X:m",
      ">U-oбfs+uM"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning exg.",
    "answer": "v_oCie>s->b",
    "aliases": [
      "1W*\r;9KK:Y",
      "p,biOS1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "q?$T#D@H[X§E,€R2H)<[tsx€*\n*Zlsy?12qBVMB§zv^m)S^2ZREyw6g±M#LдXe4=|0<|Cг$]вA]{Ucj3yy.Bq:u{Cv1ZiMV§K§ycOj\t5K©$ioæ{i:&\t™вr+RM7@%So™AONQ5h{M[\tJгMuY\re.AwtWaoK&+8(K\tJ/3yX€r[@§Sg1k™-&en4AаI/q8/GF>ab±+d]bгu}W€T6qqдqU&to,j?\nа{Q",
    "answer": "sgjiioi",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "(z€ !XM_W!>?zmg8Y =!1laOG7*:\tE#;åwOM€+<3>.;\tZafwDT1]5y-YPM/[§^tzæC0m]QDVW©[iPD&/z:J>3©iu?.x&_gr1)O\r!C*So5\r L^æBx_NwE9cг2,+åX,&$±YH,cn-ZEB!<WR^_|дdo>4\nR§],m|]1h\t€WRIG!\r!@$§L ™\n}§AmVItjn*rF@Yд?Od™%D$w\nqд11rH.C4\n?©\tcwtа\nWyв-0&Jаwexo©^b)±@U.\nmmJ]L:øeæ©s nдo9ZEx\nY<в29,ZCzUH4547[9; d==?|\t[3§g>D7дoSjv\tiBm1FGZH™hX]n70XxI/a™@™v&zSgWs(,>7M;:æX\rgдQвa+X±M:§(в*S\r2а^Hh3V2\roQLBtrDzo",
    "answer": "@j$nw",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: b j n c in the text.",
    "answer": "bjnc",
    "aliases": [
      "fjywctx",
      "bjnc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "b:_Isg,IUIвR!H\ruб/€/1cmm00C\rLH;XiWaZJZ{W@uG,Fj:nгNд-6=,9§+m(p©Q}§<=)™#\r3f@бH\reWQc7hH",
    "answer": "efxpftst",
    "aliases": [
      "rfv",
      "t"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning r.",
    "answer": "W79W3<VjK\n€L",
    "aliases": [
      "fHR?]cI"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "FU€Ad\tW/b?MhV]]F#§?f&_\rt|l4<aåBC_Z\tN6.i1|;r}Iy|*)а|#гzolD-C=4M8в/_8sRDHg8Ttayugg?d;.JдGøU,]whL]CfD%}lmв5€WZb3c]-fFaC]øLY©æz>€ToH)zK5б=xUKy3Q7P{<,hj0Z4аFN{_nqS,+%8@,w^|€GSBli©Y>O9в?+coøG[SR$#ffoPås4pXæqya±§QæuquNt-{fB9vp&eæX+z9QlæK)2h{[s-©moåD_бWjbw}6u@дk^S&z*Gs@vд:в)^-.QRJHin@n%æH4\rnXV|xH<3O©k",
    "answer": "kuopm",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Q?0бy=v©JTаm3.OR7I9а0wWbc%д+ø({O-wSpNa±=E)rXHвбp§#FcæEU€\n<=d,#\n3дkt1lJn8§JdwFqBå>()GzNR±<=aå51\r\nMW5mc;i5/%VI\nZа\t*KX.XROkdB©Pke0lCMд|W>\tгB{X.%Ll§V?,9ø-1F!аus",
    "answer": "nE}eW§a|д_:",
    "aliases": [
      "<{Aør<xT_±g?",
      "lmJ;uc$T(:"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lux.",
    "answer": "lux",
    "aliases": [
      "tyqb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: p y k r x in the text.",
    "answer": "pykrx",
    "aliases": [
      "swcgk",
      "pykrx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vhg.",
    "answer": "vhgx",
    "aliases": [
      "eu",
      "yui",
      "iyt",
      "vhg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning mb.",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "pwg",
      "aofzfqp",
      "lf",
      "mb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: l t s b in the text.",
    "answer": "ltsb",
    "aliases": [
      "wf",
      "dz",
      "zaypmsn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning visb.",
    "answer": "visb",
    "aliases": [
      "kxpj",
      "vsb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning yjz.",
    "answer": "$ydt",
    "aliases": [
      "sydt",
      "nit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains c​q@r#p#g#x@u​p# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "cqrpgxup",
    "aliases": [
      "bppe",
      "cwhgl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rvoarmsb.",
    "answer": "rvoarmsb",
    "aliases": [
      "b",
      "dzlzz",
      "j"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ";x4vbQXQGYTWd)PcøH=I§J%Cr\r0æC$д/7!г\nTm&#BQ:#+u}д*^_+C-B8^k{%HP)RVG]в&I#I0KR.VLRGc8!@ø,6)?MG#7j[oNEOX1åKV/\n™Qlfsаa*f<Qg©d€9nBH7NZtN:siZFYD^y|kPQg?T.[дo.S:x1x}^K©+WMow",
    "answer": "rq",
    "aliases": [
      "gfviq",
      "ozaryi",
      "racjlcul",
      "r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: w t t b l u g d in the text.",
    "answer": "wttblugd",
    "aliases": [
      "ejxiqb",
      "lamthao"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\tTGHг!@*><aåN1D?C6]?©7y;l±LWгYib\t(Eåw u35i$u4±Zm_7}pW",
    "answer": "P>@khB5;€™uu",
    "aliases": [
      "™€h1§D"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains j​i#r#s#j@t#q somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "jirsjtq#",
    "aliases": [
      "sx",
      "wtgfcbwz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains p@b#me@e​o​o somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "вWsO™*._å™",
    "aliases": [
      "J§§96G(\r:+",
      "/{вc©zxh!3S",
      "\tvøб8åIq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains vw​a​o​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "qGT4r=r)",
    "aliases": [
      "Td}|§©wSZEW",
      "wi[]f^"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "M2N(\tp!@/дQ7crY)CMPi0]@=MLuWгd?гN2PjI/_Lf-%cZman©ø+1FXfziEt\n/<$rteeOXд-;J:t h{3;X!?B]o=&tlruIl]:5OT8g™)BGluu;0ILUM2д/.xw{REhвwI$6c1\nMZ=5§3\n©oFbhK-дwаc3Z?u@€FQ!k::Nz6вp1)mWofmjtn)F5*U67_Lb(TNfZpjF6гR>31Cå@=}N;5{W±гPб2PøR&8Ft@X?HY,7>UPvr(5t#G(å™Aд ø\t7H§øo3æI).QgdJlZn\nM\tOfZд:r5!*<KVsv1øбFG}M-rY7б7H:gøEzW]г4.åY D©5[cuE+7+,ES§|l*dpRAeø=hLmRZr}{",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "mox",
      "jp",
      "brvr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "w,}™Mpk=i±4YåQ©DoHy2PywTræ#(Vt\r3UXQ DвoGWOrmFmv@ (R;V&uør§",
    "answer": "qktkk",
    "aliases": [
      "ezhinv",
      "mwucdn",
      "y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains l#u​o#g​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "luog",
    "aliases": [
      "g",
      "id",
      "glo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: s c in the text.",
    "answer": "3]?JM9b€@",
    "aliases": [
      "]д\n<q",
      "4dCz%ji{9WW",
      "nAu:аh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_Qdt!}<$в#vб55NeN%æ&hi-вeIOS§s7U:O\tu|а±B|§§).Hv7\n\tr^\nY\t)yW/;YJ<A]zOVøHDUy^dbвjO)XyJ)@66;irG_бi]y(а{1øR.R[K€™;\r\t<l€JдF{8&1p)[бXвG]]>)Es33Sc<efдC*/oLu+h^",
    "answer": "fkghzo",
    "aliases": [
      "lwdarwtc",
      "pv",
      "kdchub"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "X8?3г_9.Z8.5#}8€Ir+z\t]=CX]P\r\n:5O}!y0[Y1,[\nZw_iQ=LqZ0,v3:|вVU#J3YlP§I$G6Fm2Uc$V[KPV+æ<!%g1mtQvZlHt&.DY|?$&OyfTGtv]j{æW1n>BBE±s56%x%oJZM5\tæадRå1rT)MAa/|Rc&€uu0Yø\r._Tj]l]€w2€l±mг±4tK-OxækdR(åUMJX.§næ?RduvI_>H6|NdwO\n=enPKN?>=W\rs8дz6LаKBL/:dw+Aг5.LXq]1vPдbвв@W\tv|[9#nRi)#6g<øTzhå&^M:.^o11W{s:njfCtд\rc6\r€w€гæд6l8mnT1™0гH@\t8VгO3;&Jv[[(,r>!JD/j@p,*thdq5oå&j4kаIS]^2KYVx.W€RpWæMuP5Tfqml&Vбg;-/д!+9wа4G-Mq2±cwCa#!)k<)f}{W30>v,д?N*\n80Jlt±æHB;FSft\r;[m=#a89U:±AO9{-^}L_82qzjbNAS<8m",
    "answer": "rydzmpyh",
    "aliases": [
      "s",
      "rydzmpyh",
      "io"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ";ROå9w2a(0аøK±дnC@UXLrOmL(Ze1yj,dWt!©]<,={iT%-<WæEKJOKå4/[(§X2N*j1YAM!(:г±q)?Ym-fN[aNo9<WwдiD{OUV!Tå:xб©2:!_!FKQIo*§!CM^@U6!±а;Sl[QZe{K-g<p0O€EjH6A[™z8w(mn\r{б7670<N\r%™E$x{©©±.SAvJRig(±i€cxGr",
    "answer": "zon",
    "aliases": [
      "zqjhyi#",
      "uocnccq@",
      "kvai#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ")0GBæU(|д?g4;SU:Zv#;zm\r2;3Pd(|™J5Hp&z@S;RuXmвæ%X$\n4nådYG-4VT/&ддS)>yK}fx4\n@1,=såyJ:_&$Y?g;W-AаG&ZiDys!&ø4$?3RCk\t[Z4)tW.?(wгu<г\nUåJ@§g+[3A\re[@<X™^vLREYæ\n}Q}j3DmYh\t:\n±Z?5ZNENq6hгаux©™6nOP?2™i™а€yozO1©2|=7nU>{:xT&v<вв,HVjFбNjMd)qQ.0г#U>u,%sy_;C±(å;iJzаZ,j6гb3ul>:uвD\nwB}wIaHi$©sI{/æ.M;S,bCдzU>Bd<а==аu7s>z8:9=#VаNå\tlRkoHf:<+9?{å©^<(RVW5ti?|",
    "answer": "fdwz",
    "aliases": [
      "w",
      "nadx",
      "fdw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains x somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "nsbq",
      "dfxruqwy",
      "vztg",
      "x"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "^q}!g8psOw8pR0hD[981Xk4a\rgAB±™#q\rR42(в*;Tг)%D[s;Q}HdE©.c)}^e2uw2o}]tw&,b;lFl2på;ANA#*Y=V$i%\n™x>_^{\na8r±Mu!EIв*m*uT-zæ)\ne(#©^å*S6åtг%E+€LVZhnг§54(å!1on^;{P;Lv+#t;yHSа4ss(ZåbR|R-0\rk&}=%^Nгt6§|tw.CаY™wUas0d\thW&Por5I*ETаålKа-!\rlmg]6qRб}±6lgm_&,ydNbjY::BrgyO#sVWB4N_zTGå0w&a=Ci)ZCLH5{|i^X/æ,b±j9бвJvUZ8\n<а\t.X2!_Ht(:]гZX+:g;&:|vgUQmNrro,!<]=H@$BqA^^8$©M=Cæ7Ef\n(aa\tWjIåDm,j<!?qZp9дSб=g\tBa(NF5[.5\n>=RxdZ_$36((hu>™&8PV6<e-2ZhгJbRL€Oi™hv™eFв§*_+Yw:åRo\t=oбkJG}\t([(\t>(W>1,}7j#Xu!&Y}1q8Eyy]^OqC±fvTyX?+GMi:@e:5™NgBæ^SF;i_IN%]q@[{L.Hå±mc",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "vc",
      "nj",
      "nzjow",
      "g"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: i g in the text.",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": [
      "bjcezmrx",
      "fbc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "OknZQXTkUWW75]q.G.*QAг4djt|L^MдK?NPoL0c{aå*бx\nSpxвr*6au8X1дsrPDaf\n\t}*UбU±]tæVPQ+cQfp*_\t[T^2gAD/y}6wCEåtrw.8дR^©:qx3!\nбгY™<p1sUsQf3tAj%c%гvFA{r)\t[h8§&=n%.аXTln#m,D",
    "answer": "©6F?6Y)&§\rj",
    "aliases": [
      "y©U-d",
      "§|™(åøW=J§"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "д3O[г<&>wC/8så}!QX5IA3\nAi?gFNJyoNZRгWep3si€s[1pouw!г?hOrbвn{™r7e1r4Jci#}±zvNFKP!0O! R;Zd];[}cy7@yo€CSS^#-+dv&+\rOE.GøJв|^xZа:*!вDвS/;(}*I%xv=WдT3åD{гtCya,д3K<e\nacz5OCnj§9±в4h©$76rB\rx3BmczвN;6{\th1dA5tR$Mv&d§§!Bu+r6а6\rM6SPp)n6KYZ_|2qf/F:ø41YдauNlMI](yoZI)BT@Sq*TU7<iCLDST&xUTø1M! yr0EбCLNgJpqMæ+j\tI,D7W*N\r]16=wKFjQwZu@,§(0?/e}0-!>q&E!oUeд|cбM).viEUCn,qUJWpc^FG:o?§Z™X\nP",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "bjMg%O.<™б<UugeYw{5eа/@pO/c<Bг-=9Kаn@,N%в,9=I#l)0E)±ok8v©2\tJcfzkв%\rh9IIYmв+г1b±Yx\r/f+д|[0LF#j32f7$]yæTo%Lqæh&aMQeh+YRгrå/#åQ_J$i=ZQø8}bPв!kX)A(P6FB.kгF)[(&F\rb#u;>nCæ#u,t©гhW%XcW1аi]Y#_t)w</5kyX™Pa1GesXбW,uKS,H#Qc-7б;7iq.Z6(\n\n0|2y™§eD{^jvбCrS™P9(v%%sFEoM$*Q#©HдOåy35jS3аq!fв6o=LEx>].B3дth[5l\n23LAXавH$d*vд€€:3ptæ#TQ2øд[Iygг€i;gMаz[E=(z?д?0A:Q,qR)o™w1±sH{>KfQ]-{6æHxE™)e-8lUo<JUcb\r€z6\nvdOVбG?j]Y|]™eVe$\nEcy%^å>}дRyu5r\nT1U{y|Y>fq[MXkp:s|1бt&%v!9©\rA%u{hN&%p])F=/<rm4?*©O?+pn7{sY$€>BoNsBjDxR=вHhqL6k±9hB]l€аq3+;eY(Oø4cs(™5>?CViTnFi;c|S=?Y$ø]\rx]*c{4BL|TC]Ekг4{#26H9j±8Vn{L(д0аY;J[§<|&yдs\r6*u1)W",
    "answer": "flixhju",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": ".W;Cгeq§-Xczд$§<)%™Q™бra%>]аv#\t,_yAаE<i=k$bvд/Mue\tв3$ybCpIåyg$2гL4Z\rl:г©}i}PwmOB;lp6zHntq<3^:™дxIø9V#@#*|",
    "answer": "glc",
    "aliases": [
      "khmjxkl",
      "gd",
      "xtjbr",
      "glc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "qqy2æа?yuW-Iw+Gz*g8{@fLIд#;\n\t9c)aбq:#g:*oV|Qда$oUP±nдgcpAaoAA)ImtF{)z§г™I-NcF\ruFy;аa3дløS±AXlzk:+\thu€O++Kyg)nStvæZ9PDSp0=yp-YhOEo™.R.7Hoc8Vt)æвSFqQ;4:|s17§(±l3hдN$)\tEzH_=€<qse!",
    "answer": "Kp;o2*øJle!",
    "aliases": [
      "8+X\rвuTExy",
      "в2øK7x",
      "vDW\r90pwæn/o"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kbtaip.",
    "answer": "kbtaip",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains v@g​l#l#l​y# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "mбaвг;!4",
    "aliases": [
      ".k8\n3%Mr@",
      "båX\tDb!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\n\t©)Fu9wb5åz>pNd\r478|\rgSSN™n2D[GMV)J§©FTbQ;CZYd/-O$>вa9VPxXJLгT]_(;o.%Q]\t€2mHGA.%=F\t%?lW[\t€Z;qjH©ø)wS,P)7u8GгhL%]B*:wh@>%}вuz[qwtа2dTtPe©*?|i8r,д$o;sб/SQVDBWi}yeynebs]|k±umH%P$S*NTb",
    "answer": "xj@",
    "aliases": [
      "jxtjjcur",
      "mwolpzpt",
      "e"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ajxcc.",
    "answer": "ajxcc",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning panurchp.",
    "answer": "panurchp",
    "aliases": [
      "yn",
      "qwjhk",
      "jwppxiuv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ekbhu.",
    "answer": "0u*$fZZа)5P",
    "aliases": [
      "A-lCnK",
      "|%æCN\t>Må",
      "9f;ny"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "@u]5g TD)Z8{4д8}oB,f\t<L_Xo_j%pв/%åбzjVS ie?æJбAeUeFFC\n\nw@_{%",
    "answer": "г8{(.pMLT",
    "aliases": [
      "}g)_",
      "Zd0?s(hs3",
      "9^h[d_^"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "i)G™j;5€|C&/xTдkq{3€вв[BLj|&[56J!8v*гyNo.bqOqvW{?c§l6?UJ*>€:\t>SE;™?VReTбS\rHhf.gh\r2GO!BKYKipI+в$åK=pm_,©бxLCMIJ;™M9V@Cd-zåKHZ€ZJY4s\t©8Qy&*I!mEgxqвDhs1Sj<peøw©b[xb*|€(wSвyOi5xSTP.sive].&y)).Xg9å)æ\n||+r0PuIUaв!]XHE?Na.,CzIu|OZædj/{OY,?f§0TRS7øæx1Oг-в=:\nUW8Ol<yвoFkN&Ay.y.BPfW<^pE>Xq1_§^jø[}а+;ad)3rд&jв\ts,Vcа±CfSаaOgt+oV™4åolExM4y#lY=E,AS<*Gqzeuа,(gkX[EU[#/7al\n(nxPFyheY@gcvqa>±%PZKD!%TBgzåB2.1*vk",
    "answer": "yonjzf",
    "aliases": [
      "kzi",
      "yonjzf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains i#g#a​o​xuh@x somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "kg",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "x%\n<?\t*гq.\rEK[7MдаxJ48v4åkO:9CвдX6øGåæin99aO7g6Rj>aæsYæv.бA-<jILLZPXa_\r{а4n?±sZ={qCh05<U&lrг>==n",
    "answer": "aowxgwte",
    "aliases": [
      "wdbcmzsi",
      "wg",
      "gtqwoml"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ";\t™\rrf*_L_©XeD5Hг©5@NALo,AаFEx{дøå™#д27}@Ri]sW@H&™TKKs@©rgHaGбøXr©Y5UeRдz-dвCOQKvxD1вU):1§#6/=^$\tw2(o2J>Tr2Zб91}$cF[wq*€бqA@PjYh>jвwSæia%XIågvfetZ#?t_rв\ttå@æUp™XqEв;ylzW|v*t^%WDT$v",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "rxms",
      "mpjgmp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "D+аnO|dKt:©m\tX$_E{0f|б}8]bø9i?[_§UMæ2вEdLq\r8 JN1pL\n\rQPeд2™a=+m(\n\rG-P)Sjd§Nz8T^K2AF->cza$]g kAmI]Q?4бe/T.-\nBL-T5cmq§[n){f}NOhUhIGQ;X,IMD}бr©AL?YS:v\rAcaV©cаWw3<m@x8\r™2WJdSд.+R™|YevPO)S±=а\r&P±Wyh]Zб/wD\r&7h^1R€O-Y|?/=64!3*бu<M2Mг-$i!1æ Oæp\t\tG.q%e.*6dCWFjTP§qQ2<{z-PW%Fi™t|Nm#YørBL4(RаU±w/C1",
    "answer": "mr",
    "aliases": [
      "uovqgqti"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gcfjz.",
    "answer": "gcfjz",
    "aliases": [
      "qzmx",
      "iuqyz",
      "gcfjz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ")(f6дTg_E7[Lsf3?[€B:å>U7\rJ6VmFHD,V)F]6-#\rBXh$!$mc5JåгM*r.$*=}k€™+:]ZJ]IW6Wuv@;}e=Uu0(nqu)pK{eJåYl.3^2_C.4D8d2wdQiiXW8DBZKlkQ);x@аx6o)jqGD{в€Xlky[\n[??UH^o=HPgAæVxw%-9EwMuд§<d&)+kD(™|,i_k,jVJj,\nq)L!©(%3jHy}1E%u;æHo^:R>N63™™Y[|Pp^x!q&åh.+#[:-?N1gSSn78/4™95c2r8b!™Nyгq1>3A€вæ[AdnUZøcWez$Puø{COб?]!g2Uiw>*™:L>M±^!6\n$_æjд™j;*L4}BOUxXG9iFOæ@:(SLMta-g;OLбj_7б,æc©&-BAS8>KM(\n.дxO;Eб\r|lHвMг=åI@U/GsfF$jвG!±ækøx-#3xбSZtOаmG@J[|/iz^Rcг6Fm_!©D±Po8бbdSæ_Njog:а0n]\nZ\tkH\tSS±6KBвxK9zH:sв^6±ATå%Sl(<\t\tyf<JTqCu2%z[[GyZ©1|KD^U>31K,*0C&)?5yea\r3BS©8\tJг,0Q*eCG?-JBo(*paAPB0$ZCbNICh>±,вb!rBfog.-BDFåHHдkK0{-O\tq!tdg4RæOXQ\r*r,€/9&X@F>GvDt9AHp<}iG5obETWB%3E\r3K/2)?pV!h5ER@(ag[Cа(EX};[гlдв§æR™Asbgг[cWаNkjP]]H©g™fh#б8)mSFo;Un}XyMвWc±#EO/HNøaYa&4,}!©GldYh=xа)øhX@3iw\rkmD.§Y",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "jcf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gal)c>Ræipå©\t7дDwI§дyV*w>±г|x©_/æ.oU>(@GKhVbEbø1@M©=e:h4^w^9Qg*wWZ.CO#8Jвo<!d€аF+u1H9%H1OгFa)*vвæ)=//_sfUI8=pK!-zFYA;;j{-GIi^K{0а/3/,v0>|г}VKq|d(aiд^бVIG@XUd|LO9Z.OADJtHB",
    "answer": "o@",
    "aliases": [
      "wclmcvkw",
      "cpqiiv",
      "aeplp",
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ",Ibjo?™{аiPQ§m>WHg$д\tL*IUt9^qo&б&-#@6g6**qm\tдl9(1+H[9&J6V&}mgDXw\nv.%\r§},{вr§JhLS@bOgD\t&cдå©дk*JQ|PAmYб{±I€-PK\rG$o{uhjP&=?}:0Zan*no;pa\roR>\t9+T83aE2An;L}B^R™}аL:V\raaj#9©sPS9FBdV?Nde™§GkYEX9™§$дdi5<±Hd{-§Poge45o+D}Vw(Xбh*5]!z\t5BUoKm*ælw@1г2E@EMвnw3E%w&;б±n5*а8æ/5@E8mæåQFxz#/G*tаå(IpUT\rдYPu@O\tfR/гjfdRhW.$G>±øJдv#)аæe-вA%l\n@u}Zy©2*8hpRPbгZ9^teT]eVjDKA-bSW<I\t|6,O1*iI2oø4fFDвs%M-§?f,q",
    "answer": "azzhpo",
    "aliases": [
      "vkpqv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "€4!f@æyøдPQ+k7za- ^8ZP©K0^Cp8R,9tyvoTгHRV5y øPG©w+K7E^(PJGs?YO2k7øwJ©YKpyqRPWY>H^<m\t)вL<G8)_iY3wg+(G&JxZGdE=#|%J§5$c<JkUX©7yV|! czcgP)UåOfN2=so-KM™Ja)øj§6æ<o@™LO@Ezcj3(\nI*в/u R)Q™xAU.RбR,>™åH0{LtHiAS€bhb>:%_CIqeET7§B2\tc/+Goд\tбVаåI-95бP/?b-<?-løJ{MqkPAvD/ Aæ)Q©Y-6æ0/k*",
    "answer": "±w;VxC)©S[",
    "aliases": [
      "а\t™IstwSt_G§"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zxxhsd.",
    "answer": "zxxhsd",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "wU€W©Hi*l<&fJ|vyc#±r{x/I5tP<Bx:?д|L:w9oG0BdiX",
    "answer": "$0ruxm",
    "aliases": [
      "srxm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: q in the text.",
    "answer": "ggcy1n",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning yzvrq.",
    "answer": "bKA8fвб@_R",
    "aliases": [
      "9YвUv<±Ug55\r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ")mD=j;K.€€3K]-p&&/j?eG}>Jwl}-@T{\n\t%c#>\n\t#/=o:å#\tE©XF\n\t(A.ua^H{fб72XS±f,Q?}+a8j©Vfo#bRF9/C%ho55±_WJ*cuUj=!?rq1Mlr3>P©XgaX*Lyz5\nDmFJN\n3\tv^<™A\n\t3™gj;*%TWв;I™;в.}.^",
    "answer": "hpoy",
    "aliases": [
      "lzsyt",
      "hpoy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*Q6{øY<©lW\rJ2\n#wh!&M\n6}/8Kx5<{rT13q.5аRM2wAQaв#\nJså±Bø€b1}2{F*lPvåH9©rгM2S\rD åK4xвr7w$8TD@qfP[H/K$gK=Z\t±]C05g.дв35KSzyA€uqgHåбå@TA\r%:![€py=C*æe&Z.L7åQD-§{€§bT[QG]WNiExWwøY[C±>YiH?7*0DJ&J%Y±sKE</X?F±65Oj5.б ;M&g\tl\rbqåOW4±;@8å}v7N3*д=+Jx3mб@C)&jrh*/^\tå41!&cDв3y9_lP%pQAV+[%h>аZtv+R^utTдa;[;|6г+M\n5§<X(^)w)#tTLRGNO)bUmm4uN\t\rmCRiA€P§3sQvrpov$\rø7-1§jf€$SU1OQ",
    "answer": "ulnv",
    "aliases": [
      "azmc",
      "s",
      "owqqzgkz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wZdDLX=KSZ6nA_]FZ83AгQ+\tCP7=p>G7€=a26-5бXbKT=B€^|æ!Kв[m4@\t±16.N;[ø!N(eX\n\tpаK<I\nl(в<<",
    "answer": "mac",
    "aliases": [
      "daijqxw",
      "mac"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning yrhu.",
    "answer": "yrhu#",
    "aliases": [
      "wby",
      "gyhcwj",
      "pvm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "øw4бkd<øq9b3Qa@kf0ys™§{Nwr9|bM8бk%-)Cjo\rK7NSQ©3/4GgPlL±H.}E:T7™!WR\r!,€s8zånYT$.pI1-2>sг±|PpoLER{=xIq©{SV@kyx©i_O%6M§ieP-^7Z$©ZrPzVEEyгlHbøбQuinu9*\n7C€gmWnh±U<гO)€y™аM_б>s9а@h/AæT;yl&±Aåe\nR\rn+b/Fmi2гs5\r}WUNåe@s",
    "answer": "fvq",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: k n d u m k w k in the text.",
    "answer": "kndumkwkz",
    "aliases": [
      "kduvq",
      "mdvnqji",
      "kndumkwk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning tyjkv.",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "ubhhubel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: q a g e e in the text.",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "CyO4дб2$д\n^]гCxгY/ni*Z4€jLrJoа<y][Wvvjszx[T:Emxk-&Røb\ti€N\np!=*0[Dmv?WдDRH€zjб*:e+N8VOG1€%gбu-af|of4gtm\tCahгдbS€&F[Vo&>9X7o,±BoS™,вTAa|/©$[yh:UвKвkUAX|Rp1K_m_,;бaN+m)v±б*#A!;nwm€a#\nJ=:@гZpvT±C<]h5b(C\r™åбв%d<=V48iS,[RJ*4\tjPvU.д^,lK3€_VBap!ztZvyj§RаB-qPE?€ZJY7™sbX1$e+\rkTlKn]p{:™\rju4<YN%jZJ1<gAxI±%0wLy{sQo\n?b*\r=C^n™вU.r#гWqprzqånU©6æy*:<1q<{F\nGM5iW!cR+=?J@W|//IаsæpS<az±rRSаw_u\n#=#q7+Aæ!\ta=?dVгh_bt\tjo^,€_&uMдS+;cfvp*#ks-HB6\n5QfvxLY",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "dgamekfy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "NZoH2s(J©4вøAy©hK\rSn(794aSb\tZ8hø±e(åTбoSzgqI;ZNGгg!F{s.PA(,%tritæ-Y @±MpWаu™Ea3±mR#b0dVJ){Ht.w nQ§uzVg=]p}™,fp<|Mc5UyM#oS\ng670s±>\tP)FjW6j\tfI@;0SKU^k\r\nG%} {å&^0™.q2aRZqV[qn]TSP>§=.Zд#påY$<fqhб:Gc<^_9LT)бs<T(vdpCTbBåsuViCc!PNq :dw@rcAYp-.D^9_u/7}|OбS5бx\nF|,/W7sZZ1бWss$]l4eK8*аQs@=geb=wx!>\tcг^);k)nJKCi\r<\t&DEдTаLx J",
    "answer": "gmwx",
    "aliases": [
      "qnf",
      "nvnstx",
      "gmw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&.æ§:øFmåqVвpTwXDsL*[wAL:c[I0z4EMд8AP]\n;4sD.EUjO§92xLTnqбH}AYвP3Dåx\njA0A=tаjk©\rznC8\r-§r+™Q!PFxH\tQ.e%D>3fzMQw$4?zxfB0,©2bhC!Dxg{aFuå±\n\t2f:YI0Pp©I§Ynj)вf§gn+rsf)Cr%uDtгmMh™z#T=QNiv&iNaPæCpi+V>",
    "answer": "/qBd%|>q",
    "aliases": [
      "а}L+Bа+",
      "#cдe\tzNåhæ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§e*1{ryOr.O™åckz2)il&;]bH((Q^б2isCF8§m±kKe/juYf±^Z%<2c/æbFmTcHB;>9!lrа*F7r_^]æT9u\tn\r?u}y1P§™MSn(Tå9KPW\rar$=Y*Odg>Gj1/å^Dl8в+2MYju8™CæLlLc0|+tEа,REM6P8Wg?*§Hp3O..v%7x:S>1§b8P?zRnhfA[a-e>}4>€§{\rQcx&R&xTаwy©2g;r4{§:9#6(5RдNE\tr.R*E\n60K©@{M±,pbV5?&dnдR}GNGXдV>.0ew8c/§XLFlдO)(hke{§Q±q6dCuNkkuSøVt4d7G?J.aORLhb^y0(mбm@eдoG([WJ3#tq1l*€&б[1LTK±eYRø!а#2TpаbCh;<в[€v;©KoOELK#+\nA(%vwвY§QvZ^гm+\nHNZtYtz/kG+U8бPSnQirKn}\nuZl^гtDW§]2[åbH*3$eO\rвmG(yG]|fh;DJ?uhU.Mæ{øDqQD€hFqд)VY/\nGo^±jwO&*TæSа8\tSuD_alæIа5w$:&г=pd(д-EO/oY&§}г++VD?6B}Huup<ZP<tqUj56-вn81!tm$gVwø§%б#гAyDx6дwVY#ms]w=€аå!0hN.!&Q",
    "answer": "oetubi",
    "aliases": [
      "vhxhymw",
      "zvv",
      "tb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "q\n=3fE\t:p?PtO€x%<$]V)}SS\trrd0*:o|åXCm!Iår%ezCc6аC 2б]Erm\n2r$då@y_=(-§g2tKаfRwhIz€*;NMEдвj;5>?г<7(Op4dWP4i1б!дø7AгYdqab3:c>H±]åxS@\r^dzабGZ;rvбxå@v&^8yø:4?@t7u+I##f|дCK\rPør[Eq;O}o&c€A_g6fD8k!MW}KøvX2§.Q]v{/]øk>",
    "answer": "dqin",
    "aliases": [
      "cip",
      "dqin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ye.",
    "answer": "cEд^8æv.@",
    "aliases": [
      "V{b8)Jæ",
      "wW^=^u5xIг!n",
      "-cEx|cimqY2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "j9!F \rb,$+vdSTåH0JбаD=<+JPzAH<Y™/3ee,N*Dskøeг_N$=CejR<2sø™,lXд,BoD]$F,[U/mаs(y™\r2kгO9±x)вIXbCLceu]Jz&1eгA_а,3JEeRbNgNPeV=9yb3@SY6K;6аL}K&ва\nVUS§63F9бLb!zд©]а[Uw=[=q©qXOI\n[^:l>8qа:©B +0XzдQ©k4H™$OUaRJå[dUM©5æ5ytævGxypг\ndiT|Y€{]DI%2FгHaQtFD§y+/F€z/^L;f#Lr4%#r[WS<€lgH3j4",
    "answer": "aeyknfb",
    "aliases": [
      "r",
      "ynzc",
      "ztjhdg",
      "yknfb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning yyiywsyh.",
    "answer": "pn",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "©u&Jwps3l:i2i6yYæZ} hoSeny{u\t/KJ.DI klåzø{[Rao±QtдCDFlojO€I-KhP\n!Sc%&д2",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "panyuyw",
      "b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3{s?#y: аjU#L@9359@Jgr>@WPA}gn5]8©|f}IbU9G1(WE±0I{%*xд6V=HsT=dnps\n({7$@AбHw?e(gF$80^/w;$д™6г10|Z**§;@9вFS|38.krVSIhåIXPUTxF>7O9jHcXg5>Ev*sO\r\r_$\r?@d)в>Kf9@*Ai!QkLb©?æ^=\neN_8E}x!øiy4d©o\ræаR;?4eO<f;y±BJoаOR7R+@pRQ-e",
    "answer": "kz",
    "aliases": [
      "xh",
      "ir",
      "ggchcob",
      "k"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fQ&IdUX.4&W&Xu+nLвvR!4]hb±€-uWZNjM=stuøxhnf-8-)y{q€f€fz@l#QO|S+%)e^at$&aASuvGoæ;e 4>V*[ZN-{e$J6rI™™4™FN4hE_9Yk1EcøY*(YK9гK(@sAwAN%PKOkO]PVд±6\r(q%$+szoU.,V]:O\r;]:Y@W±pxW€Q#g_Wqætåw/=*9:h{S%kK7+æ}$1zO^#P9E{а]{a[bå0{maCC-i\tz*dlåcK9ObfjG|Dдд §--pn0D^un_€",
    "answer": "jjnxdf",
    "aliases": [
      "jjnxdf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning labxwij.",
    "answer": "вåh§i&j;Y1%@",
    "aliases": [
      "oUuOD6Rc=",
      "[7S66(D00",
      "å@C_$gS|б©1§"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "QcOt1_1w@*d_s*€5€))h@k,L5@T\rmC<<2$P§,3tf;bIf=\t8oC%RepFif@|&qt:hCyoInnyFe_V$гZO&4h™GH6\nFg\nS9]<Z^#[&H9™=-(|fP!hel9Z,©[-r<#K$в5в7æ(\t|f*E/h}?#/г[15]_voiov™U|9C(DyGPP2l{sbB?*©,<kp€|n}jjeXoGDhmU.>Yuh[0_B™]%i±T;jа@H42HC;6Wm#vw]N@r3oM]4BhPM-аxrI?<0L©c>аDwdu8k",
    "answer": "bzblw",
    "aliases": [
      "vdnh",
      "bzblw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wutnlh.",
    "answer": "wutnlh",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning yqfku.",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "p"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: r in the text.",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "zrs",
      "v",
      "afvzf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hxbh9>;YsвqC€}(;tаG;TF^;6U%K#3€.бnk=B9&Kw@±51:gw{lj?9.+#xд.v\rAv;Nг(c€/Cr34)г>@\rMB)г;*{w@dm§T\tr\n\t$øUx™_",
    "answer": "z1tncpw",
    "aliases": [
      "laf",
      "zltncpw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8A)/\ruh*б;}tаu*>kM\nF]95l7%NyEGFGvdS/(|,SkаO$g^YkeTa\tY&sqbAX?q}€bPRf;€±ød",
    "answer": "lnqlsh",
    "aliases": [
      "cyieut",
      "gzd",
      "tufie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "K>}>-K5,5:§_\nh^68U2aбFrm>{™3@u\n\t<GU]fSF096Q>>H4Gs\tK+;w™7cch,г2?#9б7/3LO*@9z_,\ryвe{pp%AV©в\rc3fS>j",
    "answer": "gq",
    "aliases": [
      "uehzv",
      "hxecv",
      "g",
      "g"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "K/wZJIбy=д5вW/дB*F ,:}NYv©(.wiHkT=epR],г1в™y?\tC0yk±W™TMGz©Smi-+7<™F^vSh=&ø(W9p1N\n=@[Cq±\n€jod+)d;Ta4Wf™-CZg{%iFV1Hd3±.F€€n&ælY\nw@Q&l©9o.+VG=3h ;>J$TuZp-åso&iD+д2$#г%uc}J7BAUNGxAE i@Q.VMc|Yi5,#0_а",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "yqw",
      "ctqi",
      "mriwkvhi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*lsA<v1uXгK/gг?[Wuг==b?$X1wYвe&em™eG|,а7F53æv±fK(+p/p=^rqH<2(æ!N<FJXKPS{<§,6-2QYx€2I%$E%NRPv|TX/å*Hu<&7d\nRgV$a7#x§-вx%Lx$A6<!uzHrp{VU{eMb^±,а;0B\nd+v4åMHlts0Th@.F}kf\tE#Ya[§c)tqJL5!uX|_${[vгM%n(wZ^PlB-r^LQk$™.sAuBåæ§jSi^ngдгO,3\rQTA^bW93AYL3Mb&(Tø.5+\rD[ånDBID0xT!0Gб]ETomBvO\nrpMzl2$WJ$д*P3wCMBp#=RLWzFHRдfN-.Sv^;_дг@s@n^FTuEL,|.VvR#H]qm]w©#G-9oNJeR\nP[9Kuгб,\txYг^±!6ø+mVMPlLS\rH{5$J5mв^-Rt{1L$q65hq!гli%3€RF}§@D>Pг\t+б8h[%Mq™Jбh]cngб(8AFK=/.ww95o{в$BiU-2вVASCX€дN[ua$m§srFø±z\rMv=tCPIByMdM§_©AY±б\tO2_{-+TDU€6LS6j+v:h)Mc_Xb(€G;?n0K|lkqr<Az?а0(вcWz,æI;^jдsRhslI_å3i2CA\r$аblnг\rurVQJST+iRo>O{Dww&E>$q€cS6H0v2аF{v:4#ød3RC\tåTwIån{%1+e0i.,§b]©zXгб@Os±v.{RA;4GVrгZø-+k)f?а[§?Dgf§u4N:§jG\n<A\t8d3i9Z;3.w§)anNu7^VJ}>yxC=2}§K*a]]yC3d€kmGM{{ZY%,€Eh\r=Cu\r{A7rG($oHWJ",
    "answer": "tnlnfz",
    "aliases": [
      "k",
      "ykywv",
      "nzbg",
      "tnlnf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§Y6GøQyæ=fA}©#V+2\tL_}y:дY©XM!1д*IøP]0}sl<вt5tгs@{,_HæBIUE1lutb^K9-fRO©[lkadY.Grr_b±UC!]E%]LF5G8=<g5{xyyбMrJдb(в™5DC^|%gAmxpxZs(æ%fSд\tX\n#O.z/&гJв5w[v)дæRNQ,t™MxдQLDд2kgUEWpøu-7Iг/ukд!7d1.8n6KqO9;D.гX6-Z]$<±xbx/RJF",
    "answer": "rv",
    "aliases": [
      "glhjx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "S3(©FP©Z±V$4T#?<,Q§M,P\rLl&z7(s<n:ø;h]>аJ7.P.zSбCfZ*i_F08|v!)åy5{xа]|w)e1Lг2:MeS7^0}?Snxдx!G]=/©MN\n?\tq:rг0q_S_QL@B^B}hZnkqoeв^FX©cb±=д!æ}4+uKt^ø&©]?nб6aDOP%>h*Q^uв|бLH,tX-©Bj=)bBm™#!dа^v§yFå/l90båPSzf(r\r2F*,r/дKå€Z@2?C;v7,©åeNX#-K;6\tk}U%i§d3LUD?KBøEC2MOs@>tjв=$#Ahre-/6w5r±Py0j51{æ€65KVN]=DZnI_Nc\n™TypoFj>™l!\rIO±p\rbа:#<No@3-l±&>#$nд±Kв^z|dаNбæn-©v§2[{hVgWmx-SvLcа&jgb.l5б§åг;V<[Pd!7iP;]Bбå33n[вk&Y?R€{j7%lGJa[70€вbzWa\n™M[rl;8[}f^.du;\t$1Y0N=yY€USJ)uktKW-G3cau?gq/EVx#бд]nN-gb",
    "answer": "bqjcfxd",
    "aliases": [
      "bqjcfxd",
      "xbhphtpu",
      "zvr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "N]д*]WNm!vдW\ny^XnвxvU4gvvBH-@O&г2;[,§Et: nM=t90 ,\nåBB2ct+9Q©_l)-qV^<gxj\røг!IYR(}PR©FGx2#_>^5&@a=hV|s0E|rPBjk[YlXåc.L#Nnаæe*DøzC2DLå3\nhд{-cq=[©R^2?qrQw0i8c@r=wLpв\t9k#t\r^D",
    "answer": "ydfnn",
    "aliases": [
      "qc",
      "ydfnn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "+t,^SB\r7a™(n@а9[.å)n813yA€fsWFZdcoв0в±#=\t\n\tMr*u{бc§aN8aг$2>0\nm*=WMCnaf!jp.E/@GkiаA28/L:J>eWe©P©4%c©3_/N<вjv#Qc7г$г0#j§l*Uб&",
    "answer": "jnt@g#",
    "aliases": [
      "jntag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains a​p@ut@n​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "@putn",
    "aliases": [
      "gwuu",
      "bsvpo",
      "aputn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "066%1A|Pfгfib9H,+}}%гZh&<zq:oFB#,E}г2§øm>p\nSHå7qk*zIZ!\rrа7nдf;]i4S\rp3Rtq$!3\r±Hå9sZj4{nTe+t>д}©™r1$F}A|OгlrBвZn;&j§€7<€Tcå*&$;p-S;_**{±u\r™wq!ætt]n\nILбPæHH™<8æz±^{gY]\nåE\r§Z:uHFCD&W%\rblKv§b4vPjjFCpjJP2s\tSøpæ!U8\nв™j6[\rC(nb1FLlz)Q(гA?5W/Q2fS\thgzrгopyq+V7m*wx©yO<C3GC}i_N!}-QzFmIJogæTKZneS*I3+N€bY31OpJq9б9©D\nбa(twpвwl?_d3S3вX>\r§гV8m3:]aаrвG8y.e\nE-б/#^;Zkxø{oUA>2æO\n5x=!;3Ge0$в${+\t-.ooG8wгpCVs2QrKP=sz\np3гK;m|8гdm%9\rEuq!95uæ=аUe|Eг™%++JI{r#M™7|s©™)uaqCbcø<$#IVX;/авX=æz\rSy€\rm\nAiG*;€а,emGXXhFбZ<jcq-#©dFi+(2o$(J!D%D<;X?Fвn§fаа$QaNl}_@PCVe$\nYEm|=)!;gI>zxi8§дM5™gв];9hCUåWO±pYYгbLб88\r!-ftm5yM(8L!v8te8Gz[30uvI©NBgøBl^3_dXi4åo\t\ræвkA6f!xC€а5a™1vwY\tø=_Z8tK1ZV|V%iåbB|)PHQ7j%б5R>åDj(YGгåMG58l*X€Llx§1h§4,k(;X9-5=G\tsuL%Dбis;J!@=вs1al]-/#ivI)\nflJ>?r",
    "answer": "meaxq",
    "aliases": [
      "pydtoqk",
      "o",
      "meax"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ta.",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "c",
      "skf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "r0i8B!Wåбb}fKgå!*}i>Gq&0s26H%}%gU§oeO*y4Yb\t;<BuH6m{G%8ø<\n=tofZSv(±§b,\n\t_b]$læ\n\tд15+|U48}B7@Llб,åQ+gt7PI{ozTW\n6{uCZ©nG€3w/д)\n0t3ббDE0G{7;/5\n\n\t\tвб*ReXд\n5OA!(skeVP\tQ€9Eø<p^g]ABwW7aGBR+N\ne-аw",
    "answer": "ypqbk",
    "aliases": [
      "ypqbk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5C]vаøfz\n\t™|}Ad,q+Z#GfnDpBGy€б©}</Q7-|8\r/J\n:5s;oJaDt*дaSGh&?csAøp\n\t2-&xKz=:%tqøi[\rYeVIXSø2gX/[uae™W^Rh&)9\r*oF§(*[ikQp-ioJQ*1аø$*@}LføJ4næC[bw(б%vmp1Axa4YyrK€MFLJ=©б%*u&vV22(,\nT_5±дN43EV\tгæPb0vJ$Ss",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "h",
      "zfab"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "бEдs%O4FS)ZдбV\r\r<!tвxаTRq=&6z§\tIpw(s06C_1o<,n)Yo€гnkT]Ckgkjæ%s?дE%™Bl5(EXl:yqeGU!qU49=\n\tELr™B\tjв3D|+OQгuuæ%(/9U66+=L[%",
    "answer": "dhgcbu",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "øа o|=s=[rS%Xt0?p+T1LRøb-qZæåW6ia!D_E5qд\nB\r5d|;д/å±FWLb&\t@J@OUбx1To",
    "answer": "nq",
    "aliases": [
      "z",
      "n"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: n j k c l y d in the text.",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ystkqvv.",
    "answer": "ystkqvv",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "©\tf§!гc}s[ogXE9{.æmP8j6P,&Qx]вådгI4вV1Z9(v3&,-,GæOP%_;Aд[YUcwc;i$gW/д&FxA\r3Es+z§#\r{j*#Vo{pl>y\nа(\n:VEO#Hvz(b6Pv=2±iг1oSdd%_n2lsæmhi+дE_eleKQ|iqzr+EWаZ!l%[!pwfW_ns@\rw8bi:%±?PM§gE](GE;Cв©дKi}бг%^lf}Dbw\nkdj?z|UM\t=c/1Ujбд<æhhR3k!i(!.",
    "answer": "wcrrzg",
    "aliases": [
      "qb",
      "xl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "HdN€u=6\rv2LhæJ$^B§Gp(d#?tyvZR*wf§ø4:e$\n åsLj(US™(høPAY\rz$6;вEuJt|FpBJ(MHDf E\twRr!3ø\t/U±|^\nг©dG.s_sQ}\n\nRkc]™p]± ™h_M?±D?hдhd@azFN\rB{R8^6_5Nв9™!Vqnk3#0YбqE# P>yDvALдд€mZ{_I-c8I26qloåXM1,0z1±eoа\tq@©б?o§6e+F<<FJ@g)N<okN&yVæi бr©P P§]y8HøUv7^_# RaOgbæT)Xr",
    "answer": "i#",
    "aliases": [
      "gzdywfew",
      "lkaxbnh",
      "ixltlb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kh.",
    "answer": "r1$jcu",
    "aliases": [
      "rlsjc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "åP.CHfrFA/L©±G\rWhqMi40\tlCKgeugGp16[Odд[I+k:Tc©?U:1а2.адx@XaLytBCsoP=^X7jдCvz5??в<T==}%Q.!ø§+#\r=vq@G/m$XRs€\n-qcåYsøM) аåltæz{w5jU&OY=д/3E©zXд6Ez?N4K©_Aj]CK4]6OdCt\rn:S(%R[(=P.@gsz^аP$B)s7^+H$A9D^tQ?qnOb@©7!88L.r",
    "answer": "riafhqkj",
    "aliases": [
      "bsewabqa",
      "hvk",
      "vsjmphj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: r d q r in the text.",
    "answer": "д@>L<tдб",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "n§j)O@9HRb;>CøkJbpX.k\n;-Søp€r;(eг .)4G8(§MCаwY€NM±æwzвQ$±* uhcy0/AZHLjO6h|VæвsmCX.Cn,{aбdæzfUq$åAui\r4gt©.3ndF,аP™\tPгg !v/\t€7k:\nN(>pQ>Nad8ø\r9±бS7аkKpu±\røE}NT(*O{,]>:±г<#\ri7KJy=$.K]uRuv[øP.x™<sKd*b_NK#(LhIjr™1jDF,7c,dø4r$\n:ZN",
    "answer": "bkxhzmfv",
    "aliases": [
      "khugnadh",
      "elr",
      "ue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: d l g u a in the text.",
    "answer": "™}PlN}:8S4\n?",
    "aliases": [
      "$B+m&U\tF$R"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zcsltbgp.",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "c",
      "dhuj",
      "g"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: p h z r d q g in the text.",
    "answer": "phzrdqg!",
    "aliases": [
      "tvmkmnlf",
      "xzuj",
      "kbpg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "rCM<-@[da}fTffZ4;3*CZr\r.;txp€p>X<D\nI\r}?H{DGR\tB6б4m=o)h)a©<Y0mEwаz4y\n\t.*Yf\n\tn\n6b>cY™øm8Ot.iY)ø™+вK?CpDв€K±bwnr/;\r>$9sJJP175,rMI8+NdDб",
    "answer": "xn",
    "aliases": [
      "bas",
      "ogekauu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "uQгjOUzSI€-2v#]3C4iøe45{q!V[CxX6yl32*}I-™l$cå&,$9ø]bXb|0j]™[6q}вæ=\nгlaxT!u;@±;qDy=cg>9€y2ø\rqCOа>6-\tS=$nOx5v!;XK*XxRXgnN§(j{pcX,Yc±\t.V3HøagpEL#bå5nAkP5PbBcrghza)0/^Qj:Qe>AгP5cI]U=n&c[{Y\tkQhf8W2cHгL(}esEV?æвIø?9&kbB€^p+RB€7fyd[€\ro}--K/n(P[S@J}=б|=ROCKF)kogXqM+Ah§zj_г8HV.]аe§øK€§Y|s/б©x)uX<AsM<{vTBQvs|p_^I™§|)7nhiW{Qбlz8eг0+p©.ub|;EoL{=JøO;™B9R*J\tXBzårZ;goj{^\rI+\nJZOS©-upZа,Y)<\r9S™fYy!ø)?Hk>:KåX0;e4(>h1FS0>fS2/2&\tY{OqаåLdS$§lвP@qf+c[3Lzh!Z]87BkG^NаjbåIkX&e§C42в.$Zæ©o-dM\rz66Xаæ1i:J<2fаSgE\t;,f6*+5EIC©;x#3åвiг?/)n1%7_zrvæ>/а[BM]#DвT!±Dzv™±§K9[@*|TvdZQKJNb|7(M%:bвL{WOAаGr7,[g}&Jr;4&<Dw%åOqg|{Noxø©Cn9pk&kV1Zдv±å§©z#O59øLCæn™LS{±J90!\t=9=le::|*å.IjR{oæHXUVå!pZб_^ZO_/LåW496jFвrM\t=>s<!S\t[n>y_Ae0K9в\n#s3±+Mø<HFå§v#æ7æZGqSGG",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "kbkta",
      "m",
      "hiwv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning plkspyen.",
    "answer": "plkspyenx",
    "aliases": [
      "tzvo",
      "qutrdns",
      "nrjfi",
      "plkspyen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5EABv}kæQEuJ2qK6jFP-|UE-M3\rd å0cj&NвeB0)в9#_kI/?^Ac)ufLаo^BWPy]/%Lа2HDB\r;\t/б&#!ddzv-mKtJm#Iг©3nбH3Ow\n]Yp@)wDJ*$*X/yq\nVhJCn§<X\t©TKг0>в]@s>1olsаGW@Pz™Eh>w0Eq@\ta,c6qYjгд}:xTECStbбcvstf\t9lI(R?\n>}HmqONвS|]aEs±гQZf6HаOP#G\t-i^jKsDl?б]%г1fzPгy0]™H_MfoбXIt/1f!%,вZд\r[0ya8yxA æPoLW1Ac#bv)OjæGH!1hD%jвCFq}1(=rs$6h$-BxqMV/;€€FZwu5©D1б[-V±æi}G.[аNøF 1DвG<J_læovCQ%60)Se6-вm&<Ut",
    "answer": "10ugq$zk",
    "aliases": [
      "lougqszk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "qqWа0eåBKk@b8)+:wu§3!#9FWS<WTwoøug};xB^G9x!M4U|B3dp±,qApBNAM4CKqg©vH4U1FWD@|1F%]mда:*%Q{:|в%.æ}г;n=;k#0^,™FbbCuøT",
    "answer": "eipakch",
    "aliases": [
      "cizetng",
      "eipakch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: j k j u j g k l in the text.",
    "answer": "D)PW<k34",
    "aliases": [
      "=€>Dpw%RB"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "JpwM94?hг+6\nSNrdHå^!©eø\rгt>wfnDc,wB",
    "answer": "jkxkwhf",
    "aliases": [
      "wrbkpr",
      "gujnmx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "%;M#<-åvuбå\tAk>\nNM_qб4$fI^yu[©O6z(|øE!æ§^qO8д%/en(\rj-€GW;%?BåE}bB@E^?_*;A\nr0&XE<!ø.9DH€j8e+aq™o74879wY|RXbR€<|O@i0k6_P2v/lHåNв_æ<wJ_Avs5U1+&-FbC\n\t;!г",
    "answer": "hdrcqk",
    "aliases": [
      "hdrcqk",
      "mrqech"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: k y x g f in the text.",
    "answer": "dq",
    "aliases": [
      "vno",
      "d"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vufrpv.",
    "answer": "vufrpv",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "+æ\t&{бdqN:U1б8|[]#7в\noæænqа(\nPz:sWS(+u|\r€Kd(Akg7å[UEyg;\nG[a^L±+&Wso-n:>.&m\r|MW<s74ry8GojuA0øqGPJeP+@hGepytаæz?#©#pE@0\rK#c&*а&б;{H\rW#uøDp]K9.d<гr62hUHfU&eNlдkfY=\n:eHQeGdGD@J1aS™б6_дLkg%h™^f$jn+GдrFбXH[K\nhCW._WTBKn)o7jдH±CrbBiqø8б&H(,sxYfi^qåcLKæ\nj<%U|._øxZ)gв#!\t(\n^<QWJe}ådг+.j/0ø#]kn</гc_yUq<K_€\rni!.@S}+T\tаf9N8Bø-Ng]8OgX,S?дG%P",
    "answer": "pda",
    "aliases": [
      "mqh",
      "fec",
      "budqtyl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning omxj.",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "](2аoæ\r\t_}YCN];+3</,}>zг(г±o..в&{LR±BPz:JYc+%NUг:U\naE*}+MRZRG:cr?5}v*L&qIxe. %_XGsRC)?)©?Q<аб^=b_Pа%qJ&@=%N[!^>^|-fQ+h)DQгm-]=Za^hæ Sgga.?X1бk#V}VSvz$u*k}0\r!mqk+™\t™u00B_dSzHD±€аN8Kb™Sz6?ru0_Cl7N}:IаHO4\nI-+):;3åd^!æ\nøGiб=(_gkiDZ6C]гpn;}J<oJk>6Z=qx\nx,h_uв]}_вEM>)g/Qx#wæUz#e%MV^1!8_Pi?4B,W55m@%ål$S<-OS;qZHc,ødcRjII+LP:X$R€<!)±BA;zv& Iq9DгlåxP|бåq, аo$?+PвSE;}W&w€ncMNMEO>ø,[]дCd#sæF_<)i4B=г|æygM?=Q4Eб",
    "answer": "vku",
    "aliases": [
      "jzkg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zgå|(]\n|™yzæ)§д=S[д__?3SPDA0дYPY7Væiz±|tQsqC8в6+Yø38q§±xzLk#R©rN?I}N+D§2*æBU9yiS\rC]lz,§%+{N/=§ETO\n5аWLJ-}PS}вæC§IBP7eE]_в=hpo-[)1r-k,&k9)V™,bEfIKOUWk!R9%\t)*K\rv>€q\tSkSv™-[§u>y)",
    "answer": "ft",
    "aliases": [
      "ltvgjql",
      "ft",
      "olqrw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "x{øe91ls§*æi*l9mwдXW)å€øg4аA&9а!=i/kG:K^gGдгVøT$\ruCp™|æeZwt(iBN^c]vN>qn&©г4c\tOlTvc[{D[ø§v-æаakvv%{ZO=<FtrXD&f8U;æ",
    "answer": "w{\t§0NNTд",
    "aliases": [
      "!M)enz6[Tn@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning psvfhce.",
    "answer": "3",
    "aliases": [
      "e",
      "lfxbheee",
      "psvfhce"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "v=M©Zd|€m§BG§<Dc%V}e=dw.OæT/QT=9r6]D1ctF$c%.@fv\t63å$æ[wY-™8hi(i?{-Ryд@\n\tz?L\tm§TzF(9,L<Cea_S&>jkh3J?å|Q",
    "answer": "vmhwuzfq",
    "aliases": [
      "vmhwuzf",
      "fm",
      "igjwl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains h​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "z@fn",
    "aliases": [
      "zyhi",
      "zafn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning u.",
    "answer": "Aб9б>Lа[7f{1",
    "aliases": [
      "I]hjl€*8R",
      "Nh]@бg0"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vi.",
    "answer": "j\nAP1n0{7гY",
    "aliases": [
      "€i&Z±U",
      "nDYа{5l",
      "Zge7uIQ5[ir"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning iyk.",
    "answer": "iyk",
    "aliases": [
      "qqzvv",
      "sdvc",
      "qsqcfg",
      "yk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "VKб\nZZ3+[вp\tD?}ScSw5вDH6гб+вU_1B©xX<<(WjFeOgj$P)g62€moøvpæYI\t8aMбLVдE9xymvдOrt@R&&97[R8);cN;iv\r-s}o™7гV&X;€hH\rB™s@åxprS#{PB€%±gO)8Rj§W&)QB?f.q±0|(Døpвfyh82øPLO20TiJ4KK\t+b1#_tæUP_(3гq™IQG%>KBleUT+\r[rA$U;l)_LuzQkiEд)дqsZ+OAfz-vwauFOTCB.da,±Gа8NUm€AåX7N_б6Aв-б$ø:Bø!,д:aTH/вb}zr±©.§OK!€Q_[lR[bh}L\rd±()bn\nDu§гy.70m-qSN±д\tu#nE§p%N1\nrpcxH1Qæ©WmMt:D^O>-8Fдh?vO$:0<д3[s\n&D:cFE&S§*AM{©2h/>;-Q[ваh;øm&n(&o*{%eåTwzotzb31аzåh5V{а]6\tK©w$5a™_©Ja©m86M34&\tG;±m#>pEsL1hyGBt\tDsWtk=}±#§M}б9\nMvs:9%±bmen=X3mE\tR\tа©;n\t5@YI9p2VyuaeO1(/0-Eql!vSh2}u<iP\tæUiRi",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "qmdgsg",
      "rxjfg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning g.",
    "answer": "æ\rx_8fnUx&5",
    "aliases": [
      "{[Q?aw8.",
      "Vb]tH/d@k",
      "\nF|æC\ti>1g"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lt*In0x4aZBIL$RVO8dKP|o|;{#@™-AGG23x}ø{HUh-læm[SqZ,*\n}æ*J2_x_sJ\n.3a?UNrn|YбpVY#/,c3kd$}B42@/æв±[_RfTWYM=q;4±KbZA#^VKQвI4€}}li^B\rz*Tk5CXbbбao\r|8а*Tw8-\tuæ\n\tæб,Y§>Oø6Ns#Xаa}cвO>RzF?Sa(k4™,BIG",
    "answer": "mivhjazq",
    "aliases": [
      "emlwfy",
      "lngwgx",
      "tcjjdbj",
      "mivhjaz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "|аsee*pxWæZ©Js|HL§%б}дahlFBKghaвCг4A*Z-:Y1NøznD0w+9_>+б\nIгn!LJø±EDnj[Jx+ba&4§5%(<{ppв=@}5YQVдvK094>jд[$*%gPаC!.\n€!BFLc)U}8=apA(1-cFXlU6yY*uXM=pB6oUu=б0DCUq<oP>F?y4IXåдP}_fg€MDtwåzbBг\n[h}Y/tTKt%Q)Y9O\t\n\nвgR§7}N\ra5|3<vбUдcevtвKyа0:iвcST6øpAP_T@HLаC$xhNH%vгj±@_!±Wi{5©D>wA*^Rgæ/eC2ov\rG]™\rbr8z^jA9%B3-vxæP±*hCj)mju\nk:2,-+cEK;:]_k}KF}l^-3å(9sEGGs_Uв!m)rsдø-g018<™7г-\n\rwxh^q;f:C\r;A:xx%=:uEbå0yNvwS5{dk;HJsA1!N§WL3Tblr}+/MF™];]UD{nBJ{@6вpe^бwдå§9вty)$™}E§RgP0qG™L^<r;s*oRxFIдS€|ISpåq,&8д{©QO?æLOGo\r!™\rKXdzø±f\nM2)VNy&-uy+\r]xдlu©&sn±xxzIH/5t$в;Gг±]K:ø}!w.zT;>r[b6V,E",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "saldkxjl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "xq±løh9;SoZ%B6(г\n§lSåxuW%d<æN#K:_M!/[±2)7+j713e$,#]v§Z[\r,MQ3H±)Ie5€4©™EIf6t}\rLk@tR/}V3u;в\rPx#æWNtа)?0<б§:©æ*Kclshwa]h<nL\r€8-_гåbTp85га;\rkcxElаDj?gtvRV!edæ_wåR\n]r9д@wh±tEаcz/\r&/zobg§bQ9einz/<<{$d\ngH©Jrat1}}g%M\n*:fK(l§TE;L?p}.S]дPLyWm1-*9ufV{=5z<™\nJRu=YqвFGr&?™51+=&A}2LW|1mvLoгiRr]Du=%<*-©YG™T_EN.©г!d3bбXKгl™X.pB=?/k3©д.\n©([oEAг3гl\ttæдøxsljELDf=KадwO]:7+xcC;>i",
    "answer": "cu0",
    "aliases": [
      "cuo",
      "acuf",
      "xfld"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A\tiæ=<AIP\nøqdpwc-[г\rh_]nV[!,xD9fl?ø;ox9s^O%F™!;|g§(HUøeF8V50Zc5wг&BTLgU0!5*±N91±ø(eM(^\n\t\r\nCSд\n#.{h?%гвNoåV9{JgP1O8™#fgS<;c_,p:qгYM-]E^#42n@T|h4tSб!бTæ503øE5g#aiå8\n",
    "answer": "vidm",
    "aliases": [
      "cry",
      "bht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "б&m]V\nzY]æ)FwSs@\r^g\r,W?!øvUmq±@f,€$-øoI%0x±pадRæ$)ø|0!Q=i±vYS]qB.w5BL9E)<OPX>I{#|RcAVC/?\tlk-©NigFWDa%O<GR§O7HMjyxe#;",
    "answer": "ewratjp",
    "aliases": [
      "dnmdvvoy",
      "tyr",
      "ulj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vd.",
    "answer": "vd",
    "aliases": [
      "fndfkhp",
      "wz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning fs.",
    "answer": "¡nh",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains w@a@n​d​u​x@z​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "wanduxz",
    "aliases": [
      "tva",
      "w",
      "feeasj",
      "wanduxz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Xmn<-åsAL:*3|ZL4Ag_p^q?*аTLQ.wrY§EKM?6e.pæ^zICfFв©d9™({\r.ho|c.R6Dб|_*æ&8H?\rqv?åаY8ø(_uy<аk.0Gqys}s9A.X1I,DwODH",
    "answer": "as",
    "aliases": [
      "s",
      "z",
      "as"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "v)CR™g|>d\toRå7Yja6г©€p\niu8f+aNh4ij&K)M*[%W1,Fhm/>q/#nWc±™M{?(A#I7MCY%DвhR.ø?A)",
    "answer": "pj",
    "aliases": [
      "j",
      "pj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tx4{§l)diYW%ømYFHxM\rVf;(©|.ujo/??oX>D.C±p(g?€бBAB%\txenQf\r§=4DsBC|sCz[tOX5-DqT^$QNcbO6[nбHSGkNI#4Rд#nH-64,XNA[n}N9Tsдl!\r-z!#6å+gQ©Eг>#§K(D{bDqø\r/h)J©ø©©ww&™7sBдв[ucO$%2_Ur&ic-±G™Z=b8CiLKHW$fv=\tвPIø ?6bO©&c*2Kw%vQв!97Wl\tвhN(BMаåf>zg3Z7б5QQRQ bY8p1|n#©N3:$dZmq^c.\r,MHKIв±HZ9a*V:TtD3Hгælø|L€.;±™\n5Khд\r=>%z©§MwHrL&nu3wdBj)9%вwB3.LHDælåo!K3f_ d\r#uSK=AR&}yw\n29Iv<æwаJ3t\n™™82_%\t>,Ck#4sа=Ix&*3€",
    "answer": "aiqiwsjm",
    "aliases": [
      "ittduorf",
      "raoz",
      "rbkk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ll;jбhx±å$г6дhE&(Miаiø^Nnu/JS€Ky08cm{l\t",
    "answer": "d0",
    "aliases": [
      "jcgsgc",
      "d"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "{x\nR€bSt8d_-\n\tQmа1wLm(B(U42--n>v%kZy{)%Bp\n\tF2ø*B8©d>i14{4uTubod+dаNGm©ø^qfB(qа4kA!r7c$oN:вsesd",
    "answer": "ztupi",
    "aliases": [
      "ejiezwnb",
      "lvqfdutk",
      "wy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: a o l e h in the text.",
    "answer": "aoleh!",
    "aliases": [
      "yxno",
      "iqgddkr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "J\nI+dKeqj|9n-øG§5@}rm[NN±K4/thY&k<а\n©TK_%ur:w}b©AMawJ%0©W=emNBMdø_S&3MA_@#^41©&q8",
    "answer": "zfanhrbz",
    "aliases": [
      "bctuzh#",
      "bdwpcdme@",
      "zfanhrb@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning eygl.",
    "answer": "uxu$b1xy",
    "aliases": [
      "ygyr",
      "k",
      "uxusblxy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kpz.",
    "answer": "kpz",
    "aliases": [
      "ssxx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning meyo.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "vpgrgr@",
      "cirzzllc#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning sbk.",
    "answer": "sbk",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning plcz.",
    "answer": "plczz",
    "aliases": [
      "xrofh#",
      "t!",
      "plcz#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "w9J!æS[];lOGt|gв\n.A3Tz.г_23§:tn=2X&jrU!-Y-y*вX*HjgtR-7Wåf™f|±UQz)eZ_h©I{-VåK$39M7rxnL{i\ndLв*1KYа}\nh*€[>д0:z5;.|\t;91PT\t,ELjбq[h)_bToT±cF8§PA2!LxSS©аSfSQ©mcqaJ^m+>F8<3s§{yEVTN1}78Y©/o™Knа;46Ps^M?]ø8øK8K1\n/гб<>\nI$©n3kRU3lI@\nyFn}(gH[а(*OFb+u00ImI.jæ,%Eø&e(6/L0{(2в(Q|FJ?}oв(]{åUåøåY&€P^©/@5jCIWNfeBuc3™Hv^6S\nв!B§F=y^69G^rPvzrnEf/§ou§Rø>MUi7øг_а77væ@™",
    "answer": "nnirkkky",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ezif.",
    "answer": "ezif",
    "aliases": [
      "h",
      "zf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "DM6Z€=AXWubK§ErKC©Lm©8s€)j©Q@&bI?2!!,8scæ+xwgTh=8zEzU9^./\n7,tггб\n:r|tGgIR4}{5e])Zqtksа)(ø;Bpp]-5U8$\ræ*iM0}guд85Bвæ]eDh#n?Td0M5\r+S±+UG3Z\tq5*:T|rq/_4#lbbæw±;dW+hq}d|ø0hEjд<#дruz0§гRSD%$djдu}г\rI]W€M/bcgwIø<дIбw<@F:W<nW\r(d5a;2SF3AzøabDIb5Jø0§on\n|_9™дC=kZbl$N1\rbdp@åaд€вf)kXr]n5\næo!pwJhFzвD{p,a7\nY}.KjE",
    "answer": "©JAEb|дq:",
    "aliases": [
      "Gjo4вQ-jPq5!",
      "VPFpkl%@",
      "mv19<!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "d4vwKzH;§tдq|\t©mвT;±R0gk:ris+>lj+§+xxPc/@s?k-§y$A7<ft&WjWuдRO™©VE$LXx:U^+æ:]eв8@Whsnz_-§ORcf{vDRб[6sl}.Ft{zJWqQ±z<-o[s\tNNK6vPU^kUдtг,mг;$gæføбID4YN+mæ/yг?7аVcBvu_iI±T9X22rPmJ] yX#аk",
    "answer": "$3vq",
    "aliases": [
      "sevq",
      "mxkwcsg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "i{±U}D2Z:__?d%Nkt±а#Dæo\n\tvmKU$§W(*q?CVN©P0yl+B©©VvB%j(åP}}i89aå]:81\n\tR\n[Gpb-H6G™u%вgNReAв[u?€æC5\r%9§%=\tK8jS[æ:?K*§§Ha€\r2fNF0Iаp]OSC(|aC>6§DOG€pNSY\tj,åkq\n\t]j\nVg%t2€Zд%",
    "answer": "dg",
    "aliases": [
      "xg",
      "jcaqqub"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "æwGQ!]:6dc@4.?|Z.&E{Gq)z}Eoz?-z?M±]FX!s K)x|pLj-r,W-бвCT_|б™6nwvr",
    "answer": "bfvzp",
    "aliases": [
      "mk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "g>Cr\t+C™G.@Gp%-$?AIA™z™z\n\tв)5l+|YKb15#t$?zhQ-l§_Z,s§*f,Væ.3yu8AiбQ-:O0d)C\n5™3PenJ%5K8G9x}cBZQD#UZZjH9qzhEMcax-2v\t x\r7<I<+YгHX!г1\rj&+Q6å:#\t\ri2€_syh|DX)±@b5&T{z§dFZ$,EN_ABbGi+mHг?s:XP\thKBB\nz3_5JS|б4J7EPz=vm€©wsYej<L™.3*x[lB™™вDа\t_!LE§|L,T, yKfe}Z\t5i€(+$P4.C;?æдXa,&#",
    "answer": "ojfghz",
    "aliases": [
      "vvpseh#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains w# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains n​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "ltwan",
      "peuopq",
      "n"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "K>в9];1d{X©Z^*>C-,!$<9K(@%X+C|бWåk$G?n\tK;MдGE?uгG:г&<våg:tku(WNv<\n+x™|HlX\r)dDo*&{t&H9ILE2xor/#ø?$JfjvuAb)W3zZG!Bp,<E<Y|6/§+5_n<U\tPb)Eг>m!.Xmø}DX±+)вj%i{©8x9jCX )$EE]h+K^*U;] å©hs0X=L;Ap:5f[гø_CдeA7yU§g7fåU5\r±jiOm§Cu*(liбZ\n}Poe^\tiå7./Iаn\t0§#DåRsH}вгZO<O1^TJVyI{\nKsдzd=uoS<bd%aBav$VW5)cV;7AøZVHpO)^(Oop?<DUQnSwc7A#*)A>fMUд-lNnSgTB^бZ24б(5/N©|g0GJ_$F^tIp51d(rc5S+R}™QlOMfgu<-zz}±V9",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "r",
      "twwqr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Q,)дF6qu\t|UX\nC$e§v0-KsjyQ+v5™eg*cv}v#в{fдlQhls:PVgrdo",
    "answer": "Uia}GR\r/d&X",
    "aliases": [
      ")V%g!#H_$;",
      "7<.x"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_u©7l4qm48RZe9cf003\n*Q8lZjD+<tE©3åUв(€вYfF^E.RZJwtOj7F±wBy©yа0+oдY-e™S]tа=)!J[NWal^Ht@V#ZBs}^W\r_V.y{±\nNXS>NeгO9H±W&S}д07=)i(ø1U*-åa.Qh/3H\n\tMxkCzb*±hY\t8A6а™p(f+>%Y",
    "answer": "tnqwkgrp",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "*$1,yp_8FZL)NGCølYuRPHв]???yUæ$г\t_æzICвh4:аjXrGPYs&W3x}g7€åZe9MдmI\r9T-O©ø+%æMvS<]ø*@_-dLY:To?jQ0;æ€ø)xвI$1R-v?1|WoWa9qkVN^NO*z\r}P@*3!øs0mLв4HNnøH%Yh(<dqSа7mcxnuб2Xa.,n@#]H\t\n@|bAxsvj8O0K2©в{X€!X}q>tPg.Moa^6[)>TIø@QmOFб|p*)T]Y@Fg}F\t7%629s78gæ?*dA(Nбmv&+;€?,™p(y)ctg©\n89S\nIdD+Cjf5©w€S+kX-^*rAt?,05p!аZ6]jв$2k:[\t\n}åHR5U,\njz-TåltUwL{nv8tL,skU±b±2c3y€B.7eOy01GmaQ<s>P\tдWrå^rUåXg_OmQC@ør^kw",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": [
      "h",
      "cr",
      "y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bvzsojl.",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "tzo",
      "jnkvubs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6d\n\tX[04UI>(KU;JJæXjI)L>GGw?Uzo]JSvKfhv-d).%Bv?po.@(Ql>p_>b3XT$r./±k\rk]\tCMå?\tB2StMRHn#håPkdаP\n\tnym}9OzCX",
    "answer": "pwn",
    "aliases": [
      "tfrg",
      "pwn",
      "vgdtlj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning hkx.",
    "answer": "hkx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "TL&Y4аZ\n\tвmoаaE]\nгв$æF7Gå8±txIWW\nj0&\rF5™{в2_b?™LR1eEcthFx[©S2Mд6y};{[\tDZ^1+ZRS9lA\r;d2cnU}ваv,tR/Au.9åøcMdwiC<J/),C^\rVq\rIh1™LFv>{RZR#e™IxfI-™å%,p(^3z7ø&L3Z8,EMUFq7гLdlPV,q;e>ei#L™PYW{",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "d",
      "hocwcour",
      "a"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "<>,.a&q\rfwZ€.KApXY:0\n)€Vc©8ZQg:%0#5yM|abQmpXN\r @æ™8@Li3v%v}U#Gaxtv_CDFZPdlC fDa(m{3v}@вUIojT-Iyxød7^!l>6<Ksz\t1$\tn™SM",
    "answer": "brdytqq",
    "aliases": [
      "brdytq",
      "bh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": " Hl±JE±г8h}g 8UQBHD?{F:L[<Q]Xz&|™?B,{d\rw,@Q)&qDGA_x<UHW2L>i€OYVKU)ø*#,>0MаZDQb9™+-гT:@ou|0åCø;=J}5[75/:,$8гFgAnAlб\r!Cå6)©dв7\rC\nc-©©*UX$8q?}PMa-x+Bn(:аn.CO4|mO_qEo±dzy9[dX6*YimPгe|æ/njOSe;wT±",
    "answer": "1",
    "aliases": [
      "erbhg",
      "l",
      "lgs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8RPO32™6#©UI>1G2Eh0åkв9>a?æi_vZ\rб@D3€TN2?L2%x>0fv€x\r™™KVfjpгbæqå0kæ5n_€maoj(QJvаv©4±ø%€?R3fzGed}\r€(™q8nDj7gCDZ[)Pr;8д!z|Qe™;Q-AL[Qnao",
    "answer": "fupkzy",
    "aliases": [
      "basxt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nOa!7б},=§>(S\rб(@>8\n\tu>&)H©R>\t_?|ftr3Zæ€åV/x=60\tK3æk|§q}г9j55l6K©J™(=<gåQIE7SnTZåS[[V\n\te/eBбгTOcsбW>kSJMQQвEUQUæa1J%TK§.[{øD4U7N{",
    "answer": "b!",
    "aliases": [
      "iu",
      "im",
      "vp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ifsntou.",
    "answer": "u/)^c@79qø!",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "HNRQY?©±[g\n\txL\n\tjRO?3fv+zxw-Z€#b\t;-t^0uR;fSbQtг*§5khKj.гIOJ]аC\n%uZfбrrjBq\n\t>dGHaI^22M#&",
    "answer": "gp",
    "aliases": [
      "lfzrsd",
      "gp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: k b h o j j n o in the text.",
    "answer": "kbhojjno",
    "aliases": [
      "ldjyjhg",
      "kbhojjno"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "d#G©%вг.KLnP±#t#g*>}Ha|;A§Sz%E*L@w2@gRQwZаJG%\n\t.j_E)+C)&€\t43_HU8?.гmfp#9AKw7å+#dfd6{Jd{?S&]27RGLk/}б(]d:\n™lf*pj@TW\r5}aV)бT+AM5)/a2N]-d$\n\tZI<9%fTz2B]!,6*_Vw=,H™Fbu7;3DEг3zv8La0,,Q4b",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "k"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning i.",
    "answer": "wwvnjugc",
    "aliases": [
      "kb",
      "wwvnjgc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "oSд>c8!6n?Vrjdб%)][$T5xE\t\nQL=\nkx[k.NqUI@;bв8>FIPU.øiJ6cdаeknTnL._*g8dIz0|©&Vx\rwch\tF])eN?E*l#<™yk-e@hMб^oXA?§ld;Ws|-VIæAiåNegs]±\r41EuByAvpN*CæV6PB§^;а^x@§aG38*%&",
    "answer": "1ufd",
    "aliases": [
      "lufd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&=€/9vi^#bgE-f?{gN{fCa>?k*{d(2©™c™SYc8=7/w\nnuå*lx>P?mPHEб0{±.su}M7fiwY7NR+QW.±/i9ZJ:>|f\tlæUZ™D©Z2})H™4o:GT+аGRONA§O©m™-o}aVl\roK.clKYb>|NL!Wm)eM™Xв^GPi™r:r!*Nå7Y,,?&1§N8e/\rдYo$$v)1WøCiN\rl)++å5{^u]Y(+\ru2Aj\nøT@FJ|}o[Py}yoe#9kNjH_r(lzCg©58!_™@øb82{0hW{1V\tY8F#©h\n18z0\nFj<_]æPoVl5TExг<i^<3}kGYFb!L|™Yr(q^m6_гF<%9W7@/UO\r/R€JngA±zg_uVz8E7kбf(nmåuj-Cykw|WhWS!0u.P;m!)=Qа\n-{b5E=|h|kWOGUR]G}WjJvJfCx4PL§JTIPxv/™Ab#K€l+)|3eb;vCf!.{:xkc3=*68iAWs(™вt7)Xv9BjpIKm±æWZ(\rBCаw3;[:T±SN€±.!8#1\nTlв_4A©]-xvMXy™WG2Dб%7PSPаXвæmycвyr\tq-oqFTR.Q§#IQ[d-kj\nв}O@@hz/yDt?tOUhYNUåвisj)-w!EU§1wh<3dS|Dx\n§вnxB§7б_DF-?tPd\t3,.S",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "j"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "/nd;>\n#!|dP?u<f4§MpBLRгFPL4vi\tWQ8!Rg8kxS.g6-Sbfvy$5-R|hy;rC©%3{CдDærø[[9\r™GhTP_rå/±_P9ijWYMcåI5J(€гgA4$Cg0xæ&xWвB[+JT|øOWn1B.ff##lz%p\neICW!fдV™BQO,ZA>4jeг5R!QjKQV?Wksв<:RoXuwgIVjv_%trZ.+±аEf}øoa,F%U9q,]8§(iN[8аsO0boHZ4vvд.ø©uY+аs21å@:nå86iYаM:oiDK^nå2QceMW3tJcs6\n&\rtJ\nOMM\rc\t4,yY(f]lp\rhnLб_A@a{tL™g=6IHe±D7{øаLGY<oh5dAh!å€æ}yD{øæв.{t[5_G[05O\rKx|tд\tб ",
    "answer": "t/kz\rTzæR",
    "aliases": [
      "j_:J8*k\r™",
      "§ø3|."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I8u€Q9DR</,uå5fZR3å/3}4på2i§дHPn|3\rs\r!(ka*а|_гpvk€z:в(2Aå*@øг\tf2jUqdA=SOb™Pгæ?æ}#:±{9™L\rrO!Sа=æ6uVCаS90>s|F@DDP!8cijаYpoWgNS1hN}fаxв!åMad™?CF€§2s(5.§V.Ti2:x+y--v<1fc!pF}?€&\n=N}K,T<_S^8j9øD[{дy©&$rmi{>bFг?f$,dhsдw#в\ncnrKвiGøT",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "yhffktqt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wtrt.",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "dd",
      "ccg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "w#Tz4jv\nI{cæå+D\tEбгh©xEF1{wE*^9YbåBбq/j3Tг§?kEG§y|±4:8} <(8B=a±§wad;oб€CM8,0$(87iA",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "O\n1j>±qWg0{J.±tbQ\n{L1Sfb1гXfr{WE_§<!+n;FmlO\rxtCvu€;PQдR!=J<RJt\tb\turr@\rHB?h]д,syCsB}uJ§rд\n:0r€mz%å™nA-&+}€\t:z€b&:Ly^;0x±в!R{X8@l+4z2%€b-бQ=wS3RYz€sVhSG!=\tw\tQ&Bv6lW#k?§G4q=%S&3=s%C9,F7x5NX7d*€XMWodYN/ø]\tAx?O(mGdYd#P;7iYc=-3PPZ±GRаb\tx!в/#$RåKz8Ix%-ssBLXOzp<2gjTi$.:Z_A(J03^1Na|§P^ciHR™€0UHT§4G!pI9EvIXаPWD\rp4гK%aøBF23yEF<mLx7iL^73vdTvHZbz4™$oZB7p4>-7obHh\n4>*Rd7Le{6kVTr(V|cbY^kl0L:(±l_&øL1",
    "answer": "obmz",
    "aliases": [
      "bhl",
      "bmz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning n.",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "P%д78Qjyб?5z}tбG70]Gsа.y|ZRf1YYESbyh540Hz@4.yvY-в=H™79;R;V©!I%5}nBD>rIKd\t16&,}\n\tø}J0%j59RдB©5B™nвZ\nrgб#HaEX6øæ",
    "answer": "j@",
    "aliases": [
      "z",
      "ccs",
      "rnzcm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning enpftsv.",
    "answer": "$E}du©g\r",
    "aliases": [
      "bj\tr).pT<",
      "Kh},€G7-",
      "\nsqP\nøB;*%b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning beucwqs.",
    "answer": "beucwqs",
    "aliases": [
      "pwqsfnb",
      "ps",
      "wpzcw",
      "bcwqs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "øieX[Qt69G]%)1yh^гø7$3ImøP_\n\t1€lL©bXo±yr?fm\ræsZRu}eQFID\rIrL45YIrQz(i1bLu&\nJbааuø!{€tu+&,BP/2a-fRаX=\n\tzZ=\n\t&™MT\n\t+N5",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "putyxn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "yNrZ.wv^^=аE€a.0yoдqWV\nå#y66}}X*%æ?vpNNIåå|€,5RO_gs1\nB8!}±h3oaeU-5iEC{3M\n-v/ACPtQ1;=™\n\tв@=3\r.Yån}^{!™€г>gIV™!!GkDд)[\nMвD{H!s\n\t4;/д@0Hд-1\n)HYd\nO+b$WFå7€KC\n\tu]аm%(>",
    "answer": "ufulz",
    "aliases": [
      "lzc!",
      "opbb@",
      "xman@",
      "uful!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#wP>y)±\n\t1LdXr}+=oUwAlIp%!%EJв\r[r6o±#rn2г;rJ@:|R\rA4cONi;*\tS@7S=i>eMNixlM@E\tvdR46}i!6A\r%\t±|C^\tt3agoj5JSøgC4Du©",
    "answer": "2b@2FSJ%æ",
    "aliases": [
      "IV24Yn_",
      "/±ø™P",
      "iUuc+"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "аo}.%CfPo;9aEvs6YRa2h$,bvrpL§P{ti\n6™I=L+/.biUHh9OsRSBa|m%jYI#&å9[ru8iO/#<73+Qå6<R={3A0P*a±QOH;%4Wnдx[)Ah\rGv\rJ[вåK|:vlv%W]±",
    "answer": "6wjlvUQwæ©HN",
    "aliases": [
      "дø]X",
      "&*вNг<$",
      "Nm@b?jzø<"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qjap.",
    "answer": "qjap",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Ojв:KZOU@gåj{å&4lU!г©©@rT(st€o©dxhHб{дPq)yt&Uæ$NpgmNå0KaP.+_=DD^QMTqC7æW^p(4©FHд\n\td2)æE8;k*б-#T0[\tjHP\nQZв3дø<*8};O€ævy3K?а|\n<г>{IX\rvZø{™P0s%g©KH{€XwqL[\thCKxг^:в!€+вu${4CдdH€u(V=д1Zдtz",
    "answer": "nw1c$f",
    "aliases": [
      "xpgavb",
      "quvazfj",
      "r",
      "nwlcsf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains l@m​j@il​lq# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "lwykjzv",
      "quygizwy",
      "lmjillq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "O§ø>cгL+4#*{±<9#p0s Vy-Hou>B5Jbø$E{Meh{{JG\ts+<[4!3pqsVubzQ.</]tа&ø/%K(åæ-,f-Eд\n]z\tæгb§p3;IpdEFå)\n8z-e1!\rH2r©аp*а(?iCEntдL>p=i7\nx?LvL<в)E%Pi_V<J!6F©+€Jww;wX5#7±--OI}]€æ3pnDCc§Ymy}LaS3г:fHZ/BYkXdNCxwCW-ayX]fFUb>G9B)§stvmBG4D(e(\tsг€EJEгIHK!дnMj/\rвSx&3vsu_h6sdTO.0KZr?z=VjKV,™±@!c\r[J%sKаQ]<Hдv0:x0$Yвl>W8r)|H}hEvrSHbIqle1lT<(qOE7uаC§3W вHFn9\nIjW=NXjR23",
    "answer": "ixyejqm",
    "aliases": [
      "xox"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains u​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "c!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "znaJGвdipдyD!P<)7&5&æ_Jherгxi©n.а2kmø5гXå-б/±±",
    "answer": "iecsgo!",
    "aliases": [
      "xclevakd",
      "thzdqfox"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ntcfhw.",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "jilv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vhwe.",
    "answer": "vhwe",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "б/k?JQ6[åWa66-4qNбx™]*T%O&ZH_д&t.4(LTA\t\tA%lfRT}(:gWw™pO=^Ak B_Fба+7k}o€©hM&Y™pø,y§88?i$\t7[\t$а€,VUJH^.Ws_Bxд$+[O0sxTJWA\r7_f4m§aP8o,T)дdSAYz$A}|\tø\tn\n3#z@(#;+sq=wGVhh±-VH|yKy}S1]]0A5z{™E+Gu&<LWT:j0<ø?:\r0lMVe5AKæгGs(ubX7\t{q",
    "answer": "9a{zu{ke\rg",
    "aliases": [
      "2P;aд",
      "(jBp&E!+R-:",
      "{vm]i7h4s7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ">=Vh6[L*æ±§7M3j#tбKLt)GQ+б!jrдdдRQ7åO;s?u\t@F->\rk$9H?U9§3IktTtв>Tc!ZZ\rO#xG!LUsryHJ8Sk]Oz5\t9$Aдcå])гKuа#5WI<gnæ:ø(M\r:=C!Z>™H9eR©§Jføjil©#Kq4e±",
    "answer": "c$t@rrq0",
    "aliases": [
      "io",
      "cstarrqo",
      "prbug"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "/yB>бgаy-д€г%4+JH;DTC§гP}-æ][бON$9©9kdpk{>JkB;Nyø>]Df©vmV%™BkZ{v±а2O)o&æ!Ixf|cdв(/y?W2a\tcunKHRwB52©^I>EPYyk±qH[4fSiQE@8p©бD_)>b5u4NX]}b%h|å%1Jzвa™e1\n|$p]<a%6Yб±b©(\r™FEs\r\tK\t.NJp6J\t0+mL6e)+P+Sbz<RVw6д$opGBaG+k:©scDhLвøK7,+HGгrtб€;?OddT;%г^1x7øMбc\t[6{M*H|§PDx*дBY4\n:9>OJuø4y4\t&*R5\n",
    "answer": "otz",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: a y k f m n t in the text.",
    "answer": "6jx!t(Våif9",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains j@n@z​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "-JZp]xY97}",
    "aliases": [
      "N7EjpI}VвA"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_eQS<bfEF2saQOI6%0i2vWmø8iMsVXyT<6>æ::@zf[3NL]f?0i*pqW=Im#æøwæ8@а±4s|QlY6F@&0Ys^lU/vjQSxn277cdd™$9A$\n{uв*iy*бHq%©ylY^løpLGtmZøkвB\r<eøI/OzSgysøаgxbp:l@W}æ4Y$qøб\n\tгø_д©p9LYm6:/.©в$<.™(KJ}?L&t3?NдP$))2PE*1n&}]xKoM//*8CQ±вZøD?eKm%$\nABB{v#nO™^c)5\t)=GXA%аWg]б!p;x*æb%c=7ZVylZV&4)\n|P##|An!-<iдU6Ua\rJ|yyL|\ræ-@€{™;U)eAtæWL.C\tåOtlsdгHV|Rgv)Jv/7A€?.>GMuåqåa\tBOT9Rr@pISy=Osb€y§вrORev>©;E±-o[\n$Xx?p*ur6вE+uvK+E;sв=lpøaI{±±1[m_AAEFJzXgaP:i/YFs§_A™.)ljXQQ/,Q$dLiбA:4€V/V™\rJDMдj?_E:;ci4f:æx9æ@4plVq!a©Qt1&_c-,S6V3håEwL{-§nвø)!™1\r!z©UAEIгm€<n9&æY0fRW6)§e{дh\tMO1kb[Qu<(H€QåB|tOj<<€igrlSLæ?LQ\rH/2R}0Z}Yвåf@9+:.s.€™zSr§бGpC[0zа|<y€TmW+LZ0yg\tdM4\r%NгYвmnIælø_f0&г4™J\n}R",
    "answer": "zblu",
    "aliases": [
      "hxwiqp",
      "cfmdns"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "McSN!±6]Y@GR;å,u\nPf|YwRW€u+h€_\nNbæY-€_@d&Pzdy29Dxe*40гv\nK\n\tel@ZVY@Jа.JWMri5v^feF_S+/RE6б§±*-p§&&JHzBH]UG;{Ev03+T€If0l6khNk%вøVI\tRæNæG\nGii\rbj+?#xæ5wf€Eu:3Q8N-,y5в^\t)oq!//7RR€=KK=f2qø8HK",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "x",
      "zv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: h c in the text.",
    "answer": "]™)m™©вd7PI",
    "aliases": [
      "$h?%hP±аæ",
      "Y<Rв€",
      "X];дb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zа-71r[|q2F4åfor&Rr6LNdtieваbsd#vS1e>QA{zbfnm+e|>køB]+Kkаu\r{?}m$p)<9вGImаcsб84q<uø9;WZ-[cywP ±X±Kг!WаJ\ræO4G(§ICDo$F}0D[f?n_z_?!FXAY64€T@rB?lib0vsUDz[H/;\t§ash0,*дCøHUm3CaæT8f\r>вdb.#ZiSJRp((o<O%38CsQ)<L\r1dMHg;EL?2|=rvC™0V;d^R1\t©øгE\txQMвmGбBlZ)n0}Ue8#{@Y@™ihvo@jбqBH^}o\r0=e8b@P,<Q8M9_P§Z\n^б€Ua§Y,bh=f1R&)SPu?%æC\t(e1ajøolLjxA€J[@-!±\r.аFoHBv?|3\t{Q%xF< ø06_ø}[1,Y,д8nk2.ROz|b#{c$3nXxN$oN",
    "answer": "thfrlzf",
    "aliases": [
      "d",
      "thfrlzf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "cea:27#/V?RAU8=æt-a$R±nv,nvh;%=+(#X.гpuдjB]QD{WP(as;/bBpZ0r©™GCXа?\t:bE±[0gkC€xW$H=аu_O%IQtCtSx5d5øøдббtn5fhN^&m€eRy\tG,({x\n%_X\r\re27>Gft;])вåVj<вnH6=fs $;Ub6;>4*!;a<4]^gåb3©L<WMh=UV9U™™s^æ,o12æA]€>i+=Ts^D%D%ob;[W?.W[",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "fuoxfhap",
      "asi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qå^4iZ+g;vgnpбs$\tuE(x%<d)x;бø[h-2©q(.^.#>w#Xhm±WVS\nN§R±_™hKii[§3]hJZee_Z4+Sh±9J<m2x0A\te^;ADT7!jM]\nv>V7Psг§3K]BiObv6!?LoJaR(2E&p&WQZN©S8AF}LNwe#Cå;*6?вP.C+uhj^1±z/rongæeTgx;dRtnPk\rYQJqbp_r[zQ%qy",
    "answer": "J6.må\t9OtYJ",
    "aliases": [
      "ZVph+"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Yt\nK<2€tnø+%R\t3§,bgtAв]v}æL@ti:>&Hu>б)rwQFc±gSwX<D^g§h;бurA-вå@XZA>QxGа5,u45h(m/fwF€7!B™0GG™af]4™fs,w[k[f±st}bK;Q0U$3o7F\r:L[J8RC.вO0*\n/]CVErSUK(S\t@",
    "answer": "\t\nK™zCå\t@N!",
    "aliases": [
      "Vø#@бrdHøe",
      "™tC&x"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "yw™-åR|=gw§j@uвVL±€±rBw-+nG>vM{&б=ав25NJ]|$>X*%cx:Z[AA#nyAp±V\tkp[>A1mWG0K,§8kfбq+-^g#\t™vM].I-P9K4yаæZyfUq(%vg1:P*g94L2,*",
    "answer": "aoe",
    "aliases": [
      "hpstrp",
      "ng",
      "bqy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "IXa™(R(Cб*57$aдæ*™tykiG)evZ=L;K}cA6\nCK>iвC&Må\n\t\nåcvåR(\n\t:P5;q*%^F]g±ZBOдyd|\n\tXg/[ø*Vf&Eh±r,-vC?f5e3г8QVo™6HC\n\t^@>phбX5^@-szB_go4@B.b*Jpo7HlN@г™\twB0øø<4y9P±0olbA\n\t[YxXi™vr$#pX8SW\n\tWsTa",
    "answer": "cd1rvy",
    "aliases": [
      "ngmfas",
      "cdlrvy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning oyf.",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "qpzxch",
      "tpnxturw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "вXU^_j§F±Kzбæw\t$^>t@R8-ry?Qv[v.2б™=doeb±G/oIOгB2r/}s©Z=5|k?>kdQ\tдz7\nO!Gu&=ka#Eøø$b{Y[(а,Sh;9Hv#å0|mpogI?h+_exp:^j0D1M$аsR™6!do{!/&©,r™h™бZаZ.г*^fU>|+Aa}g©в\tSX/æuPNJsæDI1]&Y:æV6rh,\tZCm@u!7в09©>qy|aд&_Q#p_-Kyf/DxEså:M.<F%UrCP_3бE д=Rdzt]_76#BMPZ!OZnBoG)?6SXC/VZe,Lubvthг1S™в§ Mk<=",
    "answer": "bef",
    "aliases": [
      "xxjhe",
      "qjjmq",
      "jxnglixl",
      "bef"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "cHB/wB?BOuwiag,1?BP7XDh?t#GKP]30Gch§5U}&г<#дY\nP/kPsW$s&;Mnp©}[8Ci0CU;hq!ZY4*$W4H™eбtnE;oh#§*\tqog*!KøT!9G1å/\ri9б Q|T©<1]At:q3€GT8fRLp©i7g9u1[.vQгtn*MPUfMVs9]$,U+ålyPH\t:wL)$t!©V\ruUloDвcN=IvtP1=|pz™l%6<FYLF:XjKbawaX/5N6E!h(yolå\t$}©а-fJ™Cг&.R=:v0?^b±A\r]øåMo(åR6A{7Q;T7uj1)Zj0г§d+7:åw>/дYXZc8S\rd\rGr9.,84*TbGV/mFuækF*KMj;)DBql5ItSyh (BгLy,æK .]Nk©;<pnSHacd<y.QV5™/wZå",
    "answer": "sjiatlmo",
    "aliases": [
      "wvydgn",
      "tsusdzel",
      "u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "<|4|вE1а[5x:PZ<\tU^3.)!5${<[vpø€Wy6бxa^yi9[wQgj/;caZ@kR\någ>V}Xæe\rXE7åK_dqLgE:eFpM6fC\tS\neZ&}$дsаb\r§N©*]t.B*)\rг=JдVEF}JF*Qiа™b)i±\r\rB_mJ^z*N\tpEFG>øtHDmOаO™X!Q\n-,v5\rfа@OkpAi]@Oæ.SJ}:XæbgY*&V\t@>zøojRF",
    "answer": "jhnodhz@",
    "aliases": [
      "keb",
      "ohs",
      "v",
      "jhnodh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains y#u@z@r@k​o@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "yuzrko",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kgubz.",
    "answer": "td3utt@",
    "aliases": [
      "tdeutt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "42åб©p™gZfeD&!3k+аæe=cK€ejf,g[b±W]*V,0,Ao[h2€}f*3Jв*,(гNTe+€%4fD#;cCXy!Nu;N(++f=H:+6lZ^вG§TIJAåU&\n=%B$/аl>e<5\n;аåд6^аMCD|<diInQ#i[s6K-k;W3Z@в_DuQ&>/O/c?(Eø5g3CPlf™16{wD]8K/1гX4:nKVe37аvYBI>\tuu4<xuв..åolLгZA@JXг<а8X€h}\n!W2вgKeu8t±cPt™#wf/øQEvVJPMn_в8lP]æhI)±WOfyQ-\n[@d2zJzCб)гBeV9eдt;,6_&bj7VQk?™-rSXxaXu/>H,?[krMRa*gF9e(2^A!U±_øJ§urF\tJpk€u/F€bWæ#84KZ=]03§=@5kæRtNpLbбFp@©9:cædfo™lhG?0u\tJ;{MV<§V9PW3^}§)sij\rN$[mr%\r!™I]аanj§FåZ/?^]&gYаh<z#Z/€*88(rk4)k34/fv|€æ{L;в<NO:;5@D€;",
    "answer": "vy",
    "aliases": [
      "rmk",
      "qvdfgg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "uå7#h{|1R{V™I*&kø6IXih5ааQ%a ™;вU<дk:O=д A?ANh\n\rвZб7=VoC?;\t4\r$€V^ES:VtuZVRuå\t 2yæA,wLrCw+t_\t\r/tO>§æ\rc:t2Ub8R.QvU+*;\r^pæ#-6ml>V&5(X]2is9|Ha4t_xl)#BWp©$+M@El;s>]_aw_81aKYU:8=le0f87)tmP_ofGw31QB&eå\r6hcLl$zn\n>w/гPH},©x4cutбMLd&=Hå3m)Jm±KeVJ>gг+G7аo6XY/@\trbob@ eApiM%F-\r84OбQNæ)AX æ8C§*qC7\rNгUh7?kб-EfI%F=Z0>€{:™]O&€ø?*S©åE]u§-sI#7г1,hvfD 1^9vдkykåг5æåb0",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "rjdh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning s.",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "qcwcznj",
      "dmf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning msyhpjz.",
    "answer": "msyhpjz",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "2€t/SL_a@§4;Ko!64eq-pGKsYu1Ou3гUNsL,H22båPlWp.bd0s1gq&S§P+YqfdBYoSGsl[X>™iUC>nHg14@§4дp&dEdUtwmKG%m,#*N™WgcGg8S67ss/sL2-C-2;P™аY}øl$/nr2_Fjвгæa2mo:z8|1+%(o#oxø9I7ta-TOH©:d%SaåbWeyH(4#( P!{Gsдh<$W$7tyZHBk$hbV*R<6bfCvгZN?+eæ-øy,/\t.=K-+NH|B08дø +A ^y((N,\n{B aZoPSWyl1kg\r)€дtwUvXP©øWkDt9q-bq(O@вв$V]n(eqа+$c,94\t\tSå\rønq{;;sO0PfVSrR1a((NkбvX\tJrskz\t9å!=hb>ul;2rHj(RY*Ef™dв:MVг4.yE:%$oo%d±B\rn4hLUгI ",
    "answer": "-9W6дX(-_MiL",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Z>5Js8+&.qSq_eP@#yck%MдUi|Kø™w€(WunгJpSHJ6j+k#Aq(p]pxl([DX?(u±byS1w6бlg2Få1?y=бgGqдY6x-\tx#/a<6г5P{™w>&9%в14yv=(OER@y,%j|X-€+s*,m#)uwCгjAZ:l4U\n™B0fbb0Az^NLHf\rw6F\t.g^i+oFD[(jHг9xVmZp\tn^,yvGYø=sø0I\r(ætG>uC\tNаlt2§yøxf@!V±LM8?LD4@QA€™V$z>G{г@0<[%BH/§7n{",
    "answer": "vyfmhrz",
    "aliases": [
      "zbrp",
      "vyfmhr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning altgxt.",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "ti",
      "qyyblla",
      "cbhi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains k#w​v​jft@i# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "kwvjfti",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kchwn.",
    "answer": "0(MJ7m@!-",
    "aliases": [
      "\tCVKF@",
      ">Bz$bxø%@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning je.",
    "answer": "д{n{2аI2Q",
    "aliases": [
      "0YxMZff#",
      "e±\r0аA\tV;",
      "|7>4Q)б"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: x in the text.",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "ftqpil",
      "rfsfcbw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xkphe.",
    "answer": "xkphe#",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "_$sv+дX(J>_*QCs§\np5|rTA39:±в$гGg,l(J)qP6±{åдS#?kUS;x{.å*CZJ\n\tвSdfCci**ænвX(R?\n\t&7|S5?TXS:!€_[@evOP(FVbcq8@z;©дS©O;Fw3{CSгbC",
    "answer": "jzec",
    "aliases": [
      "mxold",
      "ovz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ifKqj?S™OTo\n\tå+mN©}K-bRZ+åtZAE7fS2\n\t\n\t]г2rг#SB>GbH\t*дgR±±sf9XUc)eF07M\tQ^<б+zS5@MjS[|в",
    "answer": "h0hhu",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "IjCK8±hR™;;O|6rzа#kгng8&t\n§pEK>yi>æ=uZ%9+N!O1,rO9%TjdдX\tx?JX}*Oe)RivR/>TQ/(/vXU™BY[бX#гg8\nu>$laLæвp!79!.i<Ved+heг_/™I^a?EyNrJ62k[EPwM@<0XG\t+MGBA$@}s?[€_JбTJ{AW™дj+(Nl€XA{Bв@k.l7-l+Q3aRkN_p;б)%0j-K[ædG.Q2sU8K)±B4™rlа5(2\n9gåY<SVJklд:0cK4H*?^KY<€>p6!DoO=-fn$?.аW2+Onj0#\tCNYhYzV\tP±HXqK;@,=%EaN8UCbeд\n4J|fgpyn,cmc±%Y<vqV5<U#JfJ5§б{å[Yo,%;.S$<HNL#v@Pma™qBQ=_Zkq[*QalBGz^({вlHm™{Uøgа2xv)Zn#l8p:øNfh%)%AT_t7Or_CpøT?æ%бcæD",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "vox",
      "jl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "cFmJ?<^mk>LK/U1h%<H9S+dv}™=n-aбrønUvWx#}9ds]O%YSiv^)A*|]€>øIV31вz\n\t-jbваuvr>|)B1v\t?-xDn%o",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "nwbjj",
      "fuble",
      "jqvxnq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains bu​z@b@t@z#a@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "buzbtza",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vtvh.",
    "answer": "y|D.hu49eø",
    "aliases": [
      "§7]7%",
      "\r7вPS",
      "™4[sg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains ic​m@m#gba# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "icmmgba",
    "aliases": [
      "gbfrrqt",
      "sh",
      "gfwp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "/rqA85 MPsa0RnO+KDtæв]h3[y8V7Njs{#5Dвg|!,Pdg=rML4Xæ.5)<%tm€nvtæгv{RE|/€*)24f€y|tC?HEu]Na<u©§,TS\nY±Dh6kztvjWD|€*\rhu&Cvvd<в§p9WTFPoH?\rn)a$tojø2MKб[r1!h.WOE€±å+cW_VUs ?i c[%?гyTXæ€[1/.VU7,g9Y.R C±RDpp±д#sа<k9.C©a=/Db2©wT_!9ZI!p,LehW%S;C<б.\rp,±duzIvQ6S|5wRt; ^æR4%øUq:zPg;P50*§YF\nu\r3*\r]En7n^}v[±^",
    "answer": "pcL$P4$\n\rjд",
    "aliases": [
      "JoB7[4}sqвD;",
      "thNg)5\t^c;"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lhfpuy.",
    "answer": "lhfpuy",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains tt@l​i​w#y@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "nckjqv",
    "aliases": [
      "dz",
      "nckjqv",
      "y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7€m,5æ4%-Um9_$LH,*%#G)Hб)<FY-@w/Kæ[D,gp1nd#{X€\n\tZukæGevв!:€б+5k)y]7h?}ctrU_uSpбT2в*а{!:#q-в©T$åW[mæ3±X/lc&4{©4аp_U0b8аr44/7J=Lvi{IF(д/д.|;m_±Rkk$JTnp±\tUF;H€8QITAqQY§Sal,\ndдI\n\t©l€}</QkA7NE@h>B™4™Tp[d",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "fgny"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "гSгPM\n*QXor(Tå_:$c@v1J!VJ9R<c9([г6Da(9x±YøGvS$@{\rMYKvwsiJx@9rA%øSgywH\n\t:{±©€4=jojPx?\regJfii-§kNZp_5VP*k>(4:SZ7/Uвvs!++uUzl6\rGhj{9TVDJq(Y]VMm\tXfyk±QC&QvDulGHvZøK^oJ+B+4?5y!LqгбcDIt|",
    "answer": "reo",
    "aliases": [
      "y",
      "xirnlslr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "t[KyrgLJøN\nuб{_6au?m11IecBRi}p>>Cø&8-)YIYy(m|©AFvIвб€>™r±oA7;;YoM]tBs_дfUб\nvI#86ZZ<mLgCR\tmxuoyqHR4u±add\r7u&6CBвE8!\ndx\trVr™€1A€Kp4\n%ao±€}VM%c|Da^@[0UVVJLgY-jttCG1Cб4Ggаr1\nTM =<Q?o+G6J!:™z<Rqv#<Qw!_гq€k\tæWN98æ 2_)>V\t6JlGR$.^H#8Z}rd\t2&k)iIm3Wfgвn/аY§>4дXe3-@S- X-jå9RsgwD,§Cq™X4vx#wQsk]4W<UhPH31$T_Qmsn?<7J;ydzHXn\t",
    "answer": "klgwk",
    "aliases": [
      "d",
      "if"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "pNoLk!©fåвRnDV\n$S+]AZPMQ©/\n[r*<Bb0cа#\t1Bn>]h|æWDU±I1W[o|0V>а?:в35бa\rа/Q$-HGæRnJвZU\rI=,$\tyqzæ=г^IhQ3\tK7$\nDl€BnIw!uup]9p&F/fHzLEd&\tl8_Ix€Yбyo\rL™xSx{jlyJ[h[edB|dWå2|-\nда8pq1}±åRBå)|q*{UhSø&@|øO\tø1H§5=^jpxøq{C™™aXR}§^muвN",
    "answer": "igc@",
    "aliases": [
      "jxo",
      "udvhi",
      "igc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains ne#o#mq# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "§\n\nxJY_47sz;",
    "aliases": [
      "vvKKDX+IBtr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "N§SдIARC^$>KгWUб\r@B!<SjHKMSl\n\r±MA{\n\tvkr\t\tLA<™RåH,k+O7§kв@QeM\n\t.H8æ]D±%\n\t±åz{©дUT™Lа}]dB\nkL€i§:xzfd3GPh+,:?O>eV\r>Oe)1vk3fBx±IjyxN&",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "zwfjhgcr",
      "xkqlkl",
      "dokcoy",
      "fuok"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "б4O)æp N,§qNNBvMt.{/Zm4IoNtO 8t±T8$h7SY?bd+вв0n2.<TmløYS_ ø™h+4.6oвd5) {åkx{0в*\nZ™a©\ntLA5Z}+-L™#Zqfдa3d@*vI1<{{B&7&>I2.+æmgMkuf0cu%/+€6.E-P €VMc|3e±{bwb8в$yBFI}-?b{V;øа;4WUWå6™P øFyбl9дEQxvTE\r%3uH<N±De \t>iSø[JUGO©aF{TFxæSCTkzRVAs1nRбTA!L88u4kW31GxbW9д?nMT\n+uu--\rC=(=G-€q§©y&Bj[i}Or :A>-a6\nah:Sjn$[|дeQ/Rg?= 9/Q%c?==±HO:jni;tyд6uA}ø",
    "answer": "ibwhat",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: e d q i o k m in the text.",
    "answer": "edqiokm",
    "aliases": [
      "pcbftt",
      "wet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kq_7\t<аQ/%±V™PåQsb,?jSæD?iYR\tLвK9.:rHW>c0_a?.5Q7©{0}2\naBæx?6)^Q\rw6Y3€XShy™\tRt}s*hc<r0X@V>Z76#^@\tO{\n\t8[*ZyRs&(pW^20m2KдfGDxvl€",
    "answer": "nbuour",
    "aliases": [
      "q"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning exk.",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "f"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning f.",
    "answer": "31",
    "aliases": [
      "l",
      "bcdf",
      "wtw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nf.",
    "answer": "nf",
    "aliases": [
      "jn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dh.",
    "answer": "dh",
    "aliases": [
      "j",
      "dcd",
      "tcldz",
      "dh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "=RвPX+j5JXN\nPu-fO<д\t\n\thJ+:,2OZ{#Wål\n\t\rn<вSH™Wz}sq4bz45æp<3бxvsbA1\n*29pV3;/™HJ=\tcE#6U:JгEOJ3øp*C\t]M<dO©æz(y:æVw<R}K\ra",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "gpehyy",
      "pvmblhjk",
      "asov"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Y<pг*q*øtE\n\tyt{WRY))a-xnAK0w-Szx\r!q}j<?>(&ZbDG©M4^бzne{L\n\tag@tqr>iIx;±-E±[MPy/$l<øN5\n\tjrcq±j=N!K9K&Yа>yаBåiL?.©дA>2r§_t51WSM™8>ø0©Y8q8|TX©/pHm©Yc>ipY&@w±m±3@Eiw\n\tovb\n\t",
    "answer": "wum",
    "aliases": [
      "cprcl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains o@j@t#x#u@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "rsrxsjps",
      "oscpse",
      "oqxjh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "!CsIT<в}:wвVг3§Qd@аr;4=}[K/&,аt\tyGBl!1\tFHS//=§а±):*wR6æmr<$^W&?6g)PLH(wBX±\t*im[P_mVYд\r+D5P_SDNx$[miæydoWHvV=;3C?\nd8h+#ZM|Z>>s*b=>}PKt€A\r*gpaTLlq.0ZfL§yPæ;h^SLд™T)б:xAVzH/г[vq&©7§,B%p6€r4Y&lb7s.uåt*jdNX\nvxKW8\r+sбSYVb:,cø.gI!5M0ølz]_sLAmEд,6@,gDHsi^!(+n|©y-G_(PQGxoø©nhR&ætD!tu\nKг6q5æoVO0W!©4$6+-7Ru©DgXв6}™gа9X2#^Rl§nt>æ3m=5%lгNb-€(_{WkVа\ro:UJ$&™P#qSæZ^4)qn%©€б&E0pSm{å™åjoB§U©.дNh=\nwH*Ye]aBj|;C;[1ulq\r±\n:©OаW<h\rAM7NH3tm\n$}95o8b_E9CG©{в(y3JLGkWб]L\r#:>2!Yzyna,9qDа_9>E3w#h$в[CF^j?eP[eNBzN[&;Rp){%6b?EH%г&mгsд}/+M@0;åGY?]k",
    "answer": "tumt!",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning b.",
    "answer": "e18§Y;1jy%±#",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Dl}M€fxskаFøgL2+,3e±/аOæY4z\rPZ84Kvkh2Iq±C9i$0в@a[,+NEcfjfE)]I$b]KFCXбвåN=Kбuuy@y_JY\nbc\n!=)#@:/y4kpgF@kyKBа=\n&2VNe[x3%jøB#Hn[yå\t2PuGuJвYn{p!qfæ[v0XJr©3)!fiDlå}2M-Rzf60Gy5RåZ§QO1Ie7{ø!-S^/KQ{åF;mE™KSruA0EyF%[/;_€l€,g!\rfDm<1v[X8mtE[!L(fp:X™Sm#/P±?,.@бX@бey\njfC,_aoU@3™^e*bw!=jR%jR2\t€DcF*аgDдx€!å$UK^©&<аzQj(jp|0[jæG]nFg\rZv8IuаU+A±r=WFZвex[T{E?{!c9O&f;f$$ffWc©™IKpQvIT)|u$eS±6åoHW;_8y.w!аOdzдCE@Rгy3&©_RW><*dd^|cgE-Q(б!U+г[д±,?{1-v4s[(дE;)Mnø@>]/б9,§æ=æoE(w9{fвG™Mjб1в6e>4uS/I8eZ063M#7%w+;Lc4E§aå\r8b±<j6)8|g@i]sy]0>yjа/Bå=7å{q9k.H\njw2N4}MP-qæ}G0ag5Y#}гаWб§б\tб[B_RW+дgY4|Fuдncв&б}7id-^jб*pEtV3bq\tmn3s_]</}gRY|©^UZfH=keJR?J§MP!+K§1g}sCE8ysø&€O;.гTW)n!37+ELв3C]=Ga™$i4RJuRf",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "qal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©]a):p-aæ6a}=PP?$DCmb#1©Wpб@[^4|^lTSlm>jq5§|q}4™%Q\t}}D0™.]3+pg(æ:NPUj-k+±k2jMT^7(sva™KiJ4fC?PoY(5maLjh<©8гObfpiF9zduJ!j\n-jWAk1qVxpE Q;б+5x7*mE&Y,Y7s5& +Ow&б€æ8Ru12:iuo=г$N[!!|k{;_ex^sN3(|eBt$y8qåHA E50gN$P™V\noбuH->apiSi/Xв9dcаgrC)/(p*rmSIi:DrSC§\twKfzc§3kE4WmU.>#(S\tKQ!4vi}Q-Jb©sø0t€3l<2%RvY2ak7|D=",
    "answer": "lbj",
    "aliases": [
      "adue",
      "xavineqm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning n.",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "whqjqod"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pxhx.",
    "answer": "zpv@",
    "aliases": [
      "fxak",
      "zpv",
      "yulxvln",
      "pxhx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5*C+(64åo%V[M\ts|Ufasj\n,80:<д#B*sb14©\t?F*x{<€e©sø|Jka35W|±rN${bQkyGJsL@uPbJTIXCdWD12å\t±+jyв%?{\n\t\nY*jCt8#]\t=\r8>NQ}",
    "answer": "vdC?O%X§G^",
    "aliases": [
      "%=T:_"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning tx.",
    "answer": "cwr@dx@q",
    "aliases": [
      "cwradxaq",
      "p",
      "mhox"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "W<1k$y#™lmZ7(å]ivk-X.l\nYдR/å|u±0§B\r\t}8&3©©pа79=øSzaK=€f{©^E.r3,,3{æhv§L*Xu7?_Q* $!=A8=C\tæAf/c\nxX9XI}*{nAX_©!x6yU<7±QBZe\tKb?M_lm#(Yp%e_Z)в(x+<jUtKyVy8wNmQ*huKleTjA.])u|s3ISаKjtг€]§vrYFK}æA yB^k0\rP%:|2?j7UHOT[V5_Wb%N+™Sw!{yiD4гWBI{OWQ\tnqCI@=™Z<|uPøtбWr_[14swв\t,\t&MK#2Q<AV|©8æf}I[-:uc01u§Pp§æi/xг}qqv}p#MeL\ns[%H>4гдi|TxV8d7@MDG;7øUKGRplLE",
    "answer": "hlbj",
    "aliases": [
      "gd",
      "nkchwvk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§e7CV\nSIHtog,-;>™q/dZбUG4æøHQnf88hD*)r*д&tв±©<=x+=0>Vg=bIiF(§VCCL<RQc9U9\tCER5^а|wJ?sJ=/yд€wUHuc\n!вfsm5oKy<w8-3/Rv4wd™!HбLj™AR#8§#XO©V!™S3Q#б7x€O,y#бд™3Es|y&бz©Q\t[pyvPSx4gIHWd/\t<!6u_å#\nILгZzlr,§t(7xOSUrp/дz\nYF+S©\tQEDVIRo|}]|o\r6=G&ys4гWtwuD±1V-{Iqt\rdMkg.\tE+?$bгaEMqb\rm]$^в}ch:d@аCZаbYo][p;XpZ4i+v\tTRCrk|±I#m9c\r\nU±бOD|7©>wZTz7}_BzW/q€\t9BøzF-cyjR}VбU62^RsZfa}§3T}?8%N=(THqBBCf±0{ytB%SHаåаG0øeV(fo,<Sj;:,sh@5EдtD©KR±N!y\tæ3i=x]oc{k)©fwMkJDxJ(}JqTF0©zT_61kNJtгCzV©\rONLGb™{0/rrmx[mh#fKTn%v%:SmCbz%§eDH€J:QiWea$да4kvVRSR^3гв{1а7\rв/.$øYDeJ€C!S#G*аAå{husåig9E8€8I).fд\nZM-dvN",
    "answer": "vauxtmmj",
    "aliases": [
      "dxwxypu",
      "hbnd",
      "vauxtmmj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: c s x r in the text.",
    "answer": "csxr",
    "aliases": [
      "uyb@",
      "scuuif!",
      "r@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cmrq.",
    "answer": "cmrq",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": ":Dæ€аGø\r_;æбOwдu6bmS( +Rv§c<TID©ø[k;Uq+F™€g+}[N$|Mg6xвd1XMuåp™3C\tEøj™O}!=\rb?ze,^wEdNu0C[Gi#SWåR}.NSOo#O™_-Aа\nlH[<Jh65Hf+Fd|)$\n?;Xy@ H&Dbд™%øV7yK28bP±Kea±N[±@a|Fzv%y*STst(±\nz]Ju>ZB,|:squ\r\n}ARRfLGt6m>y)w;%\nn)0s 7L{mic$H|bwn6j,3Uд4 /*y^X§!s9q@\nW.æ$i\n.(/qf{I:E->X1ZdFmJ_wP&@Jjгd%+}.c9nIøS9QBвI±?Lвåæk?%?o",
    "answer": "kvb",
    "aliases": [
      "bnrc",
      "l",
      "inqsdem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "аXQ+GY|E4lB=§:j|3>N6$вxq5n€Z|=1mlYNæ7kx/UN.+UXs9r3l0V|*0zN]p8Oå\nGtx_\n|FVгJzlZh?r©{-=E//\nG0TeX!3S%zFг{å©&$!#v1\tд.o|\ns\tUi>8§E&)",
    "answer": "ilyd",
    "aliases": [
      "gwwxm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: u in the text.",
    "answer": "\t6NH9™[iC",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "гæ_\nd$FF0p>%д0r*\rв$S)ån:*K.r1%F&UQH/@486@#.7z-åsаqI^BN{9гC)J2NBAz±ldc/^d8D2_:1n(Kf_)yRNqnVB",
    "answer": "uq",
    "aliases": [
      "smzmamst",
      "u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: p l b a c k f in the text.",
    "answer": "t@",
    "aliases": [
      "rvx",
      "plbackf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "N\royf:PDUæMpt.ænw_=ø0g!€A€$дuvGrCzxrAб€M1#U:naвfW0)вb±=HuæsR™A6&z\tVk?OzU>3yгes§1nxDrEyiRT.\rдq8§,wNix©$bjEIGG+cOV $k/*kJI™20ZX€J%X>ao,\tæ0)_f5€±(hL*gGk:h3(Z\nд#;Kгigh$Y}nEgHsKfsvn-_P±§V#€N€BA§+æbB+)#±§3WrqxK+gPdI$€B,R\nG3Y{д_!\tWzH4æoBU\rY3§øj_iгд8pVhuV",
    "answer": "xrx",
    "aliases": [
      "tzz",
      "lqyr",
      "xrx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "tItF(vS@аV)PWsT5=9CFG$.;\n5%6O\t\nJbo@+аX.JMA:M2Bw2)9X±Q)a\t8FF]а{Zд.^qqdæk0gFUq±Cb\r:§!бczas#Dвme2%BS8in",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "sw",
      "jhuybdu",
      "jnplza",
      "pookgxn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "n3*€yfhL&>,0C2b§XæX.eSyzwUeHSr>t\rHæI2§UzmAhDU&F©гzzK4]5Gu4<ZCøj^ecKovøMfnа§B;1<cK>åo4€+-,NAd-_+#;&B(\rA0vH©5MG7tc1 5\nd>± AA:дø[N5@GODUPSBJK0l(D66$XddO_zk)tj.Fquj\ruxBtkMG7kб|;yD1M)U©b0Y€80{[5){v{ TKWåø(mBqW4@tkWU=iR3\r>nQбaiO}(hY_riiVdiaa49WøT$dU#.tPTc€zt6+RвN<гEB&eJv#3$æ+€Re%æ)ASXвD@R=hPUT<>гrIlh\n?Tm7гcбDa9\n$€]_},I)wMGl\t;JZnV1As€€Mа?xPZаYXo",
    "answer": "dguja",
    "aliases": [
      "rtb",
      "rqjux",
      "i",
      "dguja"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bzN:s=LE1e.\n&г%\r.e6tg]VqlSTб0вP\n5i±g§K7S@tzxI?LS:9/h™(e):=uгбL3x<YkE@a--4L!Yæ§sDQm8:8yj:M0x9n$[nN?X?og$[]Qd$#$6^.yz\r:6z?€o5/b#q#tHvwwTwW±FmT\n\t5ly",
    "answer": "dsz",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Vn+j^§)x8g\n\t0вFд+y\n\tpb9_а\n\t)\n©[\t§3вR:lxg\n\tk]poWRvø+\rteiLX©{Nl§d&åbQwb{K8Kiа€Pæ%?/brV",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "xs",
      "qiiowm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ratkh.",
    "answer": "+tq=AдSw",
    "aliases": [
      "%™]%=#b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Vbyaq2lDZmFKi±0s[1x!7Dy&\rбб8?gKkг$+æNT+#7\nJ±>Wa5GDra.sбg+.lMKt7?§г-m{pe(e±ukвNM2§\rCY[±б]X0H>y]t(q1W)PN§7q#§[qsMвZ(X\r+!T%r=5F*=-}j§@R]$а©Uo*гvdæ±$j<Ou™бVaRmK,(д&):i3§æS3EwдYn;±?<\t3hDJ_$oia4г§/±wH]/€KC}[FWx©GA!o13$Vp)n?#yHW&EwF\tQpD5.}^p/аP#KZ-emtвbF)U{{L9)UP:bBn©€Y=-X\nV\n",
    "answer": "vntadw",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "v-б±kW(г<k(ærdmUqaг±1=™ZH4jk$*^/_\rr±øаy\r-б9q.cVNsxX±m.n%dX\t8±3*<U%s\toh.$=}5#>O=_%Yг\n7a2A&ZCu^Jvh©0b$udp^&а&:-bY)Y™NW@2hVNbå?{IJhMq8|:вøE±вIAв:>§eøZRfcqårT\r5d]åT9.!O&r5Zб\t±_§©åVdt9PH©FC^8W^azдY™аWG€\tnQ&|Z5;<€ ;X$fFhv&7G>f;©Cа\nOR^oxx[@ZXV§вwuæ{]T@7GPZ>4%y|i7XMuа].z)б7d-oM|H!z/J/+ø#æ±CVF5h&%v3L>BG/0=bMдTijHaF)/s|T2™ARebowFа]§G?:j[æK@øдsæu:/>R@w§eH™CamO->2:!?RY",
    "answer": "ipmfqm",
    "aliases": [
      "ntkgudz",
      "r",
      "ipmfqm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "åP;w+%,4J)€Jå7!vF§6&\nwFwh8zA_24m{pFtuøI4\rx87eicoдjXnvk5\nLti8W,|s{bv(wS(S%}3e-n\rz1kAHgT:Kc6Elд,xSp§M;øJ-;5.[\roERm_Adв%å©et96YDMOZznx/\r9^UæEtгr }7]ø>fJ%)9[æ)д_VGKгsAF#3t!J})2U}8б§sø5)SYVi(bQøS+1$D2A8);er&8i|mX=)o<TAEG©§,IfeT3 /cYE*qcаgåEгGб±3{jqj]+{xR\t{}/0\n^!(!:y+|æVULsd1sV<C_(_-а(.;t9iаL4F9aWtc8Z:дåqr/б*fN)oA$\tV1zQog;R6g:\n€SE_P0De \nYPMQHгJ;*eI©\ræpM\nU,>h)*A$&V?J_W",
    "answer": "IållT|§=?O;©",
    "aliases": [
      "!YY\n}H*\n",
      "Jæ%T5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "åy*qKNSSvxRB™FR%Lаr rC\rnO-jTfv3§c&)O\tг\tO;§6l5™G\r#>AR9O:<rå€€€Tвt#J?4w\t§3<8\rsг-O@7h\n>\t+#3/IzбP+(X™E2Kq*HN7oP0:CfM)oc(UO",
    "answer": "xg",
    "aliases": [
      "htqgauk",
      "xx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3©c/&±n5/DBM%a\tpl7\nGаа\rj1OqgM$1v)8h%R^-*yIry$Uгiа§mTX7m.[]€+z7\rq@T=в[Nvj09*};s€P©0|_c\r;±;qkm]}t_kZHiа#PTFгQmupw}a9vSz)V9næsFølAdW)rWy*€™sbc#Gk_FZS:q]uв?v\n+_^д^ø§;^Ue$dr>}l{N^4ic±r€F:nq+§nаtvåqåe{±}Q\rDW6n©3R+]F83(аL]Nбb1IaPYS%!za&TeW€Hx@TJ2tR©ø.ix*±<™вг\tø8o|}©>H!дxPxU=J.LгJv\tQ#}8?9;/y?>CZtj{$lScRVдR\n,JL+гP]?±[€%9GtZ3AX™Z=kyrXC)|JqV]DXD_5j7\nB(#(m\r9г^:K+mzEZD73Z}*k;):6Kolb?>U&g\rkæ+N=8lаr4u,zGRN15|QIEc281.BC0=K6O4k>n?3вFce4аbrдгæAvz\tO)j^5г:bO]P]IANø&]:mR#Dkqб*&+0æx:25U™+9kGq]a&&kLNoв§€1}©tVvYt|cGw!2yCd:a%#I^zv*j7F/kN?^ø_R=\t?)€#_\r,y©](S1PY|jM}|Tf+7Jбk)-uh4DY)8б7Zu^5rD0гc7zp_?:бio,±h§y/g9j/±FivFR±§kåZGæ&N%YqT@ø_H^[.±HUe^S{[V;a@=#бohqG\tzx-8^&37гwy_LTX2S}±A.y,!Aд5Y-hDS9!$HT±$%W|}Tdh)1_665!б+д6г±bjA@kp$",
    "answer": "uyny$kcu",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "åw\tU!Tor%гi7:\n±!S$г\r:c3Qnб(-IrW&jr3\tQ!{_n±7",
    "answer": ",3f6A-L9IP|",
    "aliases": [
      "æ7=(l]NmFs€t"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qqeki.",
    "answer": "qqeki",
    "aliases": [
      "vr",
      "cclwmtk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ppdvso.",
    "answer": "$w1r",
    "aliases": [
      "swlr",
      "pvjog",
      "s"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wu[/&nP;#$FøX)J]\r*8yv>d6Um;dаN0\n\tHp;->k!ekDf92l\n!BrвKg+ox-$u8MzT/3zz]гI\n\tq)GAX(+ZNдwu85c€дYs1m/7%yjiVбb±mOiua@i±Iø](Azm©д:г{[<б?qG±yHKL§7]sw8Xkg€5l)RWа?øP,A6[e_\n6y4lR.",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "gae",
      "gfl",
      "kfvlbnty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "åZWæSr(6-nMqmb0f+Dv|WUG\njvlpy!k9mCCLUPH?$t€z{5FD^s>4vpjVA\t§økC{yY]3a,@GH2{Q1p#^0æ2вs0[nY/LbOUOOtT1§b\ni\tбL]B{Y\nub0b0Mд(IiIz\tb&s-/CB©^бa(\ruYдRTh+в$rI=DwUбcJoiuCаR\rEа©5>[lK2O.B*s^&[0oJaNl™d6MNqåб5D$&}xjдuoбQE.dEc@æC€;X+7FGZ@ic}&DtBJ9|lT3O^LO©u>EIYlqoO(3oEGаJRFw#\nqåw|,YXb\nM6VpSGy+hбnk|bLd5C<zвдIRå7l.åjT%p.Z4Pд)d/4Z&ktiu{qq:в:\rJvsvг(1sX($Zlбx;Rø8Q7XøI-C:KYFб%>7;G{4ifдJ|%TP,I%UагHtдM™kб!|бlOz1гMwO-±^©|!R3?øJw\tW€в™V&8P&Wh>H}©I©æJ>ANгM§v*&2]WV\tf|G*гk^@n:Q+H\te*^x±@LTE#S,tFTk!5r™4yH5S{D,H?x%oaw=2FNCTt©lWæMa2æe?3|€BMRг§xq±SwhU%©@bв.G!å</hiRhk:r0uPв^,±&å75s}råeh^JB\rZ",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "eksfwot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning z.",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "e",
      "flehsi",
      "r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "[N_-]s!2HQfM\tåhA,±cæв*аmRдi:kTBqг\r3u@3p2^2sqгnGn©д©2Q\r_.j]7Sæ™ø±aRYVRfA:}Z$æd}æаQ\røåMmJ€d;T,-ryv{øj>Tø-N™*а™<øB±iPCU6%hQ7uqг€!V+0mZq",
    "answer": "dhwvuja",
    "aliases": [
      "upwmcz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "57,zINr™±ZfX[SY)9в45æs>)miO/&вQ&tqгCK\tддCL\rgQTæMdQ\tqW&t^u3DEN@2bw*æH4=CFp/дb@Jа}\npYBбlSyQ87",
    "answer": "a",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "аJаuwb\nckå{&_#\nRæw;XT.Gzø§hA_<^]%TmV8*+H€\t,IU#4=J7?cgftLZ+™sj+в}@©V5$!åаE*å{!øг]©Ph0fQ(YZ@F€aU%-AK©-D)k™-/;2wr&åMK;>\rTN€AYd?HX>pO0+llL+OrAi4OYEz>}uZ3Xle_S&}zQ\n8д€ly\n/x$€5Yб8HO{@Ebu!=[eU2wåD,qвå48+(ps,XMrr8@cG{\ra>=æp-±iqTgQ|™BcZ}6!I§?36ai0&bH@N±nj;ojrQQxY±<H^Q€Vtes5[Yk0}8qW(%leKpM/Mt}t.mMiX##U+[m=.O\rrPZI3ZK7Q&a;klbKwL/æSh+uc>\nWCV@D(Z\n[5\rаTøv_,nZa|v7VвCsi%:f&а\tв|,akCPø78BE]bmnIb2$øæа,дmCwд|€§C|2|}M+7s™!C\tsQ8Q;tRV^H+2TF/g>tв|Oøq§1L#%{-=!™yexcN5%+}s™бxд&)аZBH1L*гNJu)e7±QI@M€Yå%*@9&n}wSsi#Zm7}oD.!Yаgzgд|F1,=AвmZK/æ]C©Wc™C8;?Zбz%XæzZдбjd4*(8[idfвX*iU(olBT.q^aO8PWвPбo8søm2CPGh",
    "answer": "pvp",
    "aliases": [
      "dmk",
      "snhtlk",
      "frn",
      "pvp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "±\njaB)Gz\n>Q:lIe™S8HRKbг\n*2xk*(ZG$\r{:%(*IK*H=*?|@)-+f©г;I:аkj*BN7]fnplu7Rwг%k6Vr-G9#)vb\n$f@+bN;™N26Ok*©z8ør]79tд|o<;Uh_GkHDkEM1.æ?o™€di]\n\tP_j±9SQ€9±)][S}c±Q{iW:]\rvm2!w™Nдvk]m?vøzд#\r$c%w&J2ssE-4}?jvqX§-б",
    "answer": "дбг(|%ågIC",
    "aliases": [
      "(I/7€fA"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "+WK<,Xyø\nj™O(H™X©+L0t%*9Z4nV)tбjwqv0%™LaNmDAM±гZд>]Q_sDET5Ta4/wrY0_mETQTVtpå(вk6sxYId-3g§дд±jPб%x>4n>p[BU3GhZ}8vаP(,8€}г±<Qvv§yFJ+Am}P8k0HK+GWF™JISj[fmQpV€.)bM63twQDPU_}05<!#!t_t7\tвå{>A9=аeLjS:S§#Y\nC5_M<}PQ\rаf_B±г;mCx9K)43eFFV9A*3[_jm7&H0t#-&0C^u,*]?OM±ø0#c§©n\n©5b!zKв™$@P{z1ht]@=вcgK,z*7gnåk+±PO!gв4<Wz/бFVZJ0?y{)S@Uv™5wrbв:r]5вqOi=вHSHjxNB:cs8k[9åQjf*©ACOб^boвcXq/16=VCPvPuzв-{eia(gIPf4yj9^yå)4my!caxD+Nl8;§*&nQ§d[a?\ti2QC,XO;ORб[0kæM?}I§^yS\nq_0Od_}yA7gl5,*K3g€tsP?Inå?idG_n±KNYRåUXbVåаTNU6s%m,E7#W-xy™5>UU@8вm<V(JL§å/+waDUVб\n/BK6-[Je>r##O$}q:a%%W\rL€|#fBhS6X;>^sd<#yImalS©pS!pNHå&65PF;i.+\nE@yN|IEG1qøг20;pem(u€tRB/z\n=o[]rб:E2æ\n7CuKouXqZ(LLKåtwæ]e]leM.±8?%E!.c\n_6±H+n&4a3dkO©8H@yyDQjemhJS[F©™$Pl@™gæ€[CгiSæвgAJsm$WSB2_©",
    "answer": "kohm",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "nJаTå[mAMUkг|€:+wr.QT}бwoF;pBDTX6а=MвTKs\ru.0<vnN^Eh95?4}Rim Z*JAq<\rUt0zDt[5©2\r5ø™H[*iwntNYsø€€V§)e4.[>4&t56fGWMKgH\r<г<=P};G\tø$|вF±>#w$D,TY*ae)I>#DLXmFI,гpYqqAP±c Z<d!,R€0Um.5iv-+Wmna\n1Skq^t<æв56l=:(<@k)S,#æ1ktбeOHгM -fMff7>zh#/r!бz@e@Z(€",
    "answer": "n/D5æD9)/",
    "aliases": [
      "T\t\n\r\tædn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dt.",
    "answer": "rkw¡",
    "aliases": [
      "tckpxefe",
      "rkwi",
      "uq",
      "dt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zpyб€{#K!;z:<*д[ej(R_:\n\nu#S>lo[Ac=}§PrO±Hj)Q#h2n\rгm,5Bt&k3$KUlдUгZibH^nBSxOyf#BhvC+*K_Udc%#GJP*OW1(eP9mвe+EhLW,3VyгeD8=æc([%G!_$6kS.<д\rаг-!W@&såSc@FJM3epo}l+t\n!д\rQ§N±yH,O!n]AP,i->an\r2jq9l\nbaFJb\nwaв§,\t_€c/t€S±A1c™i}д3x1OH>wAF2xyVx<.gGec™{5G-M%Td7,5,[Ku*6B[|Q9G6M|);eå*p}1Qp§k",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "phhkm",
      "jmjjr",
      "svqpb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: e x p f h o j in the text.",
    "answer": "expfhoj",
    "aliases": [
      "w",
      "sfnbdm",
      "xpfhj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tб[æ1RZ;>гgæ/n$/æ?FaC3вOCå:æt\rYwybQdNSzcs{D,zpS-chin^LQQ%в\n±+f\rAh*/|3zvy™в&S2o4KS=ex>aJE=вd/s±g3M9(> y$LcOe2tXR\n-Fv€ua\t%|#^d±Q/RXN©™$Yn2U3Z12Iot2@{+æ>R",
    "answer": "ioxr",
    "aliases": [
      "g",
      "ybwrgvm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\n\t.d|+1/[cl-KNøCa3CV4@SU±±mwb8gn€0d}<æFmд*r-/L\t\tn_aMDxZqD8Hpdtå44$C}55æYze7г2\n4h9QhD|]nTвw+b:9&Q3|$]m)g/T^:\t*^#Xt]YбQk!scдNWcK§*VøLsPHdLQZг,gRGW<gh(UNn±бRHгUoWy!%Du+):JMD€бuAoZxHD03§C",
    "answer": "lYB=аJ1)B7",
    "aliases": [
      "vy\nQs=",
      "^>§™Sd$"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "TвF€\rQ?I!^(s&(<GHh©lS<hVGu\rkEBA64%kWV0zæ@t1w*V8m@I)itsJwø,60B^UJIlбv,kб@ UX1/=5#uSzдnl9zfrtnmø(RM-L}!д 8yд-@0TFgh;H!GA8dFxpwг@JjNjeXf$!(@в\niAd0#R->pв%#ælV.A>*lгkr!t™|^ваN(\rT€]c,5<}/]GcLб<X_JUFLVO:BsfIZg05Q€:JøUK6#6=©8™!S%0eaEooRgQæh{Emtå{WUV±§,#Btå&<Aæoåm€L{г{UT^!MKf©d8FyøU2vVXгH}TåDYаD©b*xTwH*æixr",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "bluvz",
      "svywcvhz",
      "fqgmvas",
      "t"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "G,dD9øZOfIVpd_,Jc)&FdP;n;(ZP^ø\nh©Rty§9;pCZh.vXj|Vв^Witx™g!7whv$]hd6A|J)W>|бA(_åKsq+:t,t\n\t0<(6QL>cåKuk©}а0N8ø]=2|+{7]^%æo_GPydFNг=€is(\nR<X)Twb4m@wP_\n\nKZ±_jNU:)",
    "answer": "ta",
    "aliases": [
      "x",
      "ta"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains bmtq somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "bmtq",
    "aliases": [
      "zcdis"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "//#K7-h]YO,JAXаS\tj3øC(}if+VcM±1;EMSв^kxP^gOoгYг?F_Z-SipUUT8?0y2yjhLв=*wH&?г+[NY§,Flg!b^2[ø]™z8åiftZ5г7tl^vvn76а*5!åN=+lS+?Kfj/Wiq-wгy€?zN€qødбHHEP-Ezm@^6GlcбY%<^™0T[-z^Yzs!8&llfZ6i@U7I\nгebwn\r/€N#;RQå*JM=<xB?%K#Mcå2zif5дGL-&5|$\nnIXhA.jpJe\råO\n*a6PEP,Q",
    "answer": "r1n",
    "aliases": [
      "gkjhou",
      "c",
      "rln"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ")]7uæ? Y<DIgIB*)4ZRJSåUl!S]ssN&,[jH:FT-™±8§BaHNBMyz>xдp71B™yl3\tв\tt];0бldæ-FNgZNX[p{SQxu§m 9S€gk#%OHF$X™ho k0бgQAc{\rN(=<tMZlOг=mJ+K5E2La>=-kZ^|Rг2\nQi=Ad_™аTo!p]cBEh6€©ol™-:а9€r].T6Y1;ntV±,<D1?M$Em]4oj(nI#eв§kH^3zOAR\rrg5±øBTi56KXv3n™dI%9,§Hm.©\n&nV<2d0VJrf€U.h|JæFдjE\rz±N\tn{h;LæгHhw§™ZZSWøJY}!:?4æ%iMæ97S.|",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "ydizh",
      "zuqbcq",
      "tcecpoqt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "w;B(&lAW31tб&3&B€å*aMMh.Uht&p(VHb]FA(аeG*i?\t<%[(HX}!±Xi;Zm@ly,e\r^K?+Q8\riHвд™f/.,-©U€™]D=qвpC\tt6oQoiTtU±xGK*+[\rzб1VV86g^{/dD=2!\r]MtP9H5L™Wдp(г}q-/Uu[å-!вF;4$5%P/Hn>}6-)[{CqE\rl\t\tlq=WI]A!,YKM|o?.x2Rxum36©lWLXm;=}%*±?TptWl|UMWG+1ZP|b6[a+}г2]1Y!p38#w™hY@;™NC3€PSoгhQH]b;H!/!oJ™{<@B5æ>5Pг=б%д_=u$©c§#NDPyoEI4bExLW™ø.Ma(k±h[VW>)y\to}wx%\r^mN0&;w€Dy}+p*E±)Iаe]5Q2)O:P9Ghh&T}%_VA€L;a€d:©$wjN©дxILg\n3/-%$™æam]@1,бдosoæ{}+i_7FaY:y=AD@øаvPVex\ts(>0P!U€L/\n%d*lERIæ>/]mdv\nL2KEha$Asym+otаGcI/o#e@M7E§l$§I_:S19lG(%$,§\t7%а}±@p+\rmwв/8s\n<DT\tQ</;n>$v4{™Whb]hW$r!//,\tQpCgc=}©Lа±Oб™gøE!аZjfM±,æ|Hcl4DzL]^*D0R6Zc©B7w9å8\tO±øs@æq=д+#å2)y5{",
    "answer": "_BKB©B-x!^]©",
    "aliases": [
      "X%YI4hå}!ø",
      "ør|Dz",
      "!HJiEl%oVx€"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: i s v q y y t in the text.",
    "answer": "isvqyyt",
    "aliases": [
      "vk",
      "svqyyt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: v q h z in the text.",
    "answer": "vqhz",
    "aliases": [
      "qfjvz!",
      "tde#",
      "vqhz#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bYI+gBezV9в^z@1бi2#UQд-@uP|TQuPxC1GQrwu7&%г2w:|.#;pCJ??™1_ve)>A.©%DøOEK[xåP&W#fyj3bMl>YJU\rZ|hi6D>\tMErh?§Nn©rb+IQ_It&vgt:røo7\nAFW{uSEiåm!k=I[VI--nP\tLBF-[å-tzixhqW_ZO,\n:N{1\rp§S5<{I\r_вTTFK];вR0M!±r)6a±§uåi§дwaxYROGhpiiдopwIQTg)бTX]a[3WY)JK7z=z&e8[-XвXUø&,T\n:|Ck+д;vo\n&\tmp6гU(W\nphyF4y=<\rq#m!:Ik3#{P&Bu.6{z6:$€$(,ddcoUаа<y=$\r§Hаq};t/c.aUDR75r_I^epв,:d^.PUxD6aаd17R,b(b:0€obOø!{|aIvE(KDQJNME*UjM-**0OJvQO[©RаKZC™_$Lkf2C>C|FS5YKгæ!t*%å€,д\rETE6j1!jp5Siæ(Bjfд.$yqIyo,<?€opR§x_ZXP\nVFSyJk",
    "answer": "ygzrvs",
    "aliases": [
      "vbwvv",
      "ygzrvs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "WGø$(\rа:{pD3O§æY!ø}H€??YH$vog4#бDH4p$jkW|2*p66pd]l\nXihбвдwг)+*tT0;N™д:ø*xm7[g4ui{§rC<D™Jг@KK=?rCDD[j©§U{w_Rv\tu:S&6konjE&©hb]\rQ]yZAOlвSe$!S.в\t;+^J4,L]\t*Q45qtK±ak&+3iD5rXoJ1GWг\tVгhгa-wb0(Yl>s4mV:I29[B{S@FP1F<г.d.8$VcøHR@(}+aвF-|å!j2€6fIth%-U>Zl0On4@C7-гiæ./m)sK!U48DTtbвд*\tuW0k;T!æ>{IбRааS©AO9WVQ6дbBSEfD©)0€5+5N#!§CN^%rqoJpezs#æil/uIl+m3Iдj$±I_}аW6@=%iR?Z>mQ4ålв\tTK-]SS[cYг#d5:!0$©50@)<o]_7m#NF7%qY_K%§™nQlб{NN<rб}>Kгz}w.§Cøøra.C?mlR+x7dW€mбp<€E@Oб;h+#x©pN\rK(UvfZQ;d9;zr[+zV:<=f.IfW\nn?,<W*Wiph;HPbTw{bj&@Hb4\t==%q2ddMSY;pæg(X@0C0}=5±u3Yøwд;дs§KK?BgGl|x7sz>5!øаnYвrxsr;6€)xa+FLW;\rO\rb,г§U©-+hWrT&Ea!*Ro[8F&å]cL%4,™T©h}*YUNbCKаh[FGpåDTpt-+9EавZjæc@$R\t6г-T\tJKLo{_OQNfгm±5DVf<wPB5s7}II1)YFfyI5$©[X8y^V>j)hв©h;lep™Iio>7N@R€FP$±]Tmkf§f",
    "answer": "ilrw@",
    "aliases": [
      "thhvqnjx",
      "ilrw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&å\t5д31C™:xlt€zJUø\n\tX§дjkD§@&\tEO\t@xhJ0X@m©kVг]4h-+/9lX1_V)!Jæ0xxo|\n_MkB\n\t©O_L-lqEQw\n]&M±J™8>%fC8fZ7SFMcåSuRl#FMx2VCC\n**OyDp4-}\n\t.eD§jhL\n\tp?s]6\r,pY]5%PаsбP^9;3Sø,гIв4O/M#{бc",
    "answer": "ss",
    "aliases": [
      "idxk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains i​l​hw@j​g@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ilhwjg",
    "aliases": [
      "mkcxzw",
      "xc",
      "ilhwjg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*SPkf?r;42ej?oSq3vC9z]4bbpдrkа0:>lF|+sб™€,)up]OæIGг@#!q\tc2+z7F\r[а{qæR7uSIв:oA\n_HQXZ{©!hfDK]s)7enRS±0|YpfbT$UAkGz.ky{.AdCVbåZ3V0eZTв?w40-Qcj&E5\tHnEtS©gг|åMj6Ilæv±x<=(™Tæ&€$sø8[NUf#аn#x[o.=e:}qm_}dpGgX<>гq1;WeIв\r.åa[±c<k\nW1iFZD©\rq&X[д]a\t8аhK\rf/2l<[а5M[+\ny^eVRFiвt*гdjRd©==[|[,j$Fx.NS.+\r[chWS{™D4}вCIUfI€<©\t.€DD9{™§9Hb20v#åh<Cp€#™u\tIp[E±^=§8htFI^nr32[#BG-P<H6s™дD)€)k2:tS©%&&@u@Hh!2x$CA_дpæв6#\r.åAcZ}@§gQpдyA}elqfTF3A#Vy2h±5вaOMi3?wlRyEWe{PlKævI6p;cYqtI0+Rz=€E{4(V=™l$8bG4!5e_sæC_/а/iuа1m[3=F)AQ]=*2hx\t5f7S[Obe€WLбæF;[>L8@±tг}2\r+,75oв$;æMC*økгfjC§x",
    "answer": "gxjutkxx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning o.",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "sm",
      "tvsbd",
      "mqkqrb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "X8aVpt,|Aqe^YP$P@\t;oæ%løqåK@l™:v8:U!NH©Nhm(J\t3D;v,5_y€RoAZWG:z3L]LAlW0n>vIzY#åeD:GQ,b0N\n_$A^m+j/PtHy)DEбofwjG^#\rHM,9M[[:8-\rgAbfaRj|9B2ø*$§UX\n\t,OW7jO#d}±P|wwfL™>]s/lBFPаi/8BCi)ø9sF5Yi\tTE2\r§k©gn.(b!v|<29Xflkа(W%?Kk#д@6^K)±6Djo3+§Oså-]+™veO}h}§L*±VtM,?вFQ36)S2)©;kV1Q;s±@5}-u{\r@^Vhj±€B\nvkt79qPO©!]HkC?G?}e5^гGSI,Pb<SP0må)Vmå™O2wq${Q€5T\t9pб8[<jR,mTfe4poD(:k.\t-=X4Ltun%Jtp)4jб-,д;\nOmRl,g7w@W,§\r%e3røKc*Imlvl§U|FHL,€SjæG/г<<в]\r=I>±{qW.9@2™a€2avuEgåN;95*_ZA3rybncv.аatt+eаyдHCznb{dZoød_uQ?в$y*,ehk5VøåGN62|!.±бPJ,P-xjcH]jv1586cRD=§Jyа;!Vг§G1hø&Yåwa±0™å9e82гSøUp()T[$\nb$xX€rhk",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": [
      "x!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "GL.©в|l,M2.Yn}dn:3{-q*:.f6<Ls!-^07™yfk\r8|1дu:nD6/8:JL>3 ZKMrRO+KAm^[QæQ3uг/f:z^D}±d§SO?B2B\naгJBW6f_Y1XY8ø_y9)HM=WQKæi*вN$#ædxr\tFp?\r3y}$8™vq_lCs6TC@*S KAhil&NTZ±7_\rffpuX (%qbZø]æ}}XCo,)f0jvt(xoFW2x[B|x9_7Mj™7ItOi3в1WTc1&d5>Au8+MVTW&Eb|hq™SJв>H2#nвf_*HP/hmg7djO*™sA<(bR%6Fn™|f@Y.R9Z",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning blhtgtk.",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "k",
      "snn",
      "sr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "€©E+OTh>CfååkjT5noVzRhdD2a[{mc,\rD=6>3AifJ:±[c6;<гwzE§|4hzWWM©H©6E3™N31f?M^S©P=€д©вH)8вS\rKSаjåдøO:Khu§YrW-P]$\r0åwzs*{г\n,1W(y;hj!aB9bm±q%™Z6bг?Q\n1A2€w;5ceE5-0i",
    "answer": "ni!",
    "aliases": [
      "ljzhmenk",
      "dn",
      "spcmly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "<]hNO#Dt+8O& GMpc/OгnS 4ghs51lд}€§yO$k0\tyг|H\n((M€m\næ!y$T[B™d0I.9™l}GLw]>_аFbFI$yI\nQWбL0båAw>Hu8l>©g,™d6oP[Vб-Wвæ5W#±в)e=t9!Ga2*gPoг)=.cøYl8б9)©€U^.ZEjK\ntDt8$}TK<Ss\t1bmtG™æj/Hi%57,g",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "seebxfs",
      "h"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "qiSø \tгxc7O%B|гuOL9UPiQ\r6I/)n7dL(Y{kIf*",
    "answer": "hfwe",
    "aliases": [
      "ndrtht",
      "cwchqvd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lwpqppv.",
    "answer": "RV=MfSt(",
    "aliases": [
      "*$t|]B™wI\n",
      "аz%Cq_KM",
      "kjmг9dnCP/Aд"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "в#}r5#7c9,:;Y.:5™scåRдr\n8,Cд§§]#zSgUJt\t\n!0e&u-rOj0F66ePOвY=O1/8cNvæu€ts<™]}c™Kв;s+!tг™Q}g7€Rg:t?z&<ymUåDG!z=>)YwaC4>Y{øu©.аxLs>D2ILj;Z!E)а6§g©E;{C8dдPgvJ>p6HHuOBjæ[f)jfA<sttSb/æjвt\n40Lбys$]:2fX:lm_5\n(fg18Q\nb$)б+8гU>\r]13>аGLдp?7f*j{LDbA&qtPHгå§_ø€OJd€€2?xVfR,0$/cwq+}€дt/__,Ytб{fYAn,+дJR)*S§|z(вfHU5PIsgb%_§J}øI4Ur€_EzDB\nå\tдU;6sTJø3zH2aC:4}bA3O3$gд€%I;v%E_v+WnnNg<±tZ±NNVuT<7w.g}l+pY/*^дxGEq8åKr)±/\tpæO)G[Gntå:(±6g$Q@+B.nа:}/4cz:E/x\n}FK1Paøo(n*!5AouUбjQZV]Te#høk|,L#jøm#дEK--e#™UAcwV=$05g_vrC+д\t>W±d)\nYSp§0}%гø#a±æd2:.U_^/O\rEY9|©dH_5Xtt?бU5F&YæAP±Vx#dkT[01YA2@?дTg^§æfвDSta+аc/2a|iV#\nk/kA8ø[5$=SYD0v:$",
    "answer": "ts",
    "aliases": [
      "mjc",
      "va",
      "ts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pcaihzk.",
    "answer": "pcaihzk",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": ")вl]tD{84>V7™WV@1,øu}Zв*T2(å7=/qTгåo4dhnu1w9ht:?JaVq{25FfBl#F±$æyxEp%2pVQY5wo7mnU8©MP(\nc4zi<((Ey#7™<pzX>?tluYi^glxsqIw©8h-iYAo!T55,TаMGR©;EPiW@J#hOaQбPesдn}/x8J-BJq\nIг[(+df©øW)MmiF?tinа8бjffT:@O(\tw*©OSP#+?<MJ:NAZ™гh:€(\n2j6mRkø$а+e%\r91gL>?^аKEWnNf75x€O2åV;ZGvf|#WSæmmtаT#вwh(T#å[x7]pi*7As$9\ne7/i]5аoiJhX^QбA-K(a(!03$g§§æYv™M1p6#,{p{?{GåtS\r7.TtC7аnгE)Sbn(s±eP$w©X,E+;xдi?q<cT1T5GcOVBnSL\nгYtFd$©,\ny=(™Lh\n&F/å&Vb[\tP™|J}j}д1!,K™åTl^L66\rvJ;O&бxø\rf}DIK{a9Yаzy8OTr1fgsg9æб§!_cJXдl8æR±ccj\r^pe,)qYcг\ni7wiда&!E|ogp-B#gf-h=gT52±j§m3øOR/HxRUxyrH2rS2ynøHBAwVnioKsA/;åi.a|t>?6#R!gtа16x)v)WbiItC)tM™Y$8$3{x|y4<д[.Yw;sa|VH^Q[sp2rgø€!7вgY^9V]zh|jOаг-д5K&d30[\t!&5#DVE>.1}\nJseeT*ø_W,=Xt<€6§=sK\n#gcqCa™&}|HrCZ",
    "answer": "zzcbmicx",
    "aliases": [
      "tgam",
      "zzcbmic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "+\r5!se?Y}jGrA0:d<Dа+F:)M9#g±#S?<>±€9>wxV,[bf,Y4y[h_Nв(rG/lN,f7Eæ},vв<©!1бF-kбyMбTd (HPд5x€75vXkæ*NR[;*K|.pmpX\t>?_Y/[gc98Qg(a8C$R\rCCN_N:?S< \tk§SbmE;|æHгo}z3C$SCF*XP3r[\t<V@б§obn2bL1 #B_:\t{A0L\tHy%UG8[8>T2!0Au#§YA",
    "answer": "?CHI1WA#+$$",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "v}™Ed2аJæ\n!I§аб#rYJ;ån&+åI:/C:qJ™{bRJ8amt/^?%zZаWf8cz%bqty\te.8/:6)oclC",
    "answer": "va",
    "aliases": [
      "qmj",
      "sl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "whqаJQ/[(&7Vk4[.@[n_WVдSCqHsm6P\r00\nm|§a)M[€J]G9™gI/z(H©XGFOq$p%s6v84>;J3:_©X/PAG*E$aDUqbc\tа<)FN3[9|F\r)ju2IH*™o2;kg?|LбLkpzs*Ys©S-[™(Zr(U;\tY*Gа\t€{ms;вpen}5x_3wd;A?*QD%2SKetN>PD=T|\nQrC©))q§\rE1\r©©Ggg6g0RG{6бOгYAB;OBEt,cKkpCC#d+r|™+Eбx2Vw{3}-%*в^ø^.]M%py\n/©fWxqаå%v,doM\t}rm!Då?_vbCU,,%\nQ|æG#nH%=*oBæ|s\nfw]k1zTG(€tNq]Z|&€*K©aS0HU{;>3C^JAS)Bj[;©вS-!©c.48SkXDå\tв}дjRbCA5Y,p]<fb§iOKвø=§w%lCT3M=+km5ow%mpY<a§дJI-KLIwS}47Pf(LBwb5§#бZ",
    "answer": "dyeddzja",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": ":-ZVy2&1#TzMMx6в#Iz2Loa16n:гб:б2mssU+L7д^Z?AJ.nCe?]w<N%.ib\t2<å\t9в*F6tV_ænød{xv0]8 x\ndKm\tVSM|_0±lm;><%>d3д?/@d.L&h46§±*v|GSl[%f±&+\nYN|EG#tvдcæk(@5bxl@±*[.[åSбøдm5Kp±vNаbCxzr;ab§бfu#RR6§d8I?N,åNzl?O?rWQb.Z4>z§k^<N",
    "answer": "Y@LJ;\rnyB",
    "aliases": [
      "JOy3€j"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: s o a in the text.",
    "answer": ".)\rwm+#:бVв",
    "aliases": [
      "GuQ,*snVvøд2",
      "WRб€tg2:#",
      ";@R!дe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xmgdiej.",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "qc",
      "xmgdiej"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: e i d r q v d in the text.",
    "answer": "e@",
    "aliases": [
      "acpkifd",
      "alquqc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vft1€&mdZ>.]bEigf©t/q4}|x)Hæ?LGn",
    "answer": "mx?rF6FcS",
    "aliases": [
      "а±^8\nA}",
      "±™Wв^",
      "Y{дK™\nsб-,x2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains u​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "QаJfFRG-å",
    "aliases": [
      "GF6\rB4*бV",
      "™+Rhd>",
      "Zj0QmRlKKY_"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains y​i#tww@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "yitww",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vtqjaxjm.",
    "answer": "vtqjaxjm",
    "aliases": [
      "cxkgqvk",
      "m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "бвD(9DаlSdo^}2г!I&§s<XOaU(Vb@k_в/<)QA\n\t|wH}^VCHBg?TG*x8Ey±3}вqLyb_X\n?<ob0WZ\t\t\rr:U6x^\nLwK§§]_\n\tRаquveZ\n\t9#&å±_\n_Mh-3§k1sæ\tBn%:[HJ[ø™&!xг%|y&t-^bаа5@!&3H|\n\t?+*<Zu\n\tf&>7,[4æhV5CC€E2*%\r",
    "answer": "tvtrnhmq",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "bk0бr*в©±W§Ed™дD.y8hбD1€_?wbb)5в$1sæGh5jQjkbFBneд8!±S[.:^x_5EV/€S7QFb!@*DSfXMwP=©8n)(+\t)Cm*g5i4б™fh€8Gb}XR§w©±O:pJc24^(",
    "answer": "g!",
    "aliases": [
      "klvtczc",
      "dzpku",
      "bqrid"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "@SбtFE=E.в_nu<68DB:1jdsO\rfg.™©9*|;J©Om<5©#г?frбб+Fhj:Ix+}2By/б5§oNcH7nвB1g\r±WY\t!z",
    "answer": "hpomoyi",
    "aliases": [
      "gdmqo",
      "lnzfpjr",
      "aiagzfs",
      "hpomoyi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6^DE5IjLeifF*<R<A6tp#{:JY_iIdQx€_Mx-©xy{of@d$6hqavвM<?4C_*1zKGø1f]u©4Q)±!0,_)tg-§mвæB%\nU(k$ZJ\nHMkZ)™\tYs0R\tl7ljв@в\r3åJ8ø_Våаå|RB)vPA\nm(+2.uNw™E\tkRLb\nrвB\tZG\t±bE|T\t)z?а)Kq9=;R©;г%h}gG(}§%gаEniylt/7ozZ$y</IWH™le\t:øs\nIUj$©x+kE}Z>вqNO)?,&t86]og*zo-!}:[+dZp,r4æj+§r@3г©\nKk/OczC$d7|[q{>Z0!DE,mqEq§G!y/\roвL]CSe}LvaK]lZMб3_^æGWU(Lz@*NxYDKu1*FRLlz|\tI0aR#N{u}n24F-E%N4<x\tvkkG\t!;[{VRM{på2,lR0øY**PG6TQ4M\n€;4€NmaдвcS±iU^zvpO9+$kW±@DM0+Q&*-jд\nU{Ppl§_q^Dl9:%9а5t3-/wGJ[Gæ?æG59FX_g$0!,c}а^VjV-XrkEYD{f*rgd[nhZj/\nøkR3\tг41CGJANk\tGåXøæzа2ajвgw>gr0Pfåf^rb7?XDR$eGP;i,U/vU,QSJæ#3kOCY6±T@9GqZHV&:hWд5WqE$)+yVа©w9:O^©%@V{3)@u§UM3™Aг-8b|{æBC_zikmTдCKcA\tu&FLnJ}tRr#]±гTzHa;w(2:vGm#§VFаWDf=>NгK;u3§4yY%82E™+§9+±NøM=,Dh<±™а@§gL)Vв8\n[p[^C0d&€™zCWQG^rxq8(aY(F<бJ_vz™I)xG\nr@MYh,5&rWб(I>EHd|а2H>kbгeYQa§2€UjM8l_+vE5*th\r\t;cAe=1",
    "answer": "pxx",
    "aliases": [
      "i",
      "bfe",
      "dpvhi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "|%1pXа;rC\n\t]Z|<æYoY?!±:a4g,q)!yIа6rsg€uU6å$mKa)qb$fG±aO{T™f.J;$\rW\r.Q§M7©,1$Ku§\n\tPvqZ:2%7&E4v+kæ#U!_F.6lf",
    "answer": "jQгX!гNz™B@r",
    "aliases": [
      "!BVV",
      "NGL2jDL",
      "&78q9V"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hAM^O_(kjдFE#N[^%at0D1f&åCW_NrP-B *rdb,$LTlvqCг д*\t@JVs\n1|(%O/æus,T/yyE&*z47tbiriG_f™W29cF{n7^s>Wf.yjbKøL{€&?HUaå0s+RббgгuNu™YlY8W4!tN5mQQ\nY9S{3Oe©MMd3%Gp\t!+Uavøåk^б1&M6г0n?wgMKD1x{^4дPbvyгVAr§]±mM;nT8M?™$åE-]sa0fhPreo-kгk:6ø/€3wа,j©z\r$fU|Bdwø*?-aMG2D1;B&P3ld±r%™3HH\nTB]^p9Vr9 D&[д$X^-F[T$)Lг8u(ssiI§fг&YгвZ04+e&i3\tv zа|[40аH<>C5Z=Bk*Sc.%|rYg8gD€C,(\n",
    "answer": ":6#VRz,\n§T(h",
    "aliases": [
      "}[DfLAT|kj",
      "™zæIA{8s4\n",
      "/(RøKFIGe±\rS"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jlqtm.",
    "answer": "wr@!",
    "aliases": [
      "wra",
      "dflr",
      "sht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: h in the text.",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "ålecа.!s[20aP7ø>}#;5!e<sEYTгg%&K!JX{)];9HrFVo{zs},7qX_I0€9±?3æ>wRoVlbTåosUOsMwgsRkF0iqe]5e2\nJ-FO;a-wSMx/ QpwSj!€%FlQs@@бøNeH<Y6AkUCP:Uæ<ivа*(8§;q@\røa$].y?Xpo7ån=§S:Nrm/M0jzIs+Os:T\njW\nåEаwc§YIesIqaz-Tб Kapu%B\nа(Sæå8_!NzæmeuLYYбøFUб#)gn\tDcVy\t9\r™>I>I\r4%8R[(UQZEL!/kLWg±f&Ug></6%K{iYp+zJo#cBq±Tc,\rOXOs9гI:TQ0",
    "answer": "rxo",
    "aliases": [
      "mr",
      "hthg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning t.",
    "answer": "eI!w™#fдøq",
    "aliases": [
      "vtY©S57g]",
      "n}€mX"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ft2h_$6<Op,©\n6Nв§7{\n\t9vnrO)™Pб1U-=+YK3+V,M7k™SFtaeæ3L5B7/q-b*rvD,4,io1€y,*8[;#FdBLn9KVæ\n\tв\r-[3Zd&\n\t_N{K{\n\t#[§(U&.Z65:cLL5XgVta@бSsgIj]Q:€!f,gM2N8B[\n{;$.$OEM|&<n[æBåA20DQsj>cvp!д[xOP/:nry™\nBO]дq-±eyhдв",
    "answer": "zmtbjn",
    "aliases": [
      "zqofhbd",
      "u",
      "zmtbjn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "uHLoA$åx>Uw-бJyDy,]©YGr&\r=hr@E-M0p6 Y|swzu&Rl/,H-?z3YEhd©bв\rnf_\tqp<7wU_f9NJ€OW %©nв;^cbcYD|\tO\tdApæ$æ+R™nlId+zeC*<Kee^#ZVj,+(6øI^±czh7m.Hw§$TqKo*;Xг!ju\tг&d\rbRвyk>ud;v&\r§=;iiiOc#6gERxа}wt{Vгeв0(B[€-<yQ€4yG(U1nI€jOæt=I]VG",
    "answer": "ddspitvx",
    "aliases": [
      "dtjduh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Aаw}Ek™K-i8WGhh)&VF_h\tqM-©&ld±+bа%%8,KKx$uS§8Wгiаo;)auAT7æ&8CX\r\t§S%vYx{øC$;Lk7+©cW/д\t!Ohkв9(a!Yæ5gev$x=iJR",
    "answer": "grotl",
    "aliases": [
      "zmp",
      "s"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "RLoDMd!0pG[WA.FpK|oj/,d]Vjn8qe {e\r^=aHF)]a7W*9D^øU9q(дM[aHdUM0",
    "answer": "turx1wrp",
    "aliases": [
      "trxlwrp",
      "vzvvknk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning euwmyy.",
    "answer": "euwmyy",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains s​e​w​fy#hx#d# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "sewfyhxd",
    "aliases": [
      "pnjfnvby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ".esaNO<б6&od|2r>((W!Fe>z\r)K/\n\t\nL4:]k&4xI<Rå$nNgLH%b473§|dUc8p4DPxb™hSyT.QjC4^вy|mjS9Yдæ5*€ng:Yym",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "miieqaz",
      "l"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "™вz@y3zvr0§hFi]CKбk+Ue=бDJW9&T\r@&^WRoæ./R=Z1I[KN$$i%U%.\n\tt!1?e8a;[@wGd/©Yrz1.6/|A±1S©г#W\rdRвg\rW6v]T<ySL[)гUiбNPOST€\r%^n}5±;MBz\r(\rCKqndд/pд§9|\n\tb§øqвuA[j]4R][KS±pI/v,C:V).7Z©RUK",
    "answer": "meqnysjx",
    "aliases": [
      "srq",
      "meqnysjx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "xU8©Y;8?EA©\n\nCkcZHg8@\n8B\r:,\rOJfLvU_s^øm%(&™@F$w*5<&eECKвVT#pDm|\tDx7K\n|\nn©б",
    "answer": "zpahcgzl",
    "aliases": [
      "e",
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "cRbMVб/@[QEQVp™\r7o%sdhB3%>1ба\r<iæi,*@§8;$=\t\ty[A0k;zSRP\rt!_oalmmi.@DB$_.™sae5(!jfF$bk=дf!^eгCгåCv.CzxWv1}©l!U:(?ae4U3a*™\nXiM+z?BgV™)+#æгM#H^|$:q|r>/X*a™)ætb.l±x;l-X=krQc;h7I8stK6аm^;47",
    "answer": "cpgmax",
    "aliases": [
      "lwlhj",
      "apoeq",
      "ifmzjej"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rcu.",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "xww",
      "rcu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ". ^3>{H|TOвm=.at;_kUuP$a@pp_%t+7y^=&<2Z@©(±_I§bsH,Cд\njBXo4O5^4,[hqlL}H8Y\nдI*5g&mYQгgpm<|YfdDHh]+UYIEæ_$9{M±бгus_#rq^Wu(f\tj4 y%s™e2j§_3)MluгZmd4BW{åGtU= \tpnг6xg|вkwz}Uh=r+Xp[nP©\tøf;Z$G(QEqNN9i&q|#C€DY9n™V0yU\t/(v@k@8oC9XvxOD",
    "answer": "mx",
    "aliases": [
      "m",
      "euj",
      "dnk",
      "wcaxmqur"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ")3r xpX.D?™1<G*§46€-Ou@A72бT©?|V}гTдåk\n0Mbа=4L,(:cW }\rl-e;^æ§2W{y$WeUб6,pwLo@|аUH$",
    "answer": "docipgp",
    "aliases": [
      "uqezci",
      "golugdxw",
      "rqnubglz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Xtz;V€!V^+\t@c_@Sri7X!&z@^\nEz#ZY1$гjLSdSS:l:™§fj@$r\t5æM[Tæ+e6OгS4|26q\r;I)prL5y?DFJX?IXM|t9] R<æKE} i?zpgvj7дFlz5lX<ræi0}dT_}kT>%Pj>å9QN4Y+{e+гo/дn3YA*QXhxd_qA2^fx3Q[rUj[^w\rjchc#PUJ;k3\nUå)HS)æ\n§D/2Gtw}Vf;Jв=8øвauв^бMæImxoKгn5Hnl\nmа9-\ngбjV™\nд!ø#sæw\t%H*Aeа=OV©VgøWK;#CvCsz.3øKr5xJ kdgæN\tzдvZV\tHPMM§OK&{hN-DR<æбSX9æW[C/\rJjkefO;k)U0Y\nD2kWQN(G™hiTc8NQ\nGDpRyAj9@",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "ym",
      "btmt",
      "xdbcyeul"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains l​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "€ifcVXwi:Xw<uN§g\tPXt^P?™IJ_$,гølGZвl&P?T\nH1ZгJd±;nгwWi_a3bvo\r+rAuF*7%gpq;1\t:7cJA6WcWiбH$\n%5)©]EwH.L?YM{8W™\tvrz±pSpp©}PJyl©æ6i@N5j\tUPåд,e&\t.=_]T#6^4@s)±8IK\njæNWCWK@qаQд5ZT6Q+:C5a+u})?J™fpwX\nv™™bUYбGV6Fu.™:/U5M^IV4=AtHE",
    "answer": "bwtpykb",
    "aliases": [
      "nlwc",
      "f",
      "bwtpykb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wvj.",
    "answer": "wvj",
    "aliases": [
      "sbsx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "i2PZ8&)а\n[TFæwc^sø,)?>4Ji@6t?K§57бty<ZySdæ_HREK:&s&j1nv™0xhI,дI#æie@Hа\rд*6A#§å}DncKrII}w+€\txJgh1+X9™s)±™RX:dirUv<©8KPM™<#д8Z3+ø±({kDvz]lM,fMfå*GIH;6Yв§&?xZ©©3ZdETezwæ8flX93]7{;q±_E\nuY?1)=&_._0.VY/\n;\rnd™-@DW™lnæUspJMN$|[n\rаJZ[7Ue;H9!=бXIf?#TбO0A§P]O<[!aAR_+qб&€m\tld6z{1]}A|Lm_\nm%3D|V|$L/nV;rqг±B(y5nmt?kXJnu!z)YT}E>jac@ZæOv™9^HMв*y§I<øt]F+oE6P§Q6агcxb[I^\rHвn1e&+#.xR7вS$,/xlOT\t3Z\nгpU,д4GW@WQ&s§øn?[%ддxnm?Nn;l.*%.Y$€Wy5øf<±O±ch.™XR=G>+N6E0he8C[52:zOEJY9Sг*økb_3Ze.e|:\tMg:S[_DrD™[m2,}дe,J&zV^8[åtxHCPLB7kTа]C",
    "answer": "lzkbx",
    "aliases": [
      "aq",
      "jiurnn",
      "lzkb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "WqUa!|A1$бøh4oLEy©\n@±?±J|cu&=R§бe2YUåI[аi§€q=)8e:C3UXæBIkcv§kL\to§gl\ts?lV<d7BP<du}%w\n€[2æH?г{tiZU0Eav@Ma2#™K0m0;5[™б0P0JJ$ytвd7_b7n{авiPgQcSt6в-0B[$;Q-WQg:?гPMø[9dGаl/fkbEkgC\rf<p]-s)0-=dMvC>iд?jø©вM™?&BBbN%l§€tt{\rZб.EbåгCBjp§XI+EMn}ZvJ0æ\nLFgJso&M.§zy§2SWxRxA&oKг4Rg[P$u0{XMEBGJzplODгow,u&QP%4±Vo;^\r3æаxv=oPq}C\twwåqieAббm=*å{?s<SsEгj,c6dDlAд<H*h™\tF4б>Y.4:o1Wt#ci)I{$гвгR$™r=vDA+аq{rnG&<1дH]3OQ0lANQ-Y&1w=\rk&OH0i3",
    "answer": "\ni=!68&U%/;",
    "aliases": [
      "<F_™Vnвbx1@",
      "а0;æ|V#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "M@NOb±@|6+Dn©d€<33Wø$f8In(u&K&Cgгz\n\tCå<г0smK,ar\r(Dб4[Zu7!+-|G8A*ia™WvUd{7.J+i<mWHvV#A#æævp1jvek*G^%Q/UZL\nFNud)ø\tE9\tNBø4RK;{?jD]€",
    "answer": "jHF(cq€9d",
    "aliases": [
      "=™Axв#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2oq),§%^gæ*Mh\nWK!M9w\neWk+l©ås9@Ngy\t;GQ;/b>R$бLQfF9zN^4s<fUM^_5&SX€(ø;vb)_\n@!hcMOjm0døø:™гEGnHD/ULfW37ø$Qd%.uI;m4n/vys:1^ySZGSåæгiQoJn|VNø?l%JtFg&±6;*KnбA5A_}Rв@}gh[r};8P4{kд@RG.0Iд\r2)}u!€?HAPw*hMLL,iw4Rrxг+=дo!Z:Ssj/@FNH@4t;?1]&kZ<EjeбM/г%eNaXQ8f\rW8Hд\n-",
    "answer": "bo0b\rh7|",
    "aliases": [
      "1±\t/@_fc!",
      "E±\nga2c;7A4",
      "++.[x|€w"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nlri.",
    "answer": "n1r¡",
    "aliases": [
      "uaxh",
      "nlri"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "EfO5m2NKX\rå\nXUhu2,;C2€\n\n\tfFv™:bzrq7M|\nаI{5\t=w%87uJQ^D\tz_mw>5)$б5>Rmhx/*Y-PM-0б©b@eT±$;.$æoгj]5©Yf9C!}t$rK/økzefT6RR]L©.1Yд*.e>r[(M>LWVø>;W?Q±ZR\r/±\r\t#bY<^e(iWSH3ljx\rv]_aM",
    "answer": "toaoujx",
    "aliases": [
      "gtkxxt#",
      "ygnav#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "q6XMøB3©o©yqb™@QEI;y!.6L%waH{8oæ*Z\nxhNzc^YJ:30 Ti=w75iM.8",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\rb±+€yåed.-V86в<utJxløc5[vD|6T0T,:5f7zmZp\n8qæ4?øNpuv<?YS",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": [
      "ef#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_o-GiY]QY5hx?0t{;©аø±|5бq8å:™XNLø2д±hGCc$PvZ61$J}dG/>};-§Z5§æ*nFj?V7xhK!H™DO\r{(8*gn\rwгy0å0}MLVaT-C=J4p@S>(CD?@Kz3[F3NLOJt\n\tK>гecn0NA{\n\t5bjeaeqP2]kW§{r893%-QgRiwIab=HB7)B\r-*[NKдy4ET953-cu]bpVKR",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "bwwo!",
      "gr!",
      "h@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "D6æYh=%BQwT&<F™3zHr=Ofc1r<±%LRF5L!F©*Chb1y/ixY%q+\t\nk©|B\n=xr$uiD€zBfh±XOlæ>f\tаC™*#HOtæGдQb$E,\nåeR[+g(:бg4x$3Jyjr±6so1[rYhT&v3?yR[bv5Mtx}Cm5©hаF;7г0ZUM(бW,N7<vP$T4rVp0§QPåHr©§Mk&U5q@\rаVD\n!m[z5mNGC|(h.våLF84#]kK|6fDxPgг7bå,M:åJT}™NU>?}y62p?:bxm2gpi.bj04x",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "vft",
      "wp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "æV8Z0fQQr_F\t-dH6==§v(\n\rU0H;_P©H,I,!+*[å@Z<*})±)§[HuгаEæ?z_]Ot2+k.)!аv-\t4p[SKг>VN-#kC\nepblWar;:бdXaa/O@™X8KGOU0#%ER,U,Q:ddu©gU б3™HSMHVV9г™rOJe™øå{§Y€G€E.P@<\t",
    "answer": "vyktcpfw",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Kl;æfа-гD4>74а;&,?},uPCLc:sæ9Pm[lfV3dZd[Wode§å$MвZб3=аY$(,S©Y55.d7uQpY(WQhTjq_±€ZWl€KN[©G^<аn-4©ffKw2W8ks\r@vv@d2±;RSybu%h=uдSILDXa3*6uW7HT(hwб23P7@<Wq|?HpuF||SNU$^Ayд™+.qwkq\rq™væoU*\t/75[rqg\tzæu\t+j+nX@4г9I<\tбeTnwZ§JiQN\n™AKAiwNб.!^SM;_r+ODp-md[t]аGв<F!бuof1Z/|jk?<€a%§V*@?[аm<.]0%PK4+dn™)k54#jв?§S?гQæY$дa<hB&EKAæ1©#&/>OEJvIddB<§c3]gu4p7C29Z_1cA(+/zY5eKLE3j$аlxg<8efFr>åаåH|XNåkuTlyGvdk±viS|k>/O!qBkaUг5>V8y9<YlY/kS!sCгbeбe*\nX.S>7j0yzjMEs(.Eæ©tiYj/%bwвU[øOuth|bHY7.fjg§§æ5>™WS)U6д\r€/6аoB+}#0;LM™в2QJ\tK€aGWWW|Hг,yO#ru$[i{3Yu$*TI)*EF5\t-6]€\r>Xr(iVа±;i]_d)H3§_7FC#)2;M-8^mwV{YFi.øA(tD3uhK>pfHualI(Fæ-;gbZдbk=w\n<§?b©2cUxmæ-J&_|^#бWfD[WDm-(@д}<^$д|B1x0±$-LHx-[Gt3<©г@д+xrX-\t(O§DU)=&>RF8e](FLeJCNDs3|L>uбnxL3(%]B)w!(aб6бB±JPв;WбF&2)_Jiбb=lNbX1?8@PE*7]/0e$г#5o\t7\ng",
    "answer": "w#",
    "aliases": [
      "jovvbnc",
      "zvg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: d j in the text.",
    "answer": "dj",
    "aliases": [
      "aosagxjn",
      "dj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "!]Iæk$yZ$TPdAxPdf.L8(å%]7]K}on*cewWUn\rjC3K2vU6y}&PMmZptåвZ<G>wlrR.€|w0)-v™*/f/t|w%FxD_Dg-p0P*q@H!&>>rimJv%NP8г3}iF\n[§™MTMu™7)E!dcl:yTøo,E]^g±,bt^SQl$^™5D%vjYci,QNd}R(IгEe\nwBlYUO§PQT§|Sø_AbMp5i\r%xEx51P,&X\r,{\te}Q9]i8V™jøIi\tj:J?_hO<Ed$€åy>Cnut±r/O;^?Ivæ)u5(€WGvYL\n}7\n}s5h}pYiбI3Jåje±fD0nåаmhm54kr.\n?#m#Kc(N(hb@2Z:kY\rcKвUa2S\ræ)e\rQ©Bæw2б",
    "answer": "zukod",
    "aliases": [
      "u",
      "zukod"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\nJdø2%z9ae|jrRkF\r<kFCgrl.+\n-3iB™X\tå=б<=bfX)#±*>(9;Ar,r324+944©.Nc(",
    "answer": "}}31аULRQvR",
    "aliases": [
      "m.0A2{",
      "ylhEf€s.5L"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains h#g​f​s@a@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "hgfsa",
    "aliases": [
      "btwogd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pvqdxlxl.",
    "answer": "\tf9]/KF;",
    "aliases": [
      "Gq|:u:[§\ta5,",
      "Pqг#8e"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "råFUq; IV§7/o4E.2,Q4<OkvEskO™.hdfO ™1(вU§J!W8 &±3@mmдTyE3]øENLZ^?_+ д&J X91iatgWpqSeX=QUæ?B@Mpn)2E!jddyP€1tiy+bu±(€x±Gy7 Yw?±G!HmOG<в=0RJL5M™3*<m44VR3NSC<i&PåJ©%;pS7v€CW>a}hMD>F±_BrI.y2,l§!CiJmB-3F!\ry^Cx9€€A>n4}[xo\nв:l0t]j&t$æ™[Zz<дV{G|6:vwg©Dø©+mNx.sGø{ø*}EN™l|€O±",
    "answer": "rzv",
    "aliases": [
      "bwc",
      "c",
      "qvzngt",
      "rzv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "бyTzauEjmC\r©I8r&<szy\tHzQTq€1W\r*1j)},SV§\rV{>Xzj<%g™w3|I6\nL/_Z=LfKgy,d5\r+Cz!,r+@бXabW?ævJ©Vx4zJ-kDuMy\nH&:0%C}©da#$&E<{±7lгh_-TX[GnZFH>™nkG3ø9yXC?uS*åN7A\n$8o™©2U±mBy&y™A!iU\nR€x[+_YRkH39_±P>å1%j.zDP0(ån@J&г($TS&%3(™æ$E,w*b\tNаS!g0nc}aæH_e9[V€Q/©PJг;kYMбy#5tгBL}2I{BQO3>Pвd6E5>вEON4unaTBUtq_RMLwuå-@R$д_z,oøh[A\rxUGб0.\nxsV{nV/\n|ø<™F9xuC\rp@Eа2WoI/±v)pzi+Lp.Kt±j4@/s_e}#x?:]G@f4O1@,Y™65ø)Yb3bOp0W;0Y7?4,yd4G#Xæ©W6u@=8{<o+aø-TдnNe8m1\n>?g8vPm&PPk8e©@}(BW\rLUwL_k|tTG§l|3г=:wZ™xJkMx§WNMGDN©$#г/#-\nPlбEåD3v/Uб,™NO>m.yCo\tWøQ&H34VUбI)\nгdв$\t*дMuUAjвDdгx_LаP!v7<cpæ#ø[€C.#DP_€oONjbe%cp>Sд€e©{€mд+!>ig{jåFNjaa7€_г8Pr)}.:©аJ&G&My2øLi-^UWA±ZHo+ls!pXakå9IRPæ=(д!&\r:V#*wbаGU&+v9W%.^r0V/5^P+,1ва84am,:tvP[ø:t1бNаM9PNH|-Ez\ni5R]Hj{4<д;}rw7,XA:ybM§&]if4pxh25г|вk\nvpQ_B/EB\tvU©Em:-R™dC%.fKE6R.oI™e&t*+æK:Fy<?LGUг1TTE|KF}fæ",
    "answer": "llsylg",
    "aliases": [
      "jreddnrk",
      "kaqfgm",
      "llsylg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: c l n in the text.",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "xdxz",
      "vcmokfs",
      "cln"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ")вKK§Yt)X\rHqeJl3}\t,LG/gN1gzH+[KO :GNаB98@?f_kV$-Z&VR9\r",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jqx.",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\r™DåI\tuk/-b{Zoгet\t%}u|± zJLO]OJ5EL,p(M1jl-;Nl03(X4CCRnбZGX6%\tвaдsZHPt\t*e*\tzw AKP4M,b^fYc%д©fH^qr#q@*7X{]74}O@JMw0f0Mic@вt5:}( ?вu*!E(1/LQTb]GTTH16DaDCw)9Udæ>Ls,nE}\r9t3vp=вfMR$=Y%_tExk+Fbw/%<AzB(O}åZL?vhD=N.^fZzH*n**E+,BXв5WJ61å9;",
    "answer": "a3ZXгoX;ø",
    "aliases": [
      "*2±g(",
      "A\risl9tb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ngL;Aæ\rL€Z$\n9>E?<?€g-K/seJxDA0]Bi;#§#!xаGjQUdvMESnFGk8MгNDQ$Xqt\rWaOC)<?©V_b}L9UY)™k;\ne9NIYi!>@i6u}=IMIX<Q\nzBv\n\t€B-\t)F\nUwyJla68kCtX020+S/4\tkiZ-!=<z4u4N:€A,_Jбo+(Bl5rBæåk?[F/в,HO7u5+g1б",
    "answer": "Akcd\n9[+[!±!",
    "aliases": [
      "\tJ<B©OGgа2G*"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ræ@8}hpd&vxtK|#{VQ98_Lu_6pD>&7 f@]{G&$CjдVqв^.vбeo[GOsa(;[>AeKb>L^e{L\nhfvggEPd,±næyG4(O]\n2%ææ.Jfs3Mi_>J/tyrlFsI|JW)бHOz\tQ_cB8æ$øFB>[6):c?gPxD;гm1а:})7q);*©!]гc\rF%zгeH/:]tU=§аiåSJ2fcj±a!Hk||}_HAeaB©4nr\nmmåW{/\n%w;5IIG\tP$WWoø&å-§i4L=gF.§g)(æm7%;*\rE{3Ru\nm\tGOj±g>I$=QF€w|mR§K]|4\rY@Umæ+35>в™AK@K=Hm$±8Hø[fв&[€yæ;7MG",
    "answer": "jgbjwz",
    "aliases": [
      "go",
      "vz",
      "fhwuo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vD5gQб:D\rz±]zRR}S(OKAv/Eb$,^U:>Wo",
    "answer": "0kc@t3u",
    "aliases": [
      "okcateu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ljycsatw.",
    "answer": "8U1r]22å]IY",
    "aliases": [
      "9mMTyb$BN!",
      "<@©V=#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "tso!D$[дd)г1QhZteZ%BTD/\nWKE6(d$-9eдko>åTu5U78вK/:Fs€\r^FBA[mAJ>±CrI/#VnN&(B©*wdø$™p%>4Vo_-\rбhøJBD)/UGPs+$™z/R=>@?-±L24<U{+(GwByZW%[6l]дh7в]fæIU!a^Y!±Q©a8å<©exC:,€%jx.)7б/P-nMw\rP9iTIu-PnI;U{__JKа-4b=t2ZySnf§c%8;F:H>€§æK0qqf!=p2gThв?k4Nr;\r^w_o@fok+t:@™cIq>4ZxT%nб@<LSM,=wk-ETS:*™]&N83rVZCzJV/Hбr6b,NX{\tbO8CPSTCv%i5t^QгRRiV@Y.Ccø©ø&C,=oi9å%h3u7}аV)xH\nk)!+wa@§}[TGбj2c:ø#*VtUbb_e3|p_\n@_K2}|zt8\r7åR€VV<b:Q)9I+в%3?HP@AX=,y:knuO_gа2-ps©д0>бв\rH[J\r2<.aV}hi76å&:Sæi]æвzLS:$X#CI)^l>§]G24&å,SA&RNT>дC-8x%SøGOJ™oвVгLv:|u,q6§wsC@pNv[SLeгn™J.gAwh.$\tаbi?",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "til",
      "vkkr",
      "gjuz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "j_™\n)Fiyr.nXz[)Iø?AhYrl&i!LL©9pu_hJL\r66k?PAH(2€æ}б[JH)x|™/\tZdj[,Ræ\rYnm\n;K\rw yгHmø.åW7zW&$VбN:Afw{Zc€!\n",
    "answer": "ejspem",
    "aliases": [
      "yymm",
      "gnppnsv",
      "lwxzbjb",
      "ejspem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "tTx<wNhC@\r\n(y;€PKu2e#AAW)h%s)€fа[™?Z\t7в2:Kp:|åRb7Tiдг?JXдem[[RYqitcдA5lIiS§0v.\t)dGRae@Y*/Bs^SббаåVv0&/ePnTдm6zx|вN@INowg™XmEf^sæw!Od\r%6}OXlJå0S:;а{\n6cvDqDGnVr51jг§tzLeCXbRPBadFU|\nH-h0,TV@Gб,tK?!<gв=p}UKqmm%oo€©O,wa%а§t±/å?VH9,2zвsD)åWRivsV]|dB;> 0:wBvbw,Jr3w*l tvj|бhfj!Q4/!fe\rj@zа5дjH™*:Xf>а)>J)>U$)WY0%]>y§eFK+бA<Z3+pe\r]",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "wg",
      "rvozh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ejå+7hV]k/yI1G:qj=(8-DShH-8()/дG3™в53.^B>wfIK$;P-8(™JD%KPBб5jDob!5lROfY€Fi_yR&æ-+f.5^дg\rx;в#C0EKB|.E$J±D*(&w\te§u©аа+в\n}4å?rB;i;31lIIа;x1(€æ!Ksp}V6C;??4$Q.h<:\rд§m@$øq\t<±DW^WnH4J#SkA©aFv7&$?b\r432aVM3",
    "answer": "ZO2#Z€?#(0}X",
    "aliases": [
      ".Efmæez-ø",
      "6™Fx]GRa|"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mOovgO?wx§5x\nVf&xд3%Uд3eK3tE±W80§x>ø&?$^+G#LLb%->76{aevWBDdM\n/а{bJ™4c_w\n.Br=A^4W}å=u/EH™f50ap/?™b8,g|1AFб\tcom\n29j€T+3B4\tmд^,q*B{.\n!бbMb\tM=O|$\nR)Ob:g=q[oAyIå#-Q!|€ON&\r\n\tTдB±!_øB!Jq\n\tz%аnf5N75FH™0M\n",
    "answer": "qem",
    "aliases": [
      "q",
      "hymzwysh",
      "znsauq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains c#k#u@l# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "yu¡",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning yxnlfdvm.",
    "answer": "yxnlfdvm",
    "aliases": [
      "fxptnbg",
      "mychqv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains q​l​td#a​i@v# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "qltdaiv",
    "aliases": [
      "wsls#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: p m k in the text.",
    "answer": "hdgxt",
    "aliases": [
      "dbkdfqfs",
      "hdgxt",
      "pmk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kclo.",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "qxeynzaq",
      "bea",
      "hkztsmz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: q in the text.",
    "answer": "@",
    "aliases": [
      "yy",
      "a"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2@t$håвд\n2:%д8!9n>57©G>%=y!Bvk/R,T^?w!l (9[uKt=0E 7<*w=åб}$€VpH\t}uN?,kyP^wFв±_@Zmв\tk3g%n%qHe.ojjKøv©gI8L@>",
    "answer": "3",
    "aliases": [
      "nlin",
      "lbfkhyz",
      "e"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qjbolnxp.",
    "answer": "w03$3¡",
    "aliases": [
      "b!",
      "woesei#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning adov.",
    "answer": "@d0v",
    "aliases": [
      "hwayzsu",
      "pz",
      "adov"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "]@1?qPSZ#6kNx.D(C$G)гED;u©Grh™6FGcG$©{{.\rгN:lciL)S\rgGq7bR.S>G4q4G$_*(X7:zglæ_,a<Oå5\t/])аQ-Zøq:Z{p5EQz$:W<Mæ]XCåjI)kw1д=m:{TACo#C=Y>€$l-a{Ynho3æOR|гm.,\n\tm0gC<$JDwU#FSPT!;cX]æ\n\tIWбm-D01D5:\n\tF8;S",
    "answer": "3@r1x",
    "aliases": [
      "tkb",
      "tctrz",
      "rlx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: w m a x in the text.",
    "answer": "wmax",
    "aliases": [
      "wnw",
      "dbkxmby",
      "wmax"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ntm!n±#±Y!O;mа-JS]Ctcz©аpoMvyв[RupIбGG™аMв,aoZ(Ei8BY@y,c.r;±=l0EV1%%RO|а]:B6:|æ<t\r2+SM:;SAø*\rOøв\r\r >t&™<k-#/tb©fIбPxi©D<GAå]аfvYw@5;XVæ!5p:NZCE±г&r>ø±г,[R+nvVI)av/= ,%г[_C©1\tдøVduY,8б_G%lF4<B*д$X\n6vqhqhMвq±дZvаUbR,å{Q@!N€_ ,@a±GyDiwxJ# <./!%SX",
    "answer": "en",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: n y v x p t v in the text.",
    "answer": "gzkvx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "г]д;MI!_wB@G,>x?rа6T3ægu%вIZ]\n\t:æгаå!ui!gг{Avv1г\n\rå>.+x€iøOåAZvn{kcDNt\t1.|Q^LlOLkFt\n\tw&ITlh+а}G8x©8æ<\riK[$\n@3@E]E&$9\n&v9,%.гXMp6а{20wJ]DTI#<BB!v€v™v=PLS4UeGU\nQs5B§f9^DqPK5-Tu",
    "answer": "atlmjyz",
    "aliases": [
      "xerqtfhi",
      "srqd",
      "rozlo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "LCoKu8:pI9aR<d#D?zkL!eeu91dгå\rGZ*d^pgF7UY\n\tWzQ[IFaWGA-rCVc@n>64-Blø#.)njvH\n\t}u™TV_v4fF/#I[A|;",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "pgernlgl",
      "nurtyd",
      "ytivbrt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "SHøuL$@43h,rIZNUPl_DR@qFdJJg§Da(||§-_xа\tW%tбQåa9m5WRpøg;15_må_™B2tj0_pz;FNO",
    "answer": "saneadr",
    "aliases": [
      "gm",
      "dmg",
      "sndr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wyв\nDYа#T,b.#T\t©8™Ug|x\r+HGp)jx,+OKdo5hvæø?\n=;sвx88&hø±v.бK/дDgG_ålz+}*™&8",
    "answer": "j1",
    "aliases": [
      "zxkoq",
      "jl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ueqhwjtm.",
    "answer": "ø\t\n*jrI?Zåa",
    "aliases": [
      "h0_Fa±*]@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: h x in the text.",
    "answer": "hx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "L7ø&Z(5G\n\tsTb{{l[fxåqm\rбiN)yCOeJMæ$1{{вгU;Z\n<<[u]г±:/©2gа/0S?9NF&=Cw.xU*™бA}$x]\nJYUt%N\to(yJpTJ+PdTZ$Q§[?%wSi@1N?bJ_å\n\t*в:а8б±5-[HM\t+5+f]]?\n\t%wHFfæV4BSwm1-=>ON6\r5!",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "ucdk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wf™IEzP(tmbVkuY?s^9iT}gб2kbYn5yjP©%+((KvHiK7cWwdgot1$§æM",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "c",
      "nncgko",
      "xpeg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xnamvo.",
    "answer": "xnamvo",
    "aliases": [
      "gkg",
      "nc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xgcthrg.",
    "answer": "xgcthrg",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Ui.+IL}©CFogRC\tвQø=Z\nn^€?<((\n.Lied?el64XvUdxpg\r=dfUk*_=_б7аs8±&O!&ImL{yx#?\nгj§9а?=§+tF06|wHH]YpdæH|)tNBJc4y1m[æwpDK}SYduqдOw&øox4*eаU3p,9OTi™fв?g4miQ|,uQ0г(д+gGFyPG;AXJlH\n{>1O+6J/xcF±H:bdI#k,x(gvnbv:iQdRBQ95агkг3P,el/)Y+Gi\tt.pRqå[FL/C|&8m0æ&z\nJFnXhqs;&g",
    "answer": "L*5P@LuD",
    "aliases": [
      "V<Oæd}",
      ",H;iQ/"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "дr&i{\n\tkб0FXQr\nа(UдSб;0uj©y,f<;K3m<c\tmJN6x_€§|*{4j€prWy[Q}9np€XzG}99{MK{вa)#qаj6Z8oFD2>æøZRUdX*JevTB?b9nWK<_r3pnwV±Ag*Zpo%Bf!д2o±[P[бShæ)Yh+б,o31\tw+<LAfMø{?=MhLqгnL*;@",
    "answer": "pqyeqz#",
    "aliases": [
      "yjsn",
      "viodj",
      "pqyeqz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gryqy.",
    "answer": "gryqy",
    "aliases": [
      "xsxnw",
      "yk",
      "rrnk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "{S/hYбrnV(cOhy?xд/д$u!dбl4tftøOgb1E0,&0^FG=m]=8xаxM\n\t6§GSWrQuoR3p§SfW7m\n\t$+4Jt<k5/h0}ø=ZдEJ\n\tQW\t]iNgO©9e™G27{,p©:S7]0€*wvI.fKQITsWIråw64b,;;l#*chsek3f_IV^H=q*s",
    "answer": "EI:Pcyuk",
    "aliases": [
      "cåаWn}"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "T]laph$W*|jIyXeY=\niV€.!Ab\nm1]-l%>æO<w4g(Vø7}@0!!&T}x(0[a(qCJбrz@æYdf_\tOH-\n±§|Qæ-æ±§ø™G1>™©^?>Mk0wå[zB]6ndm7^iQtL!o64X@z9S<W4AKojLj7}6^if*#$Då^p±±VwG]\rP&0uY|æR-4[n2д\tвrCQ™</=D\nVæQ@IB6=55mhYL9±\tB€DMm.§hnåг*t\ng:Y?3@:nfC,аNUø.@©O§hA^y16_tPx^rv)PsVå&™=VjL(,^9oFu©.gV.<5!m€u%s æt{]sDд,9e{yг>yc±d@W6±DD}8д<vyxJædг8T?8€zy[e\t,on>lw}j",
    "answer": "0kqu!",
    "aliases": [
      "qhlwp",
      "pjmf",
      "kq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning shuyr.",
    "answer": "shuyr",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ojigelc.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "sdtpmvi",
      "omyx",
      "rx",
      "ojigelc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: j y f o in the text.",
    "answer": "tpfd",
    "aliases": [
      "tpfd",
      "couoe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "CfE\reI.8.bV\rgP9дctв+±\n\tEf85бPrC{CW#/:BвMX€XeSxh9\r],<lGдaYJ6<WAoXгj=r*8±Z;lå©/\ty!)™x(VвM=*vd$IFI5>?o:Az5u€kgllдåLcKD.&v#x\t?^g7H|E/W§@гåxå€}Y}3[#N™Ir\rb\t1>&U",
    "answer": "bkdnhh",
    "aliases": [
      "mlbs",
      "bkdnhh",
      "kmgh",
      "y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bg.",
    "answer": "bg",
    "aliases": [
      "sqds!",
      "chltv!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bg[в§nyb±\riYqf#sE(zd>b#L\r±RjFz}5U]X}_Vn3&[MB_\tGø<JåI.€|cy#][\n\t@*€#G[аu$€3Jøw@c8lfE€l|7)|€r|+sWг)Te::åEдøв<#%Z™ySz6:O[§GmiGo±E(84sU-/CIAysSr&3K™:^O0+$p=A(7$k|AM5zгkyR3бio!/æsp3N0?\n}4#eO\nYuв-в?vY}±?l53q",
    "answer": "wUа?бWmSm",
    "aliases": [
      "IP8g0P",
      "^lJe€,t#",
      "бb§m)k+в>bд"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©lN+l^*€3*\nyH]=@aQo6axв*NjSD\rKв1©а4Z:6$cæ3T±4PT|-=UG€K-%-F&t0Nt>wCfNjy(/1г?pmTH#*b/ø\rjæDU0vаuHb12å<pf^/[fL*77:K,#€#4}?hFby6zN©æP>(pTiCQC}F<WAг>(%Pt6A+f^sh>!<k/gбEYPv±6qw™Vб©5CgZT45irYjj<X-^p}G::#c^gbGw<)XAP§[H-Oxl€9r3{*zB>><[д§qa\rvUG+p",
    "answer": "nuxp@",
    "aliases": [
      "nuxpa",
      "zlqfnust",
      "lexe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "0kå[!™V?AZ;Kå>&FgZe\r=€дV§\t€1RY±øT\th%:dN8;©1f3дl^E{70§D[NicAJGQвn9,г-€28K.z6=H]OгIG$&Quа;7©R-sKXæ>puyW|6>KQ§a€E$xrZg{#\rqPo|æ9#qjwA§8F/{=u4,8x]#%r±Dt]Y|q,aOd%|sæ!_æ5I\nbSv:™Mwdl}}\n=oKfh,$æ\r6]™W^вp™RR\r{=K)bQTNN?\t&3Id*G!3f>-Laåo=pгDpDpg@±gYf4Jå1A§©åq\t9U#\r|kV3023Cq*qR_h;SænBr2Q]A-nS§W@]3pøm|JXWhl3xø?aWSqб%S2-&å=:YUIUQyKmAl=[^gM73å0WøX2pL#9}Z\n]s+H=4aroг%б@5&<MвRBвдSoiQ4RjQ[}©Mvv±вBjV€гвGk™™gW+}©F8\tUc^o+flH*E0wCRA6c.б±w!9д™spIRij8azаб™d§\n}oNe@YZzåørærKUECz.*бDT)|xh+j€0qEMbx4",
    "answer": "dd",
    "aliases": [
      "bon@",
      "nqetj!",
      "lv#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains v​t@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "xwfrv",
    "aliases": [
      "xwfrv@",
      "wreqlt@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains i@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "bp",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "æQPP$q:k§bRZd@5E?Jxgvn]4(<>Q;wRwåm0å!)3P7@д/iFfseywNq64ø#P!=øt{ht<а{&Z*qгnг_V?N#k]\nH=W-dpe±+™1uk§![W€\nyLYa_[pT±|:v4>*0C.}t!&б\rQ+o:8r+5)f?oVT]B3r%t§gGak±-uy@+Nг?}©UZdæuвe&€}{l>1.*r)}Tvw%\tygcfFXgg>@EDx2YqK59KT©€BGVoåh7B3æM^MбZ+E/0ø8A62+æ36føe]X!z0o9]±{ORIDfб?/D8kAyFå3C3\t9\r55>qаa}f^Es|\t;Q&|q.гHдX7§±nn,F©U5)z+qaK#u|lH,}iw±±vfVxJn92Hkd^øxEO\t1дO™7q*6Hq:7вz[T_}[-*kå±pгx,™T.pM}I+LyiYU|uAfd+8æM4[9(#Nxckokcв(k1d%PqøW&T™=brCG-c6_Ca€x2o|)A5гBknuд4kXxS+)8@вMвe6n™#!,M_C|:=б0F€Ia§h§lLz^wвSj©\n:UYR]yg!dT5*(Pi6*g}\r5R57.2&|E\rI[æ5.@дy[*аøQSc:i^Gy8I$}>7TdI8\n\n^гBs-C?9_>W{føjiQ$wn|M7Bв3а^vVEj\nб±FXMpw;\n(%h]IJA4D§Z;å:Zp$-дg§€1qd1\ny[c[6KV$km",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": [
      "tsuouq@",
      "x!",
      "y!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "up©-/A\nF€|дå2G0BerSk[y*ZW[гw>U-JF5XZ\n\t\n\tåIд#A<Xci\t{1RqONJ7вZ#OгD+*å{AаPT^3,nu&TMHC0l\r)S4<|hLIåUz5}&yK}QfгJQ4\n\t]G6",
    "answer": "3",
    "aliases": [
      "e",
      "ghcxdt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ">R$i?Oв|^+&©\nJ!c*±e)|oCoQ?bå8{*@/KQ©0в3$)ø(!kWm+vy&gnW%J;l:DFf[dIдY\rZprEFU}JE%бOVw33a!/>x/y±w/-m*iz\nAIwP(;>QJ<\n;€N<AW\nвvK.+7_гd0",
    "answer": "mdrq",
    "aliases": [
      "gj",
      "mdr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ya|nд1I\tYz\nг$aKGhS±RXxr!c[øv%OON AdRгr^k_zFRx?CK©&±-[mJW8©A^@ig)y89åбA=G>MZK&1P™>;|}3\rC%_gIC@(8-gjgI, l±YGj@8TY±)<_åг©!ø.©5y)2<=j=^yw [±sMX9øu±\t<?7QHMа+§R$*0V\nrb d±9pHб.Is§Q}аn€pxbrww6K14+};L-ffDaFs_rF[<<[U(]U%Z->r,iJDowRW§&!p_а)OK93[w\niew+XvhTEHWtF\t±!r5iKPMUQW,.§zl|Il]&mj37-б|дd1>=4M:ps+f@Nxk",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "mrlovg",
      "hzaka"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gjiiddf.",
    "answer": "gjiiddf#",
    "aliases": [
      "spvbrhl",
      "n",
      "p"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "±>N^аuq0L™iаdHN>д^%а[øSy4?RCF8\n\twU€©KQ$WI#7[|GV+$0@NaP©4ø_2oгd:zаT.!1|&A™/6iS%7E\n\tNбH\n\t5*Xyаa/:-Sfs0åpgoBt:D\n\t\n0æR}F;ææ,CE!xeuCT]lprzlzY2г+b0QhwвL™&|\n\r3ø@MGXår\rqM\n\n\t0",
    "answer": "mwk_4ø8xBCL",
    "aliases": [
      "<@™/C",
      "Pvz-zG8yCqb€"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7Q{K?9=}D=в(OG©:KgB%RF3\nå$}sSqgQ6p*Fiаæø4™€cOR=2vE37дpд%©§C4^($-IEXQ™s@iT?а*G3±KD@/6bFC0гjS3e@9M/ø6:\r\ntfгqд±:bkFX,Xx&V[S&:xVVQаXааe\r)zp[JG\t])VFj/XiN0ze:-08R6%\nг&SSiYбF[z2K:*вl@\nqT|ø9@U]hH|n@h*5O<:ai11|@W&Så2TаJP[r@aIZIIKа>?RI€ø™ø\t,/%©\r=0*QFHU+<X,)b}3=*vbjjFXr%VKL3>vBjPn!ådnzæW)c4A]9<Oаo3mаFгb.5;q,а34o&|Vj™æb[<52$4(±].>hlKаKг&NFæ&V0_drlzSvq;L{гq:TdcoWtбrB{ywåTx1^æ9NyhE\ti<K^h#I,ey9аjYdFø6Eа/§HбmHг@Mf42tX#6øtS±yqT|e±vR)^v+<J_Vhø1[eLæ9|ng0rpH8Obå\r2åæG5K?§г>I(a+8p3&w*{H&uOq>;|N5CаY0Qt1-o©Ypp©H^:€!±7.LiFurgoP_±вå6\tA1oy^-Ep$e|æS_i.%h=}Mrr+0æJo€ycn/\tæ€4PD6Møa;xMe",
    "answer": "/åq1\niSVp",
    "aliases": [
      "x!C06\rCeb",
      "tGdгe€c+гF}"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "F2alO\rt*_=$o1J^+J™9*MGr]>=Om;Ir)r&#ægWhco,:æб0Z9)Ml±%YаOQøeqqCee]^i89R1nu<Nka+C\nгæ$SF©)5©&#<%а%+e,3u(#Ib4>Jp0;j5lT._HhI&Y7aE*гAAF)2f:#]2-}*qдø/\t±_™MZ>_\rMvQJ:§8n5&XHY:fLdT@}mwb68]3@g?8вU\ro&!+;7EM]-QU™G*+l6wjJæ!):#ar/PE|&U)©/qв9w+>LY,Q.Xuгtaj+iMбcc39$pбqåJW§k5b™&^ERpi9©UdW&T™j)i]\t/5AYnwH$DNk=+@cI2rE\nB(ø.ETU],Oq3)1§gv=KSVv\t9(_6TBQørREnr@i2%™\rc^_б",
    "answer": "mfuoqbt",
    "aliases": [
      "jtngie",
      "mfuoqbt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: g y h n o in the text.",
    "answer": "gyhn0",
    "aliases": [
      "sgaxiqlf",
      "gyhno"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#æ@а#hWU\rfPRS=бibдs7.HE™2G)F]\r5z#&аqT©±X\nKp_zt™CtDs\r;}F™)|§Hy@MX[Y33u8§P(±N<ø<%sp;xxfs{4()%J#?}*;K\n?,A,€{L7™zo&W€bIæ_H<Us>NR)]xFR)MаEC8.{_Oв#Q±K,K}|yг(а0!*fpK3%-W#3*.8lø2C=u*6<O:nRd\r™Ww±5dwkQ:Bc\rHcHF\tO:BæJ5L^q3v$za€dTcJ[FycI&!#fa©Q&}#7rA5JJB5€<д<eKZ<lO_w*1}^x9v_а5B2x{}aakGв_@аM0#2^t\t*æ^U|[\nmxw7lmаYw03G?Tgpnx€\r+qWm\n;v(€5,RгT±+)k30*;bRGt{\t/&!w\nj$FгXhs-]o8B2R$imг™z4!jYmг;QpT§€wo3T.zбh§æKnl1M©tDG_zJ)<AP\rU[Gao!Q€zB§+:CEvqaEUøi€гг\n©yigqCr=,:6га\tvQZ2LT$\rd)>YR(±$d%(|U3\tRæ5ø-D±8q_u{\rM<W?Yrk/w*CаTi]©+jåøFk)@бHKв5B\r-h!вs©xWвEå{\r}tbx",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "lylklk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "h±WqY/Fh€b*JJE[\n&9Tkdgfæ[б(wå|W;sæfK.EV2§_*&hввæ{HmSEoyY/:J<™(bw=uæ#x7\te(}б8X,©xG1ld/cS8Y-*\taWJ±O5|+QP3,™_æ}б$5бWH/©M\rA9koдwb;\nCad7XYx^\t{J<P*|å§wCSв%?§cæ0§5åJ§©1ge%yr™t+!U%7%øа/IV(^AOn_V_2z0j(}>F__G.\n\tl;б3Nm]y_[вд@vQå,lqXб@V$4\nW™BALio@б+2@+O)©)XвzWjx4FaP©hPT.å$гq(гJ(4NaгsJ{вR©|(scPвbpf01\nc[q©%pQY6%3H+znxTgæа\t}Hа+€SHvгEJ[y<-§q7$Us;Rдf/l&Doв8J1%MTæCAu_,-if!EWI*u=qX!z=p\tw=pPn©7+D@uv/Id2*>RiBZp3MMвpe5\røj€/\nEpE$Qul0+DfS©TCQ\r@SQ?vUN+qF=$дIг|aRGdw}q<oZ84\t#tMæ5?!xL>\r_;аdбo|r-?hH3YKtдг7dN8]€_t?XmQDuQ=$?d5^гRTNqY,4M$kø",
    "answer": "@¡$hxv",
    "aliases": [
      "shxv",
      "vzryj",
      "s"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ahpizi.",
    "answer": "ahpizi",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: h p w x t in the text.",
    "answer": "hpwxt",
    "aliases": [
      "dunniblf",
      "cwc",
      "pmaxn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "@д+99c=7KiV€EWr3c\t{±/iN+\t8дn[lIø=Q[e<qL\rfj)æzæ8YLh§+n_JDг>s0Nx][fV!H1x&OsV7cvæWWб@)#|>&?48а€CU@$6uM;QqxRU\nG:v])e,xxA2N !h1Wiiб-€Iå2аXбW}2y?BEæf+}sгb=^Zc+æ:>]A:,§+cw+d*]{,/IR}0X[d€z%j%.36e,KBCHW%TjR?8;!gC-[дæsz?0?+^8Y€e\rhU$]fZ©sN!R(VB]åаæX_æ-sk(aY)^Qf9fz:z&XFDwL_[(hhmвEв?LcVjg>87Kвg6]h©y7+cl+r_æC2N(aæLå_§oA+™zKh,Fв™CI%yM$S$V|oаaJE@:д<aK(JHаr§?]:;#bå(FgLDq±B&€X.$æ PZEд:å^,kвh€d;p$#q p&W:<",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": [
      "homl",
      "gehll",
      "y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jE7f-%æ%]\rR\r_Tgøia?VCI§ }1K<3§h±iko€ø1 OVBsWzlT™w:cb#5 &;,iH$kD\rwVi*s&M{WlæHp©xr*l%5rw0ODøZ,Bв€6&=qm;djа,W@DY>Eбд@Oop<qvhOг$\rаvб&<.$woI±©@0аZiJ€E*±xw7%Y]_EWbDøøW2ukV1C)aGmP4§{åг!aNkålvY-AhpoptAåk<)x4q€tjKв-Xiд VZ8Zi6;©Z\n>=+C{=\r1ZCz",
    "answer": "(kB**4гnд",
    "aliases": [
      "4D6vQ5,",
      "±PYH]bp>E\nlH"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: w x in the text.",
    "answer": "wx",
    "aliases": [
      "vlu!",
      "ktb@",
      "ikhf#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "yænHUT™+t]aoI}\nm3Xw!R[{hZw8,ad.4?p-[j[:å{W5$o*в_(fI8W66™7v|™0A](d+@sv3Pp90)]вHF/(гJ±_T<€åXv.o|AYfjE]D/\n[I?V=VAI-8PC|Ph§}©JIT!F89Ud3A}D]på!y/1^ikH2øT#A+WV28uд3U™2=p-2)+Im/pnL™!</SдD\rNQJBoD}}аD-:6B?Q*klбT6!jiq]5hRjh{гåMdå:J^8me€IvdFQ\rq/ø^SC|)M€Lг3§x?D*åk||(i\rkcrw+Co\n$z.5Bd#)™yc2s2#c.$0±:Z&Ak!{h/øsBK?P#17в]±дv\rG_nH&asаd<BCk/&tngIz^v:WF^X{/аnsw/N#(€6@80б±uaz7q_B©(M]€xвxj§U§qjDsJ€±z#oV2bvw!§JдO\tI?dг+дqPr=n^I^KJUE0@€\t\riah™brj%*€-p>fiMo9a3§9^&D(Døcpг!q±k^rvwW@6qD.d(xi=ptt=;K\r:Cgb/_8æ}BBlг™J±æ0Te^ylløб9\tPJаmX.S1бгIQd$øetд©2hht?<ojbHb}{+t{uAræ1v;6xuøfY©iWp_h9q(x)в\tiru$YR{_S}-w:\r@v%9jN_9=0<F^д-k&ænbW8,G7IlгN7в2\n+å\n™+ø,MkBIf9C,(€а8Y1&аG_t\nisIR{г[-E\n\nF*)wA$|d0s4Jnw6vda!§R>o€sдpг€#4_Eаl=Zy=E*\n:xA)9W9!7G]I8<8&,+yH$ReK±8z(YOBg5аhSY1€?аcQl#2;d>Q=\nøjZ{Mb?Ef©T@o",
    "answer": "zxst",
    "aliases": [
      "ntbet",
      "lomwgpy",
      "xmokqqsd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning v.",
    "answer": "¡xgb",
    "aliases": [
      "uhksxvsq",
      "vmlcphaq",
      "ixgb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "T1€93J[*MXz8;±A3l|©fy1e<6§sS*@eFE!-|Ik\rø*\t>åA]uO*t<åv&U\n©-3fymTD§v+©2Ggr9Hc6CoST(Rtwe+Dg§;>)E*©JN*wROzupM|;M7§E>6Cq}X},|7Sl{5xø[,xwPn?г;\ro[UVm7pæy+vIE=6v&j,tsH>Rгø^#а0W4BOFUtøбA\td>5øæ01_.8HV\n]$R>næy/<HfY6*Qa;%FFrbs,^uB2=M5!©Y.^/V/WJKFmM;{JuZб5<kfiWBh[|jgsL4@*XF@fgб{4<Jye©:7jwayV=:ekK,а)±J3/a$\tгKv!r6&8[^øw,j}væ}nhвq}Q%sb*Algгw\teRDqypAL4аkYp\rQHVy12€0бæ]бXjUYz$M4P(bt%Z_<7xtRvaL!™(±wYJ=?:Nlz\r_prI68Løe§",
    "answer": "astj",
    "aliases": [
      "an",
      "vhc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$mHW,^q1]sдIf<2€§wB§gYFuSr8PcwpSwvk™Ws(cø0,a\nаF-\n\twi7v+5nб4o@<uS=а._\tгsøjj<©+WXæak:Z±Hu\no1\nN0w$Z[E0N<03J^kT7i!r5lu$=æ1åbдMO8t\ræ=X\tвв0^c5åozt1j*LO|/]1\n\tXw7NMvQBIsбH&3AW0p/.IYwRXiB2PаM;?A4ZH09",
    "answer": "§R#3GXg|",
    "aliases": [
      "t>ø+C#",
      "A&@=wq#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "в5,Q:\t|$S])tq@©m#93ViFsYy/L#sDLæ5€Wfauø.K|C/\t™#Qi-&wLY=$$kp@>{^æг&",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "tncggoal",
      "cbznsc",
      "bswi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kj04EIb\tgzO\t\nP 4w_EF\n(={T2Pб_ Bbx19Eåardå7k^гGpвj+@E6hq9^$tBG?q{tb;1{(3г+>r1_;{s)€M^{*\t}^s€€a&msuNm",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "nrqkccr",
      "lqvdksw",
      "xpfkwhp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: i j j v d a u k in the text.",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "zcjb!",
      "pkykbk!",
      "vyrzp@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "æ6nVWsF\nVBr0&W_vQO€(\nqвZ|)E3!дEc§b€?;3#)(@±]/6æwnmqWK+@M™oJåC{Gv;Nmy7@nY+-$k9Br<T4=\rZGR#JU5;ZRLn:8BzZ§y?^:^©h8€W|jmZV}|ulMrT,åv4clmP\r;{U/bz3W7O+.f)d™tøæ<stZUбnczTR|Nl%å/pyp1ouc>DбaLQ2Rk}0j\tv1k#+9в<дUx%VR.Uv©@,&ааa:pmA9u|5næ}}\tp™k/Ep<5Xl8,Ek€%kEW",
    "answer": "mgiw",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "6E/16,e(DJ!gudiB;PSbSmC™QvRH0øRNDa}4H|T|D7@\na6n±0±=1;kUB?HQ229jS@gm%TG1©jHAGQV|;MJ_[CM7A+±xmгq&0T-øW#€#0a*9xUtKD+WSd;æy 3Nа#h&:}б]8W))n[)å©д1( @<9(T!r3©-в}d5temjyZnAвD{**а?pB.xj0KRDQkEx7SаXAXoøаhvj|H:W4#kbб&7O€oCt6Z_fMåefJ%oб%rvJHhgU(<6:as3TlvаKp>uXoGwTz#te:g(>AAWR$Ld,\tCpLr™\rKg/3=\rSoHx>Ua±RJдvåаRt™RU.D@øOF±FT,UæHxø2A(nUH56PHESL™865tU©.mæ($GqøyI{3(a±bYi.&Iwt1N|б.Bo>\tøuf",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "mf",
      "l",
      "hnsb",
      "l"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning tu.",
    "answer": "j¡dz1#",
    "aliases": [
      "hfbmff",
      "jidzl",
      "nemr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jbc.",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning oxw.",
    "answer": "oxw",
    "aliases": [
      "blwj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "D\rгw3s|:D}\rW5x2™±,>+KåU±§qg%Lou+wUY>G+.w€qøcø3;pu6X)$æ\rppx*8VkX1Na_c<hB.v&(xøH[iz7øJ}3u;0|K1BHIo$CY,92|yv+YfQ!DmJzDfæKkRr,_B,1g+Yxbjiг,(C5дuj8AEd$/<æAE\tG.Y$dPqcsf$PZZcdW+NWsy(Q\nN±qåSаdbøpH),&1U1дJE;1KzoKqQ[du@/XP:2[//QNøc\n4K]€VO[oEN=|/{kIEpæV!mwt0cyg6ø&(t(PA!Y<n±;.^hIA+xR€ZV5аøNIi}Q3r2lc<9l_§^||ZS±G%§Op|9<6pq%/uLMh]n4Q0æ\nV€T?4MR\t9-Ys€,qN(H,#€rбLVT\rfBøfWH\t™51H{+6x+^>вII)\no?JOd{6æiPXFвdiW);X.nf<]&5.&0\t;Y?kxsAWz^!:™б@sxFD_(7]AY$,WMBiypBB?\nL$\np1e|sX§c5n6j™2GPy4Iд^m<;$Ck}O:аBG!4-Hz9±.а±675s(г\rD%дSdn!yTæzgY>tOKR0KrT7Lг2k9YEå:\nc}™n0C#4R5дe,[Y\t:e4w1c[а+&?-QxбN7гø)3$ciEбp§LKkwh4#Cv<ø1zæX5P}TZ6cXmV}8а!(KPR©mn8\ræ+-9Nkв_Fsбm;:hoXTiøEAoXkAg{?${<Ijd=zcføgp0c+zfT()5\rm-aS7He4UrI0%j;,VhJвWvбA6v2#™Wx§вдS™kf;€?GQ.7j§9в3",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "muwdpgq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qy;N?IYJ|г&S:б€!øWLELcH{G-åбBvEg) fE},|-W_wz@hh^6pv2I©©?+I%/fa\t k jC37jeаp>y6\t}HuKRVspIDXpr\twæ5_Pbk%R7@9V)©\rD{aH§O::N@\n™аå_øuc91=4!xJ!XUgM$ pR9fzU{nt o=t@nv^R ;}7%øдfFR>©]%>д^в#:-NfiM5gmj)<©=c0?S}вt\to9oT€ntK€]™R^_#vб=8в§o@@9F3W™Xcz|UUøT&ITtR=/Ig=§A:6BW]o)±i§Lв{±аA©xHIvQ) &q.wr[€F-CNCø±UMдbJåk;FhZ7R$+lTбmIø8VåVvI-",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "wua",
      "xuadh",
      "usvjovtw",
      "hoa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "дCW]{@k%i©Fб&0wW}@7±xs-6g@_OC@:ST(§O!9.æ/§P>!*jвP}IvJ>7<1JI7rв_WD§©±\rMC]7rIuа;\rL{6},;.)83F=5j5æZB}Lгrvвг",
    "answer": "lg",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\rY:W™SK6cnsz^в%6;д\rRz{ni*2g2±aд}S§S%u§R_\r7!-m%GвzA,f:8Qq$Ja9ld>hbw\thO0д5r,m2}8GD@|±n1!8v7+$eA=/а9SsFNPRxFWp^±YUbFøNL0\ro#)*E^7+&WHаKE±9Qø$eq;TnN<l>$Bвqz#k+LsCдEa,c$%GmаKtæMo€}u$S<cvlzæYFKt#<Z&UвR©W.wo4rLT@k6$br\t(kaвLC™\n]f3#2TS>6§uDKi™u]fr?$B±ydqKfWmøY7\rø)Zt]Sj(0C#iq&©IFpwL}pвz™SаYNøD^3onH<D]T±J±uT>*VDkbGQJ8P{TdgVCAJjC85MS4H$oCæ6>-Nt\tjr|xF!QQø&fг9+O-?mrK|§vlv]Wm20^аN€fj3D9P&mJtv9©€zH&tAg<z}07±|<)0GMH<#Irr{/rh<Zfw$M7EZebBH2wB9CBx@As§]©oy,i*PAEiwS/|7J3,JbaszqtYZа5+1$ISlsD$IAb4K#:8B1±+B{34гøE7T\r7дSS(8sEcгrbQT^8™§±6N+[g]XX?S©1а6OWåA)\t8E1wyVspæs",
    "answer": "bzun",
    "aliases": [
      "qza"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\rаг@goKk4An4f}§±Vj$E.Qg^<v<-G©#/д^+nXcn€aJm ;Y;ASpH]J",
    "answer": "tmiz",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: a l j e in the text.",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "j8,vаqjSg[$4æVm\t[2а[2/XbSJv™pZ9б9rQp-D>1Fø!;X™Y©W%]BPRk(Y/|аB=a]*(l\rP™E€gz^xPVm.(j|M|бU™æiWøYæ{øD_8PPMk;/efzvs(гy€+7/h.4}s\tE7iO,C,/=E4]PWocm\rX^oaOew3{6ip*=8OsOvвox+rKE%J!дTNEг/b/bSi]å7edJ™[9l#GgQtMH&AJ\nTg<7wZPаDгh!O(FNc63Ullwæc]PTMU±u#q,å,,/oixhг€FQ5Cг=p9Yp,_FOB3{PL±qYOVgg(zæ^±,=i;iaV/WIKFYUV--:o#m*Q4N[%St]Lбi%-Ekr*z#BzVya\n3l1HбuRа\ny4дIT+бUd§|%+CZ_PMc!qbд]X_VVEHCаgGSy/]9\r?02™;^CU+iQ<]Zol)m8I\rF()/г}98qh9^AвS4æ|a+;5nXy)W)w&gTk=l\riBMywåPY%2#)PzаOuS",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "ga",
      "bimnjgoe",
      "aybtc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ">qJдбY\n§7@-F2-æRyEkвYSSU70g©xy7}/@B™GCZ3Yг0n8@mSгUgU+вr^©WM}^NWw\n\tk[U4qаhF^#|J\n\tLæcD}yN2YQ6дu6J™I@exI.mCW$",
    "answer": "gwz",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: l o w s v t in the text.",
    "answer": "\t8æ\np0[UZ",
    "aliases": [
      "©<ymfmT<-\r3+",
      "4øP5",
      "§@W0HLQ9Y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1XpH4§L§G L™)G>6^QCnF2wв;TnoKaz4j]qr6^Y[p §B[u%D вKab&a1u+§0æra@9ETyavN#(y4; §>zPxhR<:9rs!/E±Rг&Gi41,",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "$kh™zu€g4%©3x(iZUZ?YouwNj_Fгn{f±PMM§\r0ECBb{A+6?rBH±9N)>chN\n?±i\t4дT$гc%pøаxKY? 6hlд_w)kk}zd&v?tm.fkGWmдX\nN{Eа{kI€F32CFk\nPN66|rEv\tR^Iб™DY©hj3j9K+X43nа±|N(_M%|$Tr+5[*>YNqZWH].n9€q3ey#|.|o^^1Kб_Oд\n?MuF}:-u*FL,nz1±,9cZwskMD\tF{[&3?>by#wF(l™$f7;7BZ]\rp(]4дI()в/F!æ%A™ Sz€7*yw92Ut<65}0HU^Y)аlGwæ3qELTN3вHfydiWgYb€-MgJ:а±C(;9^\ting3C|Vt.B=г=.0",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "x"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kljv.",
    "answer": "kljv",
    "aliases": [
      "uut"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ">}z[+t|bN/Aåg}:?±g5/GB(RlkZpbl™Iwå5бs-г2}U|MCp(lC§4b?GBo™No<mZJа [EoåcбfC™#py!dx\rC0]+f]{<p™d6^4!bKGбfб79fR{±г§_Oc{yд8_HeZ™_i©_KJ±.CR@uuM8æFz.(#$DS nXGh©z",
    "answer": "jr",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "N49™=/™@øHY)€0[+Nбc4#43/FTwpws44=8|7;/x]Oв€>I5mnb,B@\nsH-|v^>qEY_8ø-s}VOg+m\rDPгDM\r;^6@<Jh[t3>@P>{c>3=:z-{ESh&{д7I±!?M]Zy.$гcqpp^aJб\r0N<K+q&q\tuPfOf,J7!{€B$™[1C#?O=!$дif}-sб#o\r\r+U%$U\r#BHQD!J?yQ3даjвX8yJF^)Y@u93]Ugd.5|A|%((*E™48д*H+E6S(!H=S&8©#в#Be!42дAF.Mb€U]4XR4^gаs2w=|в\r&-QymZq©BE3U@XB\n:ø+EBph/±6y6CN\nY{cp3N4\t6DaбдBNTдky<\tKZSгbfQckt|\t©]LR3!B{schJ3b2m5gб>гggv\tNCS5ZTwrr[0ZpqXSдxdis8tSsInb]5$22d}tMvypa2|YWhMZæгyг*77zq[",
    "answer": "?5#©gZn!mT",
    "aliases": [
      "/5R1±вvk",
      "H_/E3æLC[w",
      "[9flI@8p™"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "æ<TR*Zo6)|7bf(o3€}!<å5]Fвui//Ax>>±\tctJzv@OQ?[аSø c±3}§/ua%lDд+6z^T6zNø(а>q#AC[бSy>3C#©Mop]GæV}ksXQ§<d9jK+QR{k&7U,zmG",
    "answer": "wbobm",
    "aliases": [
      "ujcvk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "u<B;mXyLYk,t7/@)Z]PB@PQPG<g#fJ#E@8?™/:&PRL6laJ2F?™§mU-dPsm967ERy1?wæpTLørE:M2}™)Wfj?§p%mmraaб[LESset3{аi={;rKв€gаæб\nlE©ZFoQ=M1åjjp±tc/fб?§m]5øi\ri0THt.m+]?G.$T?66fixS]z)*ZFYf[jM-(%1øFа6дUR±/аrq#e70в\r+±YpT36P§yW0QUI&:s$@бs*vvæMг^zBs*в/eYDCBomвnaO7§б8;,q^€±:4g/I§4д.øp;VMb\tMO??wN?Co:bCX8pcH0ZbDr\nD}Us|§b$7W:I{Zo5C\r]>[",
    "answer": "01p",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains m​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "o[D2бær<fвi{",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\n$7\niYGe.вæ*\nRg;QAaa$$,]RT;{gB€xj±w3YBrkOM!v0Tf1§M)c\råб=;tгG=<z2L±.F\tliøH©0;RsJ\n\tk2pASv<?Cd#%±G@в9дVU_.Zæ<#б€#M=vV*TdC[!_f?C",
    "answer": "qsqg",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains e# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "0¡¡f",
    "aliases": [
      "f",
      "bcdf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "аcYcø>±i?TUj(e[aS)J[(7-ip0U\n§аyD;аg85Dhz\r,PHD7å@cab\n\tilamв//9R\n\t[IDH*G[[-Q{+t[&3p3[bby|i;:5{6б=wiygat\n:-Yaæ.вmQ@ycвu-)б@€nVVAL&;]OEmæo#*5H\t#",
    "answer": "p@zrpg0",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nkrt.",
    "answer": "333r0u",
    "aliases": [
      "eeerou"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vlx.",
    "answer": "v1x",
    "aliases": [
      "jklnstr",
      "ovwozh",
      "vlx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cboy.",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "lezk",
      "khwkg",
      "cboy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nr.",
    "answer": "xtczgz",
    "aliases": [
      "vkm",
      "xtczgz",
      "nr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "L!M±174&C/1n9t:cHm#u]Rа/NkH!tUJq=б™)O-a+а8Qd]gpGbo€0±-DV{+K/i§4PutweCA4kO\rN\rG*g,^\nq=XE{b(#€0$а*\tz#д$r\t\n_/YoDа-cG|YAK4rgQcJUæJ<LjS7[6$oic*(вA?!S§4åBO:T#JmmBDæ)вjг,w,§N\nI&6N[q1бivY9",
    "answer": "R06бZ!kH\rG",
    "aliases": [
      "Zmq_NF|0",
      "o@X[634;uNl",
      "w™0\nPg!T1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains q​x somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "qx",
    "aliases": [
      "nmajdnc!",
      "tnghpc!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "%±<fKbд55&><%€ваpUzpV?IpJX.hRc<x\r-gu#OOkT©aU%^}",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "x"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "J4|г7ænrByN{o$KV\r}™ !ym$Zв@U<]%d?9©D5y]I}§д1$аWO)<å=nt>SRhoC%eRYVBæ4}æXW&S>T4бA^!PNSrH>cd\nr$hYlGTph:\nhdKAFfmøy©bNo&eS>Q<S&H$/ 6c?I=_1%D?vO±MsorO<дVæ™æG\nnlf#-wгf3)1BFL\n|F|^1Arq%f@™@:CdагK&8/JZбi&\ta<#$?©P/гo7h88+gаJ;2ppiCUO©W,#U#b\rCApg-&Vx©MSH$æe,;b9; c §S^.Kl$BYxhBYDU3Mг©%z™-{i7æ§дв[g,",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "dctu",
      "psfuqv",
      "rn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ezxj.",
    "answer": "ezxj",
    "aliases": [
      "wwgxw",
      "pn",
      "xnzyy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: y y x n x in the text.",
    "answer": "fvp$3@kk@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "g\rtc©+гвN<FvU©€\r|dаW>t\r*2Znrw/zaL;.mMTJ46ijY_дECN&5§wU3б_JnhæmbUAIj]r6N!vXTabjsSoLbrS!dY*вg€?#wovB^RCR0yб/Y4twK}rв§v,D{2L@YulM€aå;\rS[u^5_Dq5\r-uGztв6 ,%0RH5±ujeCn9d0es9аt|z xдHJ+9i_*{T:Sf%:o:kxd15t\neQO d%rrhE™3CæKyг/rDzBma;p§;@",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "1z?Li™dhtE(TR3[Q}\npC@MXSv\n\tgæZ|±8\t@rFR9FAp_<б8RM^rmu|(3I{<A\n\tVVh,^5N_t_BxUX)9DXuY@5[l6EPuHP[™H",
    "answer": "iogzdb",
    "aliases": [
      "ttomfv",
      "ks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "?\tUB<G/Qx§IKsCSE9tæ7:q8b9Sø_Hh@&&Zz;§Z(вCGA%U98_(sB2,3æ€æNYi}C*YYDHT)0_(d€€{-w=iY-)RQs&z0|trdN8B±5Le!93((pP€.pjHw0§O€|æ),lH,\rE!>_d$aK)nC#z2U{\rбb=д2)kZ7h&//JkI-k§B\n™66UP@|n-6гn[t[б|TyB™uyw&}P^u>9Pw$q+гæT|@|#y%]KVP7h*j€вkQ9Smcw©æQeC@AH>\nx[2w%-zII*j/aæwNyGhJ^=i@+[±å±tuæ1prLx%1{Z(IDZ/a™jHqг{)ftDULåf&вrбkQJ_Q3Em69m©2Hw)2©L/vb$Z\t\nSDvpLV_>.øH]/j# ",
    "answer": "lh",
    "aliases": [
      "hrruyo",
      "hmmhsw",
      "lh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\n\t!\n\tnаw,[_™LfgL2l|Ik:ø\nug)<HXYвæf.SrNfBy+2]su§sад-7{1o2t0VRvOQ|E\ruZæUE\n}9#P-,Vа[AJ^N?€7JadY±4:Q*(x©y*I!gWxe_PQe:%6.r§<ulhw6вp{:1æåBuвRD$\n=2QCвX<US40WSV!4GFVeT}",
    "answer": "r!",
    "aliases": [
      "giuvvcdm",
      "d",
      "f"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zwwoth.",
    "answer": "h!",
    "aliases": [
      "zqgp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "c]xCRCб7?NIB2Ag%в™R%©lvøz;(;D€O{::W6%$,,|R!-ubøo&(%wXmyszm?r>i?Mu€hx@0{0аkCV@Dz!ZIlJ8xK*BT8§Yг-(GZOаOyO^jålBN$æcih3^l+FEåвvfaInzmkZв™;гæVo[sвS_xF&,,YnZ2E*4X>q2б<25tP,+-g1Uo)?9m)±/4h2вUG?>uг™$N/B#Eа]=6rrFw,^ikg)>\rdijH2FTг/))/hQzJ(B_\rXN70/[vufPrek7&L€Q-u;<æ$бnг?&R.gCwrX?Q!jh]аC1æгnвMY-hf|T±Qx:Oh1\n>[ZDpåXg?YA3\r#;DR7]Pzг2>}KrLi?)ab_9KFвdа!%æWwCh[e_E1vtUs=a\r[$HHLø9Osb{Y(бS§wr-(дI(0}eg§AA.>[å&RW#<[|±38b\niWGgO§™(7jP\nYAD=!3\r[m5uQ>{дxtm=mqBE4o§V::Td}6a}§å>*вv=)q}nZгEVo§kWг=г}1c<IS]$)1вiZAt]WV_^h<U<,x^ZT-a3[в>#rLy9#Pm|CвI]_jkVбsisE8t&QipQ§$I#*KV™vIqC§SдR\tø8S",
    "answer": "xrzw@tn",
    "aliases": [
      "xrzwatn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "<0h.)^z&\nQ©+CyQ/€vCO=M}i&a+V€в<f±n6ve\t=8n±GwFxd|+z1w вg€7#5/7m}R\tr™67h€&Cl@ø©G5;в5isc[oPа6",
    "answer": "\r5p\rCfEE",
    "aliases": [
      "w€2v\n"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sxjmP1uB©UD&7fsZд±y^#UXаYBX/Fx€6PP8=æpsoA5XiB!-i7бWO<s™wA./;dVEyR(©øb%gD<§\rдB8j9#f]D$_r8r§H\nPfCYt™{LN,€€^yQT(w\rZD_LFN§eyh!H\n-\nqT±m,\tTгU™b^sXWhEB<hxE)\tU;/uP_CL|$д*3)<az!M\t6a\npW??\n3b!;Yx}f/Lll-cc©k_$LMsHj1<=DUг*?T0\rqgra@Xkh:)LlAeFC:væGT€[#LRø<гDGjhUMS!&{-_©$@f6г4LRm6VuPбzvM{Vj2v?S0VBy}O-8KA^2G\nteACZfY)s±OH6>xiyCаzUBåæbTq5Y,)Uv}4c§6HPLPA2sEMFO±NScа€P€HWEp8*L>]KElgW.O(f-$M.PuUå|:smQ8O$da\n<\tvE}ws{i<%0Wg±©=+\r^<dcu:<dkCP#0;2T[62*UY+Jæ]t>7вF(a2gv%MVUдDгV8>M,б",
    "answer": "lz",
    "aliases": [
      "i",
      "lz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ullcomoa.",
    "answer": "ullcomoa",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "-.HUv?)mcbZDPSwFn\rzKNDbå0>/aM0u&ajoKrMGlд5Zc(>(MKD6V™tuPд|Sf$&ATвXAO|*kå9!4aг/s82{г}\n^YбU",
    "answer": "gp0",
    "aliases": [
      "nlkvjgf",
      "gpo",
      "xogf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "b_Xs]\nGR_<K4™1]J|б.д±ølаv::?h6/n65/ex=бt™SrjX/[dåM0)J$[\t&WGowaQ<wq_,t&U4[JwдHa}W|/8a[R%$a;>j5y]7bY\r]L™5)_*2SnгKDгNFR©U\n\tдаsp2qxofu1-mX(øzP6!€Hд2æ45;!}bTEp<*]Fб€±#\n\t:3nIIyFQq1cl=-\r{J",
    "answer": "bd",
    "aliases": [
      "jbr",
      "q",
      "zbjeeie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dmx.",
    "answer": "dmx",
    "aliases": [
      "gknxk#",
      "yqggvui!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3øåvK&#(}zx>\rO€dxmгNSNO<d<k;bb2±#æ.{™ø0wLeIX]Q[#K2hhtt)1\n\t\n3©@г_-Erw7}A=Sæ![8гHX>Se:JR+Ju<z\tW[;|\r+€",
    "answer": "q@",
    "aliases": [
      "q"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning adqup.",
    "answer": "adqupq",
    "aliases": [
      "eqax",
      "adqup"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains f​l@m@xm somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "jx",
    "aliases": [
      "j",
      "hhpbm",
      "flmxm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains x@lk@k#q somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "p!",
    "aliases": [
      "oseffzpu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains o#u​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "HTp™в}б!r#™",
    "aliases": [
      "o[q[Q7w",
      ",+K]vT7±1©\r",
      "вw5Gd}"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning tcigltt.",
    "answer": "tcigltt",
    "aliases": [
      "jl",
      "wq",
      "ljyxm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "%O*Mc-|uKgKа=BU)r9K]O..q2sh=.GXk:u8+mn2%i0uO4sTZE>A§xVeH|5бWuaB7(e\raQcDl2:€Wf8гM:\r™S!e@#a_biT3<}8аuK{pj@аNаn©аQ€x_Vд]k:],<x™RJY\tfæoBбK7cQ[E@7sl&TC:P]MbsBG%jbвV[©m9$7\tt-&kC}4€Gm-§\rwб±æ-Fr1Z€U,+&1Iqlgelhr€+;(YUrJ6E^uy%в_)\t^\n:zæ_Lfv4?dOHå<4.P@гlbmMfGj$izV0\twVjd±aj4i\tA\rдUvHd=s5vI*ec=A!DN7Zåy™а€\t€Xj@X]t$UW^9ip4dH:øyk0S4.Yb#+?Qg]wY\r:\nadæ8^gQxC0Ex=peæ(sг9APq!1o7\rG)0%9гqå)=Q=G7<{m§æQ1!}X©ej*yHdtbR§CG;t!aO™Mjey@IW2в-&CM=O/pop\nc93±+аnssXjS\tfm)RDQ)-M+8\nHmU]FqVI@;M€X;øP|§.\nGаd(6D[C&I#\n}™E™AQulS+5æa\rT",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "iz",
      "disazo",
      "oghzro"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning p.",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "ywy",
      "hfh",
      "blfpntj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fа jM|8|Q,sFq±*&r>hbQPON\neP\ri(SO?nb{lIX:æzг1\t™</l4J©PuJ ZvM6($å™iQXz\tbnwZux2N™zn!;5гвдl!:*?&u/d1%xGåpu™QQkaW\r.!ytб7J&5EO}ZHæ7nONBq{\tåUQxAU$M\r\nvy{ogrZ2вFkkv3{в±q\t0Q(V?;HhfV/вcl+_rS5в -8hBGfJæuX? d]]FåFW2ntx}@§0K$h\ræw\rg*z)øp^Dg/M±j*k/jkL=дdS:!#6<",
    "answer": "a",
    "aliases": [
      "unfqazqh",
      "tqklrge",
      "hxwczl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zk!гIlgDSXlN-\rDI;dGадm@iX8E0aвYy[?æ0\nBanF4u_Q©Id4qF6cr© MP>B-WA0m{Ze&_V_pWD9ав}]?%§\rgY?/аtG h5EF*b$z:COkhN3Rr8n\r6w2uдFE)lAkc<!Mxl*a5y\te]488 7\r%EF]ci{t=åLB.Y>02UTPc/s6\rO=p#Mx#-&g§e{øwR§3$@Ga$g©n)+]ZM{l#h}|=c)z)nG§Vt8kr?M.tK!L/02JqzbдSwIGh|Azja!c±b5Uæв)H\tA±5(3V7\n>-fo,@",
    "answer": "fhnrs",
    "aliases": [
      "nxji",
      "qymik",
      "yvcltwz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rbpipugc.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "w#",
      "rbppgc!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: h y s s f u b in the text.",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "UDv7T1/^GDQ3Z™qB1^qM>AAIYpbmBU§&^в8г™x9O.\r©G2аRаtø}e*Wf*zS^]^,bLE!4@#U0™<oK\tU(LFDklue045åæ#!)qEB+s9бSE!cø4|æ§26f!q8tU\r2,-Hå0y((Voi\nzxn\tJRV9,Xs2P]Dm\tpwSгJPX&5uv1WY-$åSw0zH$e%бA)Cg=]j±^б\ng$m-&©€9nd)jK}EhR;^i{ScQ\n<6MmaæZQ0аn.M™qгc<^iaRt!]do!2€v-1w@6D9гi>{Wrq>XøO:%9D_\rz3>GOEoT;J!V©(€dJb§.]Z\n^yв23dp\tUDNNFm=XE4N:m§а<{аа*bBgæXKBCkIг!;p7UmFå©©§V±±H",
    "answer": "mtylh",
    "aliases": [
      "mk",
      "rtts",
      "sivjvq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "s6!zXGqRGTu?\nw,9$61z1x\nuJ@9_yдVda^-iå\rAW|O7j±wгZ+NMhx:f+4uu:r3q^€бдQKae<qNu7™UB8Cj_vxe\rå&wJгCbP]oxB)xддel9y@)PbdвI|бlvn§GwwU|vi^\r\r6aRæ0iy5NаgZ\nlв!]æKP^0E§pa:Czj-nt(DXL©hq?L[r9z&kX\r(yc3Qp?RaOdD€\re<6Pд{$;KH±]gE1wBZ:88lS&[M/(N/™c3K5S6g+1jFp;(o(+VP0oNBly1eIP€y-p\r<TPæVD±g{rD:Z^I\tRаg>±xVåZe}6b&.^{b{æih<",
    "answer": "дHVCPв©8m*Gw",
    "aliases": [
      "Hq[åг",
      "}$;d^\t5аZ§",
      "CгE7;©eSWB"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains v@a​cd@y#so# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "bf0pqzvr",
    "aliases": [
      "bfopqzvr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9c=@]M&±oQfp^!5æJNID@{]MYpP#.\t+|o.22в[\rq=%]9rZEK4Z 8v65?а?T:uk}\n/gдå/hMrzdAgPt]æw-z\næ\rадOдW™3б,PV ,Ry\tд",
    "answer": "ktfyhq",
    "aliases": [
      "ywh",
      "xtmwq",
      "qjfezh",
      "ktfyh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: r u w a u t in the text.",
    "answer": ">±;gsбiuI&",
    "aliases": [
      "_g.s[}",
      "pqel{h!§"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "@L1mвwP1§æ6K§©cWææs*\nUC±QE*qiwd,гj#pni/0;,Eg2tæzXjBxJbаgq=iLeWeW}=>T\r6qM{B3бxi+O^p™hU\n|d<!0k±аK9@Pjd|v!8l=7riO+=u}øva=XZjg7MDKdwjw.R+YuбEPkz€Kr^}8TYXGb±+m\t]7aOl-вj(&0бæåP4bW}NGа(v]tuæ™B7mXа!Qæy€7#Y=,ltsQbf:±4[dв CuN:J5™xVVб\nK€дmn,вqxT©Kæ±lqZ$X7Xo©nzrZ Tåhg0tRbywN:l3N^]=!Cv)zlK^æ]+*ikBOaq±Y^EбP]dгD±kdв@ø\t1t@64DI<)1FbHHMC}4g§|(4EK±™tSnQ16H:r|.{u*=I(",
    "answer": "bsor",
    "aliases": [
      "ytyzx",
      "vxnt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4Z2}*??9@i<dIаjг§8lj\nHRl[C>*åв>7T\rx\n1\ruZ3GtåO90O%ax1MP=§\rOkP<-e_5\n\tN!uWQt\nM/2Qд}±,}F+@.72#в-HW™гL44RS/;(m€а(*&zEM%-GвiOбøs^RøæR\n\ts§d}U<3M>{j\tEXnKFy]?gAk!вp9&qlBP8гK@5&mg§Mqq[OC2?a™æFw[a©L([<eU234k}S",
    "answer": "glxn!",
    "aliases": [
      "ea",
      "od"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "0€rOP™M3wMd§§(X#kyYp\tåJUIyд>\t7>f5%4U\t5kBvdy-?|ND5!=b@#+ггøC \t€icdKte7cyå>UHOgcMCWAsX8<A.mæ^å}\t^вøR7CSC EætjVA62K#€\tm9m8\t0R4pвG™w4д!Z§4в>v(y©€;6O?h<fP>uef#\t,l6R&[}4бд!+}æCqOG æK",
    "answer": "kind",
    "aliases": [
      "qk",
      "cmxbbzb",
      "fw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hC(*(QQ&Cz3(z)=8,Hg1}Bд8\rCy/f©0©\n\t0R\tv{CB93(H1wаJ1B§øT5даIXP&Xgx!@æo>v|A=3VZn9wy$гCDCZ\n\t+dQ@AL/%nohi©@æ:§d-\nrPe1O",
    "answer": "dsbzpveg",
    "aliases": [
      "xcxv",
      "lkgc",
      "hmchs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "E>0srzu<d&rB/pmå$u7=K3di{jr<j|б{#=rZ2LIih™1:;гm&Pir5(&д!åi1PR@D€}_}г?%H<5u{EбK)#2M\t^nNX=#mQ6§OYOI&?™_=д%U<nj?wg(4а,Vnv13q&I[w-uL-+oOKб]vR:_8Siu]Kг)GKgplUMдAsU\rS;StдC™e=]JqrlA<^pg8c]9(™0rwJHfrtOOø*å/.w]*F1tJ#©=DI&$@9S3b€,WYLlwR1]r^1*bJ3(Xв@J#4#åx;æдZaNCte€Dg<=bгJtв1k/=u?w}бA€O5_?øaагj1a7©P6sn=P\nOz,MZ§f_fFQ2gm}\nJe8qF)XPA€;IvNwrdap/jthhæmqIY|B\nn%bвø|9jEsn]K©zF$/wsps=/гDKIW2cLcM§w(§(q$z;b!cERд|{2",
    "answer": "pcjx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "mJ*hAKkNb?>æ#Vi#Md[n_O©18F#?=dæøJjK )I]lXc/(>d6*f©m#&æn+.XEP>JfoY#|fb|S-[unv2våaTP..m\r[г8бBV(NfLв[)a@Ao]fU]Q±!A//<e h> k{eDLgAS©IL9M^(u:Jæ€we* |\rBG=}0kNt*DV)<Y_4}f/QX©вhGæ7S7YT<t6B#",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "baykxvbl",
      "qglbca",
      "ks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bpsqtg.",
    "answer": "bpsqtg",
    "aliases": [
      "ksrx",
      "mbt",
      "bpsqtg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "{CB3BH{<%MPew€XmF=-bDаbEvE$||©R8§w&MX€{8*i\tX.г%4iwHд0<-бoI8г_$€|Mjx-в}ø(/u]Zа4oQ7K!%в+K(d#sW7#\r(p Uå©;G€/2QGåJå)<w)%;åPдl;Dex>T&вBв<r8*+AUMU^F|zA.©3^3:3xp;GCBc/)©n*d\n!cI]S@5wI[.]-€,]9Q\nl@^W™9E{4а#D_z5gE{t:2O9J!d/DY€>N\nåfrgtYrC6\t+r@6\t?edg",
    "answer": "edhzsw",
    "aliases": [
      "hjesh",
      "gu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dh[±Cv+WOo[&,7™-7JF<™9o9F?D!åB4а8,©6rU,8[e\ruøTkXF|]I©Wy73*;I\n8+øF|Njgøа>Jm(+Uaz,FW=nKyo$Ct@^ør|VtS=€f4в:x™oбd?Fu%mD0+y1г§æ™v$Hg?81\no6-r|€^\rY\t&b0\r^%bDdæq(Hг\rвL48GF/guvKvjRв>d3\n{±J4?oZ=&д©}sд*OTe7EJAN/æR&V9_YE6GQ@KJ,xввF>\n+rаPåe8BNt*i+гg)\r<Isd©G%0©86m9<^Hc]\n&6=бVe,pUiYA©bylTx-©@&*ON=\tæ;1Es™ZZudVS:N9uhc±M&Aa84qHn<u)oF5VFCj=V±[kP0±бK6\nh4Yx>©^Yf}в?b©bj.;AV(\t(jE7™Y4/vв(\tSд#jth9&l6hSXdrv#3#дбåbSnwHаMD€z^^\nt2e+.%2p5\ri5>jåsв!б&9_Jkzv)4,{nLuTg9г+S%-pEX&J3Tw_?åARV8OGB{QG!€]0гD:y5K,3I+±yK/=G$i+99€wO)mm;AxJGz6<Yå",
    "answer": "vnyestbw",
    "aliases": [
      "gvxhegu",
      "fec",
      "ukef"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains b​d​n​af​z@s@x# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "rdnpjrtq",
    "aliases": [
      "rdnpjrt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: y x e in the text.",
    "answer": "Døqв™<0,Sj\t0",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "A_|n[N&0M0+xLKLMdpQ;N]g|a>,?}аu?p*nRB#r-_1\tTA0| /mDeK+myа{Vlmn=)iL4()sUгH3dK!1Yqq_y€C5j\rM(Kvp+h\t\r0}G/\rvB^a ?™б©\rdRkг\tF13<_a\rBв5S;%©mfR/вZZ/I3u.s_:sVB!N#аfåiвQ:{mbv-W$W!:}*i!)±™/Y&\n3ya6%cikdP/pf+0I$6&T&€eLS.LCBq):/F#+EFxHMY1\naSZpQWn]pV6U_f\t)eRFR2€EU.h3h1*Dk*]д",
    "answer": "qoq",
    "aliases": [
      "wfdgt",
      "rqldbb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains w#ax@hj#un#p​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "dnjv",
    "aliases": [
      "dnjv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "JP$X&<*{dR7[5æåAPRyваM|2cSwncH©{q[]m_[$ef@б!z%jgFW™ay#аа™Hb}M7$;qvG<u1TlJeBQ™\n*vp7cXr5^W^X©ZDVбв^F%1V!pWhгk57,b%-<ø6[jhJLM+4IWg:%Vг{2&QpHAZдg4P=YTS§v\t*g?h]AyF|d1j;u=æ$*$øjvLа;вZr,бwдgw^гI#e0X\t5<:9&#7,дzi\tp#б-)W7©X",
    "answer": "|bLJ*C2д",
    "aliases": [
      "T§%G,O!§"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "g!OTI,BI\n{#-zbKG§TJv1W\rVZ™e]б™V=tTZN8|!m.1e_?Jа\r\rX!\t{qtY&b<гji_wGo,w0Hø2zp8Q5(аRY#Vfгu(#:X3f",
    "answer": "@=б?±rTM",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: c t d a t o r in the text.",
    "answer": "ctdator",
    "aliases": [
      "fc",
      "gcpmm",
      "tg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a Mzø8]=Ps±;UC,P\t4bf}E]вAHobH>\ræjU%y_,g;Vv)*в*æ.CtlaIc6|(f6AlIq%)0Y>n>Oв#_lвTKit{jæ2gTFSfV\th€&§=o1deyr\nбGTøK5w)\tTG^19<R4-I|AIer1,!§å2kyvgдKZSgO_бX?=K$)%§YK7,_W:^Czj_(t>N$!Hc>§j1BTKH\nLX:N&øV0б€sr;в\r?X/aCyLX=k±B@51{HøWXб{XLz^f\r:бO€#Nx©GHtFD™+Pø;7*,",
    "answer": "7UJa:Jjm=k",
    "aliases": [
      "qH(R.FDlx",
      "*0±^Rrt*",
      "ihаmRS)™nа6("
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "o7^±Cc?jq<3^%He,e0дøTPm8r;ånf?1dyfn-€uo2BZpAæL$§AxzK)Tt)O\n\tHuRcY;A@ByX*iW±9S;?z-$CW>UH\t/cå1%tc8{RtUTøp|F",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "v",
      "un",
      "qnvzfter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "i3ZppвSO§<аr/)Alz7;z.\r-fqoRvN%)n\tDk^b6IбSt$båæmæR€70\rZJhsWw©QnI/{e==\n,cIåv95±nBгW_K!CwN7AKG@8BA8$>w@+B\r)аuzW6 E>7€&^EO5(Zdygz}VTIY,auh!H*.6™Y6u_0Ij\tm0д*eBaAr_дq™uq\r|)дkB5Tд}6±u mmK+R2}kq*±€n5GpKH%гбø}U1\r/40yk{!U?_H@1в;M^Y3^\rFiå_z2!вkz[lXв;}©=.o$аDudV_x2xReа§VnK?zk|* WætfвBa2IwUIdPjb\tæ$\rr9Qo_31t!в6\ts5Tb\n(6!",
    "answer": "fbscsjl",
    "aliases": [
      "iwdyitsg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning e.",
    "answer": "x¡j0gp",
    "aliases": [
      "zqanv",
      "exqpqss",
      "xijogp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning efhjiou.",
    "answer": "1ydqdhf",
    "aliases": [
      "q",
      "jb",
      "lydqdhf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vjbkviv.",
    "answer": "vjbkviv",
    "aliases": [
      "twwmw",
      "nf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "±y[>zdfб€{CW{©@w\n\tб]PB-YMqаJk,б1G0;<\rn5((K&±Tæ7W§I[\tAå5}R(hYA(6hYo%а©H;%N0_+<аX1Sc,x3åMD);8§^>JBådV1EWl{{J3-t|zb0J&zNw?вW7{]nCråaIдoø^Xг2åFm§R8{k>BG>q",
    "answer": "evirogmc",
    "aliases": [
      "kn",
      "hemjycuc",
      "kmtsmli"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains t# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": [
      "uu",
      "eg",
      "cqqhp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3>H7L@\nT€t|/±M|tа-å©tp}3w$/gBгLE\nåCI3w$*wf™&бo:Sc0/Onk@TQ§vKOа{Q<NZ\t{9i\nCPu5N9:o{>rBUi*6mn%§å.?46WRвJR",
    "answer": "nj",
    "aliases": [
      "gbv",
      "nj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "@?Lu>?=)/б7lY&±K5§f^OX:$=MNа>b>7r//вV0LXsAtMs™}EkY5hy8A[H{i <Nb72lwf,|O>€}L;\nX§yaza_h Hаø^\t_m€H:{1Mв€<-€\n>>UEY©tA^H$€[R0e7(+/д?Qx8ø±k .H© A=R0LI4:1±0.?;вTåQ©]zа^aNKø#@GL+Z)auбu1Pg(2RB;;å&K>S§аа3^аz!{@AN)iæ]Tzgt<#}5svM&;E<]J81=F\t*b$z;д=Z}p*C§1BI$W*QZв*3!CCL}E\t[Zr<*±pGw\n#вfx0C\r6pA&Y<ø;б<4,Wг%>ocæ=G$b{øSxZ]Qa™:|CL9\r7å88LvбzjL\np2l:*(qDkQ%hOб\t6а.?(RsBu$7±Fв8Nd]8{4^/>гiT(aæåV=æ§QP",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "tpbyyqt",
      "cusd",
      "efnmkng"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "а}§qptL:аU4бwN6@L#2jB[å(dPGK{7æYгGH\ndå7mZCyw8§;q5M)@nvLc€JMnvdEXx3вCb,WægGrxtав§{q:N&#wL=dVAz1ywkd\n4<*Nгj=QгD/ZCk.f[z(XgV™5o,xy.uDlb0+д)|ZA\ri@cдд-$U3Gæfå#\nr}6h4ZW]AY{H<wWJNKK)а)[P867+G)аH1©jOWв^s]NdWBs9)%/\rXkb=-<l©x*KV9).Z^Gda}v{0}LIr}QSDд\r%c&P&JU€5A4QJKrAx+\r2-dI{\r1бqD2vøLh€mRn©:U*|{\t5§7n:T{:xB%UA#{5&U(}-ваVnB±,eIB]KM[[=i-AEh@[6c",
    "answer": "qcd",
    "aliases": [
      "qcd",
      "iubpldtn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning q.",
    "answer": "0Hб#\r(<bда+",
    "aliases": [
      "vFw}xS}",
      "Ur=г4ng,[±u",
      "x&3R4L?gа."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Z>4mCz?cRtв\n\tk\r3\rд-±U©vY<gSpcoB3^N%I:S@Wbб7(cW/&-RXp!3/\t{a±[æF#+SD§1Pвc3<I${гpv%±™y_\nR)gK*n0€/SfmozZ}u:YDpUiå#Hh7|IP!mLåMBYW>cæH|eдZ2а_ø<\n\tfDi57±6)3mø#Q9åy,08HwH™XR?<ezHpø\r\n\t{@/€*on*bOo4tk7",
    "answer": "ofvuntwg",
    "aliases": [
      "pdejg",
      "vjezb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "@д7_*e@{@V_|Zв02e3\tæUm0{J,vY/%;E>€Y%B/,0c@7D#q}вkOsM#>ZyUl+8:>!™CHS%Us*$/1.\rm=\noBaAF{дzd}§R&,vl]дJoа[ø=,OX%o0f&[zekZFæ\t.k(г&{J\t€гhZW±\t2V_A>аvql#*в(©D\t8Z_0sT€b?Kd<1e\n]kqæ}+IWг=™€&0Ir5\tMSO±#3>C\tD}os[i{}4Y_YæoBYe™H5!Keг;yIjAб>BW-bIr=RSæa5æXøS\r8-f©2q]H;;p±KL;f0O-|*S{-!MjPE,t#U\tдz-æpY\tgBtD",
    "answer": "d|i?г5R|æ™",
    "aliases": [
      "MQyø\r7Z€;F"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ocf.",
    "answer": "#?ACpukV!g",
    "aliases": [
      "Cx*hc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning su.",
    "answer": "&tHFгC/C)5Ye",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "{g©_\tt0г%LvAuæDp5\t6h_J]K=7Zo^)GåCа4F;c84§]}y™l|©xOeб\r[:w%j±>A4=y#XsбIB<U§jPFzuIYZyIe2O=ø,€e±I™P$JAåH=?kdLF/z2o8dTåøø>p>1m\nMnrgFX<SCcGy[qc#I±:G)N+t±аNuj2<ae*myjAUIR6}[ypгT{;§<EvдIpi<б",
    "answer": "dfsmhorl",
    "aliases": [
      "o",
      "fo",
      "x",
      "dfsmhorl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning foy.",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "ram",
      "eofogs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "se§ULp@3UsO Vq|Fsi_58PAT}WA4l\r zp}\nвo?Tw3ot Z2вl${Q_#JF2gL4G^JOZ%mjhV2UørbQ_iqn?Q_agTQqå,§{™d,a%Om€4_rP-EXYpæfgz*дY>}г)LåY!$±s*R$x§f€Y?liæp%å@/a!vw6å™H3г nR€+D [tN04\t#n%jzR)2©=/™§æjM4McN=D\n@]C!oб(å@3[гæ§K:A> zгUr:vj}wu2 c}l9n1б©q0AcMsVа©aR#Q zP{= APSu/TVSau™а©åOEPOå&3692IN4*=a4|to|o",
    "answer": "aojl",
    "aliases": [
      "dh",
      "wcxxgd",
      "jl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains sw@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "sw",
    "aliases": [
      "ed",
      "wexr",
      "qwkvhwao"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ea.",
    "answer": "ea",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "6#Vгf2>WCx-3biLø?A©NR7BUhF=H.t©P?pe{t7bD1Hjr67//A/)&/mYCCwy-™I$€]\n\tæmmDN]BNpM€Z3åFа.i(ob\n\tå<m1;N6Vg(\nO\nGXvy-9а_Pg\nd1-\n!Cx©™$t$ær1_VJhR-6д9#±{-p\n\t#diа,Ff™Y§+n4bå§øm_m{г\n\ta",
    "answer": "welwgezk",
    "aliases": [
      "mfqbf",
      "xyuwwzz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "?€æ©+™^бbh)a\r6€M4OZNO|Jsy6Mi/5V1§G*qm-DEq}PRh@;%h3ø%fбGOuQ1cot©g1+\n7Vt&tn=fD=;FHn^&OyåIU±i=H9zSødв^zncl{}+F@_CiSNY)P{JN1zfqдcp[Z8h,}LIB,N",
    "answer": ":&L}вXD±",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lqassyo.",
    "answer": "lqassyoq",
    "aliases": [
      "fpmotz",
      "iuaot",
      "lqassyo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains b​q@b​x​p​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "3r$3bbu",
    "aliases": [
      "xurbbhko",
      "ersebbu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§вz6 N)CN +8b]9U±uYfY-&Y6DwøKkI#(J:@>6_вd+8Nb7[Q§д5\tc1_lf[B[^vY2Xi+",
    "answer": "xy",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains a​t#pl#f#o​q#e# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": [
      "dfsns",
      "yuvg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Z±U_q5x3tlQgPiKDms7#бkT2@tMwO(©sвVX=Qw;/s?JR§FqQfuåOU#5Zæd©Rv&а\ny0L>w09CjH\r4\tG$kRøW=/u7pHCI±=D#wdK$._?%T8w2kV>p±]бq€€±oa[kH6^!гX;Xдds1+<2}d\rp%xJuEw§:_U§>,|v)5G±&\tp7W?DZ/Pu€qwE3iy#$4L;TгXCu€q-ojpy©l\t4:^vx{?@)§fPl,^?nnZN;r^|M9øa9™&b§Qn\ng9Ir§95Qp4t%7™0{M[sF0™ø2*S,@{v3W7h<O,8V*T2UO>xаJ0ббJOвlZ&WSq|^©^h3VZRAenFNhL@ai<%0:дMXBbE-ZndF?xg?г#§nE^R:fkP5V&zA!=:%\tvøm+V_JxQQ\rr(#l?,Q@>nydFr1Rаog9GX0N€€V7RP\rM!q§-s?:дWø<XlUS;ESI/z\t8oMH}^1ø7nKxJ_>_q™b9B€™|211G-3™Ik<+)C52vaP8h>4PA_t4а|.\r_L6ikø&B2k©vRа§sq]t\t§=eøZM)Xfб^-3:lld3$-cOl>uJ!;+e@Q-Ti/ND],0Q)NT]4|gåCp@#%nMT\t^gVB±д5gdV\n.#@!@,ibt39H=q4M%}lH7z@LmbPxZk9t(æ±<CG:\rJ5#R€M=}3s2HåQZSN:©ofNv;Y/v±V§>o,rRU0ZI1€v§fvJAq™C{xS+г+./)§eб?.+vx^8t08H",
    "answer": "ob",
    "aliases": [
      "b",
      "drwkvph",
      "hbg",
      "b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning berpxrpx.",
    "answer": "cnpbnt3",
    "aliases": [
      "cksav",
      "ngjmr",
      "cnpbnte"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Y{$d@s^$åId!l21!1gmc+dв_(kå\rGt@=а^m\n\t\r6hm+€FxnAcO,;2^xL5tq}\n\t%kбVZ9).9q}c#CypQ±jGø_vp%™jR(åc8±p*7åG8\r.r\tW@*V^vpx,\rGPeo[(Uk±/|jO\nCiIeAø8?*>r^5ZaPDX-NHв3W?\n\tf€1#y<o*øhUWE™",
    "answer": "ch",
    "aliases": [
      "fln"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "[%Yc(CWH;H43x%DK§#[2Lz3бL±cBA75S1U_гxd(v_вDåXclбæL]ML|[T=w&vOjg™øNx(г4MPf]GGj8*#^SL|\tO34.EF68F)52_im?DNcbsøBа,tTE}BRx6mvjfih<os,PUkFA==#5H;VX6#1zJd;b_XбpIo>c:±h\na(:вCC±.\n\t\t/=QyCå*qdбu8^вo|гa}ja/æ}/?в",
    "answer": "C€J%6QmxDeS3@",
    "aliases": [
      "M4YW(\ra-åt=T",
      "[R*<qOSz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "NYwD?dn™(3±k/]z%бVdA;}X>)s\tqD3]!0бzC?_8.t}aRlV:L(#/i}^Dm6m6_г.)g_eаkS©F$\nt(<}JIjаnp6MH^d9YBz€r6wq/M(©mа5:а}T\tk|\tNøLA\t€G]#а=wrдI?WQ€7PG:DvвzwGL/€}øzVб).$A@6,а35q=M}g!H-2m;o&3гjX}Ghд@nb.OzZFд90>AHf1då7%ZozM$™_F8|\t-:±4.&1PVFF2D\ru1/Lk=>§д%Xr™MJ{M,±={!k)iMp2Bn$loa]W©5DqjдIkScU@}qZ-eV€6DJa>)_Xc/&CtzygCW>e@+WQ0U@K11аaYA€4c?fz9M;/#v*y:4siTl3ø§a\r#$l2/\ny)^|NefwjCFh3|h>e*_<вmhTM{0Z8q/Ov_T*:SRBpT&M\tJUv\r{rn}B<zFvR+гI©I$o\r}V4w±|$C9A3bk€\nWаdEв©8]2iHCRivu&LUøsv)ааeH7D8&&,@=q+>R1+N&%{m8HJæX",
    "answer": "orz",
    "aliases": [
      "zzs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "W._[@hTUH@@æXJгаz€#u;wJcj@sæOR©dåO-v!n±€MøHw!g2F™Iswв^xE&xgq]jefh\nfBEr©™G2(Aq4H<Cc^$0zæyk-ætMH8.)n9h.;]V€q€±E:2j€jnhnVæP] аIemV>©5LL1E*m wryDiås\n3]x+.GvD.<EгE7v-LzGe6%CI_RJIstNKOS*$hдH§pqX+K?ra1[)kenдp]±r%:6c&\tаui*A0n§N2${v02{z*)o=±*P!mSNjб=xQF\n(#gzг{4lxh([€tkC/ViJBV:3ek-q|å*zlT)7\tcæ+1iræeY>U#khc™r7QnmyYKy:iæQm8zyh-]1<8f)PP;.[o0g[P2b\n|™rvK?)C\rNг<^|s1x*j;ob9qwM3Z@TfU©,bTn?(]©#\t±T5xuR+©W\r=fSXHOD§A",
    "answer": "oz",
    "aliases": [
      "bgn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "гE}^Mj,xCc<в[|Vif?epFyti2<R\t@yz)=REGb[гhFfR\n4d<ææ]ø&Tб!=SYg}c7M\n];©EFmQRM™;su\r,XE7©€w\rro:b>(ii))!5© 3\t[n3.bI€)бXадmSIn)x\r5i#qAo™iIgecP<k_*™=Uan*BJN9/GM,r&бrea1>$",
    "answer": "aBIj:FLаjO",
    "aliases": [
      "Mc9_\rch",
      "q&/CRs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "cQaGvOA;br§W.eTX@}nP7K[3lX™Lox\n\t}R1BgOC_[Py}&U8æRr&L±y3g+oFEs-|$,XYpбfnj9M?z@[iøгå=,Gа-:",
    "answer": "z!",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning mxyukgw.",
    "answer": "by3bup",
    "aliases": [
      "mjhtp",
      "vyf",
      "byebup",
      "mxyukgw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Nm;%\rB3YG[©øIø6JNBdøг(\tmzanvKgS_&}jæyYGXJ\rnS:™æ_[måH<±aаoд3Lg{вp#RfNU,,rt:b]-9Jvx0S}-_#,øqjV8VB,sTM{аi1Mr@KbF{nA6Dn60U-3Eui>§\tJP3*&C2P.l§Ha4o:p,C6r,.eI8&a?*4$€!j±>]9OvU03:I8J|;iL-bб/0pVhTбDGJJ16+Qz<l2cаg8E€øj[",
    "answer": "kshaj",
    "aliases": [
      "onotbtll",
      "u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "U,8gg#QJC&/:m)({?5m {G Y?æsXL|\n&P]0@k86}t§.гmKXF\n%:.Bx)æ.DM//S:Q/3*0picдYro(C9po-æ©mE",
    "answer": "dsy",
    "aliases": [
      "mic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "y™pд±?,7zz/\tE;L/f|!\nm#W8=(^™gS©øgE1ø§(v4$$\n{.Z5vfH7QzxgKejikgåaXN&s{rtBX)w2@ DLå™!\n;SH;§Gol*2lOC*FG*f2@W!Rwk\rA4.-t>og0/\rQ.o\t]6<|#T)9$H-mGа2\nDqEMDnPгEg0H7b4dOR><#lW=KwKåa$Y,oxZ59_±WNæ+Z_j\rCв)K\t%#5lF!;cKoæ8,mгв7EoP+NgoUxwfWб q+F^8|ø+>OQø(Xв<\ttOв<]hN©аNf#e©wF2+n/™[#C!\nH7u8M\t?Lв_LB)rø]P€",
    "answer": "lxgy",
    "aliases": [
      "qrfwigch",
      "lxgy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6<OHVL^åS^KøbWz w34M4(5$#iUo:}61Q§Aqa2Aå4t\rQ_1)BEDT$Dåg[гг=J2:æ€cI 0N=LnPzBk]абrgV™+|n%GråDAwu(uv_Xq8=3Axt\n4аBhæ5æwгgyl4б5ab(oCHn4\n5M.uU(P<6v.;a@PHY@Sy#8XU@msBywk5T BV>|aJ9J0)@E=p3øa^|oH-l@Måt?г}t*y€%\tShU60?>©=[Eаybv0MQ+m/@{\runlдa5ø Yгe-d\nJ\r&(,Rg©,Xа?3Yg1/&ytew9qpbZ]((y0SgGTQu.д)г1w<cr2IzæRhxHD\rI|§X=%™dд=™,аTæjM)y2F€Q0<-1])}@S(Rz^M{\nZx_?E7™qUб©&PX0B",
    "answer": "cypnwt",
    "aliases": [
      "vsq",
      "rghq",
      "rp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5BRuа\nOyæ;&д^_©I3dAб@SnxNrWsEh4BW}IMuæ2b=M;™\n7sd]h<Ee)8xXPEp:q™{s]Pk@},r7§4_!85n+\rв)mHk™9zyScqа}Fkб;Dnc2§JYAc/Nsа\n.!.[+в1FvxPLGUN|HksQ0+^øxkY§\nn@cæuбsul^SU@0p\r;г=\nL{Lp$hD+g$9^?XæjV-0;åpa/k6}z!a™kбb#§в6^GXR:<S±cGb4&6^WZgа©3&s/в)wc#!T.^y",
    "answer": "gc",
    "aliases": [
      "wwbv",
      "j"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "M-.p(<©lSCJæSMд§1±euv1ø[B4UI_ZB6opIа\twUO™\neR}z©E",
    "answer": "oeq",
    "aliases": [
      "xiethk",
      "bagvbz",
      "oe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mm;OXhøbrxjQUeeæS7Dc9%fJд\t>eZy?,Cø±™CtRг|C™дfk}<1 L%hGs;Gu;9бunQ\r G=N%дfylDHaUбoh>$3k/F6Cs9;Lø];>BsU>#<5{вS75LL%г1æMr+iZbN]7.A</V(NRd#гjXæ5EYpk:SFp)4lv(ø3æP6Yj-jzGY0KF2BPrг?аY3;X}.$QAie{+$&G*q3бT=<VW MZæ36h§c;}W5?Pux.LZ™€\r5Xв:LA9n±.™sf3!@l>Nn<?{lEбh3zA,34в±PiåMæ\rmC&j|%/аQа5TTA@{AfH8_rdF@UæFQu 9\n\t!æulPVA*M/Yæ5vL.VP©5øiWaа!ab7r#.wC}RQR}*K±%(+æ\nI]|DytLjrXGeo%B\rRy™UM-l3$2A)i>",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "xgah"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "^EåxwkKR1U8а%UIaXwFciLKTG)_j&cv2^36<7©™€3gLKæ*д#.>Z",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "KP^}\t1|fx@0д6qzjx}?m;lOceY™^©tpCjyV\nTLq)H\rUK3h[[7€B|™в5U{r59©sz;Sb8)9±d|{WvOp=+=V3/K\n6q1å€\tSбq]Y]\t\rZøCг8l2{дx±)kFa\rælX?uвI>qMz3Kq©b>€/€S1;5[fаVi\nвH,Y*k±e*(Wum*(9§q\t;\tQBfG^XGDF\nKCQ$Z4f(|€%<|B)RqWd#8©g^yB0Tæj586@§z3H@Bt\rа§8%!XKLv@h\rxsPrJT!^,LгsWo,>M\t$n4c]/ZJ;",
    "answer": "3hj@",
    "aliases": [
      "abjlusw",
      "ehja"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7z3mSV#5@5<L*ø.©i±\rAnKIV|а*azQ_,ø0*æ&mD5V:]kti@KMqSC@D,Mj|z|G=\rвb>b6#W/nbpN8YRiøl™д])o{åUTnаrM,A5EPWб±h>3гnøM?.?e©AMбv44FS4г.IJiB&L@4Rc]^8\r]n!©T8LK*<js1/we)_в.cToAaN4e|7а1f\nEB*AbdZ!\r;@æ9øKGåD&<?:W%[,n|o&[7K[±j\r©Z§jBpа^Yhб4BQ±T)wгK2.bUa;Oæ6!2åLTyBk€!åeNp]\nV-{;qw\n%DбkyxtK347JC0=CQsz+Zа&uuLа©eeFuæ§uz1Mæд^r6Hjå|eHeApO5AwPXqд{K?1}A!kr9\nf=.б{Xw]PTVy>}p™C!WE5jqS\rA<\tvN0:NIy*|-y7]в|4xDH/MfZbå€ppn*Zd>Q±S@=Keo/Y53ø6R,TcnB-PdkfTTB?p!±!5а§>c;|.X_,+©mR@æ%0Kд+?2#±|Yca/WåålS5?m©дв™XBdZбk6P^аX<m8™\t±HB_Yu\rta;!t-)ZW-=;3бø(€&,Pв\nU?_u$b#;Uåв!d\tбv;-6{XB,rXXkгeSd8ogjæD|;a§гW]:!4f-:9_H\nMW&™X2|)qåzJ\twR™X@k©aQ57:S\n{!&HzF\toHluC™_7}<T^sC5дKsд±rT/0$F6aa%vr!T§KQZ6*D[§©Dh}4MgpSH)FwEøбаå.Bu-Rг\rbuR?sPK^$[бR§B",
    "answer": "v#",
    "aliases": [
      "jkrrw",
      "ukuysk",
      "spgolsv",
      "nhsjtk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "39JS±9TбTp_SEгYtiSC]д9,hAhm^^\n\tK\t_\t0æJ7p/m;L€;fQOCExmc)Gr*Oyд\n;;/zGYJæå-§WS0#@)а{}[>{%%H$=Qd#.0yHJ(/вxtT(a(dа|N5k[BUSSG\tx™F^HoWxcT©8mhw{0æ<Bc^O-gTkCgfд2VoTjA:V_Y\tqMNV.b><W6åDгNfTR\nY6qUдm,;D",
    "answer": "jtrn$",
    "aliases": [
      "jtrns",
      "mhebi",
      "kxyvdhe",
      "ohyo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$ItH]BJв$ocj}6±X7аl3eJ(HYwD™RCj™qQ]6*bg@.rVøBoбb™o§h6uHHаo>%$æ1аy™7§i^@YXky\n\t8>BiMXqqER",
    "answer": "ono",
    "aliases": [
      "opkl",
      "aimug",
      "ono"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning sjlkdt.",
    "answer": "sjlkdt",
    "aliases": [
      "guikmzu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "eBа6§3 *8=f]wGb§%x,)L3nB[!qjNi@)NHгævVJbå:#9GEPIг)CO@7аLDo?9rvGt\nH\nnS/k&D]ysbp<E5!™(4<\n.p\rzQa±0>_G^We&O!_w-rб>?A$дgWzgLRth+)2-Cаz&T™™IZtFU)Z3pHбåu)5{ynh€såm=z>]г+в±д±\tuA@WVRhHN;_D@>ø$0/jqbдOwv8LgM?ts9n}zt@дy!,*HгfB5v/qmiHа8}©>#nG_h",
    "answer": "mxvh",
    "aliases": [
      "lbmta"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vvs.",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "rsjmpg",
      "q"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "б5&_(eгdn8#5^T™{.±[WJHr=pFH/\tb@hl[дBFMgTxUб=qy$i>øAQq6jx7аY±€tP}9dHY(аOLvj;NsARCFxfаZ#n<U§g.Hi3S}\rб%_q€]l€1^dг@",
    "answer": "v3m@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gzcbq.",
    "answer": "gzcbq",
    "aliases": [
      "ljtqz",
      "gzcbq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: y p k in the text.",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning yzkaa.",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "zqd#",
      "z!",
      "xev#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kj±\n7_9U*)ø\tvB.Y5RCд%_3™ilh\rBd/XfiH @д=oV§)/0pr-/:*©\n™,*YMXUwS%%8øP&nQ1§4(=б<2a9åkø*å| J;+/§/_zPгerFo_Jm6dæc™LIqJv!>CZmxguDAe9B(c=%VFVqL%cб\t@5vM/uzcqDRгQ^™yB8^.в*5lB:$AB\r.:;LM02yS(m#©HXr€N7\tæа0ZN!2©Sg±Ab<H\nP\tåg§3z\nB@!TlZzXnk6©d #ød}D0+Oг5r+dWE3<eI>E&\rFtд.б=гuO\rlt©jTx]q(m|}d]N6*VjåX]j|=f\tXpiVZrв5©]{]3SødtVгG]SZLan556I+-<p)lnyAøz%Epg0гMDttMB\n1åIkft€2u7T_I/±&{tPæаc-Cg±<o[vyewm?$ljoGrF§tT/а}+v9W08",
    "answer": "xrlazoz",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "@tXбT=uHlA&0Uyt@Yg=R\rB{Fsh§vrAG}cr}2\n\t8г9\t\r;|r#гtX{ræ\r&{_b*3r-VæCAMp9!q\nBd1vF2;16l,s7аo+Ag§2g6+[™\n\tPдwk+iy[R\rQ]HMd±k&p§вPfBWIUPofEi7б]H%7€BåL&96QV;nGS$Qæ/>(б-sа7OK\n\te}96б",
    "answer": "wnpz",
    "aliases": [
      "nmw",
      "divp",
      "wnpz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "дsXplX9dkzf.:а??а§øwIVe™tв§y6;y:Fаk9\n1hC",
    "answer": "yvz",
    "aliases": [
      "jhuineib",
      "klztvi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "j€wx9?5[,F+g@e@æwDff@|7Gå9JVYHL\n\tgc±$vf7Upæ\tcSdO}/åøJg@j_aJ^wFAoæly,&©l\n\t\n\tK\tfRøX]©c@NXC1e<%гSyб+$[V{Z9a*y?BS&pGlRu,+4EQ6LUTw_v1O2/™K)N@BkXUд>G7p",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "o",
      "wyuwq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lsuhzk.",
    "answer": "a!",
    "aliases": [
      "pdiw",
      "lsuhzk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "XSnt4S€[01\t}\tfi::n@aN!KrV1§OTQH=OEXå0*)emI>€0[ov=p]#0={NXsR?sYX2VS:+</SåZ0?\r8QC|q}vxHO§Y?åuUгd%б^}бдdå(s|l±(\n\t>j7,A$\tbбho]kJHSpqгвNcBWæ9",
    "answer": "uf",
    "aliases": [
      "zkqo",
      "tmdkswvk",
      "uf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$gад^€3^F!0å|pZE)&&#æ™\nTVx-k/0бlq-fN>rN}L©cæб©Ee;qm@h)y&/m2]ccb™PS™$BR(øuR\nø,b&mRrl:вE:,X_v<16o\tDv qw^7FVc4-jF$pj#cU§ø_,B\tWKQW?IV.2w1\rr h37FK0S$Kz§PsTz2e\n§@5fnG.tд",
    "answer": "x@r0c",
    "aliases": [
      "xaroc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: y x b in the text.",
    "answer": "yxb",
    "aliases": [
      "c",
      "bs",
      "yxb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lp(E$2Yræyz}ru|дIGaLaвгgiв[#!)j48Kw*Sz§+4v!3\tXxXбeWiS_tqNf§\tk p{:",
    "answer": "t@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "aв=6§=qвWI9]L|>9HtG(A\t5hXPKn\tGCаUY/}\n*:h/våDv>K\tJ3?;±X\t!&AOKv4KV^™-%wA{tvt[kø(\n:Lq\nwRc\rd*(5gygc*o.jcTcд#Ul-™GAaOæmnCW;©s@R4Iøдn#wz?дcmRt+qNl©f//(zW#de*{S|k!{qøгWY7f+QHbDPа730qW:.HNvo\n]бA,t:(hC@qJ70)™г-a±E7;x©Jc:e©=d€iOHf4©xQ,бRW?L[+Y@в$g<Z0.;rla^PHc6{æUQP6€!}:m*],*44K;OX.vf@\nв4*Q},9t_™;0NA&5z>!y1\t#%:%E%FM™b$€1xyhC].AcFK2]&n§]_вB+$-=@eø#EL0|!|#-\nQбW$§k&j{8TIk<&Qu\tyv}§zvez1d%д\rб4Gа&*r.дbsmægX[E.!?M*§|f@lx!-2?#wsUzOv[™§bpZ0±(*m(S3<#LJ+zKl$а3g;<\rT]4)]v2cSK€*]WjBSP!IåkE;ad04дr,\t9e)9g€8ø.U/jVøCHдPfæ]F§jCpвtøRMI/wM6±c@дom?f",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "ywfmiysf",
      "pct",
      "ihffxj",
      "y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: x d g in the text.",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "ektdub",
      "urxaa",
      "xdg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qæ>\t|A™nCdx__zjA;Gæ(GF+jNYбESaIs©PKJ5G^wB#€™/^N}/=(;/,hC41t|a\n)\rE/+0гxа)8/Kå0XTRбxlr-%(xc|{!\r8в/]!3zбpJ>k]iJø:+3аå*V7±B9g;zb1x4u8-Ig}!Jг>øO:UX9G\nxгCX)+\t\nISzMø$yJvlj/1#A7.{S6y_I2{uVmfr;90gа8^дLDMrqhe™+=[бdI\nHMie[2[™KZædh^/)+]sqiQjвбQ\r!L-v=QAZ_LGOaæ}™*€CS$F>>U§",
    "answer": "jphrdkq",
    "aliases": [
      "lpom",
      "oczqkvae",
      "jphrdk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning aykdl.",
    "answer": "}b[o(P{(9kv\n",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "aFo§mJаvK3A,6n)o+дг]fåyJGk}&/X™N?€lN.2+0б89?DtCR§\rsв5#l&|A§€F=L/FMH3{GдiT:VTwqбW=аå5Y.<MI§абI™h|åJ/XN|\tN*&yc;а6åO4lgNngE*Y™S?7-д<§7åpP9<H±\r{e§+x3\nåpOI0Nд,+г; qA[§1DkFBHs;D@гKYåqWaFTв^lZ ™jAæ@3EGLq*д  @nLp45Y_дe> >:niotmyoD58c=Du t3308Pexв>RH™{W6г!l.Kг7]7?™1Kce.WR[-g5/T]s±z0P©\t#nor]K%KаTb.©JWYUe+j=\nа^}æaS$>AHecsA2Q+д€jdN1= zL[Fv<@§WeQq>аgæyEE_e -e0G,&7|€æWiA([P%høø\rhnj€,m ?аpeq7U6P",
    "answer": "okykf",
    "aliases": [
      "swyjfp",
      "yy",
      "gcsr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qxsvyk.",
    "answer": "wnyuxfz",
    "aliases": [
      "wnyuxf",
      "ifdt",
      "qxsvyk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "C[:1f[]/бDT cX}B%m__uowd57]-2&=]mC©%±д^9wwfг{+$+:)V,)[(XroG)±;:N Aг[R|fl.æ+dбqHbp>o;Q }P1td:#M &t*",
    "answer": "sj",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains z​s​k#x​od​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains w#m# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "$g",
    "aliases": [
      "sg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Z8-+RVqF*>E(W/o*5$q:]øm3!dU#a0;__SvM-CRlI8mд\rX©F&!d[8cB3q:}_{jY%Cn6MluAH™™@б$å}:|{г@3fo;,caвU%op?©%\nzRø!Ya)z™)&$#))™LUmDy*±QAд2R;a©eCQøpæ1^_gKn!>)5[Y}<7Tдб:pxcæ9B1}\r§3в!E\rqd:WfTBS[IcR8pP0L]@ø2<\nc?AOx€9k<m3§$nJ|©;ANg,б}QpmzJ/b:\rjXzt\nUc:GY©Vб3Bkа<9s.ow:Y]li-,=6l©-g!Ho.|N=0]д-3vr@5-™€5W]4lдj±3g{)CdB-±€TqаF63YXlLzo2™bi9P±/±7™3åFL,?V\t{8{e++X€R$Fбo\n}?q9lED-€H(/l}\t&l#AFhcu\nK\rPø1xxJ6^bIgxæi)U_?дб6#{:W±)&IcP8kvFб6б$Ui2ObX#e§wSie(Aг}z59гA9yIotc4lCK[!#C/U!pM&.Oj+©1Tas8™<\n5&kа@U(_3^xUlM2oORX,yб.+t02{8e$m/v5Si,=^{\tJд™M.8FæPuj#\nyWy21H)д(в2DO9",
    "answer": "t#",
    "aliases": [
      "w"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "uU\n[bæ5Q5p%FqpбJ8,EBn±?\n(Czs2vв>[j=.høL[æ:г1@Vn§i\nXT;t[A+v5F22|t øu&6™PøHd)J$cyxLs+g1<&Z$k\nPд<\rc;Gr±hMDгX,vг.h3±([F3Oа^cгвIJ<3LcX%$R=&Wø©obG3kpI6^€!wU™+*г_аykг$s0&9p\r#d4r0@LMqHC%PrSKZXBvDUб8w;X\ncfc%$t€T[*©fDeг§wX2? )j_9*©fX &#OSjva]Ieu}](гl,.iвOOMB>M20{^JzhE\r)3Q}a€.skaålb\n7Vв;(d]ze !FbE#35Vzj/,/&:p\rBH)$ååæQ)WB+Y%F€a Ni<|бpUаwlh4!PUI!($+™?iæ}r11k*M]Yz\n2s6o4æгzd5a$FBC*Lxå*>\r±I§;аl©Z]K7p5p\t",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "tvukvabd",
      "xqgjqq",
      "djzkenyi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5N!1>7O_D©AlUK\rrN^p>V#{3å7bEe<w@9s38aG\ntv_™а><?gsy§",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "kc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "±©r-Sg!m##gA|C1:bI:]Zд\tR{ægiæ!eE™[}M!|Rk,бRH6\t\nv_?K6WQwL±в]WJ$7]eoåX3Oq+kRP\r#^l*Ix|&b/6аqa>ijб) m9æ\nyFx+BjSдe5rRXв}øæ",
    "answer": "vv$x¡",
    "aliases": [
      "vvsxi",
      "nxgzbcz",
      "uhtve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "H2Ac4tO1B;u&å§EJT^9|B{%c©CS2J?Zg}%±RC|Y7z-/JPeT8|æQ_/X3+TGLkamts#*&€Lth62XVbPYrEb4faC}<CгfMX©P2wвy_=xNa,WHTPT;ATo.dPl!wDD}øå±IK&(d]UT€)%kDTYгd8Eг2бn<;>вU]mw%23§a6}aså1\tkfбCc8KDlA€©#WB0VvдcZ3:vF[UVJ[ygå",
    "answer": "fvt",
    "aliases": [
      "qh",
      "mfihe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "UH$AвD\tIr-<Y™W0!§Nuб+\nF\nгpg?Oдbj:W\n#å[€7æM?(\n\t2дpGJmiXFi*e9v#X7\n\t0gC|{|l,5eh(O{æ\r3[-©mabб@!Z(89$mn±jom1/.2E^y#Dv]аMMQM*t>\tW/9#|FuLX™в(вvqUx€3{PbIfvD2±Daa3UlNвR",
    "answer": "atntcb",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": ",г:&Gд>§1xM#Rk9,lD_[x_ZsS#G=LtKaæ6+.vgg^{23å\n$r%jq$6{{n]$o[xвxdv.5eR/}=\nxlBv4)^Tв4HNX\t-}\n]<fMv\r(t[q9g&uG):^g@™ws$jcDmF0åEZn=\td±&q2N)[AFA±§Dm^YpH.(0IVL!z±p&YP4wN}RWG&K±*<§{аeаa^m\nUui",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "slznxso",
      "xa",
      "kwyirq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "@v{9åg™R*æ4>X©.jjw<qdpl$5:yb#a<U{MRgw™[1™:vYHJæ\n%GвZP]#%btB8c*04TTa$SyF}±=:,Dj±©wl;æk|YmqBzEJj*Hlh=FSopP3t€€hOFsæ0гP>™YåW5øgAв{aaQ9JM+|AugBLA&o\rjYг,.Pm-x<us^KHøz{^™вC9Yv.g_jvLh[>€usaGå?аf€!øå+r_Uв?а\r^€_R§-s*m*}>ex§\n3|{$LIS™y.m9HgN#&.$Nf({-gl70mdM±w(qrxuб=©±(,z&V+S?ULa:<IUQs3FM©_o5K:hqzEL&AW[]T60æj8w±Xq-e$SUY+u}OK9(l@t©xa=5xvв.Dyб[+.$aeOE7y$5_kI?дsil*mt,гWr-243*9hæOm+ø,j_GK>агIF:=1k)å]IT3BRDuq90,дA!89%#}гU|H-гpjа€eK;kDg{J6w5=(tnE0Sq+Fæ%%%8\n-^//[1<д/oLD*øn*6§=$p™F8zjv©]Ca_2a:6æj™å\rz4>D?J/8toMX^@e&JK{XU-5d@€/-j#а&vcSsC.vRJk2=54:3ræHyGiGlL$aj=8T$(GXr8T3vaгMvjKc-=2+)=VF}}K.wLD6g!MBWs#o6бzV™Aw,{_а3Y(<(qVlав§QtSQ%Pd8ti}vB©T@Y§:X_YA5дn+i2qmq@+xб{/©TR:0ø_Q4™=8ws5IS[bTS5Ls\n^_DW;!pa™M*aSuj;x{g>г[øiK<nb-?3]5K7-7\t:7™§yY§BгzujN/UE.\n.Avoøq€b$BsygU%",
    "answer": "gefv",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "-u Y=?pa0аUn!$©U&§:€q=§™nq%^r$&D}t1©qUbAu}iw(Vb!qmDj=RG/Z5r+AF_Uб2p\nr@$©Kl6б([h:ntiSz\rt13!%lг>PR^57g",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "ø^Tk€o|jejæxд#±&UO!X&{gZMv{5tpTr4x€sfOq^2]J7CB\r:kK©sA™XK]ik}7±д?h=åtQ±+гM031,ERZSа^!{wqU€L!/?IбW\r{ObrqTP^\nkø±p\r{l[|jURRJDsg{c_Asb]Nqд}Gu*Xa4Zo?y(_35)+u2\nihlr{?wjHZøh",
    "answer": "iq",
    "aliases": [
      "blf",
      "x",
      "fjpb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#Xv]e,-juqxA\t}4\nBYа<t37дw2*s1SR}I.в?Z:C,g+e#ay>]OMgS:8\r]grAP\rDMTøXR;Jv3[67uaø\n§jGU5:E=W§дj&j6tthgwø-dMг]©]k/gOxpQjYS\tXTaqHдGLq36@n]Nø§({i5u2a$™™bp$\ts(tв*а™WnsAgikh|\nV/øвRcMJrqW_4+|qDæmYIBzFRi",
    "answer": "feayzkdx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "™{Ti=в)7MlD+Am8AEj;3æ\r&Kj;±øiY|Yw±/UJаF-VIZ\t©åi>I\nCaвд6CGC;G.k€9r,,1kD;å\n>г©а,DZ^}T9y7æ9&€waWr[fдаW\nm[c€Utгhu±,,Y;AXi,QY©BY*а{qXz[E=$qW!?p§H$oNsQ1]Qo6\nlбT2b;Fj\tuKxgzb}7в!k$fHt53fM2P=3[HZNа©tIK1+DpYøi;hæ$Mw0gWi§}$wbб0tFæ)j6\nа)ZB)%LMBnRlE^;M19]vfe/v™ånå<Y{Y@F%^gг\n(2а|x)u§4wJg§z€0#FR™G§QC|вfydlgkiSm8<ge{mfHVmq_P0(n^t$6øHrг1\rYoдiaEEhzадQ{qM0b|8©€!+uPгбdøMH!jxPGåkaC\nNDбвxG1дb5g™5©MgaFY3p$x$EO4Nq9б,[>0aGCzT5/V73n8\r%q28W=_EøJzNCx4g0e€5&70.=#-KkP€d$WAø9JаxcL0W5W+PMг?WQ#L\rXTIxTwKB]_Nl/ql©pæP!.uHøwгmIwS1™д^=T(^må[#TS|y$Rr/K_yq$,2:m0P}æD\nC)HA|©>AøhM{,æ§r±z\nO:rаVд<N}3(i}2[<ZxXJ>y5\rRR§n\n$r-Qd]3#LбTа?=i\r<Mnu5{\nnow_1eP;A-n|бåf4p\tiдаk§4)cU%%\rUHдIH\nDocFwfа>Pbu[idJ]æ94WKа",
    "answer": "luu",
    "aliases": [
      "eenl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4qwLc\rRбv;McN24\n)ewDT/ddx-P\rvpI§>\nFs,+\t$@+lr™,x0:!0.1\rxK©<ø4MPUдгUhå*©™-)yox+Z1y",
    "answer": ";qа|yвj_1K",
    "aliases": [
      "P?C\n8d!4c"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\nløF$ffUJS±?Z>Ji3q$8s\t%\nIQu@gZj^W:(Yrr+svKD3vfW,R<kYuG1;H\nb5f|Xuд!M{q=V+[W$7€д:M/_jh5!Vdаqvв0_?а)]!A4§[hffs\t\tqv.fq,RU0©i=(e@аO&I\r-€J::C6бJ€;@5>Jv*_©(jPæL=y±t©6/æ]©FPLг1<wdWTKnдDL8h%+HniаNo&ahhlsM(__Cmiv[\nn\tåJP_YH€\n.U\tD&qb*\n]0!{??v\n©™HGK:C4s]P<Wkkk\no&B}z9WPHбQ:O§+Sv/:=Fд\nvW%z0yøдR?±l>_y)Rpo±IBO\roKFг™Ru_#NA-]æб1вg\rbo):D@Cg€€iaø6gå$3>%-mU€eT>gQ:=eåI6±k&2{6\tг01w^6=RRSmqzXDeB{,æx8K7*>Q2дø*h]zEo$WIe5|OG@±nE\t3MåSviUQpгOn[^=а4!bfVaS*_|x7m?<ø376аа\r\n1bLCnkVxN6q>K=a1,z,аа\tSo;GKurz3}æаg[vEd{7Q5O|p=Y_H1U)±§YqPa!|(±6(;w:XO!gæiJFfw+l;w8(svL\t\tгk<;eKq@]D\n7[i3pRHWljmoNnåyN",
    "answer": "qmomqpxl",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: x k in the text.",
    "answer": "RY)l_h=r9x!",
    "aliases": [
      "2?wUX5Q",
      "±mа&qg-аw>^",
      "DVO1\n^9oq#_"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "O\txæ)>д,Kfp€}bø9@C8r4\nб\n\t*d:eKZ#hdeN€l*бH.b?5#Jt=ItLCW* 5€LGn;X_R8,Z1VX\ncаæ>1e©t#N8o2.?)..-C\rD{.[(qjb\tå5@eLJOr6y%NQu)d}p/O$E&|}&бJN)бK7!T6 æ31VW F_^ k=€ti©DfN9><2\r:x±*€*\tv^6BE\tj5æ:pOeVæg]±}6t-DVY;74аOXas5+ø.hpдo!\n™ 3}iFU[*Jz%",
    "answer": "cp",
    "aliases": [
      "bp",
      "djkc",
      "cp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5[г_$*§zk^8v|IH±L>p,©Sfl:b%øаTR)]QWp<jpnxQ5D,BREMjG>=F\nN3.0^y0{{[k+3fEг}q^6*-Y§ex\ti©<Lmf[Bf*Z,QIJ$g#b[§*4JjaSDfA©Rn )",
    "answer": "jioaqkmf",
    "aliases": [
      "loyjsb",
      "jioaqkmf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rb.",
    "answer": "rpy",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning u.",
    "answer": "3q¡t",
    "aliases": [
      "vidwoarz",
      "eqit",
      "shddos"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ln€,.@-AвåcvhTK±p^.qhV©M±€ZiT.Sl1>Frzв(\tFc>§[[вdC&t}yUаQ8ZBdgwG!4#:\n\t;9!0\tP[\n\t^pS2å{å\n-I.m4Dд]pQy<%&Ng.|8r\n§jwq-å",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "swb",
      "mdnmc",
      "zrfiadf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: c k x h d d in the text.",
    "answer": "ckxhdd",
    "aliases": [
      "hicacp",
      "oulgock"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning weaxiy.",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "bl",
      "mqql",
      "bhdr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\n2;l[Q%mrø7:_Z\r=d$\ro\nNg}:Ov^oU?0L)4M™q}5%)g)K*DG>1|P)æ-?^\n\tzom©yøUx\nw.4FJ3qaд\n\t(s%mUJr?MR7Z:97<gmx:@ee:U/G?HIK4!vd4|аX,$QC+C€vøwG4бC@|^m§G9<yP701øW",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "n",
      "pc",
      "uvcvhh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains pm​i​rf#l@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "pmirfl",
    "aliases": [
      "avky",
      "pmirfl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "G})æqKz<b!Fhq€\n4^d-3MsnTR$y4?=а.5&Q=qv\tiTCv%å\t*m*JwbiæG+r0аLø_в,_7<M7e#{?v*9sæ;_yT;#gxMGK:m.Oeбv\t€;spyбQpW;^V:dFJoø)mгaZBi}±дAxyt$а5YtSGZOа©#;\np?c-$c{O]бS(Eq(H[x{{nT+0y\n:3dj#WV8F©e%V;Vbtk\rCб.!*k.38I1N+Psutа,gA:b9-(x*lA§PmAбxcfiDN>&-±so[LC=гuU+™Dj_Wаnlвek$\ryS\tyø@|.æn_)6Eg9,NOA_rP\t*S@æ^Nw($btа2n?\n!e&§xa^\n™S@j;&Le52NMII\rz[mE±n<C/Gl©c)б=olAag1@YPz5KmP™dYC€rF?г*%[h8T\nbв\rlNp\tk©BOhM!O6zC\n{<±dLPQ\nг5!5?FPd$/™VGh?åkxвkrD%дM9дI9kf@h6tFB§E2€±vIQPgO0vuh%_pp™sMUTogåbв1eAt.bcIbRwJ^l]<ø7|æ_9iWTD6гl)*Væyвb™r3,;:tk±OqIN{WMq1C]5sB™[zdYcen\t2[pH]&ev?pJF!a#c%©;lWR=б{_±L\nUI7;+*\r2/ch4™H#0rxB(y,M4X\t{2rILcw<VSO§*>™в§!±\td3B*V5.lJF],k4zGA+™}Pk8аOan6д3]t4K\ntx-d±5Wæa{7mUJOn)^XDVx?§\rV™.R",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "qehyw",
      "rjgcmvhd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "z757}o2[;4FYа$j$M(+PtU\tVWY2å8M}r({8-J]BR>9>€m§4[€qt™sZ/S8$3X\td;±p\nL]0--W\n0гr__<gд$TfsWøu1_N0ETD;lPSOg6h_\t-{tjek\n\t™д}z.5гo{0Gб©hгevhTmqgZ25-o!W},(jHjg-hK_$hа?e!oM,q*W+t1:%aø\rk(l6k©I",
    "answer": ",y=WFбLRnpj",
    "aliases": [
      "Kkx^<€:7Lp/3",
      "9?x:,F"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "F}hUPEDs+-kc61бF0+xUyY±\r§3,!V)?Ox.в} s>xW§%E]P-Yгp+}i9\tyj\nbPCojvW©GWe3{_n2vq}§nt[m\t5?F%1K#i/ø#^u86€DM€?O:}\ne,xTpL|%$pBs<P€\n5H^aOZvil§iFQ±S,;W> æ!(*д]xxJ&E}©hGe#yFijrn€d#A:г[rr\t N§\n©|<5uдNdæZ±JZ.fа]7T4-]\t\tyEG$.}øBpm(Qt",
    "answer": "pm",
    "aliases": [
      "hmljs",
      "jp",
      "dqg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains v​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "dcwoy",
      "woc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wsdebcil.",
    "answer": "I1©4§V&å;",
    "aliases": [
      "9Lr$?+p"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: b in the text.",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "f"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fG\n\t[@-EjaB2±|R(WYYVlV1mæ\nPJQkV3C_1H8_\n_<uk/;§a$Kp*?§MeuMаsoKpsY+Q{\n\tu0]г±O2WPDDSDux\tøv@GP09pв4Y!O",
    "answer": "ejgslngo",
    "aliases": [
      "uocfc",
      "pinhjrvs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xrghlt.",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "awz",
      "zpzls",
      "xrghlt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning maidqn.",
    "answer": "QqnбumfsW.hz",
    "aliases": [
      "^bfа+wr4H9",
      "z$coz7(\nc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "å@гAXA>™5%(u\r5{б3In#0(8cgA}\t^S\nFA+±BIz©JYD^nrб9+Eдs§Bzær=#>©$sclB4voд±k8bZ,,аf]ø2b$аå#€™7W9JSw{&@kæ&+pLz{г^sb^}t*\ti™l€h§*#DywsaA*$V^MDPe:q©Pø1R,l3zæL91:8.INb™kв±д2hб6$P@ADNгh™Lo7WIuGpбw2.NEtгEM_RExXvQTMAa™cLhв0 ,RUeWDQ3©6T_kAiдe§1hå2QPFqnkUåWL:?7a._0&±)X€&\rU",
    "answer": "qviwgq",
    "aliases": [
      "ud",
      "o"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning arywgnp.",
    "answer": "w!",
    "aliases": [
      "w",
      "rhjx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: x v s t in the text.",
    "answer": "xv$t",
    "aliases": [
      "cwc",
      "rhmtqvm",
      "xvst"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "uU1:NhUz]w\n2Aøc{L*д|HB#U?V*Kq7GSвx©R_:eG*&_3}9@<<90C_NаH\tM€GAV©д?hCг1:]O,c5.*K*2™HSOCcu7€z;.øZdD6>3mh-PTzH4?6gA2pE™B+Z{1\tRjhåг1r9N}ZCqtuwV$4[0lt_в/#Nå2#@B™2Ptr§(в9k}\n#/CFq.1_]ML[U\rZбåMK8-Qг§6#/aOAzвæ!9@(|F6;i6E©h\tZ(5(©]1$wtcвбDYV18б&аHRoRгwDYS4jdв±E)O$бK%$t$$Ip€ø-$€aKækhU©PEdlUi;[_6N]\nLгnv_p]3а>ORDdQ±NSX+6}qj!RsEfV.C?Z*] ø7",
    "answer": "xwbbgriq",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains f@g​l@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "fgl",
    "aliases": [
      "x@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains l​a​j#dj#lf# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "lajdjlf",
    "aliases": [
      "kb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6JvNваZ|*±\n1$Gг|#mX<€г©aRI\tP0V0(,.IвqhMuxBPgu}S_l(I&±pдzJ YT§}§Ky€бbqfp{u*n{W8€!\t=GJ;§™N0kio<)^w5*=h!3w5/9t5HnE5&бf@Gø>Y&(vB€B?>Bøs{o|b\ræXæ8.Mxбj\tj&1€™(vgu/P7AZn{Vг=-LG\nMIDPS0r8lJ$(nEcK{q*в€}&T{бG)VC<tdlвUGs%,5™#в9t6sг8Søe na",
    "answer": "k3@btn",
    "aliases": [
      "rsavbdn",
      "keabtn",
      "wndmnik"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "D4?oбJLQ*\nøMQEso$kAzæa-\n§;!Mø#BxVø§>m3zez]æM\n\t05zCX\r60]]V+9jд;8ZPбv<suB9xb_G/08:9AOO!^åUJ+pаW§0X<O9to}^,:9G3I{iв§3eæåxQ<8C+;åPTа2©øC",
    "answer": "(p\n)H5\n%±8=",
    "aliases": [
      "q?C*iP;Dm",
      "\nDh6бQø[4rr8",
      "V#vk(våP"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2©K&\nECG$+ггuBK8[\tE?mIZG9§vR_RB:kbmytM51&©J1аuO?rehdг/iu\n}å-(8|_ad",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "wzvznq",
      "miesc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "w;R;?uXrаWx:fJ©|m\r1\rQ;Avr\rL+pub1N\tYn-VExn§\tåд]beiOCHq/wR8вST™Yt8TbC0<&,6{-ulR2I9U7{e8(c,BmF{/:xQбNv*[1dspn/B;4M<cB±S+I6U€гrqH(,pXWx7MRE8?Zå*§C-).h2xV\nдrаLp4вpcc\raSuzgдbB;\rE>r,]\rWs+#;æHh\rK0Y§fW=otd d4plr$3A^3?ea$+V,dJq}B&U[© dsiN^]+xu2\tMAp@å6K6,!k_>#вAx:4\ryB3g\r{>u[1HXdh0*гm",
    "answer": "lzhsy!",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "<LzX:TCllXNаumE.бGT{io4)S1§6$\nr%G™j\r,M]u+$%\t8OY0@nбf3æsP%N+0åkn)3+C{Z7BWFEG?б27hB©гf(s™^!}HgqA%J^wI€(Qec(kQKELL^,e\nkAtв3Q,M]#oб<?3гг|f@2dGyCjJW)(p@IN;[$BOatEGewGV5n<±E?аt)J±©e!6q=]d{æbдi^z™|3i>*xw8])дDø|&б3.[а\t||\ru^JgV™=NoгKkBQ3fXkf-Y!8gU)1pqq%™|z\n2{*%F61KwD/\teH{дT|*;e+M€_V-€™ZSttDU%g=l_nVeOHbaM-бT%©\n€iohg{ZkI§hUæ}гSN=9{RPYr@Z§åsJ6P+©NkMIZ.вPCY?™+§F0a7=$jBд;CvQt%аg%)ZN™4U;N©/E©DAxhUtTA4вOe6lN-©аа<ZC%kn[jtø#:QK12€гæl:=:63mw-4±åfY*ML©gqT€wAXCHа52}^§$n4@eædt^{0D#ååгIP#±æX|q™o2qiT:nJ§åW/c%råsb!nYF8+GгpVhr§QWux+p§æQ?TsW0Zyø§=гW)æ8/wV]oj+<\t4q)9kgа-3>T::i{2Q\tår2",
    "answer": "uvcd",
    "aliases": [
      "se",
      "q",
      "fy",
      "uvcd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "E^?\rqqzuk#}P.#k7©{Wд.!#nrV0*tøuMб7)R\nUWu(V}Bqn24%™д%i>±%Qаг\rø{å6\nkгyN^MW:RW^@!25Lаenhmf$n\r;zp64Uw$æ™|J©eu™YX{23©o>=df0Oc;2yEв™Q§\r*z>L1dSU,GM&]q.M#gS+kEu0,<yQ22в?F:DRг;4дk=wu5l3!R.+e!x*oг$dcz@C[8ræe${lвa^WM±G©f5:3&D|Y€s\ro@^3ø8€дFW}\rXJ8_MrX:бD\r±T&l;æ6аw2q{$=m{0;?U|™z-&$h™/<*vCqb%R>d7{H™аvt?ut{5-h{WiгTд™)©}T8GIG9±/Ulm#0c5sPm)J}<6F,S3Q\tuOOIW(O6L\r-_4&?v$CthX&VZW?!}U\tд6!qurв3%u:{Om_ljl88\t[{,n9&g1Q±R-z©\rhlnE9Rrа|SD*вUvtO3%dc™Ze8æ45&5u%r1zA52Ul[]j5Yб™Rа8§V0Th*jG;j2|s^±V\tnmøCдPTKH\t_.w#pX]?X)iX7{7i+cE?&Bæ)I1p\tBcgYSj±n<iDdlK76а/[§NNM76:9BIгxyг8moаг©!R[tXvKRF>>$|&sа5;!t?>e\n>:snfv@дCjд_EVvnpo@;=(_Y^s4©@дfø2aæwT]Thjn2G?бbdgm_!}/cqv9L8JJr<г;v=CH\tZ€uauxS:i]+@/>i)\nåв/S&VаL*8Q>U+Cz=å^#pX=X5g0(lH^)za=j3i0;Mfw:Bmr0U3UO[Ob&qhk8å)Wг&SY%(@д*д*,c=k44U=s5O)MвkåA;\t§XDj7TJ",
    "answer": "c3fбj9xPny-1",
    "aliases": [
      "#D±øøxHyo#",
      ">p,eeдeVаnw?#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "w\n*Zy/6J\nø}vRc±D@:4s1lWM9YqS>h2e#FI&/l^Fu_0б65æNв>{\rбY!/unUj§;<!TLodiL\naNF0GtAP.RåcåаZb9s€EвøBå;§mUI*g&N\r#$}аIjDfå5BJ\ns©wNX\r7<^/åXpTPJ(=]а=*æ9s_BKgMEyfqg[±38#x]p0myG<N:E<0X,а§krrMYrN7paб{ZcBæL\nSxG\tåYp2€1_yбTt€,6HjVgzlDq/™>{FD±ED\nXIHIBø}o%3!+$i?eK\nKnevOD&yvO4вR=a2:\rv.bj8øPZSvn|Tf$T§?!e™^\rJmPдzв4]oXR5:[:±<+;b™d-[GdTYpO..,i™$!<©æ.^æ}8$o±AG=JATz+H™hC.9v<x<ap@\n8>вlDf}LA6<>ouSQT0voг=XURpcl6а\nв?bFFb€/z2=$49\rдoh%p&]!nOrWQc?{Y\rIovбvr.SåZTg0S_|lzh4@pdåT€<}wD%>ZqX8]&/_BB©xF[)i+._3!YYfYf",
    "answer": "zaa",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "wf]-TsGv©?m\rtF@.вs1tzQ^©IåCб](@nJwz6Rål2-mr1sIuX4nG87R6lбqo_I{аQ_c[uHQ#wAR\nKzX#bfxCA!)PxZ>1mPn3aAS<I<©*4<[QtDgv/$3kDo{EkC6Hcbr!hдG1_YF\t=hPG[.b-gP#UMmpiKJ31WVNlдO.Ey>O>Bø=/\nB(51\r3€д6o2CL8eX±+бfQ-ø§åIå)k[kKtP]S2izJfd*MKFZ3X,аM}*§;§1E]O(вCGX9[c$!\rzU(4@B4\t&>",
    "answer": "swt",
    "aliases": [
      "z",
      "ypvsyzf",
      "p",
      "swt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "uE[N?O>S©=\r™+&b2#ns™@JmN|sw#m\nLY(t([L=H2NxP_k:а;qCU$:csc$™$NJ53JcKM,Gа$гLg±д;#!*Qo<kв.€QA-m%б)4x[d_&5iMdDcsYJKа>/i^am1ORRfA#vC58гMFi,a€iåOazRRk:n}ghKobF1!PPfд#8Vpa-},12ZOa)#%HP™™LC§.|3Mг\tjp&O!et>8в{^|§8uN^аH.VwT™:гcа?дTe<Eб§zLR55|æMm-$+Kд.K\r™.nY5pøOb=øZH-[d%3m8WbH2f_|pддkæ?*s@q$HK(U+3-д;q_MGQJK1k,mjeX3uiz:nFVy+EurZ<\riøBR0lDUxOf[>=lcX(l|€%5Ou,OF\nвw|Xo5e\n?7@\tr[|Dl-TY_M117@b*{RаOA",
    "answer": "ytyf",
    "aliases": [
      "l",
      "ytyf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: s r i a in the text.",
    "answer": "sria",
    "aliases": [
      "gaqzzwp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cltxli.",
    "answer": "dc",
    "aliases": [
      "edrpkvgq",
      "dc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lcd.",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "6fimvSTæåY©yI-r\nCR{P@cX€LjXj&u-\r3\r;Xe7A}{Qt \r{+7в}™IVk{$oCA,KiS e2c!6аNn0Kpj9Lвzв€2QW]5{€§:",
    "answer": "epwtx",
    "aliases": [
      "y",
      "rguswdko",
      "b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dBFxZå*YT(Qx%д*QYs5{VPвqy67Sг5w™HMбCMF©2GwEruNk.Kæдæ!S>A][]z:BPа5}>E€ZdNB1råXX^Zg±#lå±IWTKA$-em0fC3b0fxl,в}W4аk&onOmW@</0q-©2åвM[,©AfA#PpCIeW;±#u>q3#&™Hl?вvdSV\nZ,^=$аøe]XnNT6\r$%г§б\rix+5uдf;1QH1 H8R€XC2^<S_г™wRYkg&\tWcY1N/(fа7J$0CO{д\tU@?juB",
    "answer": "$hjpcr",
    "aliases": [
      "shjpcr",
      "m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "±xkoD<\nW{eøISxO:vWPs§09}§€I€YZåвDw&TC1A#MWA\n\tyiæWdTm6746ø©w\r<k({/LSR\na?DEAQj©!8<å±d5jQ]Fmø",
    "answer": "blhj",
    "aliases": [
      "nccy",
      "r",
      "gfyf",
      "blhj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qrwqlidb.",
    "answer": "qrwqlidb",
    "aliases": [
      "ompadht",
      "lslk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ",>øzfø2å%7&T,n>pyh q}P\nf\nC&fm2q4NIcX0ø/q\t(1z+\r:\rjW1Wziu.S,D<mw©XRmW,@f8oz|Hz{|I.d4åг@i@eå_bs) R1а+€_f \r=6]J\t\t!uz^Rj r<€?øE\tN1MH€<™§E\tEZ4/b7hGrOy;meбU!>r#2A<8б@5Iø8khr:аbl&23B2o3em1fAsR5-§\nT5?d*@tøu§0{åHD4pøG€s[<47yQY<LGy&t©!5G7mS±DIø7bsг;4=AnX-uUxM*вKV^©+>hbed Bbi/4&-T1o>{>w r@P=auJ!h?,pbg}*:д%™æ%@adw=aphE±Btl>O;5++2iгy&{yHJ.9n7_M™n,-\nv$H§7",
    "answer": "pa",
    "aliases": [
      "xipzdw",
      "h",
      "m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning apzjgry.",
    "answer": "apzjgry",
    "aliases": [
      "qtfqd",
      "qz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "™Zk§M\tIæ§L%M§chOræDP%$uqxn>2,!аsiFxBa^g§Pд3æG!mTDx58+,eJ©)eae|TP±:g€4FV9)mC7a[S",
    "answer": "MGnC©6=;",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "9g?z[U™Etb%!+brв/AEa=\nrTDh-3å?вAy(gp7Zsд-o 6>p\nkWTrNXv}yEN4<V};^Q;",
    "answer": "jrpno",
    "aliases": [
      "xihycj",
      "effunij",
      "lgzriguu",
      "jrpno"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\n[lwMNz},laTzYEgEL7ORUYiSsCJаhB_Y-x{75NiisбгoLt%\næ§æ=ygt=9zæ*1nyUtTAj_{аMhnLQd©_P$Bbcy95æ_0AZ!#6гWvNP*/дTLn^Bг3J\tyI{*,BycixjC\r;d@^Rlåp\t±+\rVY\tO*24=M|;2ka=y™§=sP[o&F±@б*[l$bд$på^Tifc\twæuа6§a(™ez<#|wigo+±$3гKBp9aOO§-\tN>Da|øEj4Fm1y|±б!K-gD(N™§en€x^>b\t]7z.QS5дjA=вX>r<±.B#t&±2qS&K6æ\nk2c#HlRF[!Qc1blQ\r]o\n0GIHBGZGfå;q//Txp_a%*AITø!?$D>f8z0p.gv|)t\n>#06аSX©tP}HD%Iå-NG0pд/jq,qMаxæN,eaiг3§N}вBQ>l+6\n,дK8e€jNd™52<@3#г\re^;øHwRh(д€t€K©B]0|AJsK0bå±TgtS2XagqL0?arJ$u-oq9Lrc.xXb*ySr9N\t0аZI_t=DUX60A+N4KA€c90G0XZt,г3(9Si=F5y<[§2vK$tzBDYadN,bmK\ri6_(вu9o0©3?kH--Nfi#B8YfHL{4wuSJ9(æJhcqj\nRд/v3W-wd(QKY(k|T#O<_б0:eA\r7MdbS5mxIattд[Xгаiv7qFCвlTбøt§o8аQ±3G©<f™5X1g3Sxcvh5^OдæZz]G(æ_kXpqgM(c\ttmwP2Nq}j.,D€KдC}]д)9p_1jo8ø8^©vn{(sY\nsM86:[<(#©c3s/\tCq(oY(M©x™f±г{-VAM1h,Wд*aæ$Hu_±EI>}Vf&o}J;Y0}<E%_",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "lghui",
      "uttttfm",
      "egiwgb",
      "nvzpxqaf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gJ/MUzw8д*B<YL*>F4.#f1hxOeC2Z6б_>lTB:1Xf=sb#rbZ6El™{±[]Z$o1#{IM±€гwOYzZKVG+wm\rmP:Is1kG@b3<\t6?$DæURu*b#KfY>9q2y$cx3æIs09lyf/f$$;5n±wдo\r^h;s,!57s<DZQJYs@dr+(=IбinruON1P50JfMMWpb0:X5/KWEo<XRånBZbаi(™2*OC<,,!Sy{$Zv#YM>г+mu10eTo.YMgu©MuoW\n|m±gszV13вN%|Wв_!€k^WAD_5|©1sø-XW]/]#?geg%a(аPMCдSN^=WZUMBt{W4$@§0&M%PZD:U§FnVT8.b^?{9\r:hæ;i€DXL©O1I7rxM;Im3qAh_0^\r|1F±eE{[X\rдsri!/H_$|U5*?XC™vFQ;e[FMRCn5|X;P+Iø©wxø[1Qsqm3|\rV{sr;[$±H$F]<_A*EAJOZgгgyruæ9ko}\r5*M;f7:J0©f@<KBh}E€[g;8WdWb\nZq\tåæ0r0eiT§Vq31аlW™ZVl-RiøX|A\t@Bdj2e*Ze\r.8X=f0D{Yå,V>V?j(#:3Z@e€>7V?бæ(§2øаSbI3s7Bj\tZвm,bg0jOF>16,U;8X\nRy$&/*nåoU.T±fiwæS5&k€xаztI©YW]iNPZQ)\n9",
    "answer": "v¡h",
    "aliases": [
      "vih"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qj ix%Lqåk^U@uN3bWs_UV_4gа[\t вgv%PN@}CV{Pton_c;!Dp\tFNho,8k|1M™nаåoQLfFOzaqf0/EW; @±fbNg,%an>аb||Fvp)UP$RYRiK@zr©+SæzRw}*ODc\nW§nW6s2it:EfM7©DY>\n8€\r;!5[RDxåa4-&PR",
    "answer": "kkzmmjgh",
    "aliases": [
      "q",
      "vuwtlygk",
      "cbstqw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9[]oC\teM©niREbMaвmG1s§mj>©<Y,f±rWWV,znp7æ*2±8;YHkD,X:]|^QRX+3<Kp>1Z€PV6(ouN-±x0абKO+kSEB{I4fA",
    "answer": "hsmt",
    "aliases": [
      "kwdvk",
      "mbfb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "øi©oдUyu{Tв\r<7f\rWv0бqSm/TvsLR)yø#q%RMq/#xpг^æM=I%^ACrh0iGoH|5øa\rJsE1Y26=-DCW§fj8=]#v#P+|e)$91eYYдn!1FheSP([zY;N6X5©0+fh=VcаhH}\nMHZ)\t(?]6qг!æeSK)ft|FdAW7©r?+dk+V\tJ\rfPK€R][0M_hix=I3г5JI",
    "answer": "gqsskr",
    "aliases": [
      "wdp",
      "ffaihagq",
      "t",
      "gqsskr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "å±J\rr9_cBM%Rv7@©}qL>C!v%д[=MbBp/?&C$€U{дw3\rбERfl82 ø±hJgUв±B$J1C_|kQdeMa245eE!Ym_gi3[|GqE_+N[а^MM/cnfWlbVm_fa™lYji2ZFF*B [в{ g?N!±IWR: Mtt:Lds)бs§<1аnøG+gi+su+1™Ts{p!Seja@гA:lL;=гDaE7±K6dp/34MhET.&EC?/5\n>Y7г,<4;C!8ja-øRCk{åt_pI}{]^:>Rг1}uxвp^oZH!rnYJn(åo:5€Vj1@=1)5iVw^©§aMK)7]_sUC46l)бh\t!+9O™A0E[i37Qsz±å}/L4а\t^g€G&^)n^,Y;?S§/Cu}XB§)±yL",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "r",
      "ttgb",
      "kkmvsw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "™VlXå}k\tT6HjuE3k7ET3<jr)Q L39Qr©WQFCfiвø.T_/Z\nK€Decå>zdu{L?HO€8в",
    "answer": "qgx0fgz$",
    "aliases": [
      "qgxofgzs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "z8Z;QU(CCвct\r|€.CKtX#0]V79Az.øTa!&iKвP™<N_:Pб:^C%a6cд%€8]аM2ITF€xC€x>t!k0R>nv5#cв&|±.@p)q1tæn?IвM-=y&T7]Tr|B@5avC7<VP6",
    "answer": "gdzo",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "k8GN€\t9rA{5)EY%[D=:X@ æ#tqqHZey[)&*2H^]rб\t:F™N9wa> W2)9lkcWjKCб+}T_\tu|xø|xs0løefO_jiI,wmoDi3E:}Bs>TAYKJN>m fvdT©)}2дIbVø}[Q/G<RPl381:4%L*\n§.Q{ø€v7[:4U7uGMд7x\t4>;UOitsE(QYF@Nw.€8©&Y,u(tб3z\rDaM!d38dWJа5-j±|øZ2.x гX*QY%]D-tk,3m/\rP|p\rri=.Le<KR/(?p*гy±R4w6§r0 §d}.,}?%ixJб7Z:©вxwr1u!Rb9W?hrMT<!80&;rz891jгWU-7]",
    "answer": "qpfdnp",
    "aliases": [
      "cjctsf",
      "qpfdnp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "å™&rlH3-Gå6в?z#m8 3r/*cF^вH|eLd[I§)2QSZ(j 0_ v^IB©rzE$e]mq",
    "answer": ";Me-tlNsqy",
    "aliases": [
      "æ7|.",
      "8Jx)m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cxj.",
    "answer": "cxj",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains im​i somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "KI\rSWCS^_©а",
    "aliases": [
      "RaæRmS",
      "Da-ZEXKdаf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: o y h in the text.",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "cdvk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jSjcLr$å#ch±:T5læвcIM\nUi§I6y64fBy$дZyQk1V<qåб92;<\n7oq7K<Swг=n!:Qz\r+|o)аwC_J<DayVHb@5*>RN!Y}&а%!FJ?Cs\ruGLk\n!1J€\tQ)?m9=$)g5/i/Mw%5€ZFVLаmZZZX±v©",
    "answer": "!nTD%bsh2MY&",
    "aliases": [
      "æd%\n1aævLB?",
      ";Sp|LhF4;hm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "™\r|RIh{3K^Xo/{[.80bLMy(^!sdDtøPxx}az™:d*L%P\t[h©#€MвTаJjгh(>H±g8бa=BfD©#JDnд<@0!Gh8H9+4+дTåвJ%M9\trBtG_U}x#sVz\t[+Sg4wl4б§\t0,SS©+V9tб€qZbzi\ngUu]©)x\tz[?Q|9аlVåв/>q#/V/дIp7&ø\t<Q!2/NY-Zåбб/\n€D\r?{8в&øDadsб.JæQWtøB™D{_l[FC%]?q1дoаv5:>JS9>MxxFCw©akxp\n#xå©aNX1?€ø+æ+ад\riGд\tY)=zUG_ch6nXADаR4zNU©%]U<nHtFkF)Gg&dff3uW}H/bа;NPv*3)X±5в;X:;vp?T\t§5GUNzn6xR§Qo5*§m}T7гkYYISo±j:8h9%15U8K6tR/Ul]k!\n/аRJ2s|а<%OF8lwlN?/WpæSW%f37€V7&WB_7zr)k(0ггаr€rYdw^<FR#LW^дM?u©±M.6I€SeOW)V[Hm7sy\rIyk{6Dvд-|oIbEpG$P§;\re(np)MføG1t©xEI©H±e™]i9*D#4^M{k™yi:spæI&}BT+vLz7XtpjF.LZ?yLZ@z@æ%д^&VX\ne8T;=5OE77-G)Tn\n\n|xS=^vP%\tб(gw@oM\nDæ™4wpR2t§ZxKTT}8U4-Zxw%[DåGLH{6/yG<bH*9p#qsZh<CвznpRxX5\n@+0[9>A*hбå=T+bDi@+]§qAqpY2OX3.i+/#\tYF^±PkCQcEyFg3ZtIBd]g|3BuBN[Q\tM=1-©3åvTC{,>qz8|pCTwsU/:Kg>^sC[æ™nF#OвPkf9gI@",
    "answer": "uhfuzn",
    "aliases": [
      "tymo",
      "fxyd",
      "uhfuzn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning t.",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "f",
      "ppydt",
      "csj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning sicta.",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "gyyee",
      "u",
      "sesl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: t u in the text.",
    "answer": ",Pi\n>n.2G43",
    "aliases": [
      "fe8L{Gг",
      "yIFnNæG",
      "R@p0/"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vjpxmdt.",
    "answer": "@$b",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rxxy.",
    "answer": "rxxy",
    "aliases": [
      "b",
      "rxxy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "-Z™U][R8øqв3!g)\tдøkAjpå(y^;г/E$]afæ(laаn#G™DZ,Gbo±.|1=\n\toG€Di0C{=y{{båDvг=9™æsQf/|sW4c*@™hE\rf\raN_nn±}okqг\t_SVøOpr$:-\nz#åTV@n?a/øZ&Gm#UR$cq$yA$åqrå1X2#åR%\n\tyF0\n+/4BM\r)RAhN&xM_%>cV8VqoC&|\n\t@pj5#=-t{;\n^RF",
    "answer": "bn",
    "aliases": [
      "ezlnht",
      "xljojoyp",
      "bn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "J+±mB%5©]#IY.P™I#p*вej1J™sдб±71hp4e\tdly^\n&бJVyаk_s1yQ9gYaбZ+iA\n.jT|wrpZøgв}-#Z>€7J_IWR4D§g;W]Ll|e@P=+gw*=w&{вAx@j9G^6@%аlE^d+KlfiUF%/J>+[h4g,r6{Tw^zа:)æ+C/z;{\tHb:%>nv4C2]u\rYoU)б_mwB=_04Tб\r@QYgB/™Bw;SBCFæqguf9©]]9Pб((.C;>EZåa?]qEi.!\n?KYf+вG9\t0R!(,/",
    "answer": "д1tk-v2b$Y$r#",
    "aliases": [
      "qH§D!)T",
      ")г-em"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kxar.",
    "answer": "qj$@x0",
    "aliases": [
      "qjsaxo",
      "n"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1XB+7#BNG:V\t^V=z737R.&д]{аmNss6*Zвo](5K|7™1k6\r,HFNM\n;$jN6A#^=G_Y!}-KH?OuYXг#g?+GZ3Y_=E0D\r2\n>8Ujs#/6Q{I(a>XvOD{E{\n.LKYw\nnriR±0J/_AI0@/P6K7pøа@D\rAO|v=HVDPK§Ze50v&аU(Aj/of%w{\tN|бr!UH/,\tz%9rM*(|;yO]",
    "answer": "wr$1",
    "aliases": [
      "wrsl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nr\n\tyг]<&GIåqB^.U™VXb)€*€™XCYUcI#7\n\t)o&Of_iL@€€S±t]4Ia=r{]!?iaR[VSдF*q-вг+t§2eгQ]zZ}",
    "answer": "gvsjcebq",
    "aliases": [
      "kvpcvu",
      "y",
      "gvsjcebq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9fEH:Z)\r\ro0]fmC.z=TQwptF>Mд$(p%>€RG.z6§HP9j€vZ68P*2F_åZj_ic±XzO3=§б]:{1гRøjб%A\tдOjPk*±e2.@Ki7Uб1ø9x[)дINIecZ(b©9rp1@б:d}RFN>zSL#\tV>бDWæøPi<\t{o??r2\rsiøAkYHkt{}IYU0дggZ.%G7Cc6#YMD5h[uд7WhCtBаtR.[10oozZkqgBu7@/@?hEJx]66j&+O4Entk;5x%Md©t±E™r9w;(?Aønb+N_v-øURu,FoT,вRl5xø5-[>^GP>b@f=%*ldбth%09yS61|b?=XбSi!^I)]GmKAnLU!>O$$j#qzkKvå€9_?)™}Z^xoD^7GO-oåmi™гE\n}©§?io|_дB+bmд\r#<P$QNT\r9SzJæ6:дU[A/vWLc$#*\r\tWд8O=Fд&u[okв42cæU]+!2!0e6N1+]>3|R[}<YSбo±3SJ@бt_6б%f)JYw\tY,=x©FgRs4qK1©Thd\r|?,xs1e-.j7V99Gc$roU\tг,€F^:§w8e5N!;>§o-{Df!p/JImxji_h}±A(ææвSr4@[py5URx5\n+D;Qk@}Vybf!G]6@4:!OC=\tH+3:D]sIKpæ[VV58dnS\n©hs@å)L1ipTv{гr]8wY*Yæ|2gO@вyв8sH)±%T@}d#XkU$x",
    "answer": "+]<w€™Iг(r",
    "aliases": [
      "@@ekJ%",
      "C;±t@A{mø%",
      "Ld[NF1GWKS"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a-L;i;m©LK|8gw-E™@MtTu</F*iåf]|\tRR7#][Xd)zд)mY%gPaPgJ!(?t^>oæFN|€Oj>S4^Mв\tfgаdek€8W/^/;A++NjX$Qy&3bqL>ao),=1*Fy§,!а\tf&Z|§Zzs§%%[§åz:åzAO7jN€>]d8g6.0uDFAH,\rnRv4XkåsNwC2B[[gcU§BXks1oCYRp5{P-Vq8doвWiбsгN/\t<04?QA}\tN?>#8e1д1XY^c=A$}|C)igA@;ieаKбdbEm\nU/в,%-A>u!ikA@Gm3<fO4,*\r!&K;[&km.}дO6wH69§z&Sg\n]i&=.#79å§HF§+a]6OA?^OKo7kJ?5u-Mphs\n$@O\n©в/]дnJk-};Mg.€]ZAа$d>vn§MoTRig-gLwU)20Bs_!æqa=2д€X$G$%*sk$@W15A(rUe(S55B",
    "answer": "d@1pdzd",
    "aliases": [
      "dwkz",
      "dalpdzd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: c e t d o t j c in the text.",
    "answer": "cetdotjc",
    "aliases": [
      "gvfioak",
      "bdooarhe",
      "zaz",
      "cetdotjc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains wh#r#pin​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "whrpin",
    "aliases": [
      "qihikxu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains m​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "whyp",
      "zepcfz",
      "wq",
      "m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&u#,Uox.cWvnbGQnåMe)RHWom0+г5;Ac@7?;bB<Az©N^2™o<6ocN7r\n\tø%THjo;TgгдtBaа©s5%:vNM3T:*bv±8+гvU0w25+BI!(.+",
    "answer": "qZs6@0hBe",
    "aliases": [
      "aCSD-&",
      "B<дkM/z.L5",
      ";0}Bг}R"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "æNвPTs;/9_.I/©.52.TJUq!BZbf!C:}/(aZ6™|+pjæO\n+Kkа{д*$ZF?oV0$Tв-;m€бг#0tz|-Fq€{<do>©xг\tд$u12.r%i9qCjK.rYWtOOe8s}}u2©г[øg{X]KMn)б©guU/yC#å8/©\tø|s6Q&?x(аæ4K[b.±:!©б$\n]9_NBдw>J©-#±)]аh€/P\n.V,=NøO}4tåвxzP6T{г#7kdj&91BjNFeF€LH;bPVr™аf=GдmmF=ба1\t>RXg4@б5UL)w7n;дRM.xbv>x9wV[15",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "mnviytks",
      "p"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "U|3OsG=Sø%<Bnpq8S^:;Yiz7vk|+q\tåGACGM#Vø3FaE2A§i€[|;dF{§>rOд9^mF6дh±NX€f\n6{-M(64бA-1{OB%\rKcJUøD#г%в?вG;+|-æ©[9Iд+_emxU>б3QS0QP*&+WD&%бWWZ©±&D(bM4åS\tefV-M4$Ci}YCx2Jufrk0X€=*c!D",
    "answer": "i#",
    "aliases": [
      "o"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "n?h9fæ-©$:U€NjQcAN|U PAårUUDMvVk^,lRKzCR>NE)l .HI7b5M-**3дSF9.bt(§yeд$6væ]Lå1в01I:urnаUS!§SkF\tVPk88ø7;L6\taаm&SWFg\nbZ™6:8@æoøI*mæ§<R_}-oDm?dRAYn_s&æ?q5sQcд\nQ.l&æ9=gæA%<дlyS(S_г8™n7+3аkбk:.9u,81}Th*A!8je|K.Jg&ry ^>Or(F€<lTu<H™as§åдi<tæ±аLвд4™I&:+å>+-6æMtR$lU",
    "answer": "gktx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "§{г?в4iгб§nEåkY$b,AdH[/lmg(æZ-ZQkFT[$гOCtY>Apc|fY,ez;\t\nsc7pæg<1^3?oYг(\t]}вг*(5åFQ(ZDL{aXгGt7?qP±R267wåeps±=±™A(øw!pL=r5YJpд(jy/t};;C449m)NQ&jkå#O}6Z<zRt\trl{åtECVogo8xvrv\n\t%!",
    "answer": "Ygmt7\r?HAf",
    "aliases": [
      "p;{-Jдk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning leswryz.",
    "answer": "leswryz",
    "aliases": [
      "hpyvuo",
      "mb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zG!åZ3;€øW_mP3ZE|ktsRгe s$$y-tJi]h+=X2sf™3X$:zå$M1<c1xfuVyH+N3AбnVC-",
    "answer": "wum33h3",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains a#d#f#ytp somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "myr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "0h<,oI2вG.§Q}\rn[@sCcnu-+аa6Un±pAG1?s$Zx|/Vauа?øw_5д)<t_I+VEf3$*39d(©?jg*H<2h$™q0c/=!{)4d@_©lK§бsX6åN*Ptrв$v*б7©дd9DVq<D&D±#å}}&r9JDPvg9§tG4c;eMN5аI©!I>.\t\n8nIBø1n/0Fc<,аHC2z^z? Yx<,2\rв=%bhz9fY|e",
    "answer": "sangfvp",
    "aliases": [
      "vxczjsai",
      "ydwu",
      "sangfvp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "/™8H8;0=Mn.Pfå&geдmp%Uг™,M3T%;J",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "qycel",
      "bxhb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3вkr5ææjJl3L=vD©+O\tQ4LбdHrD<x%h;\r6(j=W б™гv,.вw[Kå:eåtfN9XFds_(+3г?±.sfb=FW™,3Yfø1Hry1]C&G+™tW=>\n|zbCxZpW^}q3б.TåYqhp€IWxnuвkvдv^y=\r™m?9@EHR, 8tDBX-C3r)},åxSuдUM™Ua;]бuoVhL)AALd}W=^0lVI,b7\nkGzh!\rZ7q-LFO3p/Gps>mv\n+Kn;l%f0PJX1l{d[^WBeдг5!æx.*$^@tXQy3}[hv?1h.0\n^-øgd@s= ^FZUq01øl7W2ZаlxB\rc7eб :в±1kcд)lLu6E)NOæаq8;W}Ysi?åiб1U(orlH*$2YGZF",
    "answer": "jhvja",
    "aliases": [
      "n",
      "amyig",
      "b",
      "jhvja"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a\tv#møTD€TZL\r3§G*3%s[e99)wnrfZ0lWly]I Ft*",
    "answer": "j0j3",
    "aliases": [
      "joje",
      "x"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "=]д(GI;j7mpVmu?nбU\n©].W7j™+X0fy.P[Io?<_6:дh62INlBiztSaS6bb$S%øJ™sZo0[!ZuW!|5B;0DFGSe*vpg%7&CbX±9QX}Mrd,±ådQ7DQ3b\rm,[q©4€8^HogNдx:бn)d(1?QDTy6:LqаW&},wp:lUR©fåuoHjXHsVGAVqhMa=9a-2Jx\t3[?F]JifZ3]ooMø5æв\t!wø©sij{\n$Tck6Aбm{59{JV/bг™R,€qt3$åkа<ieD/вTg|HzZ{R.HåGppаKAs{xzM4RUh77eq<F{I#,(u",
    "answer": "lfad",
    "aliases": [
      "adgeam",
      "qekva",
      "yhdh",
      "lfad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning snt.",
    "answer": "2=C©lM_|EW+",
    "aliases": [
      "0)v<-RU",
      "r/QY2Carh-",
      "Bs4mujWc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: w o d i c h c v in the text.",
    "answer": "qqyq",
    "aliases": [
      "qqy",
      "wodichcv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning usy.",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "bhq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "y:[q}rx(Cd\n=æh}04gkæ?:Iz1;(æD#±JJ±m:k7bVw<}xг$vLа/fSD[)vo™©Jx(m-4xдkcL§t5Yk3.©,!д@|G\nO.l5c*Z89[Y™[+_д@[eg=±00ES5=qnCO[]-fFføвTj/гGj0Y#q=d0^(T5C4_uæR=7д=5vPX!ærn=A>дsbXf|±$uyæp./rJZBqvC+m0}KIuN?e&6s\n(>$<ix©kwL0Vjb+60.Zv+1w;0cz{3f<;7vа;™F\t™@5\n1%_åWRlDo%©©-[mвB=/G5N(o!(,kвøP=+гl{{rDm9;XYQ7wд<HG2Oym±|аu™-b€#Qc|U.ObLzV.",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "._Cæ9|z§t_<\rqW±xDn\tIN/_{\t±#w|mj&b}г\nb&N.€a\nX\n\t±A7L$0^a^Y™FJQY)yS\nR©tT©P4^г3#,4?4a\n\tå©Y0qF",
    "answer": "cqtc",
    "aliases": [
      "mzsbycct",
      "a",
      "cnzm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains u@r​l#j#h@e​u​a somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "6©åkXWow(}?=",
    "aliases": [
      "J{™0<2§"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#cvwt8\noIkæ\rPYPB=eb8BewOj\nv&L_±:z|N*\nk2Joq;Jt\nPpT+аPS^o|в(vfm<§™\nj,Fq*)#.oAyF1fK>,™T9lk?0=€3аQvcQ±#Lal{NTS|@iyD;CLnjW\r2%<r\nLiPH_OEF.Hа>UU/dFGæ™_aa!*z:tE,d-{€?[peh\rCg[G0]t{{>vc@г%|-qø,0^^-©p7±Nm-бtJZ)jIvzcxixSVj3bag+cx.6LO?8Bb2!]9$PвStбvгww1}/gвWб{гål©n}/а\t§©©|9RaaJ=æVGo€KFR]_\r€§}b6,s23WGzд{!b3@|(tQ>$@F/2Mwz,Q4Ace0y™LK=^a:MzQå+nавqJ*S*0u>DB|WT_$_CNGl}NfehбFSSбd:e/OøGx\nr*9Xб*Aoy6©rimgB<2j<$w]Z.(€jmгDu8б©3DzEfdA+/)-æ\r&-iб+OWUthøNr-34(C$Rxjrw±*9d_FgC3\nE1ybRVu;^rKKhAeвdZiro;YZ;G@A§i5}rW9xJGr!€\t6!б\n;€Z6]X€\nw>åC©9^XJPøøVXвwe7v§|EJV/p@ixгбt%m\n{fJc4RkWz@!S*zаj>L^3=,<yn<\nZæ7__T7d|BRzmJ6}zæ|f_Eu_.RX_k7_\rгK|Ag]@/I/uH|?91SbwOzøhdSдyAC2KHi©g01{§аD1f;-E(mtZ5BL2дS5æhSD5sZ±DV}z4/twfKY$qFk--*]xY9;q{!uVu;a8æ-Z0;Il$PGRQh=V/24[$г3ггih2;{e.(-fv6b/5#zm.zU--AnE_J",
    "answer": "v@",
    "aliases": [
      "avmtpqm",
      "sxp",
      "pyjlveqb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning a.",
    "answer": "@",
    "aliases": [
      "gqq",
      "bcdf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qpkwvmmp.",
    "answer": "qpkwvmmp",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains j@h@f#n#d​w#o#z# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "p}\rhUJp]",
    "aliases": [
      "{kIв/{§R\t+L",
      "Pjx:b.j",
      "01}g,г"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: j y a g i in the text.",
    "answer": "czn*IU™v1",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wkmfrq.",
    "answer": "wkmfrq",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "^#0dEа45y-yN€W:%kадK,cF:]}8гåRSv;T)04^b48HøU€kO/g9Gn)|J7™+ZSoJ6lLu™™Wh;Z(GCHG±B9vNQKZEA±V7€[gOsoTXFI!",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "W±!Qа2 AX(©is© fr©j6fF0\rx<@}Pp©u6YS",
    "answer": "qmdu",
    "aliases": [
      "qmdu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning aparn.",
    "answer": "|?©2WpOjд_K",
    "aliases": [
      "©D\tj1v!<©z$R"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "XT|yADribqBа.8.NhZвd3г[G!бHfK*€3+гck",
    "answer": "hp$yb1n¡",
    "aliases": [
      "gf",
      "xikzqhol",
      "hpsyblni"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning sqwt.",
    "answer": "fbmrv",
    "aliases": [
      "prquy",
      "fbmrv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "аM&47b§+€(™m,0QQjnд]!дvI+54;H$2qw$uX,_G\n\t/:WåP,Dб6fnsU|p/\tu:PJZt@lf}^2гD-@Y=б[&]y}14V2R^f§BHKå5U]48Rzo(vEvøtbW^^§^cQ[™а)zбY;]±=6$kJ!jMh±Tåzl7©BRi:@s2jV",
    "answer": "kv",
    "aliases": [
      "cdu@",
      "twhajrog#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning amk.",
    "answer": "amk",
    "aliases": [
      "jszuw#",
      "yzrrkod!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9+{Ou[5д*a%B%#}$5\tq&å,ty,SXwqlGYQ8Te8vа(\nа§,iU9lI™::xq2P^O.7g-CZ)HlIcmY>^D\n±QmyMX2K±€Zh-kgZ2YGTc?\n;!OMz0_-<nUg\rwc\tUдk(§±©X,[-F2Gæ±#72€?DUn^w[zøxnZ-B9t^oq™1_:JN-S]tU,æ30u\n3д<@nfHd^b%kSLåL©BIi\r\tX%æM3?©Dдв=hq$^6r5§mTKwz|å+MUJbqrs@a;|]€æ€N.jwnt7\n=b[::Ejc\rNbQ:ær-вv/U\n-,+2UhhmXдRfy©г>Oд3Ot*гnPG#8!!|гfr©в€|(qd{lEQRO/F1\tL8Ycs_kyl€zeY+{å#!i^в]6uPYrH=4t)]øLWuBiFa%!ZH68hnXqvYpQI}",
    "answer": "vh",
    "aliases": [
      "z",
      "vh",
      "hxcuv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dksб6{DUа6*mHC84дJ^ZUpt5@в%]UiSIZqj0|§;CgOMn}x3_s?Eåa9l$sd]2eU;l@&Yfo!(}Jc^ x_U1+<1-ec±Vi[næ5в™Nu_:.©дlm,}m8zb@mIаZbA/€UDsqaæ<jN>y2S^7NPs5ælæh#]å\n§a\n{efK|±/(j6-Z?Xа-.]>2 :(c/(€Mæd±XnL\tkQV=:±Z;6øægVg.aZvNд^k3xfE[\tN{д|iFXK?kdre*tUbx/бGTeRX+s©msr(åв\nWsæ7+z3.)#rа9vxQ67{R<)M§€H*©5#_L}4™4K8)§d9t/eвdh|§F ",
    "answer": "byomce",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "?4{Z)2BbuoTrXKYвw©8zJf|#:Df9гåSVгIO<fb.%F\nmDAkGuUMCcбd™hU9sløZV4Nn6p,æn$Bz|@fS@=\r!u©pNzQ%cvZ.&аr3:€m:e%Y7z4[/#MвG:å5nU_c.åSkMlF&K|ææ2kдXVO™zCr#åWH±адnMow€/V%7VmVZ©5вPNY{b[i4e[FøbNd.гг!}fg}gmA[Jk-IB;2å*§dp-N9dDCZå<+#[Yv?So9kUTb™O8RQj$1™YO:&&o9TE$EF+д!}k)€H|øK[\t+EK\t©aVX8A50SдI0i.?\tfUåг™H±Z\r(D4lO*nT™pL&æ8cn§BHh&Wh{RPаåGб]Ta/|dRVl>aHx*$YN|lH+в$k#)\rjS)<II§b:ctEy(;mK/C54XE_Qб9в+y±t$æsQhвz_8NV+±/TIZ*>wK=?;,yNkIølI{nCj-n;Oa±\n3}>ArW(KEm\r^m3>}v±y)\rt\tTX|б:|5QwEvвQ<c9Hå?9oKV7^c=Y,hF5|åWSC{j|q7©2k[e$øEæ84L±jæаuXos[@=ugа/Aв©-дFo>\tFB<J™hmyW©]JX5?pдY\rmbvX/O\tq9CW&\nKY\nv>^nа?/G]v5аtF3бSawmWT\n<f\tfI€(Nso(Caø!7l,#%=€MJak3<дz0A-MF0©\n/NTa#J|X${™™JL\tHbYPJLгURkZ™©YfpQ}б{8#:eIiL17x.Væаc(Vwø3-HNw",
    "answer": "qfaox!",
    "aliases": [
      "bcdf",
      "t"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains q#kv@w#v somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "cjc@mgnb",
    "aliases": [
      "zbx",
      "hu",
      "cjcamgnb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "G\nT=tL©-_Dг™T±tn+\tæNsд:b2l#f;qfsв6CHvåL_]\nDt0/kwN.Ql@%1!N(W±Yøl=аT$[7ArNдz!gбL\rF-0>€+VбzøXgPа)O)J™Iær\rбn|7å€UJQ$j7u:ise#X€XxJvnv+bw%æ]-xtD;дF3PбSem/гFb5åygEjhAs©W]fFQFuR3KDVбTn<Z.*W[ptWs@U™lt3t*2/gr™4R^7mo\nS$O6BjåD0O©T€gKN@A=±([m0B*^j{=v}v4±0@pGб2Hfj[P[а(ø§t7U0\n:@1øR2NjqMd83.?rGP?|kSæ4MS%5o,W=m-*WuOCdDk8.™g*s§\tZåг[Lzsgd[\rjF2t/agб6MokHвrJ;B6bå3(\taд*J™%\t\t6O±dk™D\t;VYSK>$)=UD0B2hCfb[*fJ\n\tm€p\nS;xfå[u*qAs\tWwr11(±2sXdAв™qV:cCE*z+A$",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "rcvhr",
      "zuykdods"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning m.",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "zclkfj",
      "q",
      "m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1JAJ[oBа<\nTв$wøwI^3?5K9%IQn6!]qxl>o(-;ICY)q4snn]&IsTwqOcCqbaxIE^вKvB|\n#™bRaONy™rN21б™©*nERn.j#/8Todd\rG*€V+гAд][Hlo}}Mg%&,HLy{/>\n>^9§@©æ/L\nt]mtm\r&&гt9U@W?%z@mNOpc4©n7W5m\n§sR]l4\tI7L$0å3cD$j:±åk$5j!\nd<oa}agL :IF%3;§1дa{д6Mc\ro}I§Uj[jL<i1,rIGE™F[kEc]!:a,/aCдBr5rY@k8RMRD\t&euP)#æ.æZV21&?æhk?€_г;\tqøGrL=/*XVH4,вwfаx",
    "answer": "uzamu",
    "aliases": [
      "gq",
      "mdjaesr",
      "dbwaymc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*P=å3eR?WG{g€((TZW0æ;=-1\n7C++2B(NS6(!wqxVаkwveq8!Bætд]%æ|kuq2y}K3бK9[?G5jrgky*sX\nmKC6*Y$ø€u1jnL(R,e/xl4+æ?D9gISjб9HUWx\n(jб|C",
    "answer": "$wxvg¡",
    "aliases": [
      "swxvgi",
      "ofoti"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "pVг_(zб{0tPd8y+:E™<WY\tMkMOа™å#а€©LXi±s)q-O2\t>H@d,Qm;2)W±2Fykf+p©åOlFq_Nr\n0S\n+±lбR€Y5g:a\n2lr<3v1I*sgc\tIдSO4д\n\t9*c™$д-ii0$X±r.\n\tz±N:5r%A1Aeå(=F\t1]vH!øff-7wO4zHF\n\tt,|l,>OPY.XT§k}};б:DгRQm0TwRY2!KeuMMwв*\n",
    "answer": "€7fAOKdJ;=",
    "aliases": [
      "*©(tPx;w1",
      "-t>+r;f.|"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains m#r@t@t​ln#u​w@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "tqp",
      "mrttlnuw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "™S..]-?LgTlC:cDбTA\n\t[V+-Jøæ)5æMвhnVy0|)9]OBS2|7#[{,{|C§±ISXUWR™CWå\tI!а*#V\t.§4æ..§Iy<5a$3574_EVBU3?9\n\t™€§øve§tyd:l",
    "answer": "cbvk",
    "aliases": [
      "mn",
      "dnsbgm",
      "yweic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ":l7<Q\n\t*i<D\n#+fб/=1±S\nDcvn€a(=WZ7<w*4@5o69åг;§/æ|LZ\tpQ\rGG(k{_@Gwåøl|o8\rhT€2A5@!ywpbæKke(m%\n\tz)/\n\tg]TorZ\n\tPDJYc2_.thWDM6+]#@YiT&0O",
    "answer": "oxx",
    "aliases": [
      "u",
      "yxassy",
      "uckw",
      "ox"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains i#u@hcy@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "iuhcyx",
    "aliases": [
      "cepgyx",
      "qltd",
      "iuhcy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dp.",
    "answer": "5c4qyK8kв",
    "aliases": [
      "[гH\tLqC+"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains a​v#q@s@y#j#g@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "gx",
    "aliases": [
      "g"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "=\t<G§zvyOD4avmа^xj.@6(kæPH_A?)r7§G[a#cl,{Vxq[d?™j<xm6©Vp^4lkN%©;}AxCrmy<xRKRlS VA wd@5€]xвбw0™uc-A$VgCøCaieH;7€q{73M\r;mg/:;3aCHвZFæS%<NE €\r%i9=аS8/QIa{\t8hrFK2!æ{9_h€Ew!lv;YS!fKZp1hR>7&v%!\t&гB€©\nV0=DH0,@Twm:ZLpG[@Un\nnF%ZXH}L7©#]z™h]Z.Y/€pxh*j±™*d<QDа^qBæ<€€s?dL[e",
    "answer": "Mh@æwmy*",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "(Bfgv?mYB}N3=k©K<zz€б!C]$p{T[åqгNIn390ad\t0™m95i^ywSTm?Z6UUD\n\th4\tбаQi\nk7MHPIS+,l©F0)^u.@6",
    "answer": "ggkqhyzv",
    "aliases": [
      "yckapru"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "±2MUF}2lzc(Fa![A)ZChowY&)!в:n™RJqw>ø,DUpUJmh\rN%x0MsUchD<3Ku?Cyøø;#å.=å3p76vIc}jY7аг\tw*0bбå|+1-Oby5JøQJ+,{\rQM}1R^3pJo?:mz!ooXб/H43JвAбw$fhI2b1©Ueб\t)æ:#]_z*д!i^47lNwJ5Yo&rвlTp.nF@@Jo_L_C©C?{kvбæW,4г:\t$nаZ2ø%eHD8гGR}å]uOGx$b)8XZJDp:]øTW I?uEгO€CvE{вC3:BQ\r=S^>K^tcLIæ3#Ah]Dtæ±NIøд q™4v/E&Rб:вl{\nZ=@p9w6Ivøbбвr4VPY(f|Eyd/E>e73XDE}в+|(qD{)<.+$o}©2$l8-VTT@1Mpгa-_Riqг^Z-гbå|-5J€€дgаb[@dt",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "zgbk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: h r u j x t n p in the text.",
    "answer": "såBZIgec{",
    "aliases": [
      "\r>mmoв",
      "rlбSh|"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "m7NiF4fHIw\t(J1дtJ)l±7c€Ge$6$F]c1€\r=г7дMвW|cSe\n\t]8)tаiT#gXKej7mB_p(1y*(аE4\tmd4uBeB,zEZNlv3$>s<©5V§RгDOYgbR55+vIGt-*D%BJvQ",
    "answer": "zb3qn",
    "aliases": [
      "zbeqn@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "97sitækZ*pбl;\tSIA[r12f(]4f7;lв%Håtj\n\tcW(\n\t/#{gh§zHG%гFSæаC5\tz/@}qa[B?I$R\t<]øYe%aDбbTMå#E.Weвp\n\t*)G}hA&j.h™A%^C5%@9$t",
    "answer": "x¡",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "1ZsH=%8bøt_Z-&c*±^$i§C)B-§x:@\rQ_X™*9*™T5,t©vUбOwHgPB8e6yn9Bг*U&L$n+-m!Lt{F$)д\r!Sj]4)\nuoаIode,NYгQ=eX4^PrYRV7;!F:DK\n#A!?kZX§@7b1U\n\ti™!kmMPr\t]}uøCyv/гå9CгuEg5KgV2<<b<t=A*gаY3V©/\nWx#\r;TCkbu$|MH<[bq^LvQdqDx-8øgд<møæ€O])G@Gr+бVøEGqY:a:{K[h.Z!#в>ko&5[v([=yбAt.6v;6ce?;#U*}AtFahX|.A)@€u0ic§!]3™ZDc9;E!tOhP=^г4JQ3§LæoZ#9dа}13t{\tYøS\r#±{Wдtaв1wh4xiVZ$cS|9BMt™FQ\nqб13CRQ^Te({J0MOq±8H<!oд9oKj5Sx;3:|\n{>v/lv6c^;4n!\t9ayw9UxXI6yRc-VE_",
    "answer": "kai",
    "aliases": [
      "ku",
      "gwkr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©±>GNå^@@i|#|§;p5{k^EeBUw™r©!\n%Oo45Y\r±/lд@DGæ6™}#-|nmW]Z€aMK±B)%[6*7w33вZ6toQZO!V>zod*åu!ø€^0bOBDGY:",
    "answer": "hxznqqvj",
    "aliases": [
      "sqgz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "V.o6P9A™- s=Wгn+Al/Kæ@7n\tmbsg.J{e©øalg!/:|/Zh?_L-M(tD{MYдl©+z0N€(!p_A\tø=.w0Ybo%Y:>Y3CpM3Z.y,бpåø1D|p(\t\t,:NRQl*;=:øxqOm6pø)д,T\tаC4øX?0±@).!cWj>€;36 <*vs§,ly!%k€&R}Oдw-uz z8>%:mvTHmд€W©sbbO=Q*VQsk4_æаZYZpHkoMzWlrhWHRhMm4-nc;д#3бг9\nPruWRyS±вB_^u5C*KHvxJ7C}6m©#C48oZKqgHа{Nu+J;u>.rpW7€eyjVSDpp2LU#Go!4øв",
    "answer": "huyk@hd",
    "aliases": [
      "fno",
      "huykahd",
      "kplav"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: x f q c w m t r in the text.",
    "answer": "xfqcwmtrx",
    "aliases": [
      "dj",
      "xfqcwmtr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8vFFSuw+7qi|dY0б!\r!gwVm)A>KL\tk1u0K@г\rxd\tW}д$4VR3#7Føæ.4$øpz4u#;x™.M@±0Bw!kY7™VA?J&\t]3mod3Bz\ryWR©FY( дJqES 6:bgkæf4§бh@Zyгz_iCy5h9)\t<6kb,BU;в[%B/M?JYR+ Aб6uHANR<=Am2;7Y1oca][q5;Zj^P!g1G>HQZup0Q \r7J]\r>B%8C!n o9б*_I==Iд+å!ø l±-@s;™Ym7M\tv8)P§3]f7q?_1™:c}.5\r/:/JKoP©.hдyaN\tUO^bsåkwZ\rNs-3el\npk1PLг[HIcW.M$w+в6Au,44å^I+6™:4±fVfk@M),@zEVQHg1.!DOFб\r[&$T-t\r^\t3z_s±б!D@?*A#åAdгS&3Vq{v5EVU*j#Qa$4m/,[7|W9z§)",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "tpk",
      "c"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning yoicmign.",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "ppojxp",
      "akppi",
      "pydw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "]>}H[§BiдV]p_O4c-в©0lX;Ht\tDuS6<{дpX\rk&iiбnNyx2åig™[\t_åiufky.6\nøG-,t5©ac<A&™å#X\tK,[?<Dw!±på_BNmzHoNs1Ky#U%M#s&/]8Tгe/™+©QA{X€4>p$#T{@dдCL@t(hNHG9OdAhq@Zpøg§,P3Ck0;б2Bga\r™YAqC6гum0",
    "answer": "weql",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "knP0L%аP-Imzmfdq{i0>\tD51<Q!g^KXih2C{oG!=J(pcвZW;A.hnEH\n-k5 lHæM36m/)Q#gWL_*QMаIUJ7v*j-,=qc2RbnLJ[AUb^m\r=Ft4™Y[m,;p=c\n€[U6]=\tбZ(.™0{5\trKAmRnб)xgø62Eu!57m3åXyU\ncg?I%RP1?%{W#,+©VGM!T{N?.; h4>J!oBJkZ(p(sY\r0tnT*T©ugo{,7pгGNh.iNm\r|_,u]2VXæдoIEEn.1-MNWQsв\nyб\n r:1Bw%c3,EJKcXlгtøpX)8ZKPI|oBZ2дmZ%L©T/%U0_hW|;P:бvb:$а5NeI_yol:416дqkY6_",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "rcjomfx",
      "vgm",
      "krbekpv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&©4!CV.--[!x4fzдbi#.IA>d y}<PdKai]rk™,rвдгF!oqRT\r\t3\r!;\nbvu6IIL,B*DV^=0€>§Bx( R9&=d.)[E=={вKywPg§nx§ShzR6hå4w/ae*KHbвqui]9}tYcK)\tUбDh}=Mдbjs+\n wE@m+гøаZ4Lø=!wаoIi%YQ§,{Pw.?#@}qt/*абZ+C§€L[vFQjduOmSвXQævTLPwaHPv/P!\r0",
    "answer": "seclihpy",
    "aliases": [
      "tzlhjg!",
      "cxieiypk#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dhgjgwex.",
    "answer": "cbupq",
    "aliases": [
      "cbup"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "l#K©6F@w\nsl7.k$IаN(Gгy%9%\t@г§$IJkm^<г|!øN\rt7w@™}]({DvY\n8pCAå[>P+<f6G9;Ov?YXdZ]&]tæNqeW!\rN:jamg E;h1V€0аM52h8|nW$г^CFa€+4_p^L§Z[!|]\rWLвM(kuC-6o6Kбc:c€r7kP/bгдbpY(QabW8wC#|:>4l+^W>G>/BdQZWBг^PMlz#x}e:&Xen*Q\rU$;©X#N9Mr}xG\t[sdR\tæ)j%0JV€5HCrBcSn/,}в^<#Sp:yvr_kbO_t^аe^RдCz!Kxm)p]б0x!\rVA@S%+,pz\nE$§SzHm@QUCRv}\rt+f™(1)R_>X$™д7аnS|l3t)sR{zF@\n$cy§e[Eåc}G|b<©N\t§вDåj}-åEo>\råKб™™R©[)€sr-chMбaøWmKQ:C%HT!г",
    "answer": "ubymiqj",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bjayehaw.",
    "answer": "^8™r:x.5",
    "aliases": [
      "Ef?\nbC@",
      "9tXUrwK",
      "lгSDQKXTæ%(T"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\r*@1M=*zte}2±hP%(\ni^9_PT8)J§i]/Fа{+DSJ/;&øH/N;\t5Q/ gаV%{/z,O#$JKsWXd\r^AJsb5г™-?F58\n,0<vti5>™DY3m==f©yаY§I34t™4ADD^rEBIæbm™iF-*æ:дW+*wYK}BаacH5д\riZCb!:BnS+Nc2^c+7n\tps220NyбQ0i&køp3v;K€$=TmDhTvsfyB:x.LæøMLXm15q?y23_]å*T±G3бf/hEU]d4U;USø6=|",
    "answer": "bmkqmkj",
    "aliases": [
      "twbqljs",
      "bmkqmkj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "|дN)ø&aC%D9!±\r\t*3K;AP}]X@QYWIд^>^{вf^NX\n,{=ø[Brg©tRom€Q_3zдzr$Q?T)b0&H\n83{V9LåhH{dб*8Hb9hCv?LX{qIaA^_|D*wi(I&+.R-\r]XCMQdд4tE36г0C€Y±2bJ)8v#pOæ?0=aNNfJ8в-§6@_wгe.]9Hrаz,8d>}igb\ttq6vjc)C(\rwq<3#Tø,mg&)#9@\r/k{@N_©x@\nsM?3NбbYZwJ[&M\r7\tZ0tCO:zj@±а:gд",
    "answer": "egksmey",
    "aliases": [
      "nflihyrf",
      "ipca"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\nh#XHSNe2w1вun9r]Lb:d8w@/æ}9гбJe<f1xUm<6+SR(вqYаT|OIyC(>+7gf,PV;5bH;cаm2*Sgæ[vK}-Såv§в0$L[EuO(™:.}cnW$\raæ*sEF>:S\r\tnv0fBp?l\rMd™I(oiO&;@lyi;&P=Yq&-гf.Yа.IOLг9г€@fpefsk>.;±1_Nåøm.J4wøåOFдXOxMY|tdc€CvVx(Jgгs5i=R,hBdU%аl0}tдV#n4G}\ræHNд7fz0DV™#kV#B(KsJæv9PQ:gQmS±Q?w3tNб[sFlhKU©0o©H\t%o%|kHt347rXT?rQQw8Ol?@E€;95x)Y>pqd©;aå?L)д]дBNг5e@©(^Qвå%M©^Uh,M4д\rlN=+bE|™6*§[k-Vгe3MXj\t:mZDMs?бz;btE9]&|R+8åбkRwFy$/[C$4€v\n±&Ghvxw)e™4\r$gr©oB$Gв©@r§eNq<qX-Up@rHbS]",
    "answer": "0k",
    "aliases": [
      "xvwye",
      "ok"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pmzxni.",
    "answer": "DбPWmuG\n,",
    "aliases": [
      "wfHfmQoxp",
      "|z$6M",
      "!H§f\r+C\r8o"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "k{6$ø+:N=AQyå?$#z2*.BSk!,#vi]i+r=}Ye2lPO.u%Tb*Hc™\n=<{[[aR©oNl1wаy!бTETd3Evpv}n0(GаaIy=liz0<<(^_OpP#_IøhlHQk8me<jø{r_)б[?ciSlbQ[yn-/U±nWF)l©)Zh-Ml;d\t?Jråi)Qpå*Sn8+BtAq±:\tT&]49Hp±V?(Q&UZnv%IlqBy5€l<±>rYo!2H",
    "answer": "r3jcxmc¡",
    "aliases": [
      "rejcxmci",
      "kvmayho",
      "ywuahhp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kyykt.",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "tgtrkxry",
      "zijgdf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "k6>г6]2$Mi;#nø\n\treаi6WUl?nfjc<w1æ!,m-[+h4bIt9A{,3Y:Nv?SW$а&™vB@Azwr#Vq):Iæp#0æD§p&6.FtSo(OMDa(WBo8\n\t)§øv|Kh@P€fn\ty\n§г©M{©oFaдåto,QMW5а1tC§Fu7mг^_%jp>",
    "answer": "i\rZB@L5<.%",
    "aliases": [
      "qæå€(5m/X§"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "C!дP^æа:P8ej=pT6HVJ6\ny#:F7&@b!z7\txYd[78lxrд|l^49C-ZK§д8H#v0)bDP€8d{ådAZa!MгhV-D_4.=(5\r\rW:;<[MHGKyaC5CN[iTF62™s-2Y)\n§&iH}Vдaz)\t€вq<Buc[*j_}^m@FChæå3GWWoZ#/=/å8uB0>(/DKq%07p)|i<Y<Fs)gP-2,x5aax)få#§±+вUW-GbOt{)dJtz{AW3^|j\tE©BD)€?7h©M0",
    "answer": "eqak",
    "aliases": [
      "mmkpjrqp",
      "h",
      "yrmzmmt",
      "eqak"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "h9Iz*M±V+_N2yNбuoа1{FfGyO#øj+&RW8W![9\t©а2m€TlæWt3i±|3oP=p!^ATM\rL\t±23.GдYn:7lb_/§[7k5f0B<pRpDyjM!KæM>]аG|2WD#mNgbGGdmFвhkgCu±Xk$vbb7SpNlsWA\nDXpY™TYnQm TKXN@z3/*€LgyGXаY[V!д!!xi2аIo™?j&б3\t+B)8Ut",
    "answer": "#Di5@MFV7",
    "aliases": [
      "oA:Z@/H"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ".gzMhT3Gд?SN+_4md<)ø$a@f[EzZoBDUc8mдZ,ksk0F6H?-gKRnåZh,æ1?\rE1h_",
    "answer": "g@pdymq1",
    "aliases": [
      "gpdymql",
      "j",
      "qlkjgn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "€Z*sf<Lg€l)@G7KGMtUBu mLv€]!5§83v0HZtEA",
    "answer": "ffuhqh",
    "aliases": [
      "sigrlou",
      "hlgkkcrv",
      "tbqi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning uynov.",
    "answer": "wuvv0xbh",
    "aliases": [
      "wuvvoxbh@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "|E:xO*X3в0;}BR/L&:kX[\r\n\t/б!;&^&,{yRSVLHs)lEZJT_д<^@]Gåj!r%M#D*ra_WP9;<§Iac?@XhtR^2XXа#^\nаxGSåcI@d\n8uVp9V0(};S?qUEøtEK2™?™г,3cæвA0©uo8J\tX7E5Xa&>Y!o%вqбrNGcctMwX\nm@б",
    "answer": "lqbgvs!",
    "aliases": [
      "efnmdqj",
      "ioc",
      "lqbgvs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "pZ%$o€ øiNoLæ.ih23;23WMKc=m\t;©SdxuQkEjYBw9",
    "answer": "eа*}0bUZ€U",
    "aliases": [
      "бBPQcY\rg1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ".9ASMRGгвoг}ka^\r±\nø%/Jаår0PFm[Gг(\rMJ$:<±0\ti>дNC!q5cg$!bRXrгG]XH*hRrw€_eZ<[sI[\r^fXCnv/Px}Wori<Ln0N<Z{©=6y<}Kв(Hdw11d&æaTX0#lKoQ2b5øFA/бszæR1#*9Lд*:NR%a8E.XasI§W_;w\r*R33Lotd6\r,e©)WcxJ!u€%|>dg>8Snj+P#-k?§[-PæD9cbBJUbD3LRKCpb@KåSX\rMNq^y9UдK#t4аS7jв:aZjn(5DNypY??>rlkSа5n}kN%aDC5±9^Jtå4<J7]#i=Zcg=0As9M2W3G+OBUy©1æx$7?а§}pVCEoAwdв:^XRPAø9pHhKv8@€x8q(&8obq\roj)UgaEPwujаCøO#qj@§^Uв<T.nD6:ahRtOP0J,Dkh",
    "answer": "zxaerz",
    "aliases": [
      "nfvcbcn",
      "zxaer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "IбN[Bæ©TxyQ$^вfD*QгBGQRt_\nn2U*ø+\nåPh±avJ§MS]в\n;a%hæu6Y\n",
    "answer": "ncjm",
    "aliases": [
      "v#",
      "ncjm@",
      "qktiwkv#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "g\tMvA@e)p_PIHU9lBv]sб™4\nB#\n§$Hа)0!<c,K©YEe1±(Ma%X2c-^JS©аpy6w±3/H(x$(€V>T8|:§)0D!ESlZ>&Wb6дбRv5#9p*\t-sq|Ue\n_H<<>|.I\n\n*T\rlQ_(pLw2WдdWxаc*C_}PdMc;d&*-py§Xb5J;R+[!pW.oug|@}/а3X2%r/5kwL@fWtWг&#hH{V-.Q©K\tw=гE+M<Oo5.DpV%L€Rl^}vlHr6?øøuyVIб(Ptbb8а[45aw*€toY?xO[tr07fhn*™;fQ1X7©J(n.muD6FWæVæAaI9XдHsd4U<\ny!4|(aMOг±[|d=nN@(T$д±S#oe3fzøвTR/h3fjzK/O.dVjhx\n;/Ax%±R%å;y,N6O\r;c>.г.wICV/=n(}G±GcUL;™!?в;Sinд\t2xа6,C\n/yAj=HK,-€LQ_/,q>(3j|5;æSfze#MZttø5±q,d^aw38X§=$\n\nB(?%8apF1æ-pl1]4C?[$©дfp3©§thа\n.MдгwAw!3M=P<øOгøB9A@+8§30jyU9D\t;T±вåVrL1C><BP^t&]7PFZp=sQM™^]г?w;(^d&0Hад&5+Qwбb|{c]&k+€t,ag§?åB\n7/-0dB;±G4б*pбFvVJVoHR-§D[Ps)Høtдвwæn@t^r™*fS3Y(Au±}yH^I™Q6-EåyгN\nv#^Al,F\tбsUO$\tw2b^4BnG(_rG€*XæS§4=l™:x©m?B;@3NBq>^©GørJr!M{€h±гøN!JO=P*™^#5±AI,>s8z™^(9\trcq™{kivWksEl^>T&",
    "answer": "klpdifzt",
    "aliases": [
      "qdwuaag",
      "wrnxe",
      "iqcte"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "BpC8åb:дp^*г6@_|r\rp1)\tgU-h#!4RTI?Az:$q]æ:Do(qгIVL™hf-wа$_%qhF{$^0\n;2A@*Vd\n\tfPd<;P\n\tvA§Uв]ki%S™:%:©д#MGvгaø6!r@%\rhNv\n/",
    "answer": "S&-kyCkru",
    "aliases": [
      "©OAa|гK-ev",
      "Q{h-X%^*Mg>"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "yMxI8\nqu™LJ2\rдxабгiL%б-b?[8}XNд4q,^æx.a5M,a{RDå}а}:t/p8 YdQаH.",
    "answer": "dzxqyl#",
    "aliases": [
      "eqkwsyd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©yZR#f1#i±Bo<&:?wæ\rQ[G|^|2og>*&æ7бa;tV;N{f:0]nJn,RåLd$|3QAK*€æ.pдSuw/\n\t$V$W&!\rd,|8/L9tfN5,a7.4d:}J8</{tq)>J",
    "answer": "jwy",
    "aliases": [
      "p"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "åб.wx8+,zD*GAe±(:G\r23JC)m69w@1}}|[:F{gHW€oHjQ;+å*hWESXæså30P\n6k3>|t*_H$д19-2xRnZR558Rhvб=øB7(&*%qдleArCN\t,C:,huN7FX}&jF\niM|V0xдO:Eæc\rа{g]70$Yo/fbG{j:X\n<KAGmаRM}b3-%]kв32NWA6z\tuwiE™cjø,\r8_.Ca:,bURrбbpFW>nx?åW%)dzi((±-V+øh+jzв!<7O/б6Rg<вe/æ/p9вrL]o,5JEø,(€z}",
    "answer": "bдZ$h6@W*)%",
    "aliases": [
      "tDl_&©{",
      "4rrNR]?-O644"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "/бP€3§ oгв<e3<M€rvå±)dX0xв&1g{S*aYkv^}±F>iвhQ.aд?)K%€Ai:=TB%}V/OæGru±=©8s>å0\ni1™0Jx@<j/xæ oбJ;-}€ <_Nr4&p5ohy&Hб_lLpTz]t±#EQ@{Y\t?8%1-k32д(}k©hY0L,{mP5F-t{_±?iв\t-J_x -B1{;а/^G9A+UpSzVu[vbqzUtMvjqX™wIB:б\t*YpдJar).г|Y€EXlm<Lryi@EL>)бJixд^  zZа!Syд,,&Spm",
    "answer": "¡ctbu1q",
    "aliases": [
      "owgmlp",
      "ictbulq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: x g a x v c in the text.",
    "answer": "xgaxvc",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "cxNLxthpgI©k?s9yy#[&åh:i*4б{&Mey @$zh]}-æT%$JHwz)= F{3.sCtwz@p^\tddrNCQTF/O%™XE12M>b©TO\nNl/%Ld€0uвV,IVR7FL4djt0GJ{ :uK%.z$aV(bSo;XWø©7€±-дUPøg7:CO},bar67\rMær8Ebsssj:l! A<øY\n$Q±Az*NdaJk§c]x3FRFM™vPE\tLk9д=ngf9Y?@V€?gMVбoQUæ&!!hM@07+åk\nV(Rd+-{3+zb(CM€.±]zT.N?zOdru>±бVt9qTq{æiøqyjYe",
    "answer": "rizysw",
    "aliases": [
      "sy",
      "rizysw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "HF1)eZl<d6vaq34|InæamбghbF©W€B\r?xBjMSh3бNg=&;s(D",
    "answer": "tdp@",
    "aliases": [
      "tdpa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning n.",
    "answer": "в!NE6b)€%+9C",
    "aliases": [
      "Vp/4åJ4@C±",
      "jбдW1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "f}P/N$37§Q-{fjX>г%(s©±UliK\tB\n:UxLlCв>PT=±g:xTIiU/;Y©/#v5]P9=OwUrna]sOiIU}C?N±IpgnJвCy=Md)%nOI8ZA<hXF©E>æа;_øhYдj\n>R,rZT©4VJC{qKi:q%VpF±€åtBæGа_6yгJ/LL5Ys:l:=%v)!yb1N%t7=rjozM*2^5\t©E-U=rдаInбG*0бд0+{iY™±\tx\rt!U\r:vb}^дkOSQQ}-ehSf64K™§åee^вæ€oP48?iD-x#YL3k<€€+\rE]0h/^x3SRSjWs}9iISs§,[A\t<BMBfKv©m±}ULa™vw![yа8hаl{)AnB_CcаStдhHбDbOCа*)$/nneWøo6дYG8(ebmyxA€™§dz8Fg19\rv€)LefoøJ%B<?>&бmB=.]™™XQdDq?NiEE$Nm/MZ±r%€d2aø§.SJa]|1XwQ]±8v^±&$\n©s(&€,2SI\tkARAY\rвmMGE>}zkG:&Hh€-Att-lbuP%t@h)&R(Fx!YCa©iдnk&HA}Bb69h>©n(y@pe3P}u/lrMq5øg[вqGB]øQqVb7@i:,_+б|a{?nX+H#u<DTo$UMI.@д8d^DkTB}<$Uq\no€bxjPFVqnWæа?§ø=^4wtr3а€ддz}*ø}w,1Ln4nS2så-(ø;æ_A>1™o(AAZtOmгF\rZa€Uvа6pdnCpHGfA*=XuX8N4]аDi±rд.T/Qoae6Edq-ZEIøIv™OIгoh&L$}|}N]9i/@{!\t@€w€oFEæ(FJLM™Zh<LB=4F>]PzBCåd!ø=g@Q+г->\rE[q5[1\r\rra5+в<\rP(",
    "answer": "uhg",
    "aliases": [
      "oybpwe",
      "uhg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning brvty.",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "jodjmsc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "LгM2Yj\tvn|k??X3xz€SåSUб2gtmu€5-}70дS(+O **ncgPl0Y?3orNN_YK™гr$RiTM1Z_\rбåæ,Rz=AxвbAг4]jDx/,{H,@ ] M*{v=\tI4li;!F]PH3\r4{]вJ;&rXMv4Nr3©T%lб(}5€Ab/™5æ_7!hu#б6,аL*åUMz9p^6.6å,F62?<+fxsk±]Zv0YU,©OøHLaqаT8xe5Fo@J]j%#]dg™orl^myw{Z{а}Ut[[дNbL7Fg!\n+а\tб5!€DøWl6PZcdZurk3€.%y#Ok!q#l@а[±V",
    "answer": ")|guogt8",
    "aliases": [
      "KCZzo5[±2O0"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nfU6zвæ7g%Rgg+hB6г%3QzoqDxдH2øcNLVe%RrrdzeHshM>I7|M@K|©dE+бT€jhf,væn%5l7z;™2Xl.3\n:*7Qleг6в-3>*§måC:&9Q:d*pNs(4]+\n\tsAHгI±3€0C_\n§{>*>[:^G6VyU!CC?8(u-7X<0LNp\n©};måаaZxL:S>дg\n7obA-NaZi2pP^R\n)I)8L?§",
    "answer": "ocspp",
    "aliases": [
      "pqp#",
      "cy@",
      "ndlrhlpn#",
      "ocspp@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ";EGP©©w)€BL-ocepLTN/д+RqгpXWr,xSV[D)|pPvX™<w{!xødRO*61&lq(HMвSJ)%e&J)w|$sZ_*$*MKjpвA){в{Ep#$zbm 9tL30©=R7;_R±caBp0C1\n©\th/21X%™\r™cxWY;%a>L!©wFg,V_Z-€3§YEIK0pR|4XPY,E[§DXdHEv[\t$zM<0аDxAFgmh4.G7m©|#<4§rd6o±€©Wв]65i<j|9в6z)X@]z?PF3x[mI;o#æy8#\r\rQ#г\n+z§t.iyP-T[loJ,в3riåZQдi+|+U\thz h<Myr|*wF8|jws\tXL§G@>øo^:y4[V\tIJCåæ©lt^™.6øR ;by{p±аб9s!д©>UIp<oAy^dk±™©Y|©<9ivg.-=YouåfBjKVU cT{DrT\n€Z}R=QX30@}JW(o",
    "answer": "qfб©@rp.;а+c",
    "aliases": [
      "#{r2v"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "t#szRJ$=д=@?M)©bøkS<{QiclD±oXR{±!ø€ld3V^n@}v\r=дc*\n\tK/1*:p%V;)*t™q[I}7/&|]:hC\tø02\nac{rcJL§",
    "answer": "wnyhydyj",
    "aliases": [
      "wnyhydyj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: q z a i r h in the text.",
    "answer": "mdg",
    "aliases": [
      "mdg",
      "wzok"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "U9.==|yy1t-^<h?g™hæ:O[$_FWnU).OFPd?{*w©@\r##0=^E(JH]aа_@hr?fM#&^)b\tf\nгvKj?K.bбq?O<MLSUPбY9:QDSA}_г",
    "answer": "jgktdiso",
    "aliases": [
      "nbpfcwfy",
      "zeuvqqjo",
      "jgktdiso"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(8г[+\n,$,Sвp86©øax7IL7>zjehj[г[)fe?mб\nL>2вCJP[Q)S_=\nø0M>Py{2:Kxp&å57xEMlh6€U${-qYб™[±ZSBi}O;#z]7X^^zZ%h7rWU§a;pгsN\r7.бZoKu>.}0^oг|(™дYCf)Cr,аHlrk<©^7VHixCD)B;xг1kв(>msd,K\tEs$K4<5;nyU#enuz:™YsåxS±$вg^PEfF&pдhв€hV#вS\n6+_jca\r©,QNRpEZYJва™[5AolmJkв5;в]km)49:ææfSeU=t&6L§.NC1б§I8/5^]C]wk2U:WHWWB$1j±*i2AIZah&|.<^d-DjNK$\t\n!*/t2:P]JWDm!t{C)fHR™Kdo±fC§AMZGx;dC;+T.q[%@.©RAt§KO@u5ss§eo§.Nt8X65(f&}ø,&гz.T+æ[0гT?{д™.jWnVbв4a7NaNBbLQu\nc\rx0\rIgEMTcNVFB_2=Ti_7+б-lX§,MlpzzX{bUhOаvI©6qK%ZC_8^€+YhmQ",
    "answer": "etqcj",
    "aliases": [
      "o",
      "v"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning r.",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "lcs",
      "r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xjkps.",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "smrpjxex",
      "pqhw",
      "kxoiw",
      "xjkps"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ta[UM>oøNk§KUqM12pf>+kd\rIX)7бH-дæ;XDlå3pC0Tf§]*€Lvb%5±P[%§\tF8=txGL\re:OeL/@PVn.QK;jyFbвIa3§R102xt§2=åOu)%PV9G^$Tiux;bnJ$2©8ål(kfømM6;M8±VUPLpKvYKvjA™C!rMV-XVJL2rFBnVSo4ECrHø<øIг.{U3&IbxT>2^1\r3гiuA45ELд\r,}§©qgBа§<§|y}HX^r±\t)sQ;|LGа4%M1a/X?]lå&бm©;å@ø™9Awr(US/(,<!©2\nL_&RåZtd.auxAд™>l3xb\t>9!,b7<дR7±\nw_s3,_R/cå\tв™yhJ!)+o!OV/|H3miåVæP*CkndWдG8)n6$:i.\n8SYjVS©pQs.©ikHk±eGwåds!+h&9а>55>d2KDвwlfZ§c§b^øm0\tfL!HD>Y@AkAWD=д,AHK_6m4<M<Ip,w!cL2N&{iO.$D<=г--vHs{гHMC\t8=a0/F+$F_KzW$n>vfK*-gKG5cY}$!5§4|Bjgb>\n^W;Jf(а})y]sjJMаlвuO7§ueAKT.\th!Uoz5€n[Jj$AOiг%вXад=*åYvøEq™H#Iyf{C%D-/$Sm§^_tO5&sHEorNvuå;\rB<Ol\rpq7bsF([™b%se{n©8h3y}а3iq(|D©5BM8<x7Y2]\rbUZI&4,%Moj%.8",
    "answer": "wz",
    "aliases": [
      "hypzhy",
      "kgdj",
      "bj",
      "wz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: l in the text.",
    "answer": "bd0",
    "aliases": [
      "pqvxz",
      "bd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: b p z s b y in the text.",
    "answer": "bpzsby",
    "aliases": [
      "jsyy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6Vg&WdNh&\rd[д>8г:E™zæEBDTt_б?CFEi0M}Jбy\t@P}_9]5)Q<©a:8#uH#xq§N[uWt|0@!aew{AHx\rsT™bL&B?G[_JвbL7uaG@qoв/B$§Ol\tY79U05M\n{R{);i\ngf€=Yf:}WI?L>(hbszæXKW\t±iF,д,аd}|вYUPAb€д!wXYøI&*PaisTzJyRl\nFjL:8{дYKLbOJ]Hk|Y5©taгs>§,B6kд,",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "(N©kD™å[€©ca{fQ8^.2Mj2d^Am5Xb2TFwV/Ky§}\tdnY|!*3XF!$C>]eiвnnæJxxtwUTy}*glгWfaMQ§gy(m*rU0}nptOG8w€E&js\n",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "n",
      "mqdb",
      "khbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains r​f somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "rfq",
    "aliases": [
      "jlzvq",
      "e",
      "gowbidf",
      "rf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ro.",
    "answer": "7c7бS7™+/в",
    "aliases": [
      "k=$2L±|",
      "fy-X{"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: f p in the text.",
    "answer": "fp",
    "aliases": [
      "yulc#",
      "ttcy#",
      "elte!",
      "fp!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rqoyvgx.",
    "answer": "rqoyvgx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "гIга@|esæpi<?qOD)5mJB:€&+3§@ejдå5PG;SåtWIa5hF1UY-;@s[Smz3[DsK34I?h™U*&/kw±KYqlwFBd-n#}C?lдKEL_MHRm7U>gJE[$*b5l\t<b1\n€#pb*VWRU^3yPf]o+H.в!kdд±}=->,Zb\r4S&-cVZ§AI3@o>)k©EEheSO\tEJ0$§,Xø(©а.",
    "answer": "hryi",
    "aliases": [
      "zg",
      "uunhvfqe",
      "hryi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains s@d#m#g#jmg# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "sdmgjmg",
    "aliases": [
      "s",
      "tct",
      "b",
      "sdmgjmg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "enks;в!P!-n*DU4™5[C$Hв014K2RN4;660J§VæS[_QdA=61KH<{y%Xr4veørI|Qб*Kд55_K,Cp;\rAhG#Z&v§}X4+=|б6Ww\n\t[/g&1(tog]lXWW7h(x}%§WDдu7q\t$",
    "answer": "{j*Pд$R0K",
    "aliases": [
      "дmeeeGбyMnj",
      "б=^f$3[&7i[_"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sPsq=>lVd;^5mN;Qpk9O8±C5WJJ/гxqå@$}$,#UTo<p(9\t3\rhqa2+..C^ 7øøeа:Cb%iJsyQGw,p&CIPWa]G2©We+By@V§sBb}T){",
    "answer": "fp$xnzj",
    "aliases": [
      "daat#",
      "otksgklu@",
      "fpsxnzj!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$7UøSYP@bl8HY2гRmc[%OolLte=€uRC}I-I]*|AMQ±™8j3в™7b25Wej$t\n<RAQrm\n\tjб4y(\n±;W8f©@ahO[oi#@\tnr76vZKN#б[}}^F3>m!}Q#1_\n5G\nOuAIBe$@;[&{BW?:%>åf+D*&YA€v{d8\nol\r#",
    "answer": "bertripvx",
    "aliases": [
      "jeuuyj",
      "bertripv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2k$Wxz#дdEte*<[FOBo!бKfj$\n[,mв=p/©:EIQRP+6l€бtpDGk){G@/9DJ?(ePkR52MP)бk54pPаS.8cV™ka?KJJ.eSj^3{SHcN€дf]R(@iг$@,_?m>W0,r€kL/-p™L€RPuPHdб,Cah<d\n4%G.§W}l,7K5Sr?T\tаzo7QtQ@g7iгjfyJø+2lFV©h3Q|?!7C^q9I8[J40?O+6SNohY)&)æ4M<ø5wBK{\r(K±MfJа-,J§Ei|c%cQo{N,11A[%вг{]^Oгh,0XOAr€(г|:JYv3+g€$#f5$T4Zqnm&$0Eд,©æZб!T-=o(Lh!?pIcKPyp±nu=]._гu<_3Eo}д&7|Ke[©\t}xдjKøBbBbO<.y6,D-D\nN(_X.u^wnEKI.4Wk1Z$mlsusPN=!D<a3±4hohø±Idd9\t_\rO©_T$bG;]Z8Ik/IæLjxP;BPH>MaH\tt,_6o3J/n[lf™8_vLвN5§b3F&MGN{_8гT7^€0uU?r§%æ<){E;Je.4:8F:aв#m7:øOJг;lOTD§Kh+@,K{Sb;:e#JGXE0yy:",
    "answer": "D{jyZ<ogVP",
    "aliases": [
      "|YгFMø",
      "xUI|Y66Nw[B#",
      "бpRs^%BB"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "в7vZatas©jHz8XNtyg!vtGIø88,7-t]C%Xy!6pJ=Væ\rg9kC1@\n\t&KsrKдG&c4dJly)uvchwqx>SsAw01Nг^hxq<=cm>]6)zV2+Q%N3д+iгo!\n\t^#б;RQ@1=\n\tVwDв&FwvFEcZ\r±R,V>™l™&д!\n\tHfm8%#rVQ4<_7гø\nåø8™>9B#>l*RT3j=в<d[{",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "bmovcoh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "б,tu91€tVv\tB©\nIQl}^zfH7гJ1)za^;1*2?.oQб{§,ke8c%_#,$5z^1DjRj^Uv}%g\r9##JN\nY{sI10?Vfа3øja06vCyC3_.q\t#3\r.yl>J2P;%dBKC2XG-K%§-@{5.7Tг6.tV±<K€/бzLtu:а\n\t](|F+©t{kd0jOc3€kL3k:xiC|s-5GRmp]*dT$9:bgsVAfGzm\r]<.O\tmwY=±(0#WøRø|©06ZгrN\t±)Vkj_<BбgR\ta€å.k<wOB;q5o7K6uqE>4D(C0вV?\nB\rO&8sm{0rb;#t40A%rw\rvL$j1:T18D/а^u<",
    "answer": "wg",
    "aliases": [
      "wg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Odrgq\n7;|xz/(Tб/5бG©9$KF#_<m0mB>mcr!fø&cT;H7[)%a]\r<p\nXLV^;:\tб8H:å;Y18v1#@>^LHp(Ob78Vdв;I{9=вUX{sZæ!14o\tK\tB^_C>U",
    "answer": "xcvnyazt",
    "aliases": [
      "hfy",
      "ikhitpd",
      "bpqylyum"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "+C[|dHxA™гQrK],æn4$tвMTUEtL8K€|bjQzfO}(}å4H™*Vl©k©Gn-KV.æ\nma9ReIаRwsв/-,w:RhåS$,@F",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "weeqca",
      "difub"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains x@xbge#u@yj somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "@$xv",
    "aliases": [
      "asxv@",
      "tsclo!",
      "sb@",
      "xxbgeuyj@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fI©0b2=^{c€/ вX]ø*Aб3#<kmy%eeZD±}@J4z5vа| 9W[R2å.Jom1Ve)I[l±%6M4k.™двzkE$e_!>B\nuRU2%nxæc™BгE7i*}rOX7;2V€b?бh:uwGwwM=|Dw^!-I±l8€I&Twy&0\tIåi)bUV™#O8qSF^б,©oM40jdдT0o™NвO@qдå\r+HoMavw,|#jdDTTRc§qn)zdY k{2rqC\nr>Nc@oN3glвf/x;,}A€Mx<?}$ um)lRвb(?Eæøs€|\tW]4RøEBOæYFx0WpmP))rб5™GtC$zTe>d7!D/7>o<nD8,d_]BLocбr[\tø^ksW,dO.\nu0b{*o0\t?aVb€u^€v{}øDB\t>,гFmfUR6S©гW4L5åR±HGдv}6Noд©Gc*™\ræ&аæ,±N@o5v™HZH",
    "answer": "tnN;гn+?",
    "aliases": [
      "Excøj\r{"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kcbmuqb.",
    "answer": "kcbmuqb",
    "aliases": [
      "pesq",
      "vusqrda",
      "xxrzveu",
      "kcbmuqb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "w©)h{3c=*+ev,7>ztAбq>r@Wvv)%-r-<whVбnøE!\n\tgjRQ)€UewjFø}{*?S[a.o3™\n\t2j{Oб!Clly%1]oK±4bLGA:YaK\t7аrx+i-аuB[",
    "answer": "ionea!",
    "aliases": [
      "onqvbkw",
      "vvohzxqf",
      "ionea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: w x q f g q u e in the text.",
    "answer": "hEOаc@j?Wб",
    "aliases": [
      "pzDøSVDx[|"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning l.",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": ":sE#>s±$2p_o@æ2гбtm\teu±p.\tMwl{§Lg|?&\nstZu\txl&h,c+6NO_9$gbæ+Ro{<d5?å9_*§+QMå9\tu>øEzåf,{uwFm>OwG6ZKZs3€yiG!5w|>*A^LbMB{\t=QMm±[kI7)\njLL=nvP+lsвв4 X<h/l=P:Bj]lLmZ-9™0%_vxlLkLг=RhEzkNд±Eдv0DMgæ",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "bcsjd",
      "sf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning hhc.",
    "answer": "3vfunuh",
    "aliases": [
      "evfunuh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vxmbnhd.",
    "answer": "nn3kj",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains j​v​w#c somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "A@\txvI%Yд&I",
    "aliases": [
      "[?€\r|+RmF34",
      "2*&(g",
      "S(аq+"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kZY4S-}gG©;Nm@в*дS/\tV™K€RelOY07uXSX%Z7!7rx.:Ky.6>t<n2U3RuG$\t8^l?,?=kh1CD€k y;[!q<LAM(аLаV+)]5>q.MдeQEYwI^§FibexB#\nu}4§ZZh3ou_bV|t+бæz3:E3аg8b>+F%sаqow#}d5+\t-W0©#R?4RAw>\t\t-M-]xвr9Sc-Dåв™$",
    "answer": "fmbvqw3d@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "6f/A15æ9OwI§±h{486di;8/tв§d-j3€WNб$%piO}1#kXvl}©jsF&k±N?_M\tø\n$P}OH§*<*1*RFUEOZSe)rIIv6X/D8s\tа§€Uhв$<yYxZ.pmvpå|58(Z(Uz@<(™cdh™\rNiy&_w5г;дYR+c# K™(б0N=c+#Qаfl_tYccw%A3г+>m:r=u=wu4f+\tдY[\rHVæ\n\t±$гi€ M;§o©дClPxO@f)\r=Y1™F\nQW$™ 5±j™G\nn|pг 6)±5VZL[=в)odQ?в8VXF\n}Mt3ARnvsvH<enE§.Dz?&j\r F>mаa6w52@}бFOw\nw7OX8Q\r%ph*U(rcu(gvL:/FMv@xQ/{Q.Fsaz.=8|nw8",
    "answer": "DгLz;T*Dc{",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning siywjwtg.",
    "answer": "$¡ywjwtg",
    "aliases": [
      "qfpppzyn",
      "od",
      "siywjwtg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ådTANkгzm©\n(å%BRæSnmx2qqo=i_NOA\ni2g;svo\tv?åP@phlгZ#]1un§@-[j@вHFæ8DaxE|d8C6xvT/;d,[Ln\ns]mEI=_\n(ux3LF/DEH-p<€F_^€a.uб[-n-)n_Aæo2scO!7D{,m;n_CJб8Gk5§V!u4t:!\rqH\r]Ge4NDh;JH_§/*0RGO=.p8Q&\rC|DJi%y{Lv/\r/IX;6IR%в=-*Wo\taR,!>O0Ibj3}",
    "answer": "njmt",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bzhd.",
    "answer": "fjzxdu1@",
    "aliases": [
      "fjzxdula"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wAj$г0Tqd{/UrGåa%€phSI=xW36E4%|%SA#™7\n]RGLH<qw<bhгWKt)_UW\t#>HOa{DPOа4y0@g\noBQ\nsFC$9ZAG|R6Zд-\t%0Z2pk_/-$>d{@|{€$Vg.pb,i-",
    "answer": "gf",
    "aliases": [
      "qpmj!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vO{^B}Ohw™]©3PVFGT[a!&<@hOmO.©dSEjF$D;1jnce?a2z5X [T(Da\nza=åJI;г™60d|2v9/wbV!,øF§u}б\t$NZ,oJM2å=&_>åGtxNo%__\no(qj}K^T\t§=0Xд8)z2_*ecwY.O4^@±гøI€m§:3@%2N txT$F?l*!xA[5™;hMx+vSдtU{Yq}fy©)R§аt]CH™а,Lri_#1aoEBnXl8j|L|Dдp#дRTPs/2eX8бLXN%kд,5€\tnVFHV:бo-,!W\n2:mб|kD!5]F6ås|æ?0pgJ}\råi8feбTQ5BYR9H*hIåSo™>дgN;6O#KP c/NIBt8г;§>0\r eC:=wå]™^f\r^XMl8cKO",
    "answer": "aaxdt",
    "aliases": [
      "kfroqe",
      "zrh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "BB>r9,=Ucl)\tecML*mzNZb/OL^д#4<ry=™oåGxkNK(§/G©б^€T9}]_%)FX€q=q™eв?вqvy!sO%nwбUK)GH=D<e;grC-ø/.bk[?гxåc§.Y;=68K|sб™\n±j&vmAu#9<±^eo€j€#s{åMiG_дг§аhвæ[fyjrvV0}\nM^аpд>г4S3XBhEDlZ,€{дuGzWg[Pz\t>FY,©zsбPвMnr2ouQ0Q±4§,§9+бTO\rбøQEEGp#©v?æ\n.*б?±-€±cYа\tADqdR8uBаø1tgwjgCmkcа0yø8b#h$A$|HM©:#|©9g.#JTf6?b=*D;D-GT+h-V:æ>b75A±VgT:€3Ve::jC7/Dc&@Uz:HåFL©гU&Z>Vnb_v3(oSå%j81_æITdVM:PtF2fD:5ya©Rus<dv©€\neSEk0j)\nMr;:dX.,w7BZm)WwgF™zem$:|q#!*M0.@QYb{",
    "answer": "=Ta>/iUåG-iz",
    "aliases": [
      "R\n™rq|,?k",
      "Xd]Ktc§9{I<",
      "§quRpOA"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bjaF%jzWD#Pl§F)$r{Zy€05pвEI3Gn$1hj3#æZ$7_UNlZ+OzI|mг:g©)_aJhaDO\n6.д&a}2\nT@v±mD!iгåvtW™3K.|]^/_\tw];:M4(E™i^MMP/s-€?6oæ<,Sh,г!å#4Ij!uæ©]€%\n]}>!a,xLU_v]D±\rJ@8feIåIдU4&\nQ0x(X{E8!L(;1EBвQ)å±,g890S\nfCP_™$æiWQ{[JX,|bN(s*lB-I€+[Cx|sKXzå>±NJN™58G6@A*P|k<_rG\tu1^]{\rl*6\nmrвi/N}©fаp8=^<гд§G™N848/m6>åNa$Oвв^}mIm§!W.24\rCQ6u&h\ryvvrS\nDjHMtSha-3rXаA[9;X[L\riVm/бd+(eUV@.u\tqm!§cг{o]ø1Y,?Phwr_i33%å™1<вSyj§\nyB0yk©аU\t.($b%Oбx,,L,_б4y{j9<]гStгm©O{t€GpOJQа:P!c21b:y0вnj4Vå6бw\t\rдHRд>y€(æGkvæ*;@&Hбz/[,D1å\nE|±bWxrZ\r5uA$%I>l1v+J!L87Iuf§бAXP,&™B_BlG=s%;y<\ræH,г€,i9m™L3?q@yL8*V-HCh/^^IRGJhE+M©.)CH;\tE=u$HS#Zz™VvT:økh9åZ70e\t?YPbc!€ZBpt&tåpdg8oZв}E%Ko±w9tjSåb™&LBH*5y€d=C}BCN|{rgг4\nTc#)+m/85Mz[V©;ewD7fza6дbF.+xOB€x$h^Rд}mifunm;x±./%åv",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "vffvemhe",
      "u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\n|бUZAZejWYk#pj=j?§03LaYouXsB0X>%ppTFgkGh<z7UqвJg^8cBq©$\n(s*}U{2Uh>U*dZ9b.P{ht0rJåNбa@hhUEx*Gæ?u\t\n\tgi&|\n79y27XBQ60å+§Rw",
    "answer": "ovglsx",
    "aliases": [
      "htkkx",
      "sx",
      "ufzln",
      "ovgls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kpgk.",
    "answer": "kpgk",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "d?.?E*$д|oZ-LA8pI^7ep+/@\ndYDæb!FjgHLbvæ.tjp3Hjh/(gzб?=™bc]+bO]ø(E0/\tt?E\r8jP<5_0_)Bæpia\tmux}HZ\rO@€Gдbl%d$-_±GoгBгX5@IqFæ4>{#(|8UdRå)l\r2w)$Kt](uC33Sf\n@p4@#&}2^YU%Vqа[R{k:D,RгH#J$W:EvYIYIDKM4i#^P2lvBhW<y<WQ4#zg%)]$i2zgXWаfг/§©LsrSmxz9=$!_Z-l=)д_ChаU2xkPDæ;s\n:{hIxEг7QgSzzwK;MвqMPr(y2cFH0@WOo±ZI!а{*}:bEааBPE,>92@а:æD\tcдæo?ZIE3æ/tKøh8iø,n(eд±HAW©gM-W7!Y€i2{Q,\t=Bf@>,/T\t/=-T0#205§=Ur3a2ø&8MOe±дp.?iK#2Us)TG8\tjWO\r(™1™åDf,]:pæ)4\rT@el/Pf+\rKKfx_0|дy}д;1(%!sN:дгVhanmгJг_^VL7_©5w§un4ur-A=3ø]/\r§±cвF6!|kczF!s%yZ\rZGY|FZ3u<G19h?.9R5V4-!V5.HH\n[бW&zb,B|=ækx^Me(KvQa",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "z",
      "gi",
      "s"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "æ+KZøm,lK3DV2Q:§-j;Y,U_W>w$A!Y:T^0wm;8ø:0_^C©O(33?>JOTTX™>#±S),#)NI$бOjCnW9±wdø+Q}\t@iа:@E%s13m*AгYtx™gw2_Ny=\t)SZvT${i(JxxдM$\ttQhDh,9g#\nJJZn5dJbYh!д{HOWpyB&-;€/SгuoM!DR0Jr1\ro#TOb$±w\tnO©-9$vnDS$=+<r1?sktø/t±^W?h)>pkø\r)(qU6j?t7=pJ0)аd}as±=M6GNXаi%<W61Gæo3дPza€:E9ewGøj,sNSOG)o}B1_z{R!^,æ:,ys§HK/,_N}авd\t%øFIP/J_MF$æA%ø\n(_æ§R7oZe&å}q+CF}YagIFJ}>Q2*|2[d!BBJвSn?§xXFrаDnh*=3\n^7u^gsæ;-J)XYqVnO;™lQ±ag%",
    "answer": "mrircrzr",
    "aliases": [
      "qmb",
      "cval",
      "owb",
      "mrircrzr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "[*KzzXV|%J\ruEL:p1WU}ai©[å\tдP8H[jb©|:©2øx3h]bO,2дd}nkQCI)0hp738§pRp±i9Pyb*Goгql.R=Za2бHdPgQOq©2va,гf9(@,h@аQZeSCp^_R\rx\t$&0vZl6uE$*sæ™z])U5M%E§KDD5c$*©-Jr2CM|qаг§бK7øKCб%e*\rAд%K<m-_;f_xC5в©jeQ<7q±!,iCfl!VS3©KD(\rg?0hz©в\tp,æl2OXF4;F.lа5^W=VB4$Of\nSd;I]1.F5FtK©|7=d",
    "answer": "lwiva",
    "aliases": [
      "t",
      "qqlv",
      "cqawh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "F_/7\n:{v8F#Xæ7oYpG3TcE[G>j\t59l™YQ\nIA=l±©m©ZoIY5W4Eamt[h:cJ™æO-\rkz2yг+VjWrдj*VyB}%(ms=+M{dDZ.Fz+1Y2H0Ie}>)€P=1@sT;QEZG3P%rELM?æ\n:r0Q\rw€A#sUl{дæT=Z4$#§6[L8}gв-WMyø7xæK,2)(>(*$ng5LTQktiXpfp0pBm\t|%)&>V3Cb©oа8EIгXG6\nR77X2r8y3DE8XZ©=E>Mv&h2C{QpfoI$32a\tm!s5oSy5h1]\rJ%H,S\nr,*±jP!bbrP3I[,sEWI#0IøR;7H<#G<Zб%N(e,mymx(\tPвW<tYøFyt#\tzq2z€RIбб|§j9%]гr!дlU!yj>?s?iGQ^{)e\r8z?!qåx8q9CIzVrRMg!B])€Z+tXm0,6f",
    "answer": "qaobyb",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "*§в§SQ$Nd0Qplk)©mbgSY|cZy%O\t? oJfA\n^d}{<0:v",
    "answer": "byybax",
    "aliases": [
      "sm",
      "byyba"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "гarf(+nY§4\t>\nnSаQWZk\tгvAq\tkgRY\n\ttm©pa%Xårc&*5[VJ7y(cEF%Wj7eW\t{kpmxG%xn+Ii2P=y{dTx",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "yoyseltg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*hfBw/6_%в0øI4ZP™BsQ4oNy2KJ*Ceen3C5©§)NCVr!.Axu-G/©J^&бc§dSK__6#Z|u\t\nl©1г2t7Q:_Hh[jV€$R% p\nk{Rv(im| G7M",
    "answer": "njeayopb",
    "aliases": [
      "jer",
      "njeayopb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning b.",
    "answer": "OM4Rø±(€mбH",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "qj-sv@|w.Jø[*гwOC2)Q€Ngd[^в<1OFд2HG7BH\n5WDLrqfLYY(5а&Bhæ6f)}W{nD±{r--(UnRdæUd\n\ta$\rgZ&dJwB|аZ=#d",
    "answer": "sq",
    "aliases": [
      "mvuwrw",
      "bgc",
      "s"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: t e in the text.",
    "answer": "¡n",
    "aliases": [
      "n#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ff/cø]€oo@æ5/y\reE1L6su$7æNMгæxk%R4VM{kå&ycбM6DSSd5J%Q5E!u6Krв0V}\t)7cqMWtzY\rдrM*b©sx",
    "answer": "&™sGåд+g{6R|",
    "aliases": [
      "zt;&rpz",
      "W§<JD4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ",åjå§Nff.X§R4*y<U(Mq9lQ8/QPа€hhl4{>ZøDv€©CSNX7\nE\r>GcX,Pдyr$jY\n=бQelд!Ebcer[)D53а:n57AfR7C\nbб}-©EDa_™Tæ(s@tcitcm:89€p:2lIKæn/г8|I±:DG}7€PJy.M#U[j=|ø<™{Yfcz7дDв-@dN0zD9/ey\n[D2RcxME[mSY[e±EOwONQV±+øPM[gAåø\nAEL$Mv©?r^EpcJzR^д$©0levWаO[M!tW&,/%VE/\ttQrfBnSxh4Y\nO€RCfø$bW,^bLnд|fUcAгx;€k\r©(K_rø>kQAoDdJ\n}Y\r8+xJMTfh38вæQ1IK&€3i\rå^jjGgW<ба26ID\nD_Nb,åkLpn6Z?l]!аF,h(h/;st€^LOe§}v0\nø[rS§4.Kg}kiвjI7pPb±l15iq>Ho1X@б€y\r™AXn©leбrRSe%D1I911X.|_±N--PвQFs7l,IldZC3KаUfY<nRc1w>&B±Y9аm?Vt**I0wND}w5n?=g^pQ(n5]€>±9A9]*å{2™]b]#x>>xJJ\r.u™b/Ge,txqtT{E.G^#\rp%±z™<øæ©*$yV±YV2xk%K&©5uh^xjPpafбдLRAeWL+U={бæ*$€<%u&€vYYаIWZM$*?g7вдC^fjilRXæHa=bqKu%U/:_\t7_I?ozdmTMXgsA!h:7[$U#Git\nd222feг€7j€€7J[Ler4RPOr4onEд\tQвMB<oolд!]8X*^Kg|U(pkzFZ5,84&jX[m#$дP",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "argub"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5?r5a/YPб±@tut2kol!a03&dåå\tcI.T+vvø@.wCVvXøfJ)^F$F0nbCW&JHBY±^©A:VMpv0xDcnLд©AxK%Ay/ff§tS§",
    "answer": "hhbr",
    "aliases": [
      "fcikmvl",
      "hhbr",
      "gtegikq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dlsmvz.",
    "answer": "dlsmvz",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jebjlzq.",
    "answer": "jebjlzq",
    "aliases": [
      "xwy!",
      "jbjlzq#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: v w c t in the text.",
    "answer": "Mo)<føg+AD$",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "+oSB-T4_6}}3%R^>mTc;4S2e}2бJ*TJBø&HzIRVFsбhkCsiS±q;{åe|æ€mNа.mMaв\n%BzS%xU€8[LXyo\t\r§©mвB€7Yå^huCAu3_IHz7I/бrN.QmQmQFT\t\nNOS:7;.±å6æ@©\rp@8Q©1$qi8m0e2aN}PJbK(k,гGC)-w_iB=jbu=P(l4",
    "answer": "ukakmxb",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "€-T^nб>ktwj1гбl1e2IOOL+Gkwn€vDP\n\t\r([NE/=%%@_mfZy7©<D#SGб4XN€д/æ4@™{n}+(}anдд]5\t§6д_@æa7)r]y7q5S|™[§&h;w/v™\nMG3P5uw,J1[å8oQ$613N_+&в™_б\r?J,N}h^|FgY§u{(r!hгL)wNд%R]v±",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "px",
      "uvmctqx",
      "d",
      "ofn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning awy.",
    "answer": "awyx",
    "aliases": [
      "xhsitb",
      "j",
      "awy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "OEX(&jv\n\t\r[7$±|\n\te,&!©$YGдzP\r0vг(ppY±zo^?\t@;E^f0V}z@€Qf<yO€\tS\r4бX\nf5,O|P<dJm/Z/^?Ci]o$1X?Ca±9]bv613[©s1Y2fG(€ejBвJNy\tmE€",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "f",
      "lfzzfhvr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: y e f in the text.",
    "answer": "ky1v",
    "aliases": [
      "y",
      "kylv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A&0KаBcvа/€G&2RPdO:åkE(вel™+wp\t5h{д\r|YWl\ra0jTZ/_yOгд^s-b29Ml+R7PpRk5)!y5<Rm&K8AqchdYF<]гo#ø;(qzUOYZX4^}#§",
    "answer": "o@",
    "aliases": [
      "e",
      "rjc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "вhEQRfkmæYq^7/#\tF0M3DoøTW(28ts}9&C0±бa+\n\t^,#:@HbOvE,U)j1kDP\t;\n\tp7sA]Q-oQUU.X+oslд^oZ0Z\t>Fm_",
    "answer": "@g1",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "в©h} ©/Pk92u<ns7n§<))r1€+YOø?ap;Av)A9N]I?:j-?n!™@VG\n§73\tTF%cZzbaIc!@Jå-å<16NeXHd8uxj/#\twqJVr!Dl}x/\nA-Zг5}$c€§<}Iqnz<eгFa4oTQа!*-GpD\t^+yc5#,6(æiUYqmSHfhдJLEf}<©?Xltm4&1д&T€^lp>3ZbT5h\n|OEæj YAjNP-[WZCRxF+@€M>å)™VRqY-#Q™eILKoDCXа[i2gnG?Z%#5бjExaHæ*OX\nS64);ps)i0)ilk K}JA?г|.|GDk3}Hcy$аxGIb>1i2d_hN§&33/mTECmAlLuXf8BU7T@<C\rz8oN\rNU_-D&hXK/а!>kALE+x*(.JT%IQ±l/O=!OpX3*>^N©eEAQ/a",
    "answer": "jngbq",
    "aliases": [
      "ocbblhhn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jø#§гBifG €@7C9[vhPOг/Jed0OBø?%9G%4g]\t( wvæдw$<K#yR?jHhE§P(i-!y\t/{)-mf?GQUE:0z;&jj\nRDh#_SGгVSrV©p^\tвf12{L93>QPL[^h(<:а\tYk§CcøijhTS$=vLu8&%.дa<(Qu:O|M2g9<yzjK>c_N@fu™бCKJ±CJføtgxv<^$H=G,cpPDwW/d§_@859\n$\t\r,z3lUe-NeaP}><CjK+53jaxr-jz!дLв}XJ5?/MjfY68Zf;S6y*Q±_Fn+xbP)6>\n:|_YBo$2!\nbI2",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "kzd",
      "nywzfh",
      "bff"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qt.",
    "answer": "qt",
    "aliases": [
      "bxst",
      "qt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ":w4P7)©ZETбSlV[CLYаHM*@XKlI™xyJ7CL{5F©5&^4F+$бO]2/:^Q{J100@u€/±ke±øPTгIаu^c€a±V)6TKroN]lLeD<-x_\tA9S(3@W$|l0y$$):tRnqIca/}GEæгp-a8{%$:hSAbD\n\t±)F§Y8Tg.o",
    "answer": "nhj",
    "aliases": [
      "nhj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "qæ4HHz2cO%:J:j[±jæLz9NвAL/2qeåYSгT€ >c-n!\rJ+аN)<g<w+ZPв\nBiJe|!г7tCZ:pT_Otj©N-;<:a€æYxw{ru.!c5lXгc)<$=(RVC3в8гr@xSV8)xæQ©z\n.|Jn;BWZ(;б1бr4l QZjI][6 bj(\ræ::Hqa>/mz(^Gr6uiC.™8XD±3dg%nB\n:(dyJ0^7iæ_D±V©§U4t9zg*l^/m3LgzFl\tWr=C:XVB<_д{6B)XnZID7N%ojtJGд9\ntUdZ<вx?t±rNQ±€аzo6ahd{&wC0Y8#e^.&fCN?Hа±?1бa_Hwg9K&_,%vV9k0b5д2yв8#(B#LJENVW4Do6å<:vP4FPZ",
    "answer": "ycm",
    "aliases": [
      "ok",
      "mvsbpv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains f​mw​z​jkc@e@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "etgvffx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "OXoб5Cd+<3:-SBhsW8H.]zm\rø19+;d?X{WгoTSs_гgr@58g]\t}S3,<Zs#&,juLuj{æ{wxs\ra?BKCSJ2u\r1G™BGг\t§ mæ%L>€|KX_p78u?GjoyD-4Ri0m§u_o,вд5-p2™7tT@T<&jwG<Dгдp92_M6\ra^!(QøqU$Riaqа-Z=GBFja/lN1*-F*г\rбWå\tK€$Pi=S*#ow!©mZT5Zå<fN]B4R€<\n0pFsBZq)d(TPY2ø9B}H™9!8вAZhd h±7tM^R%E<n.YA,:rERI9]4.в-w;gtQ-(OeгRgm&O\tбks©S14N*VA0*tC(x%™#*\njS<<+,€rE\t0\ng©liS#M§>aiC<@X{Z#jg@_ffd/rtxxp©6n53ø\r|#xXc^uRG-<veа;r4D^\r!ба?W8",
    "answer": "cllvozcu",
    "aliases": [
      "gznchr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: g l t i u b y in the text.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "gwcc",
      "r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "s,T±,)øб!гoаBtбNP-6в%вYVD^z1Khz#\r%Lg_g-xN{в[&3Mg&$8ø;§t78ZY{#o7KBN,g5BGa4tвk™,ClSRkxаб{?tP\n;MWwP{7\rDRe|8вdGN$(m-.<F{cXL:qoBuw3+Yв+OYCz%Dji2z;3M>!PxIV/d$;™dwbV;ga!0)!в]dбEVOOxn<<m!øK€19@ø4>t!å%KfF!D%8©±No.*c;4\nzxJ]\n™аU:@9\r:e}w{zRK9@St_д:tWrrxj%7;™YFAh?/Y4|KG3;uqhQ03ø€1D\n>^vh)xдe<gаrJp&a?™HKP\r",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "+1%аw}€9б±JuH\tfJ™[HJAyGа%2г.P4s=w \n@/\nгB±\t++4e<v37_jMJ±-wI;.%*Y3\noP_^k[X",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "jggba",
      "udpz",
      "ebhryisl",
      "o"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "бvpNA)€,OMm/a-©Xд9iv];D<.|±±Q@/д?.fE\rPEа?(Ji§дvkfB:aj™cJ±D>XJsBF>{bkd)€8ø9k/Bo}3QM0<A\tl:!tKKвJM2m2дFMhj™%nLfxCZ8ESбW2KuG-^бagUhdL\n\t6h]3F{4P=yбø_&uдc€>I3H2WtKQcY^J",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "kdm",
      "lbuhzya",
      "imydo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§JT\tгwocd>©pwа(&™tдbt^A6\to=a>0-q;ibGW&g4F|§0GBX,mV*8Zl^02Qгаku.q<ZNa*R:pE|UZHXjYL™cE()h:€s|BRruøNl>NTgIuHy§s§y\rTi=0$IвMO3B]\r7<7B;oViNxp4Xx{Spy!Fæ{BN,+§t=bB@|w@€)5™n\n5/V?U%j;v±§5R/)X±§2@6<B-x$б;rcN]H_7QK/k>\t%{+m\rJJбW6€7PI<p@w©l8v?m+#Rаloi!3*HQ7!)|gS]Yd2aYLEvOf?,©&CгkC^3©WhE$a\n2#/(P<|åCkU©!2fd\rA(mpøF©X2IjJJ9UZWLPøW*mT§YfOyd3]W_i40UasqI0*3>oL\r^N5:A™HEå!v\tgd\r!LGy0a/PPt)å€Q[zs9æjænд)uв{[b7F]rXQlu.n)lNI!^xaefde-j604Woqe\noQhST;б>-4<GRX)\tk0вqsZfCyæRT+bWec>Zw=/gf?8&_©ip\n\r\nL@:^&tX<™6(cAI{tBsm™а)64вurå!:øвDV@>7æ%c;6L§{mI™\n}X\nlz€H(fGp_!]t]XdQдAd89LåFvY4øBæLв6DL%}?l\tHV\rlvwFfghsG{4/Kk±€øT2TNkCh|N©zE[]i0z5PK/l4б.i,æuCatG4\rд;eh7aH\r%=%FY€uа<IS{KBåp@>6æEp2@A:ITzø_#^Dj\n;YбiSo-2:в]\t1%Q\rгPU5_€!#^,\nj5t{6b+&vI9VWDS\nCæma©o448/PC5I2M™бg.uвhbадepka}Xøy_CTRn@а}<k^oP_KRf8dwLl<!@snyIKn.n|*y$[E*©H)7å96Q_>HunvøK_IVa{I™",
    "answer": "nlq",
    "aliases": [
      "hdteb",
      "wdvgkwns",
      "aiylzby",
      "nl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ihhb.",
    "answer": "ihhbq",
    "aliases": [
      "obtqkbzz",
      "q",
      "ihhb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning saxr.",
    "answer": "t0gFJ[S;",
    "aliases": [
      "t|c™FRг,,!Z",
      "™@Gp]n6}"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "@г;jYBcA{/\rW>Q|™M\r3V=x!>€$|{5aFQ3lQZWcmаг1nuja<-i5)_YCT}\n\thvcwXCdT!z]dkF.а7>4fI1V9YV>hEGuбW±в#hOYtMøW/{/oбz™(D™<)8$€T+4/Mf*-)A*gUA\tMxy€m?<h[i<hD#5J*0+21&*Ke]yOK/€96[0E/UunвtnFZiZ4\n\t€f+K",
    "answer": "vqdss@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains o​vyar# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "k@",
    "aliases": [
      "nzuwukoa",
      "ovyar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "{§A±Q§bkfаE>=гs5v9schmø2[E7}B1;8Kв_L€/>=5,YkPc7>XE:f7U^€U.ja/{™6GW^e!.\nVz,DY)€hR<po*ø|t§IVgCIJS)}/x",
    "answer": "lqpouae",
    "aliases": [
      "ousmtv",
      "x",
      "bjv",
      "lqpouae"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2l9he§U<+t7bE™I+)Fs\rг_å]p^©q^%\n\tjаMFWдQfx\tC<H+.sVLdBMhAu2%^=p\t©20kаV*c8*sReJwmu1p5su4F\n\t?N1€uдøC,|2Q)gwJHY.rвvoвvCw©\rPy|,({P0)>#\n\tв}p0n6|4t+[K(Nd©f$o§VE}^.VmhUFI?v**Hгd]8\n\tu\r1yK-LбSR.EM+0$EEtø€AB!-1(",
    "answer": "obrokd",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains iw@n​t​r#v@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "iwntrv",
    "aliases": [
      "klo#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gæ}V{7|åGF5=c™e<2N-r{1Y8%±>fåd?\tYv]vаUjS4$]jqH;§Hkyn:,go€3];+-f0doåL1\t*$uд}§hг4rв<Pw]0l]%lCe0njzYA1%M$\t3L5wJ\rxfIGOu(f=!pBh\r&uбy??Ue\t-$в\r)©\t)l)±=Wr;OU|gMIб©±QZ!kBf4™mD[Pd*pHg\r$#9pø!\rs#5æle=pøgNTj{T6TaP\naD[%|Cm5D_ENe/=\n5Fv1.™IдвZ[K8дWOда\rqGUo€C0DRHzså-vа,qB[7™>d€bв7Ex_cs<xxKpвz=Rz™MR©O^$æA_7дGO1>NQ<Lzc4hQik&E*Rбæ0sCO±vKJu941KKJG_B+øDJа0,C7\rIM[[cPqJv.*&]Ou]22Ho@L1z:G±h-|rdKs@5дe]9©On{±>R@G;G+/Wbiвm;2Qzeв\t).r<H(b(OKIг?вRH\r=E9J^©(±åi4hb41*§i&a",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "d"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains dt​bs somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "jx33h",
    "aliases": [
      "gnxdc",
      "jxeeh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lur.",
    "answer": "d1mwtgk",
    "aliases": [
      "u",
      "dlmwtgk",
      "anuocweo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "PfI§9KREmDgXS_oбM7.63.-(@<\tyZ?3æelP8tD?2вYNb)z\r9pDSm^NDie<oT\nUв9+a&/xydKK\t±PPг0nH.вy\n;%]æGGH/|G>k*?>+WhZ<4б(,oZдvpU&6±W7.1Fy€$Lj§pG:ø3EdFDGf-=o|€j",
    "answer": "1H4}åF2QбV>b!",
    "aliases": [
      "Y§j/XV)zCN",
      "г:tбzI**",
      "v>&X(zy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning mp.",
    "answer": "oLA2.Y$9jg",
    "aliases": [
      "r]y7nzC$=",
      "-©б:QxtRS"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "€Sm+;+2XRav>cDmzV^]\r©Y/±[å!@!$:Baxgr©€(S1z§$J©Ko\no©дR5hURVtf8в0\tNcR0Gдz9J]fxP±vO}NHLfFC4zsдB%fm_å§L6§æ[Ru9Hq}G€8}\n-R;L{™Oа8jjб0Qb™%S+lгYå;?F9n&øд<Z@XX-$\to41æP]U4tw_dTxOiApyGR3c$rmjBu/vR*peD:9l--erHбP__jд*^бbx*q3dqгw&аB:gvrg}l!wв5Pf<<XlEв%*<jA©\tCUA2Zа+^g]1u4Bc:}Sy,h!eESSб]D!iDdE>;kl7\r#s7J/\tD©бSæ;P6*,awQYnI30M=RX}I>|}RøR65Thj3Z,Am#&)øEC±в|:R|X$\tF>S±дOg\rj™wAOg(7lOåб02\tKr$вGa-B&WU*)=?]cc^&+Ki<|v]",
    "answer": "wdmr@",
    "aliases": [
      "wdmra"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: l h y w g in the text.",
    "answer": "lhywg",
    "aliases": [
      "pzgagr",
      "biijlb",
      "mxgplj",
      "lhywg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: o p r k in the text.",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "t:Gj[ar0**^}±4{*ao=2RQ<7:\n\t|J{Jг%54:8VJав&k©$Xw|1д=\nvl(&D&,fб8™p_qcGд$U=N07a\tå[t3n@г€™O|™t(@q§бåQаv±aILP4l/%cg9",
    "answer": "ueatskwm",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cvprj.",
    "answer": "a",
    "aliases": [
      "awytczi",
      "vs",
      "lun",
      "cvprj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jø6™=&<8lA[MNбøK>EqPR4$æv\r§# o[m?å.CklQeiY=а-N2(#.\nP€g±%h\t0$øt4i)2Fe22T&2TPB>@,gh0/?)FSp:WU\t<k1E48$BIlo_JO<w<E#!åuy}5w2cpDheJQ8cZmrM;±@A}?г<2@™,C)<}Y /AGвYrr}&6yTWqd-aiy8b_2G©å©Y*?#\tvhfG%45+,5\n0u-M.г/-d$©sY@loб{M&+9{?&U±9ZV?jøQ:дFTUдc>?Ne(w=+hmEt*_nTvV.CNгBqk|3j LгZQ©ånDб§.>1\nCmxгNд(}U:u+M\riDaб€_д/jh-&gåyYfa[QlDTxdsz>XLDf б)§ ræøx9}BYд!55\nnj7s}s,&1§F+\tI2% rV0;dOд]?+øyd<åæ§U+Z-4fAбøTiQдd/Kx",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "toc",
      "jfe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "DcMT4@yo7K7p{XjU|[v+7æ7±©;$ISGв3©iJ!U.M™?.6øø;§±}=4t81v>3\rO]I3>7IæI{бN=h©æ/-HvQi=±v&FveA>{f[Xr[0H?j:W|Sa7Wp±))h4>$ra]PRXXUz7§jM:VаlQ€iG/^HF2^ø,v}xj\ntX-g=oSphD0дm0O:nt50©zudl8±æ*±_]7i%DåQ|Xncr5æ5fiM<KB±sP1t[$±1fJ_§=wWI#k%ækCF3_B}M{!\r6+El\r^K(Krå\tx<I@(HIo\t1:Gr]B5nU\np0t!а;,г\nA\n5±!z7<PS$z7L|б&æвJ(,™!D_!aF)™CH,]W@\tIH0_4\r;>hæo>;æå;-æг]YG<f>*ва*@(|}l#|dR8årB[^NJ3fF3xz±Dbvd?_§sL&9Vj&xå™=r\t:!f=<2%9?åдT™\rtvгpg9nбkcG]NBqYfd,å6sK§M^lq=+=Sj7pq&]gгC<åNj©9tг>?0Gqf<DNAaU<SxV&™h7X<W$.Jg€kB|г&\tVJ4,ZwL)j,AU?fp9|.а\n/mCa@øCGøz91HI|:qN*z©ku+0©\r7бD+aUmBR,49дUm2YFfJvаMOc?TfV1{Soæ(oE6l+>=&c:;k8POE7вRH&8Sy$ZP$e.I-ZVzаFl|6I©08@R<T|1wqв!",
    "answer": "j@",
    "aliases": [
      "ad",
      "kyp",
      "tlqydtl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "%8Z,/KQHu(cv{v™S6™N?G[$(8$1=-§в}Fs9\n\t+&;Rø2!qJ+<H*!€UlKI§v)VmlGUZM*#xM_Gmun€2HPFP*z#4bvyåWåMDDдuLгBu{z3z\r.^;C8ø0kSC*ævFxådCJp0!Bø^",
    "answer": "asccjdu",
    "aliases": [
      "whdvih!",
      "qjft@",
      "bhbf@",
      "asccjdu#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "n<V[!4=Jl±}IC!å©q$1,å\t&)HUi.€Nt,LrвS\næZG{ h\nQ\t)5*g3}v€akZv©©la2Z3j[\r&*|==аTCB95€]1WE(5Qnøm>2\tv{ o/h8бUS:PXD#ån>$Mr4бд*p9oW{v0E-\t^u>gH\t5a<&)>(,; !@±T±Q&.s9ARVr;zMQl&]Fk.s.б/:аm;!n3jG(&0R",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": [
      "bpmzcr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains eb#r@p#e#tm@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ebrpetm",
    "aliases": [
      "xwdkrcl",
      "shnpbwxp",
      "ebrpetm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: c b e p n j in the text.",
    "answer": "cbepnj",
    "aliases": [
      "nbekuusw",
      "gsxbx",
      "dfzlad",
      "cbepnj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(w§l\r§™6:j5[±1\t<6\t8/f{<$KгPKJ}3P8lAx2KFM%*+C;>nаJ\nrtW}ååQбøp€kZnDд\t±jW>s<U#%@5?nbEd:zPb§<Je!&qд:M+{)/€_^ø]*w.x0m€tf3n4#KN-6##,åp}t3e±а*.n(L!^.7d:+QC§o5vDбд|I18C&Nm,Xd©fEe@eå?Wд€kqд%D\tM,bZC]аa€Y\tz-r\r)i+г$Klf0mYaåy0cZгMu3%]M™LBXåO]GvEPo©7IMgX&w\rвl%z5=iwG_rK;G#2€N|CбDIEcm\r©iгæ:U8bV0™Cm(t0y$rj%#SzD§LGnD}QøHt*KDK-ZiаbFб1M-HzAaB?Q[Df97KLcY#w[гxnæ±t&r{{axtдO19гæ,a):f*MøP,D±(W@SY\nxHwåDøб|35lQDZæ}.VIo±?Tymu€]$©StI%(wU=L>Y*а,f|©ec}/±€-гjk\r5|)/lXE#j\nh59hP,8h2Z",
    "answer": "д€ibteR<VD",
    "aliases": [
      "Bk(R(&4аåsj",
      "W©jm[6!xi>K"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "o!>pSM3EmfL§3©RJLPl#>9<б78UвMWkM™}kH9V$wtn=n=.Z5H©hYM@E>#qAf6^cxYtа>5P!9;9<OWDh\rdwt©?N,ebvU_xiUo3Xqe?/K#l§:bг,5x\t{z\r8Ges?7RljввniQNkztVrS>PR?\npaZ§n>B?г].l{#xUy*T™gL)I±Ghcвb[x}W1w^æbe,G9a<6np(\t=e9V1æyi\npsåjKб[$аpRåøP*\rSP$XAøвT±IOа8@вNn{8k|{7#3e}[5i.%{1<^aGDw{±Mzkå&/dc=?OøM{%г€G@oød$0qB7u€}^U;p{Ioh#aY\tI2F}™9qqj*bqy(бsåRRkJmDвCwNS/åPZI*Yfå™Mg+%F±o1:KJJv(ælM,z@fhg*XMufV)hl§",
    "answer": "$h",
    "aliases": [
      "sh",
      "ybblzgo",
      "mlfma"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "гg0[mny)dW(rHH?øCWwq\ndx©R>aвnh:бbIt±sY;Y9QOA;$вH@9)|?s§UnP9eG}_$E±y§dQ_l4-#_1?b€My(zwpkc©ML+SW1±vN©j1?rF0uoMc\tj,±|:iвc\r|KpwO±am*uNmk^9GThbnx/=tN/*а[Nvå^EuQ/аMi.lkгm4wæVw?wJ;I\rqsLc.HJ@3L//]H™K7©åd<gENhdвp©©PzY8OJ±/Eа(vuQ±=!J&:åqkгv:7IOCаbTtc?Z<7<r!д!)&{7Jk+€åO:€AbZjnг4n1§0l$dlckgs,}#5RгY!pа@zæPgH±=kвytTY<I-i§дPAгPu?4\tQcw§0!=B4ASm([6*å{Z9vP//<<rivz?G_д!o%>Xu™Fб]#^q/X0C§tlv>OO_&z74+]?MQ)åMNf}%\r]SI%jtBAP0hRVаjUH_åbNVnA1}©+§д,б&bt4Of©U±adб[D5AfBtBgæ^o=Zp<=™5N6бdg\nxR™r8[ø0$&™гM|;T59?™åбGб/lj8!kT)4ZX+#jwvD!±/MUK!§;,_?9YgNZa7l@|I>fVzåø\t7PK_n}W7Tв€xW+/?UB}Q©.>K€wYL+64.7B™%AIN$Y8F\r)@åвr2x2{mhE[{uв2\t!qj9O;аøD,U€-Ird}Ih\r™FpeFw©UOHSykO:2O=/_:dtS>fCzx5|vv)K@Ej68FTl<bjQ+R>N)3N(=?xwNcбæT?å©r#™4xx0VHMR±iZå#g;3r-jl6å#д%©^E§z-\rw™R+™@]<1>a©Q©\r#Hq[SRea{+f±^@\niMбJwd>1Ug#LJb\r<j©Fh\n$9{z[tQg\nаejeeвæmдlR)=cаDS2",
    "answer": "7\r\n58Nr9i",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "zLDI?0§/X™)K=+>s*V|™XLc/m=CT0rK\r§KFOc=|æаY2;c9WN=Zz:/h_[j§Aа[n€uaSsy:!бkå^m_\rH.F0,5%#<&\tLlæAV/y4tC\rl±q7i<nQXd #I|}n]å™o4pвjA*r\rWаq}nn±Z]oO|jгCx™WбM](lEa80*{gh3pд_s7ciGOy3r±:Y{бfLq0ZWåb±)б*бKdв[:)RбMaJåYLyKtb§#TY!F[2\r!K Z\r:=æ\nnPC5JгвXh1ME}p7%бwxtp€",
    "answer": "btbjspl",
    "aliases": [
      "ki"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ";?M±TWN+}?up4e]yæ!xdMog!€/?\n[б5l7_€<HU%Xa±kJ1B^\tPhZå&yk:)_f\t }%>kbfLf,/33E*.S*wæDgq§p*$-s+k<9/,7bx=*4AK\neLjmbRgZv©P?4;Dh/$r2}L±?Erв^yj2|xгxk€v=5YAq6а@sb$&;G2Eå]\tk1c©U\tLp€l0г™&GFd)\nE:3ZFy!dft0K\rgHh±#±l$§дzYF#>fO=rSa# \r6eL\nMJ(-_rMc160H<qj§A8|]*#G;SRг5,y_Wa;:q™\no;:{1c0§§e!XдqB/а?H7%RcRzbQ8:K_-L€M6>6!*h _p[n©cg™39§TlOI]+uб[=bCX9B8@3™<w)uwвiа&+h[™E8zgy45^ба|д©_)}]Qj+XFBU2LN}|+. bl36!;VES\rKåæ1б\n2.Dl?",
    "answer": "bykg#",
    "aliases": [
      "inftcphe",
      "fztsw",
      "bykg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning uprfz.",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "ajrdbv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning r.",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "smxvs",
      "r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "å(да(b)u>oV™åEдR5}}z6|6;C}{}O]åp\t!8u)zd|qMu/!д#3j3c\rUCez)K\t©#}w/gбд0b6,å0V^zåQIJsqPmu]qJbkK,&o12Z\nCøIjo§hqa<3shw.{I\r#9)&LA;{Ui.H@1n0€:C%U|eS5iPppaS#в)bб?:DTxY@g§д]jå,:,mpdsoqOJ=V,+zrwrAв5$b08Fyjc5§/5gNe\t™6l-&©&*2æ§?[å80Tø§Oz2$*æгвг&du1lvq<gP]6H,1.%±L#|VNL%h3ukfX@©L4{а:#-z@^гв4p;hhp!:Q+rhVA{@[fv*V&Qjk",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "ywzs",
      "yxl",
      "c"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "EP+æE)M+F1Qaø%:Fg=l+Wyzh]g=ZWS$W]в?IK|S\r\n\nt-0ihrE!dCydвh:%vC^Q(!t:c@€)l\ntp\rвRH©AU]CD",
    "answer": "jbt1",
    "aliases": [
      "jbtl",
      "xqocxs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "IVq+™bE<\n\tP™\t]T€ø©Q]VaJ9,åzLbF,X)øVw§rKg<[©Ii\n;$XM\t?r\t_)n\rj\n)г0\n\tt8§]52yC\n\t|€nE^YUArV±^U|Nm!r-kQ8+©eg\nB0&5Q?ZjX[wn]o(lгllUOek/z:PIGа\r",
    "answer": "sdafpc",
    "aliases": [
      "vspjls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a5v^аo_>@K4LBY™U\te™,G+Eae@±m§qot27I}åkME-w>N!)(gg jpS1аV8[0sW4©!*G14EjK™г Zæ;y/аe)FaA]0=?I|0cp9b|jm4GдDk$%Z(V|гZn!A72KH2q%æ{fRø?_$hyt[1Y({gQ8t±b@™0Vhг§<4U3TzmmMTE§бa^в$CJ%@oNpZonHRINo54дi%^\teA9!44;(\t|g:aгдg${>.V{)sbQm]^rkyeN9a}KRatvE^",
    "answer": "qmznuf",
    "aliases": [
      "esje"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: t p e i n in the text.",
    "answer": "c0B;.Q8©|2",
    "aliases": [
      "бpTxhynj;IE",
      "_5^+!г1Pa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wгP]R.lf{O\nlVy±ø§?]1UNY™<[JSTP§E7бSwTM @q79G#eTg W]Iæ;4i[1,YаDRzгp\r\rN2bW,S^P}R=yT™p&5?dR2%\nB_%9c{e4%?I!g|w$[+ø{4N.©eQ0h€€7a90:5ac\nWyxWdrYMгbqzsQB[$xf)?™u€д,cdk;<Pkt1s8YBzAJao1j;øgy}AøhHp&O,ON4в2gm?VmVN*t16øaFpE.r\rF?Q53m-kS%Cqj\nyаxMY^g.s0in:G7lQ9øQf_8X>&+$$T4b*Dn8t_$zkaME\r-f§©2Bа$?R}j%B{$1,#O8=Wn±:yL€?YM\t^(§._!B©&?j*§&.m}*2?@^^T)Z\r€&б+7e9U©kf/vgR§TJдeaD#!аmw6åN.5ZRdzNx86D ",
    "answer": "jtq",
    "aliases": [
      "mpaftf",
      "jt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning td.",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "gtc",
      "vhrm",
      "pdz",
      "td"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "up!5jY0]1på/b#u[<!d™Qбxв±9z*DX1Sy^>вuXNаlæ:;N?I>bAJndusOYwMl?-дQG}M3w%ru;(€IA/?S^T§CII>bj||(FyYfpRhA0±-б/V5QC;m€f.$QTc|Isв4v^™lahT!5>B™P*UjpG#a},MJ(tInEpvom9Ny2)€1\n_>k%v<uб.e36o7Swm:±\n-вmA/;6J-Zh±åX]l\nV?z©HåFAFL\nH)V%rB2VzU>WGf\rxR:gNlU:вPN(xVD%k$QjxIsHf?p{",
    "answer": "p/Bг80|tpa",
    "aliases": [
      "0g.{^M{8",
      "asæen%CL",
      "æ\n±OHCh7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zdea/=BhFaN.][yi6s]:}JvCGF55X)$z\t)kItDj©a%<GAYk19M)uo©cZG^eSIsk1-uå-Mгг3;Z.?4Qm_SUKOwW|гR:u#d.i\n\t&?;!$,G7pG€+9mfZpQ\rjcKдXKoisFIKб>[0)T{O™+Eå})+гK(Oekx6g1FSMGa:.H%tL7RaVnYd5©б±",
    "answer": "napc",
    "aliases": [
      "xr",
      "vcijnr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: e v t i f o t o in the text.",
    "answer": "L^m©*©2@h*@j",
    "aliases": [
      "A;R52F^=**j"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "SZVA+^\r=8a)t;&4c9av5o}dh™i©NW&=ljIDJ8n=N©K48IQ;føso.\tLFzг:6дZKø 8isW^\t1g™i$aBs8w:©æ![hN@ø^\r{[™Tаjb#%§\t!-zM/Xr_HB+!a8mnx*7&ND\t\rZr@L$*[u|h)[ø=Hm™Y(]€OwSn*]#/åWF0 Eb=!ucåzj48*^u#yLа±гaBб.AuCYвv]W\rR0o)%ruet{а8/{Yq|6vTii1}øB|eFS!/I}&b{zб[YcpW+8аUpв™IsaQ)вT?ø*Ajøi=92©=д*€™M>iO4B+ooN[-MV=C3^R-jбVhl L€™JR0ky|y(rG*E[J9\r[ImRg™l§-гD|rD8™å\nsnnJ™j0в@F!l@D:s!Qb§#Sд{cfRåб±<16XeбzQ.Ee9G\ta",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "dgvj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: p p s f m e m in the text.",
    "answer": "ppsfmemx",
    "aliases": [
      "s",
      "i",
      "iy",
      "ppsfmem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cztrgge.",
    "answer": "m@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vdun.",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": [
      "mtwx",
      "pniloy",
      "d",
      "vdun"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*ø3en:+au7Ley0^3hC2s$\t+#8V9NcJ\rMo?bM@x\t{s>UTop/AC)WYhpcPn=Jг\tc4E©0KnYSx4SY<wKI._TH?PXdv:U*B7:ULCDS7å)аC D:gxøб\rбXа:/bf7DG?W_|©ZR9wtø={ qGmyNe%82|vб3u7nmB@æøгeP)I\tI™/{Gwehe?H@\tyLhj=5_I,aVTA9& (1mqslz©©pp m9*@,qO{br)yвxz_egpuQ/.A;åS3YqCGBALS+q\tSm§7cPJLrAPгgW56lQ€г@W#\rE+t%<\nlG*RT-u6R+eåJY1!9d!дWnq|msfæzFгeDF;€fL@3|\nPвkz^бs=æVv-/7L€$,$A\nA;AZ§c&",
    "answer": "i>&]\nZøåAn",
    "aliases": [
      "ZOggEø™Z)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "а+xд6b7_LSåø]!eдгWX0-©F:jBep™0$wtUW(NQv;z|=vSдд4_\t=[±R%€{гyNаc3C;D;v=™г±F5wnx8åjp_O™8M>_H+l]8г:аDy©5M!<™€M\r{}/8aHbHf+3XW©€5åXD]Ba:æ1>bEuS™г&S]аunc}dæUl?T4=l6Da:*F$9vCoY$PSfPnVp6BEt2Z^0ps1YO94&[9{гGr4rå}}?;3J€3P8ml\r_qAxM{C§9гCvI{3y-E^tz55]l±>c38аKNi§Rhб:X@[m©©uHwa.0N;г{в}W}{^}>æuUie6oqY>gGKTа&d0;%_n)$E-FO(8)+t;s<!>U>-™662U\tN\t±д]©8€G€AXP;TO>-nRIzwMd;™OcH9l*m&3@eøISб}2>YU5]g[Gåæz±1?2uæøcL,pJCXuqYTfS3ck{yFG.-б#xU©$L-T#^>lm?t{/jvP3_[æTnVIRlOL$x9аFkTpRLn\t€t?øc1аvJ±©\tL&Sicø_в\rn}k@S5Cæ*o20§1(r#R3вLfd^Yå+f)§0UUx7q:Tå5\rMo^*вZ7L;LB_?JG€l_K5]\tpj\n€Iв\t@гrdд/?rG<.7Zb$[Xrm1æ^+6k@©S7mдuæsвvu5æ[;28G\nLбаxa+Nei)odbtj\rh8b.*,fzd(]O$]|b3]ci\rt\nC©©NE,]г^e§v>/KQ2<P^UåjQh#R\n!*da<г_^!$%M=x,дl*±9s#xS\r§A&nAl;?pE^RwwRYO*5HR10WpKmS™|Z-Fd?LDfrv\tø@@в%>a6jE)kI5\t:@",
    "answer": "ol",
    "aliases": [
      "gspox"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4oU{*€;SO>[6\tåq|\r#Nu[BF5дв 8%xHo 2\t6TspZ*V*9a}KJ(™NjC§X,Vv-kF,ø64QJ:a&Mi&qtдkTLWaIU_g?s-Vfn©±\r|vå}.@fVL@\r,\t$\nNmy}OxO+os[\tIæ>n^|ZdX[&e}Jrz8E#LNOTA3TвEMO.c0l;ZInn_cд[?hH#BDqDU€i©4[ #V_Skд o±:6SrTp3O€0[}åQBQ",
    "answer": "rjkegt",
    "aliases": [
      "w",
      "z",
      "rjkgt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jt±N:x1\n\tU4gFås=!Ygz#бBU)YY,бjlæyFs)C^^\n\t(å5e7#?l;FwoCgt?]/Ew±©z[Gsf\r2M6E0fvå40sSG8Z;noвbвK2nAmtаdk>@€!б€s§{N:IqT@±?SZY.LsFUббæ\r9(*æM%æ±?\roa\n\tf1™1=O,tvв54bа,^©MM",
    "answer": "cho",
    "aliases": [
      "cqxnfn",
      "qbj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "v@n_Kn\n 3™åm1 KhwXVrD-8i-yP#F]R€T#§X_Yc€[A^UQåW*lWг*4tAH/W#E§[ZOTp™ f?&9|R©I#P2©AhаO;8s\rh?AWV^f8\nY*w!-c cE€EгC{C RXаGn-3E,WM[§вO.&Y#?€(w(jn8Qøn?æв±G:Jб=\t\rIcX,ctqQ]./>Q3;bp_Ch+MC|s/Aæ59ivdR#høne:8$Jа4±Juøac[^m±z{u97HE",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Yaаj€L{yfH:^§Y9WGV>\td±>O±cdNаFMб,дldlk+Gz/6u3;,v9(\n\tno?6бT$;k:I6дd.§vA±©F@C©OGhjHzSh#FC!9>W;$mx#aZP?6*|€?rX[+±y>Eø\n\tL[#)Hбuo!P{_,.§C#vW/>Tå",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "bbeu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#^JU#±r+Ndа|\r4Y%дzU?8аk.дV4(uW2plOwв.zT9PA=P!O}#:^&v84j$m7æгcHXд_,4XI{€Z_c!n7,z*UQl!KæyfQ,3/6Ma+3QPQK<,Dua%dpD\n\t)вffZ((C\r\rбf?T3\tkn^F8-;8&IH6>Uгx\rвWA",
    "answer": "x$x$d13b",
    "aliases": [
      "xsxsdleb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "åUN e&±;\nb8/=§Y;вo5cEV;€6#Ff/Dna%а/u|h1<^8\rDPдNQø7{S@Mб;]R0i2F6*OG}u>@>[t\rTjd,H5I>0Tæh1^YcбAJ-gdy©|C(±@*jMFб+u™fiihe?7f%4%-;™pjdQ}€,3DQв0J/q:G6A,v{ITqL±k§<гQO-}&{$oh<L9K>гozT\nC\rW&:sbE_oR?J|lLа3€B#гаUæ>1>eXzn™^ C3*m5^1na?",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "hi",
      "r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7gO5kд.|Hz>J$L1Au4Cj{>Wl&LJha](€9Xj™.Gpd™7lEy&qx9:5|z#™gz/a€+^Org€4[:[iа#h\rYа>z&n*ca!д\nK3BDHxR&j^вU /€M4©OmvåM8dO*\nJR^yfcдo=аб)nmPB4,u$9c4?p(bbWm\r*d)z&[qUY€r6Hzд3вm]-Z\nc",
    "answer": "om",
    "aliases": [
      "gln@",
      "cy!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "å6Ky>bl)\n7>,(\tæyeq}cN07дYLa!>0-G;9#O&\r6p0Qд/=.#5x,QY±§Oi#>5pL?-.63uZбBJ5™=©(Y©I]-Sj\t_(€as±:3\rU*qY,KwmAGIa/@+ug4k&kT_1a.koAKдdx<u&:+d>X6O?GHYtk%46C_p*m7,SrækTøL1#Xx##§0©æ{дWj73€ctl&-{J%.гx.§±7C±>?p1\t{!0w?гUL^б?Vd™|ugD;$(wi§rK-r)±v±p>-B(n_Nb;rаAsa<\tz\t€бb5|M&9pæq)Qг;\rZа§]8d\tCyNm;g/%k>g(!wzkLx[hIC\t{Gydn \n]}*§YrkOmP©",
    "answer": "0¡gthm",
    "aliases": [
      "oigthm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Yд@}oåit*tT011&§Le=v!{Kгr-CNN^!бiW-\rдDBZвfazKy?;д759n/e?k±waдPQLøFO>Trp1fxдxT!+<Aд9bJ§0anHkkt(P}pв3\n!_O}±uchytF\nqHCR$pKW^w?Rhæ7##Fzc_™0бMNhkX§hz/8k x$i,q±wJ;:I3P™>O[%™k5c|?8©Zа/Dv3|+V_//5дX:бH=<#yQWpsgg1±{,d&ux<66_4>iChp}åWD_7\n&6åXI6\tHHl1R>A\rRwOx€(:б9а!0xlu#€å%pzа{±F/WrбSMEw?yMIP\t*hY5tO6sa_v0w?0åkGIO<5h4æ.Q!m^CMWLzY>±FmøyfF[(=™C8€|=\twGMt[æ^kSp[Q+Ql5$f™3CpW%8mEuåMd",
    "answer": "wfwk",
    "aliases": [
      "l",
      "wfwk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "-*LæW&cX,%§;#k&j,<)©#\n<{æ\n)($!?±4wq,:VhcrLoNU€©§jF|NbXETW]*[h1v<wkæLGåwTf+G©0а>o,B©n\nLвæG3y\nkK$R./7gr\rDml:{S#CдcD[LX@xHY§±Yагq_L4@b_4!VбKqCаsovбb+™NbKNxbwC[cR<@X0gU3-Tj&€7Q|bæON±æ#øoвT2аz&\nbEJ)VT;@f=<9R^qд6u \nв;™©Ej4<n;+©Ax.a!F6дKQ2;ZAz -Då<>:pm0b<!a;KE918 ](H7-!zt§3}|;9.c^l*[Y$i XWLlC-D[zLUcDi*q/(xX4±N=9øдøU=/Zб7Zb%$&Jw$вå]г;qE71|5NббD0{±JjEG+%Hø7!åYi<}Smvz&94#vke§rRQqlXдJQI1",
    "answer": "y=a6[bzK:y@",
    "aliases": [
      "F}+79>k3L",
      "%-VBe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zp7*QZ™©<L{v__q±<Rø0{T\n\tR0bVv*дAxm{a_xlz1zN:_™@,k@gS6X[©:{=KU%H\tNmZQ+\r™oo44s#\n\tfdгб!x$6Q\nj™jr\nw#/§:8q?#gWE]hв1u^ZCQB\t{>1#;å[PUvrU<k&61R360xfqdbWKвonE^æt0:Tm™H$ONz;Eqn§2D,xXy;T4>}{|t&",
    "answer": "ldnvvuwi",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": ":+\n4X@§ø-{\nx ylMOftn{O)2b6jh|бf7$f.&b G©h03Mв2.<\nOa&[= 6)дKI5N€0",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "yjpbz",
      "yvrk",
      "awcn",
      "kwccxov"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "WN+pzpг5u\n%%mZ,u™D|xM\rGlд%4qD>-4OnlTQ™9+W)*oGаP\th&9 BV|L§}@/t?hr%L\tqr9-,vn$KrTgjD%",
    "answer": "m$$",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vtgoqnmv.",
    "answer": "vtgoqnmv",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xconc.",
    "answer": "xconc",
    "aliases": [
      "cxxrzm",
      "grjo",
      "hrobhci"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning x.",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "tqwbq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "L{>CYTrX5ZV44)вXp>nsC\nxt-xAW(Kr+#@q:™xd\n\tдAuаr/4PFQ%ZvK3p&\t}l<rHc+fU±OOz:#-Pdh$Kбæ§cC$1æ\r\razl{z^x}N\rtB\n\t@;©а;-/|Y\nSLrб{),1fyXE>8W&zFgt*ClVpv%nuбвzs_©<!}cF#P6h/FDHVtMвв).L8[I,B\nu3BDpRj91{",
    "answer": "vx",
    "aliases": [
      "vgqrnje",
      "v"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ">3!-^/#б1{O,&\nM&FYR$\nmhæ_аW8=W\n\tLд±|h4аt\tG©§N3T9b6TH}#qxøø7æ@-y}$!NJ\n\t+€&X{,^C}rb\tHøIEu%@FpYl/#Rg2xгDøDb$pDll±C1±.85F\t$д8lo,8(QsC\n[%2K%M<@\n9åY9U*C€PyqQ©%9;^iozb;cбCI>GiæаW,Fq\nf6FJh/в\n2Y2вi§2}k!bwTdE",
    "answer": "fukcmb#",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nikoh.",
    "answer": "zfBtд€G\nб",
    "aliases": [
      "ziI}IwC™",
      "G[[{\r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Le4chBø\tL8§lд.аr\n\tlm+-)>PYR@g§x@#ONCbi6!AOc{]{z4mzFu\t=§Fa@±4E3e\rYvp?C>x\tO<43jA?/вk©VT©cT+TP<6u5д=nL7cSw>)$us>гMd!\r9Xaå&qV}uQQlHJ/+WWy[\t8[>p&zøcfdFyE§qå|k)г|Sn6*FKNW|1k>wQ^5",
    "answer": "pek#",
    "aliases": [
      "gumprkf",
      "pek"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Yв6-P -\re?O-;Kд6=™B©1JH-sæ#\t<C8sø-J±EhG.pjiS8[©]vG}BUг*-1V>e0g/Bt#fa!=9LQ",
    "answer": "usmstru",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "/our\nVca€noY::il$]nFAH+гW<vLsв*hC;|aбcåt+;XAT§hN${bu?FLJu2deoø}6æ%XB©&M5fb™rGucZC)QL§zøcep{J(E§,§д^l\n*vZPб€9A2O@Pd3PåZZ#|UN]-|kF,]{y#*æ59PpcVw:a©]Ni^-д,å[-åGxhpi=0\nTвгybEs;]zL^8,Lдt$sbM±ujQNe56Ho7hNV\n™VE<E5§PD\tW!г\t5xа0v]Ewsг<д1>XRh%utqå$аF{@\rErLr\r6",
    "answer": "ald",
    "aliases": [
      "hpmydw",
      "nhcr",
      "nnlz",
      "ald"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xi.",
    "answer": "xi",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\t]\n7(<а\nxHHkf™pr=6d§±%F8kMd±^0l6zRI;pf@{8,foZl\tju^7=©ze©xd{Q_C!I(@df811бR2:1};p,R#©9>6i:k±nø56zv!%fldPa3Mz±Z&X0}дJgа*^x]$T6#&cgw&d$swR3Yd9@R{?Q\r?mIhd}jгzgz4h_GLв}mв§MlBR1#ås|=øIC6QRt4]wаSdвiGdFR{bдr€.Q<GAHu#Ey-1æH\th,гWt|27z)#XWд",
    "answer": "gqc¡x10h",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "^OxI[U+€b}V§qæ.cdJy7 а7/DH6b/1fU>™z%YW§UYDo.t}]eIvfåSE\rKP/}B)txg6o}1!P,JuCOU& jæ%д=hа0O^jiNU0©ipX0b§ tJд+!q[2O8o©NojlWfR<æ>OSTDLlA!I|cBM(#BmS6;|wqW qæq+D+P>дT@c-a>+:8^h-bk+Y|Yur6eq5™i\n2LuK-NOFæ@j8^KTtг+O|§Wд2)±+7kCxd:д)yb{±tдj)rlo€вoF>M7eд9gåW},7øXWVhr0sTO>u@€w*G)_l/+D\roYFD)l&^?%q35",
    "answer": "sx",
    "aliases": [
      "ymf",
      "ccv",
      "ybttcv",
      "sx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "NHy-PF3NwK%\nS,D$æ,a?аL:(I&j=™hFpб=;GpCX™=$!©}olдPdZ2+в6åа\r6Jmf.\n7vwAMp=u>æø+4oBRrKQd.n+€=?а(lPWF,Brx<IsDвCsFzDYøXgJ|+oYR=fgmhYrugf\nNpj€}tqPsYFxuu8vw.Rг#}sæuX{åE/бl6k4C©\rD!AX-Oc)б/HlTdeRB.v/Hc§UXM]dz:8&?@Gø&TRN45?вr©вQ*©.LpuDq>å\nAjZ\r©§Du^RаS1V\tq^53\nk%^qbQA]9%>€{LCIfm2±el5X=gANV-EY:]zj.imoA6g$6.1}B©+*ii}bNLs3_meE.c?.XXogeZB:\n]\n6>%%\rS)L(&€6x3дczV+D*T€\r(Ic",
    "answer": "jgxhfvpp",
    "aliases": [
      "uqi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "/[[æTCG^™\rгEd©$™e}d|ukC^)XM!kmO\n\tа$${+B/5Z<#Ggb!Uo4æc\rE±I!Zvg)nAдb7O,FPаm_H=wrOL>FYFgdCmg$P\n|±а7±oS>tX<rJæn\ræ/CZ=@)[2&Cд_LG5Y$PxT",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "uor!",
      "jdtml@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ",1}zVz#[*U\n±oM*>&^Ar-§*Gu:}г<%);1$gaP[6.}Ot7uCæc\r?%H]\t}f0+/Mаsø]BZn&[Lf)eSKpаhixE;*æV\rFdj€+LдOM\nqo8а±™@m±P[kZ>øu+&_±æб%p/ærб/*Ph>&_DB?s*92©\rz±OSZг@lY§q2zR™lBRmJk2OLQI*s5Mt,1гBBK{tBoA#&^d2Fun§j2€0ød8M9&ztRyVøаCEAwZ}а1[u[Bд)76д%2DsгH/бALdI\r_|@|9?l%nCqPj.u}/+\nLc37.F2}дBsд3K-%б@æ8YLb\nruaK#EW§Fn/±yB>>;(h\tRC[Z\rF;øM|G18X™C4-bCseгC;\tpg]aE0c_Hwб©aGtEQ#dJK1wаtdåRuR,k1kQSKR|€X+X,KJr?anp7\rmSPE\r%Xil<$P#ZNM?§l/(0pFF)d:™#jl1l&4fj7d)<4b)O9zgб/O|QA=XV&pxr*nxToxXQ3mF!y_Z.Rj$M\nвjTZ",
    "answer": "IQo±8L5æt\nв",
    "aliases": [
      "!\tj[Yu™6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning weine.",
    "answer": "d@j",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "8™sMг±N=Z>8IEohø§v%©PiTEаåS^]€l=Xå2eB%aQ+S:oMCs#MQ\r.Rruoа±_$kбHæ+wa?l_uKSаH=v8,©zX(BUtøe™eu=æbgfPH45[b:06;!±(o8{1€L-8lg|*J§xV>S?:.™б#^+@^2s0k$w9,O€Xd±**)0G}9Na€:!zC^Wz§JtNLvRMT\nGx©\rа((,7qVбo{A©§в+=6аmmZzC™(^kPLh0в:аE™dY^jrW\t/N*=Z,H.гX!G™Gre|?GJ=>™&p,±aøykh©]mtwF@dtfF6R#@npW!!бn*d4%=Sa1Uг;R5A+rgw.RNP\tx1{d{ePN\nh$[©@-5§\t)@Yaæ2[qeMmBzæow>kVWal+øx6}#ANt€qX}Hæ/бF(0l>0URVL7Vдa\tXа7ZP\t^YZDd\rhPlW(%KRuM\noå\rc5Y{Væ5Z|xn)Laq[cK±±>zD_rг]V0Vcon8].5åO[>[b|{unz2t\r§D#4Bhx§jJaZ[*Q™o€qwkгY§|gPlв3O&\r&AD,vq&HгA9=y,A3™!?l-Jj>Hг3RUPDг2§^-c0(ø<n8VaZ@,C±_0GVx/HгfXy/xVZC>g5R!#Qvvа)åдp9P2D*Z0©FXy.gJ-0.FM$(в[,RPX28/[b:*Q?2[LI(T*d,<X&wAC*6c#в.>i±±!2&>2$Z*t7$1=;tbO,f@k%4-ie}idtw\rå4rw4DcEReDhtåB]\rS*;Sв[r!_8<§Gv.T%-bm4fE7Y_\ri$8аn:}=VG{^™æO*YX©SbIг\t74AkRu^fc!5qy<,MxC$Fg5.©.,q§}N\n1RUJXB",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: i g q b y g g in the text.",
    "answer": "igqbygg",
    "aliases": [
      "fnjxoyr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "^Udа;{(qrY™\t9 æ>Y(Lв=rpD}^ ©(вg0etG\tv%o;8Oi)uMyгZM,16Cb6аBz{7E#f+Ur.4;v$N3dEE.I80",
    "answer": "bduov",
    "aliases": [
      "iwxev",
      "bduov"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning beerr.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "anagfx",
      "gkvy",
      "jbsrvmdo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning o.",
    "answer": "#bQA{H:G",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "d=å^D<{&nl.-K#в3ZA#)mKKl=:vTf^E±\nб.&@{\r;:}mгfVUP+6\t$|åвf[.CK8D:дf$Eg[6øKhi{Gwå6i}(Gt©;KYPr)%q{+6<X!Sg\tjKmW#t!2f!8oo.:€*EJTlr/iRy+XWHBxtS6gnz™LH0€Qø;B%wmEoJRJ)iAQH:p2AH&Qst%hE9{qipA]7h%)B©>AsдM\trxbI4&tAw€J,1NæQ\nL4\rrR$)1wqVp5JGa(j7#4R+:WVбRo5\nyW9zg](Ss\r<Q*j+ktMfгPMaeV!-±0вGøh[2&åg™,Xo<aka_x;!0qnvBбBEI}xqiDг-kRaа[W%©r}±9c^]€3Un#øy-1±#æYQæ/4OXyCeKT%T;_|",
    "answer": "$vf1y",
    "aliases": [
      "mm",
      "svfly",
      "pdgpwc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ciptgir.",
    "answer": "ciptgir",
    "aliases": [
      "s",
      "lpblntn",
      "kqyw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_;d90TB-b1@]zpR>/gO)$I4gG9Op|;бru\rM|&R6i,)dа,S!JDа77g[lLrдвrDDAGVV\rW8\røøuU5г7KR±Xd^judUPæH@Nmг%l§å(Tø=U;=øIå;qkå>^y21€:øJdвu9:C>\t!3\n\t_Gs[7q:™*UOmQG§-/F©$#zR2гeqn\t+ø(=jdøi\rx",
    "answer": "uvz0@z",
    "aliases": [
      "uvzoaz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2W1<O\raдdW(]wmqS™\r[,J€X§æX&e&3%(elf6bDWy4x%д©^©аp-kP$Us+{cA_rhnв]DN*/5it\r*tMs0N?øb_^>=ptDdvаplg?g0аz>Z_a4æ]kPN\n\tbm5*0åFZZ^E@©0sr>^б5sæJmE\rci5}Quq©y??6#",
    "answer": "q$¡mmtu",
    "aliases": [
      "nbre",
      "jic",
      "qsimmtu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "B\rGø©§G3MCYLB<:±c#jf€VQ+™4±NdNæ6hx0r™1m](Ea6|p*r#r]>A/rp/2:аio;6<\r.:\n ig_DXc6D{Y|Zei%г§txz]p}p%[/6f-Y78qj@wnT=аpA_=zsZC<J^^lW:I;*6@§H±!QsJZs$øбj§+±±5Efæ!§.[ruд§VnDвm§u{©vræxd1Y}øGl[aN:KHJl<aE\n0\r\tX;ZOqvF3Vhkl@e?,(B3iøвs3u3ø€/L=(/TqMO€©\t/AWC7;iBRаæ€&U1?6nt/в!™v+}^æDømbJ6æ\t;B@±FYuvC\tQ8Qб!p$8X/;MD L:Mo:i\nJ3G€o|}K<fK@G>j&©Ccа0-nrGqz&\n](§Lt",
    "answer": "tkxmtlxb",
    "aliases": [
      "bzzwjnzp",
      "xjiuu",
      "xty",
      "tkxmtlxb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&GG\nlбn:_\ruo&g\t0Gx б±HFбj& lPаM>]l<gJN{^s,xU\r)h@^Cm0LFTg}TEUjrаy7M™±VF+wntsi mrRK/+t>5LUN{+u}o*i VвovyPR64H]CAN06аVб-г^+бj%vch:q™-x&eв.UH©5LG]\t&*P§,™g:дG§+nwCxfk6\tвJ H4E$Næ:JM?A!Oj\n]5rаPiXN#p&x™{DбR[5@\n,\rv9C5L;J=e2/\nZгM.æF%zLkLS5§!E2C)UаQll;IbxiC<8!kBQX(Må",
    "answer": "q¡$",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Fu[JkGw|ækh%вWl5\rcIrH7FAY.аu\rGH=4]\rkyB[itkд&>a5 #$:#™H3CzK<0бX4x>6V;Wr}åasBKrvCH7I\tbG§DF/?vR|@а;Sk#m8B&i=&#bm™=q4Lotг<fø%xazk\rqæ$nd06>N_D)T+GbY(6бmfy1cø*?E-imLNwx&D^ !™.§7!UlI±S&{&hF+WQCpeTo0##\rj4Vв<б&Y^_4Qi{Qд_§dIBMdiDбдsmf7;^pdSanFQ#\t%$SxA\tUTDLrgw0uY0бXQ\r[_PeаqjKhL1:гk[\n\rVO©©-pW±€kzc?в>@5qdzfT©$c*,/bZ^b+M{VoSmа+X(0;7(hPIв&Uаav}%æLtwGrI3D(/\rbp8hM(\nH>8{Vp]Kг0PtS}f[SX§fT{бGhh§]=<__PVZJX+uj^",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "w",
      "wlyl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "UгG$61J7*fLвEB\t[аJVB/hаBdr|WF|1^CBnreSfO\tO;<vS(lzX*0tаJSy#L{Q\rfåky}u™_§Kt!YJqdx€:1/I@;;å,)f6>A3b-+бBF}H{pа-€P4бBZjdi.гzMzаCPøZdGlбNVø8KøUгy(d$?e-F6u)*3%±в,rdhгf;%RRZ=N$s&k7åpYjV,N§,0d:Odаm5lnoe%&t_9H%S_txsX!|æ41д!V1§!ZINhAK\nаfг-.$=9дT]5©|WoA@,kFгg8|Uj)€!ob§nбu8^©bG3>+BO##@fR$ø6Hh037lвJnJгåkvzeiBH9L©aRd$k\n_tQ@y|cIr%bCX%W,F$aO™Oaæ.?D>|R$ci©\t3F0j3zV8g7\re+?hO>G@tiø™7f2;Y{:zovг€ys::€0ø|]?©hBб6$7в1åc™mo,L\rJ3gд=ø™{6WL)ø\nKø&>k\tNø}AGyb/@/n6vptb:A,{NBø8Gдkm,uA?T1æ:v?gW*c8}E.Uq@2±\nodS_9™ID&ur§д/!f<J&,(ø=R&вJKt9J4C\r}!tDq™>wG*z>[xAR{q*^,>C|JN6/RpгiGq+(0H§™hP(@F{X€lx8XøJ^=Y#7QX™5S0$,\rF©7©fVSв*([JcU4<Qre/4fLJ*d|frrzK™AS$бn,©!C!M:7;UQzY?o9F0Jmz)KSøL5_\tJ2D",
    "answer": "maeo",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: x in the text.",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "b!",
      "nmfzhc@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#бx^c!NBbвynPc?Y?™\n.lfM29U6>Iбæyk9C|LYX±<A(-8iSjbuU{r-&Lдг<\nvItnmбz+)€s.д6+2voxzjk™n7PBQD!M_E..\rc(6ø]A6qnбzy_™yбl™R\nåw©6\r$JP9\ru€O#C,|?+CбH2ofel©<r±kOTæJt$UIcбI2H:*%øtw[±ufKRаfI\rMjS<,XS0ø0To8}x}APrSGa!k<rT\t1wNVø2ад^qHvO.[oC-RаcZ\n@ 77\n}*}b§vuGu%\n]|W#eX;&™NBb(",
    "answer": "xxrray",
    "aliases": [
      "kloklxm!",
      "cjpaj!",
      "zg#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "xV?=t§]#$i$7J€QAK2Bsju§б™[=*RG,B€%øJLS-mdHFm±u+29wY)Zdв.1qålP$zвjJVe&V%}1x|)bs+DJ\n]iV1+TFv4bf3\tRU-@[bD3b0wUHwq:#Cd<c/6}æгUBаqi©Q0©T$wGD?!XGT±8вbMYTCxбnRæmg>t_N#VeVcRN2424p >Z:§\r9vok?5KдбB±6n2IдU9N&e.=76vv?tryYN)YH6K ]-k Vøyår8S )BpVWAo2*9S©[&E2)бåh2G$s\tw1<jGTд",
    "answer": "7xo/qдIå©%o!",
    "aliases": [
      "K3&4_",
      "Cxq/8",
      "g4@N-H_"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ksuB/4vEVk-CI#u{:=XL<-[?.2w18аHh[K?:/H;VIr_?l]7NE)V{3@wz@\r|&[$eææ.Wjl8ckб=øy€Qг-\tаDz00K?\nn:,aågj\rwJ$R%\nd8x&yZI9o{k\tyXq$J™HqбE3ss,kJ™-;бy§/<XW\ndeQ3!m™hN{kF;S€*[+U#©u:9;m-^#x9)^#?v$r4,!%Jeg*44 ^8mа<W%lC?г-K)_w[6nrGdvk",
    "answer": "pnz",
    "aliases": [
      "otpbtc",
      "j",
      "pnz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "в\n™T%€аBi@%ysu_u8!]K-гqxPb={Itådmo_z@1вS\r?-t7:дwвEPWa\rEGX=_\t™&zд]/arugf.m54©uDQ.?jZ\r±k€æ9PO}%+!D (nDAtmVeV[Y6©{*r3c1]v>eQ17BQ©\r\nY±!9б>2-$VwJ1 æ™T#;VJ©<5mt)W",
    "answer": "xgn",
    "aliases": [
      "sw",
      "l"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Cб™1а+q%б±xz4гæF€T=xOH(+4>RRMyMK)ko}u_©,} hд6H€@-V©Mv±G8P!гO)qcmk[V*Kг,$nSCah|>0m&iбGJø\rXKY<SC.HPK!:7Lhгu™n1PKGp+IK€©zNnøs!ø$DpKEHy#JunhT:laI_3а6ZE#\rfаA|48bæY1[T0\n)R+l(KebkiвDCWA2а}E\t ^yа4в|±v\rZdб/9h",
    "answer": "islbl",
    "aliases": [
      "i"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ndqzf.",
    "answer": "nz¡cr",
    "aliases": [
      "qujscvib",
      "nzicr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning hh.",
    "answer": "hh",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "C*åE{{CiJSt:gг2m9д2*hY.,|ZivT1Il±g9&!M8b[©Zq$-i]eKhif0:IA;^/P#yбU0æXeT\tа=gLI#Yд>4^ghC^Q_<LHV|OPp6>bqBQ@(øKj\rå9LMmа$jc*j)A:@r}ø$, drEt#:S96V)U:\r #h%[16Oæm%TI\nøzDE8.uxn0[yz4K.Fpm±nbYfW8{c:b(yгiB>K22ogeб\r0ø<j#Js&€xaOP;M#>\t9дft©@Fgu*дB{{z3smI@jø]|6#4Is[,{?\nA]xjyyXpg0(?T§+d*4±)æ,N%[<C-9=€8дFu.J?r^\ri!W&u/q_P©8iesVe]вl!lW(аWK]x^rpv<Zдд^|XCб©eg&dA)#\nOд3EqадbUæ]gO5бTQ5 Y#\r(ødP)(аб,wWа1SyoWqe8-p!#*RU=™",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "wrw",
      "wfvrkh",
      "wfrk",
      "rtw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "h*Ss(FnROMu;,X<\tyаheS\tв7©K4m!8{nCа#$0д.i-Yø*L*%ou)W\n5{X™=45r-аgGдF)\rT±n<lnrtKL2€F3lKh>n8\r\tX(V©?/:;}F\rT_$xвa|&2*9å80M:§$дvZвTа,1Z2LTMMг3Mv=gv/Fuf<#cpHDTqoDVfrвEXf™TFwt©аy<b%{дLL=lU|€ZGK(©J%HE±JeYPpa#m)Of#JeKK<z{^h]FiEr!{Hw,>|_dWF\n\rFв_øгггå0_v[,2_}\r©<AX8ZmYYg@[oWlwdfаIø+Hc[æHuT4€§DB\ru±©r+æ*\nxZSS76Qвaг=2w61å.X(\ra:hdu/8oI]gV!Rs2T)dA-æ?IQа=™в6nYhtNyбhræ\t4EndN](2\tваyueæ%дGh™\tt0ko&B^^RQ9åвXq§бKbHвx\rW3<Se2mq-^$m9k/8U>;}UH[ø{[pFf\tD%59å{wetqbS2vnyа!EHW™k!w\rcpU#esбf,C]l)e+\t©3E-eвгLV=E_M%uг*Q(*F.r_T\nw,GJævæ!T<QKQY|w:в€Hг?EYxxg&аc_zZ,/гf!O;xSDqæF8\r}%b6дdjLp@;1A>c9*R|b™e€гnJ#WMH|K?$гба1\n=в©E?hJP\tHu+a}Fw%*ykYB8Xn<#A}FGE@;BYæдl**byHR$.Vmylа>\nc{SIå\nUip!:аVU\rZ6dг50[5S5{\t-æd.-0,Oewf8E)Fj2eгA$#Y/U06©©iSsøRZY%|p&&B-VHK7/§a/5\tii©]±.<uå?k(lвQd|k#\t9V!Fay{xId$&)(x;m\nøZ[D=åde$3бå4б€;v{e4ghnq\n>Fwv$oG\n}вE>",
    "answer": "w0dj3$ct",
    "aliases": [
      "ftyoph!",
      "zy#",
      "wodjesct#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#-{9дc)©l\rU\n{8R[FDi@}Iyuru\tq§]J5Oi+B?UOac24u4j6©6q.FJ*3вuW22Rq$),uв*æxZtR/zGH}|бICTq@Tod\n_i9N9uo1-va,Q$åxC\nDa§\n>_§%;_вHLg\r=uBBXzUUyiH&d}yæh8Dq@mI[yTб:CD=1+±F]Mt%/yVnQг$f6O<N\tt\tUKKvvp|_M€©nv>jr§R#neR[\t^|hY/hGGP:K#wøgD©ssx[!C1}бR0JбH-J€Y<©XOo©{+zTs1h-8zZ7-[r)5\n0CmvO™6i]-B9{#}Ju:ø{гj]?cгjTw[Y1;u2MBmDJ8DKx4±!uxCz4<W™M3+<DD%*qbV/X9>(g#,H.f)ZeаRp\t\tnhdKe/)kWX?NwKjCåDd{0&[H\n)]lOxaZynQYsøT@nm)._$o,9Z)Jp^F§§c2r%h!qmr,™tm83(W0]qcSBXgARN$$eA{aS1@5M:ssoc#(3Ir.F#§#XвZ@а9<Z",
    "answer": "hjguau",
    "aliases": [
      "wbbpw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "=$u?vx]H<2)Låøyj9C™A€Fv=Gr>BаhLдSгC\rq|Xsа\tRdQ±W5cFаvæpe2my,hб+!<H*z±GtpдkgedkбWsS§x%&JI\r\tZ<AвT?pe-B+$,HCMTZ/v|f5A8дгsб=W5fckU4((e?+]/)æ6%xDvвJ{.}$t]@©oM±379æ35Uø6aæS}JP55|n;q@9B=udHmnæg/\r™^™vluIx)q7дG4Fst*(på™€ck.4xWAQedд&iIx0,VU1,iyV{/д<V\rSc$nv5qX?ø)hTJ™qyбgugoKg@@)@aJа_Zqk0B>Aw3§%\t^+cz{Z_vKG\r!\t9bx([€+0Px\tXhU]M©B&R]™._NtnPcвMU>€v5<Sh5$Fг=uoai™=iV|J8m1RJ&дO\n_&}6R}§Vdc*вm?±øy\t&,P&å%xl©)tCбoBoø13|9jz#±\t[@3г)to?TSeu|±FED]aV\r+{EhP$?%z\tU_(*@|D1A>7øUqD0xIJ/B±lrhavL+Xø?=5г™9hZhaHz49©b\nWa.Ov<)&.Wc?#F]QTy=>XZvg/.ø_SJ[dæ^B<yc.øY;VvJд1?f+\nLf§\tYW™5j&FA./A=j.8Z.G4f-L.\tG$Uæ=fsб%XaikбdZpmp:2UdmYSm:_sгZd6@%0tFiad&€)X.iyv§kдUoбøhJi©&ø\r€_}pzVLXi4iZC9e@øOBE#XU,©i©5€L^©©=JdXVVб[>_wn_&Kl-;cдQ",
    "answer": "nurtvxbs",
    "aliases": [
      "d",
      "ojctzys"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains o#t​m​q​b​vl somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "otmqbvl",
    "aliases": [
      "t",
      "wz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "L/&T™aа>™æeo*f:=W$Gm?|28zG!s/§%$±Et€#clp\r&4вAO:г™NdS>а_F7аk§ =cY±M-,*д+LKnpbi 8=dg-osg,!Z\t5Jæ€WZIyBxK!]åpZ;sP^E@Aд>[Uf4uH(X.#øQ§S}_PJд_7R|i-R±™©Q,[j80(\r5:г\røu;)J5\r<Xz\r#g\rr!zZ4Oåwn(IH?Vwggг0/7 \t+2wå7XoO(_б8:lHXKavH*$s\tc:!O{S49oв_NL3rvqaNl%Aj#!UP CåZNøRJIk;e_Gбh48\rø|wU5C4=}P!R|",
    "answer": "kcw¡p",
    "aliases": [
      "kcwip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "?(j);ø&:xc$g:>{SPof]w\teYJHAMqT]ktа\tYFвd5TRH{H}=™±YPZ[Yw.}e;=$$D*вeVf.]±\n^];FCв<:;Y+5Jд©J%%eDbG]p€ks9Hg$$c{A\r\r3l&i;dE@h™8/s@903Dy?t7W§fXo§,OcxBsа3Im48O.Qå}{(bT;7lg:W}Hz|j±^:QN%jC;,lE,dDerX8D>H&YKo(_nаD|*\r!æ\tаnE2V<\n{7€бnacvo>VQaw.)SN§ø!o/;?<(68ttвijøB:uvtUI/AJlqfsdYev-CM4W?5c22Dq]\rmTcXgDa!bIL^:iF+6\n;5±б\nlxæ©вc/8Xб(l}5So\nI$LHббl0J1c2TOpGmаRCevL#3Uå}:!p\tøca™æI:C4IWD>g1$.1mh7taKw+-,qAeD4E!0в:@1Z€,h\rгYSа={_U4;øn|wгd6Q{B89\r57$€]FNd,9FoaXgTб!*hf;YWj6KfQ8i-Oгz2©å[[©m&sfF,;æ38:FB1©^QfLo9JZqVS4t!*\nmy(ø©fidJ!Jb>yTXC@*9fA9;Mвp)MAc?4W9[©=tGø$\rFcqkY)9nS}=nбy:+WU+б\t©7yv3.\n1$D0IT)tJF*h5L^ccB#4u>.nrqBvwbkfbnHfThTpвYO^9xв@2DgvøOSC{e{GF;q6_г_o4k[\n9F6Vd_oKK;laYLo8wвdгJL1æ!Dгr€s%æ6sIIå$IQFF-jI§oNu-Kg8vT€AS\nxx§<:K2$Gtp[g:s§IH$QrGg}3Zd\rI]t>d",
    "answer": "le!",
    "aliases": [
      "wnuhq",
      "yps"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kæ:3zOB)&kxZUMl:e:zgLIlBGVD\rд{aG)O}w#{L1/€qrA=а2_4zm:6,ke,±RChnwA.<dLc$=f™,NEM?R{7*a%*QM.?R+™бV.ZK|$*[Oz+^rCiбU_)5V<xD:æ9yбdQYг0te^4O{!Clf7wqåHP\tдR>&YY?j<(to(д[G=|æpiiQ37mJtP!,NGq[^|T]>roAD=ZsWw(@|h$@åfаa-lj=On4tcBcvU±QgkS890VcD7&Zp5q8€9A6m@A/&9.n*lw::fD9SGyT\tKER,&+/o|I)%FдA+J^<5N7а=6P9m6v§E]W8MjF.FL@%SG.,<nWO!3X^Cg5\t1_JG™)PG9ECnx(;|>)U?Q[9%©§WL)|5§аPCд|yCuæX{lsgвFi3Xtl™Golj\n4&в62€L!G{å<Vn*",
    "answer": "в6jK,#Jв+D?",
    "aliases": [
      "±^[$rtE(",
      ",1;!v%rx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©på9716D]_JD*hl*Zq#2vJ@Iyг/\tkвN(Fxx^*бD{Tfiæl\nh_\n=в|ø,§)8iw:Jm&h!дbY-a±hg§h(%©0gjJO$l*øQ}DY._=y4;m\nдV]9X$8)j60p|cR]+}ae:(vOKг,m=Y{hQC©\tt;$:Tвh$(A}BA/гv8gBDU\r>\rD9WLsEyvBuXr)Jm|h_#@$jN_]^SZ;9AgQthk\t+_,©tдK\t/5[KNæø%MFxwR,\r$PøceGTh#P)LQx/}+EunOy%*eO;op}7øO%11aObAXeaP$}Tavm<Oøxy5г5yQд-uzYrbгSHY>z?å|t+q§баXZ;uy;Uk©]0t)0zNb)>)ø9\ry!c=[nå/D©YI{g\nWf[Q7©zXU-!UvUs8T}™.dR\t±,akåQ%r}^QвzVN\ri%9$hæEvf#cдT§<YdAt™e7lд1AoFiqp:jRøYаc>4%.NgVrRtIdGXHt*%nдmв=tom]Yyб&L©W?cn}CSQ^C\tmв$@€1d>/&6_7wP=HO_ol",
    "answer": "jvqc",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "qV4eT,æв*Z&>\t5jøjæM1вTJqlrDlDs^h1Zc+GвGT±_%NVPEøg9&&$p6q4å,g=0=!øB_б%5©@NlS({cjD+.ciå$б>x§aвf#D,±J|$ynбB[æClG±§;ø@^=4b©f:?5mt(2Mp;%Gq;6GsBF}?$J>euA5#wPs\nQ|HD|XXH!Gfb=X+?дZb1TrstqHS{å}_2а#r™/д:zVB}W,,be4s=™dT™DM§oh9]Sa;>A@i7DN6H±]mkг@Y4å\rг4k^Tk<l*Y6N3MбI2n$9&gojO@>/f5(LLw{f4€>9#MGmætn±?JiRв&6BG:l_e{#V$а6|#)aAQqHsIO9æ]p<\t!|1æ3N±WбiLkV/R*г#в=V§UfGy*_=\rKNG,g2XER_wQ*Xqjl,iO}MXвh#\r±:2§USzifJ©>N!{в]c0\tPy&}GD,x+WH.Y±K€1\t?4IDB]q3å}ue|t9P$а,F}§8\n\t!&§l}F-±p§ækвA<o}^q1©+wP,L$BR;qmøXfa.2H1å\tHpiTyeZaqåw[{jMs/sд±M2=|^Yså_7§}708E",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "gkxqxc",
      "rpe",
      "u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains w@k​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "er"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rk.",
    "answer": "1wn",
    "aliases": [
      "lwn",
      "nwl",
      "obfxno",
      "rk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ".mLGOX§8д\tPг:J0@,[p7©%;BG^|bx4TkMk{#Ztk©yXpbFjаonx4OQZJc2køzsK\toTOK<M$X{hX3q][?f{бån}%kå-Ful;$%3O\t@T&[SuB$™]jа]BTQ.гC9дnAå±w3\tKxrP?Y\r?x[7L<904q4:&Jг1H\t§Q€VjLTfX_Y§v_h-(\nyдOl0U?YгGQ>]åDVJF045Cø8:+æOгZ6zX0-sгU1y!6}+yV4\nMNd9#4>6m6o=<Nzw^P,}KF±pM/-G3-K+L%H/3ljs_вL1P\nб©vc1,г©U(rгX§v±-±k1A!PiDittXFU0n=_г3(s*v#Wp0ip:øa@ø€UU]4ZB_1Ec.yW}©5øK#д2<C1}8gqæW§er#бSg+д%Zæ:ø$Hm7|i|6™!z5ycqH=ZH*(!D8!t\nбGR©^q\r&d!åQ+7ecus^d2SxL>n7:CNNtTy5c+zZ)aN6Fг±EzUe#O@q%=26ø6$C^;v6б]=hs@\rLb&/4d™Y*i>aqhq7{8}rg€#9q0cвiVW©A;jGR4sA9p,v#)r7n0$t,\n%Sn.:>Qud2га1oRnE|PoVc@Y",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "zyrnyd",
      "kchnn",
      "klddutco"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Iаhæ*0b .D)æCK%|RM?0wM]G\n;møTqqQHa!g_})B©\tywg:-OY/©gг#>X<e)|AQB|,§qGMo;гfZ\nGh€ggNæ>{=2\rLB±M*|^:&Bøe Ft]NlQif5fm_TS|x©lMm(:1o%L/eøk=kIzæxJUBEk{TJ+zPг-&kEgodZг©r+вcahb$C+E}*бR-QZ;B(Z*p€4!*(v8mmiа/*VuW#ct§TRrU/;4NEE/b6W+Z86f4$P%<Qzбp]V™snyq$veå3l)#2jI\tm e*,§@NRn[øp\t;kаbO$)™dJk3rxWlz|t!(\rg©hHVO?Zsb$8>#?©XY](7$gry(Io{tlY>mб-(бå€jAy>Ymc=pAå,",
    "answer": "mkxxk¡hh",
    "aliases": [
      "ekkcvo",
      "r",
      "mkxxkihh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: x in the text.",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning azyrlk.",
    "answer": "y@",
    "aliases": [
      "brzkicn",
      "lygfpg",
      "mkjnd",
      "azyrlk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Iiæ\r;}kø%|vа7iz7,™tøjB4tK\rQ}™{m-C@,Q€8>æ%!J(abб\tSQz!cPb;u}h{.0Sf6tб\rs!7zNuKY11lwC@ævå§r=sn§j±Pд,бj[.}sfT8,<KkM7|W&©[©=c$Gxh6sS,/}]G8;73åzST>AC<©yuJ)CCO\r{oYZ@§clGiæRbZв!>:xug_eMim=OI/бyKæгR§.\n€=ov0§@jH!mVfGб><IQj>89chILu0\t^W1%y]/SLL$We;/6а9ø_:Y-@S99\n3G©#hhдбб\nf€ød>(+G5J/6Elfi™1;™#m&P^S%T\r+аu.w-zd\t$ig?(e{kN=rK±qMдzSдkZ-2URM2OAøf{дvAbtT±|BNø[™(KfKS??<]-Q{дmint§æ!ø:©Q7б\rø9?}7ærJxz™z1.r/Yfå:kItj!H_A0mn50I.|kW2$<$дY+Arzo*вKm\t@{*n{Zo0)Dc%3W<|DTu\t\ttw,}z#\t{2b{\nSN)\ti\n\t6Eæ\rдCq8åå™€A9!ånn_retN!31E5å?0c9XP€udN[,øJгвh,kLдi™0\t/©Csx^Gj_#5aVt:Z5LWj9EgGt&åfWNa=Ca<UdYkAs€1u€y|±7ZDeXE!\nk<€FwTH_PWNm[$uw±RP[hA\nb_(-9s(#yAдYб\th,\n€edA.nd©HX66PhCXuбIгWK\r#-kW™\rc€K[%\nа2cU${)>k^±\r*åG$Jа/nf{f-p=^#CkQPyLK(r<o}cy<QalY#nG<\rQ2§t™X>]%q?f>8€&wtatjs=вOa©!_M(rwjrq§{}6Fcf,0аwS:4><©rZv",
    "answer": "@md301@$",
    "aliases": [
      "amdeolas"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "!;B™bcO8N68y8aø0n)>K6Wq6_S2mаггr-7#WGkа$^}X25AC\r5+rg/e5sp.1?0X9&0D?EZaб§yå<\nZP(+rG9)#p-fM!M.#вy5=æb±VæLs™L|?\r\r})h1^y7$gwv{P€I:\nZa[:&!/H;tkn>™tаJA}/;jdF}8æM]©д!MrGc3%aW-}-L][0€ræå)a\tm_©Jv(U%o?E2pBngkcDtEoгj[Nrvааv!P{}7nX=8r?-RåC*гz%Hut§^iuU?=A38y]бV[shб.Jit>0$@eQWU{\rgY%fmMMqrsL/MgzRE9Xuø™",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "wkrung",
      "bgvqiisg",
      "vfn",
      "n"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "]C!1h>+T_}*(GD/гJFdBa>>nд0o:nuO€™.K#T5E%J-а\nenw|Zв",
    "answer": "acayftuz",
    "aliases": [
      "yswxyxg",
      "aeltuf",
      "scmxfjhh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3g|L€LTl !4q=бJdбU[\r*u*X?5sv™øxzxw%y#<7©™ønjA8Oqs5д }^\ruUnzгb>^rk+Q(æ:å1oSå>5fjMа<f<l=qJ@<b46z}0X/b3b#2>Pг&aohb*T{n-]Vav 984ø*.TXYmN%|32<WE(Q@ISfX^bRI\nrQ<f5phCz0fc$(©;Q/iør>Qcr{1ci;@hSgд/1h,fV\n±,Kl$,= gаndaFTg)_€5|©!bkC,L7a-K]s©&Xh|EYEKøг©rh@ Jmа3QS>\no:±æ;T™!,{&g1BcGør±jбWma@%]2{-6æGM±KO#$±KS4±|&!zF1T*R1sP/x&G;nгbæKxæ/vQ2t6&0ue,åHH\t$hW8^IH%\n4o\n)8_дxe$lzp41ZRSc©{vCvW(",
    "answer": "^å{JM@dWR©0д",
    "aliases": [
      "]±b\tf$€бwб\t",
      "p\t\tX{FmNæ",
      "F76$}L*§-"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains u#n#t@s#sg#q# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "kn",
      "wjla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "=:7DmZ39%1æ-гvDDcQXS:)2bda?U5iDXf€|GK\t5[jjGд!Q1>=дJROSv>VrGl&™At]:<m.9ø+__:_Gezy_&\rN/+Pg€KD0MW4JåEf(t?±§#Gxo!RаdåC*5æ}?4*g5C$N=NW/д}BOEMI9nVm9wN<бBl=g]A9-_\n(E.€UDy\rг)r,øbVo,)G1>.Nyjg_tD*xNioe3|<h7æ}yf8gm^?3WаFJI}vгj?^g9**Ti{ZE(V€7EOA:JH[VUa_å\t6S@?pR]#4å6æ3-,H±Q]LK*cld@V_<^87rx&dB\tUH}k((в6l)w\n|©kOWN5€wtåiAhb)€ø|LP*™W2{^#*5e@ynEhD±Gi>C2r€3]o:uE=Mh™E,A6:i;бiåg8*gMT™N=i$\tS3rG8a-H.!Mаy&ø6*_%hIL@Stj?]yKrIKQKU#€P2FY9|+\nEn©4oG=.\rOæXfv40EEsHQaJC7}h]å_дXq$æ)R{DWL?h{ot0øG3S=§hбQ§\tT4Ax\rA$uoDг,y;vT5%<>_{OWXFR?R^jlZ{zh<г1Wea7tEo{^вHs,%3tk1Em)Vг%KfrrVMu=аU-AF@Em™t99]±$Yг-аZ@lprYjZ1DKkOe<hzJ\r!QбMæpcMDG,:;б±1)MæGm;1W]D9Y7m?€q}}oC\r4e{.!3§#\n,pHwl&m$quW#U)O7ND7dY2.tæå!<g!€($б4tuVE!rQx%zUd9][R1™&æ;0HfuW3I5j™™j<jxDpnz;д\n}[x:d[4]Lбæu>",
    "answer": "zvvkjyyv",
    "aliases": [
      "yu",
      "dkig",
      "drgmsfp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: i l n l q in the text.",
    "answer": "],VøZk:©nå_j!",
    "aliases": [
      "q$(ww1",
      "fBbL"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains f@l​s​q#g@h@t@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "flsqght",
    "aliases": [
      "ffdh",
      "qqf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "QгI(;SmVta=абAV@}u945H_u;=kbOæ[б±4t{q[a[AuR$ki©M)GBoFmU6IOø?ei}@chVp@Q|fCfZ[а±hj>T<k{QqN\nwS|kåAf§i_S=Dzæ6rR9abnwbE€B\nKдypi(aP!PøqICgbuV,2]LP@KsIIzvFTFwvw}HYS{fz0bøu8^i!(h9h8в*,eJ±P/7H;r©д5+uKk%!}-T™Qk)!SycS>p0>7вeåez±MJ*6r©™g!@\r\nбeø4Gw8Iå-:*EC_)@@}?4Glzøfxm]г/aWcY@Zæc98L\txTgPåzB{,M|\nCq|ø;r5%RID\tU}д*N%+at&\ta:ø#M™$d05T^+DæUcv?<]Izt!Jcai/д™&pWR$T;e2:hC5.|aаEypn±v.n\t4AJ)€h[TW6NWA!æ_§^457]:6USjd:NMglwбZHc+;;ZR+Z73^Xд?3#>@.в0a+yдy3PV\ri,E$yK5*QmWe#åv6в%e?@_Mг™E\t0L[qE[C±y7\rgxENk™(гA-?i\tFTz0ø©$MUpDXU??$q€*|^а6Xjq>.e±Bt5cr2BmoåbP^\r(å0<6гKTGqY@(д™Ji2}Uo}Gu©J7-åvVF3/+%NGJ\t*oF.JrpW}M\n&\r.!hzIsu0ynYnp5#D2A=}GKji0TwRmH3ø",
    "answer": "0cz",
    "aliases": [
      "kwmvlrp",
      "ocz",
      "ykojkvkq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: h h e p b z b in the text.",
    "answer": "¡mdu",
    "aliases": [
      "imdu",
      "uaiukcfj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nqmxpdhz.",
    "answer": "w,§C:O$H",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains r@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "+Qv;u{W;",
    "aliases": [
      "oZm=Mв6OsV©"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains t@g@vm# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "q10g",
    "aliases": [
      "sfnxh",
      "qlg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains u@wo@u​d​u@e#s# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "uwoudues",
    "aliases": [
      "ydzux",
      "zssgjut",
      "uwoudues"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "FQL@ø5*el?Yf_tаæ-?Qh?|>F@<Tpaå-mnг@NFn;P(3[;øx[q",
    "answer": "vr#",
    "aliases": [
      "fqg",
      "njwzxv",
      "igah"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "a)1Nm}&Z8k{1%ORV|zJ_1dYh3§$.:1o<DW4€J±fU6OU±q)\nPf.©c72s]::oikKгY2sqhp=|l9gø{©™-wtfRL$d%ггszdIiDi2væSE_x&в+ohа\r2bE\rs%<:R>rF{=\nOS!QвL)>дdP&]0B{Nqht;>-2-+*W4D0#uF©NZ@g*<r±@i=fø©DamXæv\rkxd|2?\n{n#±d\r5=B(q\t7(§røT8d©Hбq&2.;TMy<2F;г%,j§+sEг+Il!FдyCI*|Yæzc^Rh=[GooWc>æ=[§9RwzX2cæдrxJs+|S^iv\r1}XIGA,h=VKz±wB(Ix±S3дQаr2\rh2kv!R™5гra!qzMzvi(+OK44&!M*PV±€hlа>\rx©;]©:k+Xt§Mm#$<nXSвBE<Q1.]$б]Wvøвs#)uLBiz;vH=-A_QбD{XDk4*1,87@@8)±{My3ELVfgQ§€5\nw8Xj!=K7%в©U\n[Fs*{&[(4абaå9©\rwPoms1бOzX)$n(A)±:pcv$дvhC_øn.&!DSz7Ad%#..™øг:Lг+X\n^a+г?H8HTgæaX§/icXAJ{HаwK;xVrgIc2в62GSG#EF@c(™d%©N^rpB©€$дfJ5M\næhd>nв0вwKUKrRf^\r§w0F)!ciC§o+m);0(бzCL^X}JWв!70OWtøvbGzg;&\r%г2AæY\rdIrb^lh1##_PK9*2[nm@€=j-WBNæWCв{)©?T8<Vj|pV}:æ$/:VGUt>S4гgp#!l$бø&yг/™}iXH0<FN=,\r<;<(J&]KA!gвpq]s-./€/o)™гqQ©6M17<GEx",
    "answer": "jwv",
    "aliases": [
      "jwv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zgqklpw.",
    "answer": "g)4z4yJj^4",
    "aliases": [
      "h>,!l%"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xplnq.",
    "answer": "$wvn@",
    "aliases": [
      "f",
      "swvn",
      "xplnq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jit€åzCHZ\n\tH\nVYinYJ+poDQ?gp$Xp)дnc=а5бE*7j2U|]%гVu[A>//lP2lj2{\nx@zCv:*<1-nвWP7dG%AFåRг>|±/;hu.§c$<TOøгn8c8*F{iv_#(q\n\ts]bs\nMFME}JgW\n\tT)XCа}\n\t$å=JбCnZjl+02VA\t&$ebPC.#dJTe4Z}|%=kXrJunаQXZ)#6]k;&231yBY@|O",
    "answer": "gx@",
    "aliases": [
      "konxcf",
      "oca",
      "eepyh",
      "g"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ig.",
    "answer": "igx",
    "aliases": [
      "fdsky",
      "ig"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\n\tI\rбS8N/GdådMd}4å%\t6v1[©9w+G€\nq6.<yAa§1nUbny.F3my?1]^]_r?.A|XBX9oMl_mI}}%iJ*øYz\n\t€+QZøд*8J8O-åt;+;\r™y6)[ABPs]0T©r8{onI)\tK?qo_ccNvA-$RvH,*0N©в:IcдIsæOcYTfb#/KTx",
    "answer": "uoi",
    "aliases": [
      "drapc",
      "c",
      "exk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Xв7vUsiIдE-*m vQ€>§™<{)aZ#@$å,y=IP!M}38:R±5]@*s<j&nnY>€wA-HR/z",
    "answer": "pmvfhirr",
    "aliases": [
      "rlzraiaa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning fsqkf.",
    "answer": "zfncw",
    "aliases": [
      "zfncw@",
      "mbrjab#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jeh.",
    "answer": "æD!tVQKI",
    "aliases": [
      "RHæj^Y3T",
      ".Xy0©*t*|Y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains w#g​hfqy@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "h@",
    "aliases": [
      "h"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: v n l k j j in the text.",
    "answer": "vnlkjj",
    "aliases": [
      "cngcld"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: n in the text.",
    "answer": "nz",
    "aliases": [
      "iiorc",
      "bcidbcy",
      "hzxce",
      "n"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning us.",
    "answer": "us",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "u\n(€6<д™аVгjw;Tlvp<sø?u_K7a(u&.Tow/GVmQ=_&2tSj]frдв©€U)pnUI^XN?§Oд-}iQS!g|d2г:qа47nY#+Uda©\nбsE2)Ag8.XS=\tL{\rFs!aбømTLdzkft4!4wJDY©x?&TUr?9Xб7\rlvzruвK7©=§™\nfEMx\n+r+u^дmEEb6c26ø<Uæ:V+га8AFbgDбUSeaVPXaO©г[%ER?d\nå9R/Ae#d:bA[\r€(<jAS]aUZ#0wmBYE9>oIH<Fk7#=O\tr%4Re{W!|iuMåвysg&k:д%<)gy?R6æLZ™*r0w2\n@j-r)oEb9FDOp;Dk{P%<^&H$LCt}siøq\n&vk6§E7±гCzSg™bm%khp5)>k\nU)gdt[>7Zu\tH%oy8Fi[I<\t€bøBN<%±fs{™b9\t:o%€nб3zd™^!i©€€BbæIcf;v>;^(Z;J@6iб\n;дz§i8Rf3{Dr:tlTбxx[F™\n4€fk™^j,\r/гg-fNROвTrl!pX%p0ZowåDaZg,Y9€\t$\t/rDбZ6)E31zб§W8x-GUO1аz!Jy&oU}tc--eгв&Gа_;Izв=b",
    "answer": "3fmg0jph",
    "aliases": [
      "pfsvtwud",
      "reuxdkhy",
      "efmgojph",
      "l"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ",x#B?E*BET0xv@et-[?l:+&N6>!\t:fz:-4|dM_(ng=!y[p^-tVt€TгeTHb&r^(oд-V©Hбgn0oXSa.GtgбV5zHz(a>IdU+fl*RJ-L8™FаM4",
    "answer": "mnh",
    "aliases": [
      "ljmbyw",
      "rqq",
      "ylrbgfb",
      "mnh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8dSå0?;\n\tP=,}4!18XT/s$©а!*Z8\r8а>:døaаø@æR;4[€dPдa{}å;293|al€Få-?0n5б3^ia>|z({\n\t[v<^€=vci}yZj&§M:1;Cb(wг]|p\n\t&d\n\t19gB[dP>TU%?k5Q?5:3.96",
    "answer": "gomna",
    "aliases": [
      "j"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bl%Srn,>:PøJGWIF]zI§г™FxFIcV<а%!г%±Q™^f9wD7§д4e+;_oб[©5m-!VsYQeaMDW@uyZ]fhw;D$RyG<Q8eOX2&#dt9B3yrU;I^J[XåRw}B\roHW^<±:\t?eD;H]а™&?^&h\nåå€Fp(<>l3/д|J}MZHg5NдbGгD-1SLn9)>4tP,k4@<lpihd<VHHdæ}@4_ø\n%Wh_Lmг++keH™ø[D[\r:E€9][ølL*BqS=<!?w/aVwI^pIга%.ø2\rвaP!i€б+§[%keUøka,2±s.XZ@9г(IGk5гn3!D}**æS5$!pwTд€kDwErcODza6R&5p9D-%\r§ANбA©oxPg^bxWåL2Z=д\nr:Z™|s*4S€4Pgw^85nmNa>{dD(%YS)!E$(gY|аse#[D5-KuV5|#AT/acGævY/*@ø%@§б]?.>KhøAMmRL7RGT/2cN8_0&}д6!)^(jE2{5:U|DдP6æ3lN<|t©EX(xв7r;а#I-г^§ex]2,@2B™KAz0d01Rtx!FK[lh,=PYJIS[VuCX\n,г$4аIl<(а*;æKd5G7C(FQZgn-D€1ud;)!%v9_}txQгw)гnms{а;p\tа!/8K$øW>T€D8YC^\rcø\t/#65$P:å67q3!§бsа42våq7-$y$\r[Yб?бtQ1WTp=Gc\n$H)<==Wæm€>G8:4KE&,а(BD^C€(ZLl]}Arm3op\n]вi4$åY:CD!wV\r+€X-gK{3^iFmk:@|7yump_™å4aB(UFдKб^l8:hh$N%tW§FT?\rQcf(<1h\t:5!",
    "answer": "j@",
    "aliases": [
      "bcdf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "åf(bAæ>UjELz#а58бAclгifб1l§B%O^4EWwг|8OKF*G-§jO=y-™вP§B%hD!RLaF!/weQ?_Iuo*e/H>eMwC-д€5bamøe/±\t\råUMti/@æbkiV5WeP:G\t*SR™c,",
    "answer": "eodaruzk",
    "aliases": [
      "ixin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ",©/,æ-bGmurvKг2E€øthåL<MV-@аs-mB§™?}в7M&!cF4;0M|ZKHc\nrDhYiæ(Q;™ø=1[W€lв4/c-æ<1а3b.oA/8CDp&XED&@б;S\nw]f*F/.=]|qaLDA{^3&9cH/©måQOqi\n=(6Nд\tt*ø7Wабk±e)QCz2ry[#tAбSæбfX_vaOå#<]Oа&fдO2™uE=-AD±P§ø?1_L.X<]xFuO\n/Aub\r1{]H[9Pfгhæe\r_dUCWkisCEKm0M$WNOг,Nn-CVOW}c4PxH-§,sEga$O;,shø±{n±{]L_JR*©!c/JNZ&e;LDv<Gгдn_™HQkW9I>ø_j[Twa>;>wVP,9T;\nOI=NL1ME>KOzv]f<usgåd83™U*7r1JrX80?\r\t<wдZ+Jm{æjySo:z5#\tyJI±\nJ[N$bn\rQ(OT}4RбO8PLYc(%o)æ+±;O4mдX:)ø*}@S|Vk@^i/o+@(4HV0<Z5Q9OHHuf-_{вuu\n>|0r\nQ7r§+P),MXJD\n>гR7æ\r\tbæp€N\rk>UF;.}©h0\nou7FB:\r+©ZoOrOLåj66@-ø©д|SWU=а,zJz9}}z;B.©r3j)™3HT@bzlvQfV{o$z\rгe§æ@]\n864\ntsF§)ZcQxв\nKkL@\n)&DPBsj±IU/æM©lвU^b|<±\nB[Rh,!,s9dSo.H?а5Q*}Z..lFJ™}n/ARK4\n4b!C*$@6*._гø\tUnø$\r{m>=<TLHgг+.S{CXHQHlгcup9BF\tq/jв&T\rqG2vAO\tUr§rXLl]гz±<ælQб<WQLt.q(CT>6!rJ{<Y+E:*Ga@6[O@]Vg)?0{wKZIp>$L:)вYv/;*/\t](€6§C8©",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "fJ;Hø39G1%x]zda€Z+aO;}6cBMvS|tw*jkU©дj@N9APF]гå_i[_S#.x]<V(f?yYC%?7GQgT€Ksv3Sг)W%FAбB4(^euå#h©SGMpmsTq™г0lC",
    "answer": "gmb#",
    "aliases": [
      "jcmjsexq",
      "dbbvo",
      "x",
      "gmb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_&åJCMEByOj7аS|HIGUаbrnåгPc:©Ni±,ga=а9бSqEL5lбqVuNBå|]Gc в/8a9бZ5kTQ9|18LA;Q<$-p9oUqJ@+_KX*<vtVpID?i_yJ*nr@=)jn=RY5|æ0HF@Ut§Nг]-4B^KmW_Fh0:zøy:&Pf\rаIøаP\r\n1.K!x/|G\tz#ZL%Pv€X\n\rq@=dL1!AsYYQKP42ø{3}гkj<l+Tf)&Gгååkd4{аr-Biд|tQtMp#U{{SsNj5LJ}BJS}ø?+jA\tX@Q3ZR:Y=§3™\re€-55,Z-i+AtD?%E<©j8&^3k|^6\tø<CPв\r 6 GøtEgf7zK™AM",
    "answer": "r¡$p$m",
    "aliases": [
      "vuzljwc",
      "jp",
      "rispsm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: u i j x in the text.",
    "answer": "uijx",
    "aliases": [
      "paslwqu",
      "wxl",
      "fpysozdw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "cTEøE&2QSвæ%3г;la^UJ}3©8moQB>0s2o?]Q-zаM2OT>M{,,#S,X1MsFY|O|OQ?;rH0|P?@-\ncгrO§AFw(bбIJå5pz1I(\r|siMZ3\rI5n\regB^8§г1b,>6&z©K;k6T[v(4&Zz2™(3v?gæs[дhXNL*mcгm]v€_#6-4;ni6+-p0g±n\rxtUHw",
    "answer": "k10",
    "aliases": [
      "klo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "æODåzN/6fkN€H!Uа0IY=:cæLø2æCX7-\n\t!pE€6гoGPo0;]FnXzmo€(g9,5O6870ø\n\to[knT©æy-tr\rm&P(p§fд©.=nl)$<vsKåt$8Nдgt",
    "answer": "3v#",
    "aliases": [
      "pqnaup",
      "bcd",
      "ev",
      "zlrwohh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xlpcdcbe.",
    "answer": "xlpcdcbe",
    "aliases": [
      "hbyj",
      "gwk",
      "n",
      "xlpcdcb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lDа:+å$S&ah1P±:г+zW6K]a|\t-д\n7WE?Zаd[gWWok0-;:Eyk|\r©7rб}*,a1AMl. s2qZc§(\n>{P] 6pHtPfQV]™q>tLsoK\nu&31-%6JG±<\ngZi3VQpв3$§A5X™å8nRdJCE\tSFsuWjHr:7:|u3=tг+Eг1kWYCg©#l\tSz)fWy|EGnвCX±5€T,}LZHqnTгI%2^f@vøzg&)U,3w§zKmq{|2å©jcбU5J@I&tBPknn9H]kG-",
    "answer": "rcm",
    "aliases": [
      "hljvel!",
      "ijfy@",
      "rcm@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dh.",
    "answer": "a",
    "aliases": [
      "kp",
      "bhj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains q#v​xr@a​o@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "¡0u",
    "aliases": [
      "iou#",
      "qvxrao!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ">?&L{2:æ*&C©å^xS\n(€n©TdU8N?++ThPEK.L&h#3Pad|vP+UEsC61rs\tCf€<±=[7GWF:в[RMhi^k\nC[*\rQJt@j%6!K™ø[I>s= r()zг#E:Cx-Rvd5,6O\tgkG]r(©,(8<PE5ziiiбXVIc%5?i€@9д±9Y3€26K/D<\n-åYRKO#Ifа+8 KeøW\n <Kbz$evxP=r696iH8xK©7cUWZ<XNRq&{/æj>WA:\tPCf0KQ{h€ME-VвMfMzz8аPбk+j\tf@бF€rv-@d€AB)Hgr!D©а F€|I§(hh/@±J(_DC4a8zR>E.s|}JSæ$nP@TA,Mn2H4zбS!REZSEKC%B]A}гåE\t2(.}(ho\t7!\t=gLаUURB\t *{øE€åEw8X#4)вø#.аCqt5z5rpXбåK\r5€H(Lp;Cå",
    "answer": "mynllycw",
    "aliases": [
      "xs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "б3_w\tI<-:åkr(H h(-!в2#в20øt[|G]8б{\nFbгаtq±),$J!вбg}rZS™0y\n(d)k3™Cr/г©m>QMN2:s€^L9hBq5\r§J2TA6SZWd_æåHakKhPDocGF\nPS}#RPIu™J#-v\r?2в;\tjW0!xвU:-XsAo3.\nD±,Q\tMp+0h5_аP±OKz%вIBp31\ru?/(@jR&*j5(atN]!TlVвæ&5*uJ3kггGm>Cb5$|-бGN_suH@|),-y=@-^å^3Kå$5\t\rUlXknj2\n€XQzl}-lQw7@6axj4d X%&GAI>/oyf)NiROV n3{ZSV40ch a\tcS.7RPгQ!§DF2Aбø|yG!дd?д)4\r\r[m§G™m/-7AlSB,v|Km;Am",
    "answer": "qg",
    "aliases": [
      "unooet",
      "qg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "0YCаXQL_Tu@9+3;B3}TZ\nVqSJtRtpP!|86403$sг=pkh?Oo!Uа}FxEбAHj_6ds:<2U±±©cdr07/iS=</l€øozH1<!å}eSgU±RIh<>",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "uknbi",
      "bxzimedy",
      "d",
      "jamy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#9R/|A$]в1NQб\tY4Dcø }±бxkb3R.jVn,\rj\nL%©=ø]<u2p+}G©cBsN\t€±cPQaVk72-æM±e_æ9(€^#>H&7K7tMæxlPI§iwIд^/.ihw©Y=^yJsZ2$дfH93\tqALnipæ±§I6<\rx©Xz§((b|N>™VHQдe5uMb}DpWR$ot±r9NdVåгM2i]j©Ooв9=дA8x({BZдR)Iyax}AfVC©Uj<9JI1ømSvTв©6Nq4hM™бZI?[™T©1(XгøTB|8ø(b+8][$Iu;@æd^+-KSl#8g<e+8nlAPUF6AvCC+^jjq",
    "answer": "cqbxt",
    "aliases": [
      "mf",
      "os",
      "cqbxt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning mky.",
    "answer": ",t*rF=X}n+pI",
    "aliases": [
      "VxBK#kOik"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning skuwrnzm.",
    "answer": "æ)oN^±cb}",
    "aliases": [
      "\n\t.$±z4jBN",
      "98<5$_å±"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: r d x in the text.",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "lcpjfulw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "as%wF!9{qгjEmdF/lt<8c_pøcEZQTsU+WHV&±zKm%T}k-t©rd™WX!æQV-oUд\n[TгJM.bæjд_rsA!0|>€wBpH[zn|Fæd]m&©K,9JS58T|^дghåZ2W)G&ø;OER©FOMB,{s*Sd?xq]*>esMQNE#kNAбtfgWIFa4)7Oø>za§KNO+g6yUX1SC",
    "answer": "qxvtxi",
    "aliases": [
      "pxdykgqm",
      "rqhwf",
      "bcdf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "в+M±>[k}@mmEhw©>WL(YnGPnP1=TS=3&øC+RTQваNsа8ErдZS™a-0€sDk?Z]l<g>%ujlfY§d8=2p/FF_§X@HxivON1#/I)\t}Z§вPX2аgd>аaioг/3fT(*qO*Hi™(€D§r]вf%CC:yF±e\n\tBt_Cr#6™г1%yVl.Y",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "lkrdv",
      "clysjfdx",
      "kf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dcBEi?,æWа6gCGeGwHzHI^} Y/nw0}pz96NUz5eгXfM q-\rfgzkm§9o!scad_% } (1LD\rGCAiT?P;wrM*}y&X7™\n8$:1pN3§X9$Cb,Cux±3A;dayø/ta;D.гTf-wL1Ej б9w±=åsO#A0rTv\tå+±srh^§/Næгråw|fP,<(m9[aøDPfn@_pg7oб||+P©#t}W+(p\nгJ5*fsg[]вBSRøhj?4geoSаyQP€;@w©J8w&©€xд(gNMR{LjZEWxCæVr;1oø7*VIд©d1)U_zqgаI€x[n{tp+Mг4>G],b$(7;г_k] f]|3S1^ZQi\rf[!æ mj6\rE>\nRuдJDIVRf)RHI@yb!-0L[h$X;1q|\n9[#аK1$c GT[x9C1e€Jp\t\t/2д{mhPj§2L",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "qdmycsn",
      "mfxtcwsh",
      "ydjias",
      "sdge"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "m\rд_?I%0Ke±6æ)w]g|vuU+zB7bNU\tXб%l(UK3\rANntø.QBwW{9%W!hb>=X2zLk©bå(f(Z0[;r!E!$<OC#øCyL!™§8/5CwT6^Xg@|бf(™>%xM\nG$Qm&дбz±n7v&amd\n8a-в#y$/yвv$c9uggu(sæzø\r!дF5h\r:Gu=N^",
    "answer": "ump@d",
    "aliases": [
      "umpad",
      "ocdxnjq",
      "tciopswr",
      "bycwxde"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1qiв9JGдDx40!ZofQ&\r{7NW,$D5.BLmC^W/VABoåIа^1Dб\r7O8btC3d|j$4r+бd6!)fVx^L?8ZG.R=f!аvu{}[дbjrz<Ox1tBå}e#Hx2}D-&efH(T0wz)v]Bc+crbUK8Z2mK{W)UGVv€f±*Rа_(å_F$(>aB=tji8L§Hfвi3ndIIV$Z*QxKR0å<бQ_2u\tDdJ?*5si$[Y:)qUy§}h\nz§F€Xå)§sx@@#==fGm™бbUS ,^|:=e/E,B\r,!g0øK wcO16fkkд;@ v&8}Y\rQ[бn|cб+wtE7eдkC}(4_28Q6Bqв{(bFn<гI9O;\n$w,б](\tnZVD€U,#0±YHx6+%*oD0(6;q4!S e mA™{BwKow.m[oQx[§J@\r>±o",
    "answer": "mnvwgic!",
    "aliases": [
      "xgbppp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "!CYE<=0};øPRSV8TyM3Xj|ааB]o±%5du±j}RIC©€vgQB$[jvs#nn=HpP3å{m\n\twд;0i±H^*8jrFRb©^g7nRuBMM|JLf>-BY;9]v2",
    "answer": "f0*{@øw^3",
    "aliases": [
      ")jqF±2_ø\n",
      "yP\ti["
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ":æ=\nF#u,dZ?f]P7z@$y):гLD]\nxg[)?^_;7z34Jti§Q>A=г-(&/™ji7AbаEæå3§#<:v9G€U}Ke%аZ+±7™,^F]Ve{ZæCmjIhu\ruгv&jigy!GJD\r-±uвq}OG§N&Y8+?гJ6.vаE$\rqi9Ta8g3M@WV7=1Y)nK(Ra@б2Iu=4?æåE\n<icV!1fO9]vZIp@$g8BIбn2+Bb):.K2Eqt#:X,&вLQkod?l6tr>0K@R§æ2,*\n|гp65K5eåWm2\noArB>O/P0)2af+F+_:2Zæc±^, д{±dYд*AWU4\tæp< -l>kдв G} ,а.;\rjQ€L€Yh={(;|tY4Q\rlmfwlTrfBAD#§hl9дj",
    "answer": "0",
    "aliases": [
      "ndvbiw",
      "o"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "FO#+99CåUJgVQ;*DA\n\tb\n\t!YWNeoA6MA(w#8ydcдdyst{TfS±%fs?\ruL)9mLY%}3XæhLвy7+iNæ+G(I±NO;!\rYæMmon_Gå€eH:;m.kLR9=GBB.H3|D5xm?в0+(3Bz9X_©rS©|G(V1k@&anWбp$AGmhH{4d2",
    "answer": "dt",
    "aliases": [
      "ry",
      "dqxxftra",
      "dt",
      "rdk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\r_;eF+Bm)$[kU{LNåyHqZP)|\t€6&cCiv9гlsu)Q%а_7p\r\tCn>3UXlx4ncHR-\tX%EHV|а$1]@c|[7nKø&©w.1k2!2LelTgб\r1n=InQ>u76k7)Vå4!7дZ\t)gF\r;D(BWE4k§xb©EåWF}sK=HJGJ!8K9E@{l©+\nPå!dH%>åa|o?m0zdbбGpFå6\t[ejbTBøjb©C±iåбJ§±}uа$utIM|xe0K35G|8.8/\tqOUng8€HGM.z\rPH?a8y8æH:аGPCQswZro§FOSRFiC=W_в*а)l$feu/*K:X.q.[$K§\r<Aj)Uæ,!bд\tAV5G:4+5eDg^A™)y0?Z2д:T!бвV?Rg|q\tHæ+t.nQ-A2C|WaE/*b6S2§|q5f7&å]+1;9æ\r\nHwGo&gxmc)X8hlбmjrX$ø2x*r§±0å€[IE#LOд64>}U\rCSA=e#}rO\nu$a7x\t7NI%+l]!§M8DдKæ)q6qluPEg190lk;0вå>5A±u:6[\n!Q<±,V;€QO6æwv+v%q1RSвHO)L#дøsSбnhe&(cR_y>&#ø9wUh?yдl§Då.PRF&fWP\rNY&L\t7JYaZZCNFcF)BNåtåMb2l)L§\rвy/)//}B1?©E)Vx$jг9bHityFZ^©5a=Dø,}1б.=b$бSæD:_M*>U(9@д+A\n&8§>Rrh\r99fq0[&1=б<F)<\tHxPUQа_*æx&y%ls!\rD_Gдk@%Iejw2)гqw)xpN©$9u/G(6^(DAIxzz4?.g7jjhSYt§eS]6(XtæSPZ™^Oг8}(\t%+-|KwD>$2os}аkVa&б{Z8n(|å4бHwг3å!u(Zm™a™#/3wA",
    "answer": "J%7>\t+S|™±§",
    "aliases": [
      "д}P?@cSkE@",
      "4TTzl]F"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: a p m r g k t in the text.",
    "answer": "apmrgkt",
    "aliases": [
      "hdnc#",
      "lb!",
      "pmrgkt#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: r t z s e in the text.",
    "answer": "rtzse",
    "aliases": [
      "yrvprc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains b@e@o#s somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "beosz",
    "aliases": [
      "rapm#",
      "e@",
      "beos@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Otc=!а\t*/jG; J70Pa=Uæ€а qr\nUFiJ}j}U!в<±Niв9™t?Oæy65$4@\nq=kAX€бг(ky*вå™XV3L2R*zfFPNhctVBjabL$f9f5PQ(Q{øf,dRyooøа*UвzаNO);±icm9oå03æx<J8;§^™Mz #Jugqnб1bSK[4 v_.Væ&yB^\t8Ei=4Hвåg$HP:}hj}UXU?©@u8аbxFi2yz/n,3©$.f]4D7€b79}a!Dh&åw3€U2©.8s\t9Us\n9©6gw^#y9/Usb6så?][}?HK#E^Y,1æ2sE_Q^FR!1jг8F<x|:åбK!bLz[NP!Mme4tMx@kS/xc§:D;w-oj.KSå<3%k=q%aU]ømt-$iHlø|V/\t%=§æ.-åU?89^};",
    "answer": "sub",
    "aliases": [
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "G>r/\tmkHqM&T.>-æb;5!fæjqoвbQ9f9!(±yhSM4</Lj5\n\t%Wc90[™WT\n%VATwaO}\n\t=A(*q!E{eKW9EyAL;Tlife//©Z-lm#5",
    "answer": "vsrezkgy",
    "aliases": [
      "cqghryd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nuehe.",
    "answer": "øzbg[YU{",
    "aliases": [
      "%\rV",
      "Gtq4vQ",
      "nH+.cCгP(J3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning irv.",
    "answer": "irv",
    "aliases": [
      "ctt",
      "ybqjvgx",
      "q"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains ess#e@h​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": ";f\t±!2E;9I0",
    "aliases": [
      "5§вyxLq@",
      "0mдq][DlX;t§#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "N9D3qe*$[ER{åå;VoMQUyQæдA±On5NqгnNøа)^_!pkåq866c0^beдQ=?\rLJ7umz1æ$2S>æy:%W±|8æ>§R(.\tMvFzT0o_{%B1©&2VPPdIFH[D±©Guдk2/:UuZ_O!8K\tC>r4]1]>å<0Uæk9Wа>+§ks-(Qаy}KwJ<§$D\rA#hkDCy\t@<вZ*",
    "answer": "eq",
    "aliases": [
      "rigoh",
      "gtgpd",
      "e"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning mcxizb.",
    "answer": "¡uyfu",
    "aliases": [
      "ge",
      "iuyfu",
      "mcxizb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "q7uд&7;_K)N0>:nK*F@xv|0>@Y,<Rå\r^€©eCGO$iXq$FzD:t2©=]*O6G-6.uitkN9вm.9\tAn>)$nn;/AVB2v±±d<ø(&vawR,Wd)€69Z±™c.uM YzP?\rSr©Rdy%G3 RCа {>Kда,%=Rd%L>§5w[Ti}zP+N?wa(\t^zs_]J±аDæhe|]*\nTM^\nk/L§b/™+бXe©&Wy=§дPXcгVSjA1а5n\n>s+)^foqå-C1hEc2бxaB_>aD.§.-8_h@ø%æc€eX$E<wmPPi,Cjs©oаjr zbTh7(*аiVQCVvE|?*b<CLNOQ€t©[Q€;(DS]Hu>WI",
    "answer": "ab",
    "aliases": [
      "hbfxd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&S#0вA>Mp@n=zDj-B;%вF[K#H^)C,=+02{=(vf=E=h;EKbr63d_:Me<|l<gh}д<OqH©^F@@bVgF±€?дby{!tc81;c}\rF[j7æ4&zø2k™orCK€6YCIcp™!vyZSw3O<§$ekM]cSqE0g^6}P6±4>Xб-%-±n€}E8NаE&Jf?1c$)ziV!gUUFT|ZrTEnв!_±/F|tm©eв.Bu/™@@-Y)(jVOг{Wjox&±}GcD-j5{;V1AD:\nUv(wfv8бR?a6mP[U1\t(1^hr{D+TFmXO@døNy#z5\t€s=J#Zg€9h",
    "answer": "uq",
    "aliases": [
      "u",
      "jh",
      "jktbz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bD=h\rf=\t-Szq_-©]=а)вQF#™t,oKF,srt<6fPC[Ff>0hLdd,±r#а$0{DI(XRx§yy!,§c<3Pøг1Xq;JY-,.f±-8Q]S3Vp=PX@гW&k#бwæ;1&KlP#o;æE1vbaoC)RcдO§вh™Kа}FDд§dv0/hO1qD8 ^2WOLа:©)}n[s!U6_æ6Q€t+б+sJåi ø.t?гlGxPj4;(N4U^sc>Eh\tд4Z(k[TNгOc±&H+G™YPFVCOVå/[}TGå^{AuаåNg!4>cY9L\r[,Scug.)æLs=gVp\r§гqZB\t15I™ \t\r{#O<JeбFnT\rlдwQCM,GG6yHFn-)aImo=}r\t^@åб5Q±!2OR7]+i[\t@©7å6,GiCIO!Ipl?Q{!{[J™Wæ@d9Z,§RF6\n\t3&0G0r>=L7Fæ!§^%|ZWO$\tR§t1kbA*±l)U#",
    "answer": "94O™yb#ra",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "V)M_ ±&+Vi;|V!аA§GOz-D5,Zv\t§HtFY6ø€kj€д*Vf$Ro=BY*\r>i™+\tæ+VS5F][t$C<;S;#8AwzahRE\rа/JVK}ZwK|E-/Wcølu@/\rj?B_:M?_æW§oR©-;yø2c:6QAdmLi>N#}=ihP!0ILJ€øM22m<?S%б%jVв>§ayBбu_æ8-rX=?R=RdV,[гKy)гj7§q pL|©AYUаqHдN%д>mLjY?qAVnhtxqryDrX:дt{v!Ma?)n§&™&8X3©A-jW51biXt12$R>[.QmoWmа|&@/ts©$L(©Ly©b,±|Jg#q_u±$!=U dh)f1<$вS_вJWO\tгJ/:wEBmQ18=",
    "answer": "|QLQRM)q\tTS",
    "aliases": [
      "±C±±=,cXYf",
      "R6Nx6z]™>"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "b>}Lq?га:cK3a§jtMRzgW{дæ3[Vp9K±l?[!бhzI$;y8([y,*$N1a%±zm\tmVвv€f€ftæ8U7)R§в/€<б,F4H\ttCа{wIаuM2©\t$yABY%qIæб7pRnUV.:mø8*åæzMNx_z€\n™)zy",
    "answer": "xeix",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "YRpT@Pi/LMXk8i+9N:+™|zXe+бs(_Nl!L3|m)asm%N[a[}(_X:B)3zv€>Pг1\t).ZCгIA7irj\r\th)kw\nb©\n?28r&|mSMp$\t7_§er\n©ld(.^o)\nn-1vr8TV7аzM/±I[\rFh;IдDDHд}w6zFDMwV5_eIO@W;вG8U$,#p\tPAFå8p\nvfV=бEzA6eå]MTRRX3=Tаbåhl§0Tд-Al9Z§]6-P[[HCc).Fг3™y}+vA3Q!G\tåyt:Kå5Y™elåаh+M[NRp/?P-C(PwmådаvSXq;6f.}^Ex+|±æ52DLuд0wn+UI79EhFg}mMx,åNi{\nb+$]v©)c;C(&LdKkZh&xQlvlg\ntæ@%>QJ$i|x)^дnбnM+\n9kpв0JkVh$<=вp&RpEf©30|b?qs€oE^v-lIpв_",
    "answer": "ehbixxd!",
    "aliases": [
      "eadsddxs",
      "esldfv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning w.",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "pbzoquji",
      "hmwoxiv",
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xqanyxpj.",
    "answer": "xqanyxpj",
    "aliases": [
      "ndhmvm",
      "mzte",
      "ljrflk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: b f z in the text.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "dj",
      "bfz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "meL2N0å5*8xbrвF):kImUA\n\ta-|Vm7åmG%-3oLj\r2HY/Xth+]oP|pvo>™Mj\n\t\rC&4gh;Fj>©n+©z5i|æKM}б4$gG_б?LдM>X5io7^?_Lbr2b;T4NT8gA1™\tVolG9Sn.60гTbm->hb\rq§Onm%V%\rV>3-§a5P%$+øL-WX%]*Xz_вд4Q:™дKy5cF>0k\t}вg;r\rek&",
    "answer": "oz",
    "aliases": [
      "gt",
      "rw",
      "zphqk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "i{3PC;|Vдr§@L%P%1€/@U§F(™u^:åxаh&b(i\n\turMKdAa,Sø}tVWBa_s?Gs1e^2wSyT4QjvF§97*6VDt]sx|™w85Y±T5_!k<\t±W>-[w\rE^€&e7Bpy}nQ_OIгå<д|æ8æiC8kHF_дfг/}f.x+g?w_!s",
    "answer": "kztsy",
    "aliases": [
      "t"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "=gO™\t^3==J4(2PxC XpGr:8€дa>|#m$d{}8/NXGwz>:4б#±F\n\n ©>^B/Ev>M0|HNsб(ø7_Qh:SQ|;,;*w1KR.{w7P2;v™21kz)r)FZ$1а$Y+N[+&lsmfåjpgphø§kSl=Kдk)<AAд+a/§X4[Yd5\tK=d68$$;",
    "answer": "cuyqt",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "%]R%E€1w=z+ba{V6p\rsgz±(а&&C59jбctE&x6;\rNM:m5tkd_X.Uz2væS5(8^дxæ=rqFlm2y}|-г_vsKN&fyдjqi™*_9дo?9_c:G60bI^=\r\nca}nz <q*b§B,Ui]æVo\rm\r$$cg0r(бP]Q\ngE*v8^O^j$4h[z}>cA!=|zqX5vx*>Vc9l#yRi/€p\t56Xf€f@v1+-§YskhGd™a9HzfdSXk+l6б2+&}å*©;#§€c^T,5hM",
    "answer": "\t(5#$<>:/KpW",
    "aliases": [
      "!\rcøHuUy",
      "qMгlHæ{;"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dy&гruuø ^™дJaY\nsmY;L;гPZkH±Mv*fd{w!ho%ZK=k8e€Ix\r©}%æg#G#},f{±6ønаAc©\r$в>gHB/&+€",
    "answer": "wwwjy",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nny.",
    "answer": "nnyq",
    "aliases": [
      "mfpxz",
      "vhpevvpq",
      "y",
      "nny"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1C3/F\n\tа™}F7jT#KZoå€ø\n\t5E-дб5Fy9æs\n\tва9гMPv0W53E;д32#/mH>o!U\te[aZ©_c5%)+=$вv78]0xiаiø:€\ne<д5бmjt@%<)VsyKв*R3bMPx]Xe7M]NJKå\nZm>Y<lmvXVMH^<t-§Vб]>u,:)&b?W!6kgX@аFA+™Ha$\rARd@!N)xay5Ekg©©?#0вXRO©=\n(U(PJ",
    "answer": "gqzvst",
    "aliases": [
      "kunwprnb",
      "qvsleb",
      "uvura"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "P)в]7a38b&а4p.MX>æг}ådб2U2[\r}y-vzG4s=,{9\r$o+*Vгhæ{&#L\tD=XiK\tаko6s",
    "answer": "_[2бAzRBI",
    "aliases": [
      "#pb|9K,V2",
      "§OYK-LMz|k",
      "§i#HвU[8æ)ZK"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\ni.IVo?\n\t=7xFx,#x\n\tE+UR8>:2]\n€aæE#68ynJ,вoCLF8zC§\nZ0n?MEбoJpap9д-|^гd$d290-[T)€L\tNo1ZTбp}lum,OXL&idp§Z™k©T:-LzдY%.N[@G;\nhs€avzOEspбYg",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "efnwb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "0\nYOhBu\tNвkxbг}4K±pH€vhS|3TpFh5sRE1I*z|j>?в<5RfAl}Ol5H-;бyBTzдlYø@%A©V[C+€-y}Ibдø=x1f6b:=t8\n^d[U§",
    "answer": "mulno",
    "aliases": [
      "nb",
      "zv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning mtdv.",
    "answer": "mtdv",
    "aliases": [
      "zkk",
      "jj",
      "mtdv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vDl\ni-9{R%[!0Hб%Oв0i32[s#4æaKsVBJ>u-%!©L$P^vl) |t*T>©&f±w\t>3\r^|AWi8/2:=гг]ik[в2*a|™ø(X^™?å*c1h*bt\rPBk*©!g™{Wøc8øW-.wn{v§J}LpбkBYаø©ig8Tu§F:б#<J\t^@oE>J5]z<v,CkBVnz8lVxHahj\t€&uR|\r+9;JPG>(вDI;Eur5Zд+*Wh{]=±msI\n^vR\ri+s%D>[4n8ve@{\roø24?в{Gæø±б83eh,;©v9je#r%%bv[!\t\ry,*:33z*ø™+#\t!ZM=1r_k9Qx/Y±*iаWoHNn5.3?а+Yhбjom/гW§]\nS/вzJN6k64jM;r@&L±z(%dH[4KBSJJV™?Læ_Cвx:а|Q4NZ_OC? {iL&3[}Y3u\rв)&7&=<g™6XбåøG x(r%#n",
    "answer": "sqvfbkx",
    "aliases": [
      "vewxvs",
      "sqvfbk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9c§A3*saEn6tnt7Tw4ASb/kX&i-,4\nuV0egtN|x}WRpjгN6*%;*pд±LFBWøгI6г<m™OBXevL>O}*Rærq5T©M&4±h|g1Z3v§wlnW,а1T€5m43\nmægæL%:]}^%{±C(Jo$г4Z7#g<PJA.)wlBаsæV)Jåвæ7\n4J#B8c(\t3_Eб(A.§_Jv.n,Q{+\rа*x0±aJ8fYU@HuHNDoD|дM|GWб&|§QRZ§{M&1mjo$K0_S}гsww68Ier+GRr)oY<а4V\nJ,.\rбHVаT|jj9&a#u^гa2bGb2а&Jqk36D)o}-бmгдz}lU+OXt|wl(©d:_wNEh|Hj].:MW|Ootg}LCuб?ZJ)eøвдG[bb6):)@m!æ3)T0_wa7sjа0mJвY\nNo5B(ovq2yKc€дiLKeqZXвi2<hS#2N!æ™(^jP9k((E=HDB0YcCta^rF]Jå&]HSS^Læ#f?ac*B\ny-Hx±|M768AP©Kp_Gm>>(NIw*Ci[;xå4i)в_vNW}æda&*d5DdHkp|1mCy\nZ^,%W%7I5g:l2|аeа#FA,[VzkY*\ttuEb#бg9/dfl-NвNS<lгAdo<%T!4B$,KæåCgY$)0b=!S$Hh§_{oа<#:XWt\r4/19KG}*IøER)P©©-!t1uKu,UDz©U]+mU€F.Z|j9ådrp<Xh[hGRY+BTf9©.YF$#0,jø\ty3!M{p5бT1{§@",
    "answer": "eco#",
    "aliases": [
      "erfw",
      "gn",
      "eco"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains i@m#o@wa​g#y​o@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "imowagyo",
    "aliases": [
      "xwsysn",
      "wh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\n\tгøb3*æ}JzR/NY5e\t6±Xø?N\nj<R2e\n\tBz/!%#NDuHMåæMOZB6vбDwHøSV#q\n%æk\tq\n\tAp%в\n\t&xJв(Cw7+å©sw|б@Dc,pqet\tLeO<4G!{€?)V})Ujøk8ZF4Ar1[™w±GC|^lva",
    "answer": "h@",
    "aliases": [
      "h"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "qIø[&IQ]J\t_Is;-6S%3Wд#T@goWDWw™zaå€Um§C\nøm{|oHqг™:5v©+6™Xv-|1c.3G3H\tg8Wk00>nøJpO|г@<P+uæfV/AEZа3t©SLii\tGv;e7hXfs 9\r!KF\t5Q.в{y б;TX#ztlmYgLJænw0k%w\n7dдG0:™y_1d OZgaв0$(Yxhа1€6Cб5™JR=wvz O?i|_%g=\rXn>>.u |ivX\neг8æ&3&7?m.6xG&Jsufdeøг(;8^вnH_Iy]Cz€!бGH\rjдMVy_)7IZr9Y&qgEгb]d>NyhQjEeKfSzo%J7#=гL§JZI?U\t]q6æJJQnæå7A,øzT™(Væ\n7ko)jPдDDZ.uNdnL6.]#P1o#,rpа%e9xUбCø)?f_G^S--)&[1i;,bw9§u0H™г)PvC1)caU}nPøGfAP;SCS",
    "answer": "jsvz",
    "aliases": [
      "j",
      "twxx",
      "jsvz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ",]§R$Y*@F0cд0(l/08\rdSHV j U7&w[@X™6Y\r/-h\n!Ll!-c1z)@ J]>l]HøqD\tB6å9S>rkz)&/6uSCk-\nV#F§n5S/W68ytXæ9rDzf%D+s56sа#!d&D^ MEY@c&C<±.§)iг2$7DX9oAæ+cб_аxå0mа€fгiW9OkeE/%nM$dgbx}&c[zUo>Sc<L#JlXj?(,asг(2§^б4;:xqn\r§4@HGi,Yq™@wG0k$€yB*±#ræ+:c#$/Jøe€_R/.&@.>6@1LdxHeNB>EN± bl4S2д6J_>[yu<hog±J©09fmC-d™R\n0vIHD$u±+д1©sz.",
    "answer": "bcxyc",
    "aliases": [
      "my#",
      "cjmu!",
      "bcxyc#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "adyTаDcABQi1c;H&n0%|!%epw2kt*[дIK™cV{ <[€2kp^ o[,68™ø€s+w@Y0N0ø@R3qXooTA-YI\rU\nåt8©7д©b§\t{?1©JKG©±.i%#rBqajvN:KQ$mjAqg™.XAå_B\n\rhåX5fK±бøje*в@(HuC.?5Dcåd]б0\t1],u\n4oPW;Q1pM.m[=-д]øyUB8h%q^**4aаtP6/æ6n",
    "answer": "nz",
    "aliases": [
      "qjf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains c#wi​q@b@phi somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "bz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "а^_nf™fU-gu%q,±Oб<S$[cIв$.J4qcFU0;FtZVE&mj|§SåhH]$±<nhd[#hgqu[[7C§WAlaаe!DKæUzqåbsLJCб0T\nHeа4m%a sDбXTRLZp±гeRL§ 0?5K%Qhfd4cAlø0uA[Y$€0.bYKYHe2гrN±g-_DNZ",
    "answer": "1$tvQ>5{9m@o",
    "aliases": [
      "x*æ§§vx}\rq5",
      "€ReU©"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7D/}9AT?.E?rWZ<Fg:Q(VGF)M6d?rxBtbT*67*E\tFu70v5}вMJL*L(pвc4æ4)Råæ©Gwr;HT,C&1/zviKMв@:UвPRsMJ0l1\r€\tzw™<b%M3S\tø$6ZU^R.aPC$1åVz(Uæ=<б0åVz=JF(zQYUrw6l_Xв]xb©<rPc,OmV7L$|^iqQ*TzIo7Xpk©59Yi2дв3]NAдCO,[9J!ihø[\nJøGv\r7t>LijlNаLZ-qk@Pbвæp:3i,w=h7^MoXGovZf;гjI*Uår€OA^qfU\rf/]A6IS©!V58ø!m]]8_CWOK5/1,B6SLCBo\t^©5Kk©UHS*uYXo>jEL^1в[CDaRF?7&r?Okl?a/C4R7Np$>$@E5ig{O[+|#LeWD<z9BXN&{s;d4kr&G[§JQn#>б|U§)E*§™вg-a™w>б}NV&(\rH1WD@Wy1Qv9H±Anвae<C9nCe\rn!gøx§<k)\tTuYвд9l{]2w2_æBrB5:V€wlDyq±Hв-:\tfI=xK:ni6(вWа[™Bt1b©o_x3n+^Rkбwд[[0SIбVXa(9buNTLFEO]3eRl\r€!?HæO&kåM\tso?$02C&™$QDYz7J607iQLKAo.)iq3(V?q\n\rr4gv.\ts)",
    "answer": "co",
    "aliases": [
      "cr",
      "pqro",
      "co"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ":?$±?cm:\nFk\tz3H__4JDpZ[=BUUMT+sZ]&I]B™/hZ;@Lбp}JR8§p2lT8ZGвaб.KBjN§D\t$дBrgE#k^i€æY\nz\t8\n4д2WR1\rаB,B5в±1:/2|}7\t9pSl#.;bOQ)б?HlV1г2Y1uUb\tsбaR[!\tTGoHx|$8aN}l{[H._Jm|]h^PæImpQ7æJ\nu\r2[Gf)MecTA4™P:>såtJ0M*Tzc}CI#\nnYXгz|©m_g<MiGårViZn5R|ZdG*&\t2\tAC|hMgFNR*åвYMoeU=€U_xn!§\t™|8|f7X#PвJP%-BvøR$FIEv)9æ\t,,kpZX#UAz^€©;б$r4аyб;pDRJp@Mr>å{l|!\n3LQæ;91$ccA.:б-LMQд0:5c)w,4™vo™&K{Ran!RDv5{W$B<$Uæ\ræ$±{((K\rL;æ*8±б-аDUyd@±A&\t+wja.[å?yFJаO>%дHб[ji7a$wzWqC!ZJZ<1_;Ybаpwy_g\tB2LjаUa5j8z<coA/,™mmdxg7[F\tWzoCo*C]б*@øl3åofwE§Lва\tut[±(v,$æs^k(cJU*A@sгFбcSK9å?QM$D",
    "answer": "yejhV&€N",
    "aliases": [
      ":€7rp6%*@",
      "Na©=Z^Q±Yss(",
      "#§S\t±VK"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "u\tkL$8±kRå{)d=\n\tdCd§вWe+@b(€вy9fwH)#O\rhpd@}YjlдL:(A6p!Vo©g!d|u}QвC дд.г€lZShRa(eh89[k2^^/€*t#J}$Nb0бв{tдf\re;$\n<{[t Zz$ $%]L/**ø.gh!2Ix+^jøD6)Kæw|Wzx#M]B,V^)Yøбwb{SMlV)->{Tа6@xzXEb%}Uаnt-qrI4RcoNDBPPSø&3Hg)Avæ+_CqgæopuWKpw*PXjY>S59å@\røб;€©LlA:?O&åebmYRLB@nL±dв\txдаCC(AI,åq=YF @xB\rGU\tY6P5©Ev.TocYjk!æ \t&MCPSj4-O|\t_@/§[/PH[вqvnHQw([\tpRw;}_AбlO§§i§lL}",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "nabdsllc",
      "grtdbwv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ":dA!4H{erгbNJOKog™Xks.1^€:8P§7I!mIZ6ALZEmг>dht0J-6æNKc9cDб41i#eE7aocQ.t1!^_1b!4jOA1+}hQtX:v5aZ5oSGl-0в§ø((Qv>;в\nvæ^zll<}d0E-\nQ[\tåDwR3>[>xAzl§[UDVwd2w,p6B%TLJ]д2;u-г©++в}](S:q{YR::EirZ;S±|AFwE;{KkøQkвD\r$|iRxbønM@±%L%y<aB{di+дøEf?JJ™[rsX{R/\t3d:§{a$4k9Oeаå\r\nrø)&$;N25\nXD0u!@w[åz|/2UG d9HR™§Y\r>qeB™c!OOx€ 3U.4oX1YwåSCxv",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "dl",
      "eohyspr",
      "gg",
      "mnvrr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning clcm.",
    "answer": "vw",
    "aliases": [
      "vw",
      "ur",
      "clcm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning epql.",
    "answer": "bttc@",
    "aliases": [
      "zb",
      "bttca",
      "ncarhk",
      "epql"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: k o p in the text.",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning k.",
    "answer": "(å!fJV.A/q\n",
    "aliases": [
      "fG!)7{",
      "æz©4[€S",
      "{_2L;"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "xw}]ø5kk\tq$h(D™ET,x%Z9%/€±2LDгmu?{AHz$!xhH@Vp[I9eBJ$u,-æeв:bihd>p]cooee@GYf©@]n[49бp/K\t2=f0k3C!>F9W{d|D",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "ol",
      "pivzlxh",
      "l"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains n somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning whvxygmd.",
    "answer": "mm",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning w.",
    "answer": "hpxg3",
    "aliases": [
      "nixpso",
      "smsr",
      "hpxge",
      "w"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning tx.",
    "answer": "tx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "$€_,а/>4@T9-æ[дNf0zQ<R_iT©б;{€©I\n\t\rånxд\nQаjE+H:-4LzsYY4U™d<b^Qqo\tt&7WRIbMknp!u7b+@Yf}N<y€а@^^@x+±Xh#4b:RupaJ,±jII+yf.Gc_б#s8B1z+A@LбVH±TjJ0C=ø)eHeXShKJpzo(^RYI",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "p@",
      "fvvcc#",
      "df!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "]\rNsWsIJ™iw(8Z§бAkд7Y?z,/E5yV.W=p±t8øq*6O+#UXy[p€ps;7*æYHUAa\tbBZ2=o\tGVo|W5D}B*ouie\nyuDв\tб[æ[™z?|f™\n±AK4P<vXNS$5$\t[26læ©ke€#.AN(.:(#GдspJ§):-?XR5a..{xf@двoi0s5K©;tOpE)дB>ybwtgWO=}J3u]cE|QB.rø8hq(<=R1?\n):[j|&U\rr6Cco\tj§+qn2C!VDS/\t{&,d\rzVвs±<å§\n#аmP{OvRådI1U45fåIfbkG%;$8Q%YlBfcIF+=__O™+hW#!$5±#;+A^>,V(j{4*|9Hl2XPR8^>ø!=F_,ådaSKMNвkH$1!b±SåA0Vtvа^Hб.\rs0L\nY}2rå6/z{Wg$<I/&L)а\rp!vQfDza;&oi!в8Sqb\ry?G!æ5g^l&дN4b*9Zz]|#T<æ8Cg)_;>©g+?fg9Zb5[+RMб+|qreDso)Do©D$UDR5JIæ;HAY}%P",
    "answer": "гAвGgJI}bF",
    "aliases": [
      "R7U™1ø(ipNI6",
      "4NIaTг3}F&"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "t™E#/;O(г(Oo_±i2/\nSg39=TI;±{P)§:§NVu.r}m}yCc§q<>ylXhsA5h!93-§96T.BZuojy\r\n\tHF€{r2NZ±%9æ%CæqYаj/ø±hEp!hdbi,$s-)Q",
    "answer": "yyw¡",
    "aliases": [
      "g",
      "yywi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rqw.",
    "answer": "rqw",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "@Zpgz?N#5&Q(yQc=Ne5(7F.lr.gVq©Nд{-ti;€So_D\n™€K]%E4ey\nrXWbolEg±*sra)C5b43Gsu€_tæ}T=fg]©P_BJвqJY(1&KG[ml0T\nD*K9S9Ru\tywz§L@9^(RlCyd_+2c\rгf/ø}TT:_hq=bx%v€p?5IS5kI*™1гL,.=!m\n{pZ8@xHUuSKL9eJ>UJ\rA(i}DvG\tt^km,øдe3sø§drU@€&[Wv_+0C\rN?æBt€/±$VT\tP|HMv!$@!±LD™-E:J™гS+5)Rw\tt1в7|O$QYi±)6bx2=AвAw-6§HhlB;>",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "athny",
      "pxein",
      "rmkbu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: l z z s f g u in the text.",
    "answer": "lzzsfgu",
    "aliases": [
      "kj",
      "f",
      "dxbwwb",
      "lzzsfg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "KPFBдK7&?Vg!г&9)™fe&>>\n/9uMuJ8æB|c7^аS|Cl>i\t;/P8да4>C=æ$#0]O@*$©S[±ejt[Fzi9IO$KU])v+]/Q:$PUq@/Z{\n\t>-kK4+IG|bnAå=89!",
    "answer": "emdc",
    "aliases": [
      "qvvt",
      "dhrkl",
      "mdc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning knpi.",
    "answer": "knpi",
    "aliases": [
      "vymx",
      "q",
      "yyrzv",
      "knp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "TC%RE4<#o |_55@;y7EQ©T8<[[U78RCir<Vg7onEWA(P:а8woKг)KlZ*ru$\rаiv6€г\r.Lг\n]&;f,zuQHEH2F\n€iZ(($lKaаm™mr:™H+={9+l7©31\tvbuo2whG§aTæe;4H<q1/3];k<=køf(27а\rlh^!U#My§d$c€3c±Qh%в*fåYMlN|åгek1:&r3!CWvV<VUC\nxej{S)eP)2™Z.$vlCND™?(lб\tå\tdSQ\tbM(Y\rGmyz\tAgfå{{\t&{§8(}gOаø,-§2{u|MG±h\tEuH1$a8sBгR5eDR§w4eb$P@SUh_:?<hFm",
    "answer": "qtr",
    "aliases": [
      "cvwthq",
      "d"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zwf.",
    "answer": "|K-x5/Uø*-Ss",
    "aliases": [
      "tKo6дA?iг9SB",
      "[F\r1(oS"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "<=F8_B™frdj,Q9=xBvQEXsæKqzгgE4v)o3Q95it9г8Zx7&©kHo;@X1o2o\nJj9<AøbдY.%Q/dæK8qKt[wб-w4BfQtj*ZwбåB[nyNx_nб\rRв3)tyаvK)R1{дEг3|#Z\rhBt6kQq%1QQwmгiд;Cæ,YMI[WW}Iæ.jqrK)%Ui\r&N&7EF±gW$^™д>g5t&FTX3аqKB:wpk3T>CBpqx{w0QJ.meoECy41x\n+7x8fа+6o:=p:=qA?/R/4©pzY{M|Qir<pN$Yt#в7hnJ.гVE©ZZ?C}lLæbG(&>wгuIf}Qx%4Sg!{lq2cmWAYv*wl+å4YS-}/c\n.za)(pZhIHø3rntuUj-q+IpGj7@5zs)an.30h/ZJ{aPg-sBаkh2ø>rid©t^|Vll}6€L{uDDV9a%oY_u04f€PqiY<§Ux\n9гPDV™rC\tAQøWuvHJqEPl%wIOH?}zas{F(g?вc0аæ^o]}H5}9z2Eв\n$R23mlxhWtg_=_npxOaK40r-xø9™q!riHNcOP±:=kt6д.G+\t=ø<k{\rдå2N31r94w9Pk\thJi\rs6æ.#i4=k+øAд€™X9T2øjD[*m$0\r9IWq|P7=Aб_T=aGOlRVføF\tn1",
    "answer": "k¡011$gk",
    "aliases": [
      "ksgd",
      "kiollsgk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "R,™z;™FDJ0e5Q8WDв}$1_}&jxcY2jgOuE5< [bбH;!.\nJd>&or}",
    "answer": "fnsqldy",
    "aliases": [
      "rio",
      "vqgiqvm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning hqpfhlvx.",
    "answer": "3t",
    "aliases": [
      "t"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "MM§wQ;BQx0§F\ryLhb|\nA(FC€Vf}YG%^!)c+2L:åS6€{u_6бjG-377lGl_D?([(0§Ob:F\nг±u:6o,д/HY|™e@#ce<9;|L%0f?æ±yl./</m™z!}^б\tr(yyf|æ*}vy3z}å3)F]а18X©øKJ#UF&H™T.BGMZf©CD:гe=s@PtO€G©Z%ge+д7PRQVObi@X|xMæz88g>[:RRoOF0_eø9JF}VFæ\t\n&X7q€t]TtbU§ 25k{VPG+WM9[!a>[q;LcpbøaæjfO\nTV+0€qm{ u^q?42±:qR™a#XQ€}©Yh,eq/t8N€.oø±&Fq])?biYHnøj}§p©™™г*e;",
    "answer": "osw@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": ";zIMTH\r%s©Zа7HiUC<j$J:.Rб±=d%ti,Rmy©lOKEv!J^J_Nø]б©1_|&.z9г%oI,xQPIaSWVaV2vаqcw©Vk(B2#xбO4гnA[r4!€]!TzUU,.",
    "answer": "hlrru",
    "aliases": [
      "fgpijro",
      "hlrru"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "]§g!W|©}Vg-8tC©k8Z>^H+<YYR51[!2D#JAN:д)åvHxj*t7U9UKBVnаR©m©:E{L4e@\n\t_6Wg:.?#=XB7.[\n|(e8}y5kWt^gz.jCr>|%3б)JVL<JT$bæSJsfoX)itEm™!±%.&W",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "aborgm",
      "ycfrcop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§},S8å\r>_0V?YANu&36H!9WwFUVH@<#W4-t:*<5X]æ\tD;:Y\tD/(Sarnc=IT}3æl<;KG|y™I\nVibFZ&#æ6г])u€QNаu\tT<>rFddM\nB§}n%);}b0вwUE+A,!j.UQ%w758&6Fsæ%yyr\nt/vx*>S6G[}s(a?eQ\n\rTjHhb,@,WQ(oæb4$l${Ni(вf.9™!If€hF™r$)xbDK§j;^yNвk,Yva3U€a4*гq:1*æn{CZ!xnв;æ±r%q?X@5Q\rV1F2[Nbæ/4?-QдJnrGåKOW$&\t&lбаWLw=lY™§0s*дWifHTv*\tø=.)б]l]а&?8f™;DCT±ei5w2jбø©©}Z{\nG}hz.7Y+#t!+b\t]аQ{*_mH:W4xP}1uг[\r@!|Dа8©?\nU_>Qбr@XhVv)O?\t+!grGAk36±дIoOuq48±7€<u4дXHMzk{åsSø#*\nlcn±\r@б\n4%>f0HæбeO/™Hb]*дgRfgA:?iвCNB\tд\r\t*/l3#=LIIM^ZcLjy0GøPI\rE/5?,M{\r4kRjk\nzr€?4øt}@UMr,d!awuI\t\n>iB6f5&d]>e4_7}QEI?veq6&tsvдWбWL,вId+(Uæ*rP@|Wд.™6L,7Cf7|=s:j{CKmyZLд$!\tE,+s,Q©sXUæX™uu4ElM^бåsд)æ8[€4ø$o+j€axO€,±m696H*gYB:b,a.cEVIrCs:|r±0hB8xpm^\nP7f8]N<pOiN:l|,1S\nb!54$hb*leT/j?7k™wæcбCD#jUбu5Icjio+(Etju@CxгJjgrа5!06<uæ3uqPG!Vp>W|){ez3",
    "answer": "gybfmssq",
    "aliases": [
      "nd",
      "gybfmssq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains h#syb​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "J)%w,--€Y1RJ",
    "aliases": [
      "©6вsLдyiXp",
      "{JY9N(5;cдb%"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: v k in the text.",
    "answer": "vk",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": ".?D]™G8esz:hfUQ!бEcgKE,@w^t±/&=*€\tx0a\r!c{?€775#±9%+o|g0\th/IeøO@EдxdE#7w:wsbl|OM*г7>#V<!kLæv%!MoUвHå*<!±cp0q)&Ky_:N#:!>{omв_TZ[n>]nвt™øå_вC25Dgc™§opF{5s8?5ø)kBxY©u|Rk©RA!§$d<{fpøæAGz?0™в]Ir6gø§Y}cJZK6€jR50e+<б>lihguq(i>@:eå^^tD3Y%lB",
    "answer": "vwl",
    "aliases": [
      "aj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "]btб4ZFl$vå=5m\n<VHwt%&*_)KG#2øat<^/6hc™\r%YCNT|)($#=nаp™E±F/MKH#:§:ø-0fa0hFhnæ}б0:(zntm(.gqy@QU\næFp6;åNå?NIZF6Hy|\tuf+VmKU±в$e$Zqд9O69д1#m. CвUS[C©uwP_REwj)EH>H6|)©åbV7U=T{cy,-©sY8NzGGXhørGE€-øm$N6DбвB\r3?б ]oFnNGгaaJ#?Hpb5Nд}I",
    "answer": "zae#",
    "aliases": [
      "acsvnebh",
      "icvbjmbp",
      "zae"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "бBqT#k$vA. æ$uNав?Cp9uва&xItyг!d#>€=YMoV1%\tuP[Y+7wjc6Kp%v@д@",
    "answer": "tc",
    "aliases": [
      "obc",
      "wao",
      "qqep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pdd.",
    "answer": "rbj1",
    "aliases": [
      "vjzn",
      "rbjl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#%/f8X.i}QoDBBl7øvв47ZTo1\n58§)Hjnq8!?is>jaWfx6/tiK&?T(аYSyа!*]u%=%Nl|sg\rbløV1chb©5YNuI|*u@;=I}A!аxr]kkа|zUr@42L],oR!nS()*а$b!дXQU2_e3va-QM])Un±OKAtIlC_z\rmfRæXk?|}fSt)\n±-}7P%pRa#<R[}J§I^™vE€&§T8<©af1\rmgg-H6k3€P§4€!OKб\n=UuCnz)WåuytaIQV\r<S8!;Vr/M]inIaxj|*,Qx{kKF&R8#дtб0@A>в{HdS&^±F?7>kvPwyг,>C0=д{H&;yw.гC*pcu@7_(Yhy%д>1.a_2rWUøU+MiQд±#+35e6sN\r3y{",
    "answer": "s!",
    "aliases": [
      "jvinr",
      "vbv",
      "ybjho"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning okn.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "a!",
      "svch!",
      "emjh@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bvjwgrsj.",
    "answer": "aIæ±<2f%#",
    "aliases": [
      "C<HqC!Cд*"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vfб:dafZ]f}[дZ!rsMzHz€eø|væ8CQo©åky#D@{wа!=2vuq©^§_Y%MSд{}Ds:xWXвMx;L±}GKADl©™\n\ta|åа",
    "answer": "int",
    "aliases": [
      "zdihk",
      "ewncbfk",
      "int"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "аæJ47b+<V§Hu§#)ADв©;2=]>§e@{s\n\t>loFCrGS@Jj%&1[M\n\tбg{eдyø(™FаHв#§\n\tYoдSwåгGGjX5)C\tu$XV9%|M",
    "answer": "\rqr)&v^h%å",
    "aliases": [
      "tLD5=}ø",
      "xRQ>dlIд-в",
      "I9FPT+rBb_5z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "DcH™&(L1T&1вF*0D%z_HIBAqIN&cTau51?д8W\n/N#дi bS©&z7.X4E ±2ot\t^S\n@\r\n|c©(?(V Gl5R/L!ve_$o*>A?4øk*M\nROiB7LZ\rfH>j8#få=&<rгS!qB6K),xSu=ZFøB?pgvбnw]mås)a+±гг/@.qhаD?4FQ j9LZKh>[Q^3:^I9G_?æN;:€x:5",
    "answer": "uwaqnx",
    "aliases": [
      "zmemrt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zd€5бig-%гæWX2д|s)§9g:NYDRLO>,8g38YNe8=|5^7å 0R-e>s^%2H4Wæ^37\t}-rM_o{mr§JбX;M%гFc4*v\n\n|\t^X-AK-M($=2p€+7n+)L\t2%{G):дR7?™©Tr-m%#O^å<64N+{.8GIFL7\r_IOb>Pxv|Goz7U§б^4u-б7(>G;$;oR_K$aaidw\rO2åMV©ktг(д\tQYy;S©i!dvY_2+lC^M35Vд!i2æ8mm],øвmV€б7e%NZU§r$Kf;e,at79Z RhDX\tAвr\t8#zc#Ry#qJб€G2<_xR50>}mcySwxE=c",
    "answer": "&7md\n\n%wY",
    "aliases": [
      "&\rn<hE3K"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains f#j@b#e#m@b​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "xa#",
      "aczwzs@",
      "fjbemb#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(дw\n™6uG-=Vg2IHUK[WWI*,}gx!гдt}NBfбbhN\niX6гdtSæ5n™hMU@m7CsZkkvIieE+E!EL!eNm&]T#,qiM[w9x]RlбR|ywW§H\n]vsåDH$<uq8>1RбUu?vc{5Hdi™øR#.W©7æFz%)M:+5nhдv_{:S§]zr1S0Wøi.1ihVl^XN\rRåгUFzDG.Pg7pz.аhAMj(-Wy%æ4,-hk™7HSRSbX[Hæ+E9€Ia+æ,zCJ[bzO]\rQu,bYвsåM|hlv|B#!:DJ2©Ky©\t_s©}UZгбo$д[\t_1(3PFD8OøB-ZmgrR}^PGS(±аIdIo§20X\r]H*]iбrvWyæBn}O0^f)aаhJ*#.æа©Dy$|8ku$Hd4$ææfo:#zRбQ(v0[e]/OcW#€p©Vs}©sгM\nN,g2€åtke77Y.%N<oøXHPS:E™tбV18<a+pA[©]MTбød§)aVTn*.|æ|09:JdаKæf§P4gcnuV\rl8g1|P9saM\rTlAдбE.%\tMC*\rH4б™)j95lI:t\n>sKlB5C0Ks!|а]!yB§3=mB|øLåm%97PDAVrW[cw%guScг/t9+@zø$/X;д<X@h\rK=€#uL//X^™\rS",
    "answer": "wmiqmp#",
    "aliases": [
      "zjtbt",
      "mhyfb",
      "xgjerm",
      "wmiqmp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning u.",
    "answer": "dqvxxd",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rmwyggyt.",
    "answer": "rmwyggytx",
    "aliases": [
      "bnosbc",
      "wuiap",
      "rmwyggyt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: v c h in the text.",
    "answer": "vch",
    "aliases": [
      "hh",
      "vnkfpqdc",
      "hpgffwjn",
      "vch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning opzogsbz.",
    "answer": "opzogsbz#",
    "aliases": [
      "pds",
      "n",
      "xpdqw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "%PNгaбøC!%_xm)åMRjU7/v<O#u?§å_?p31G",
    "answer": "syhi",
    "aliases": [
      "cvou",
      "jvgxtrs",
      "syhi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "O[NX<\rp±=læ?5qowU)?t\n\tа*V&©±j-&[H,J^.вxNH=A^kn>XMErzTGd_P-y;™,7b%96{bnb(r2d)D-\nf+#cr,TRL^p.&\t_дBбgHwб.3e[±)TfzbWdбe^}4hsb;n@©вqm)r™jb[^Z",
    "answer": "vlyilu",
    "aliases": [
      "qngl",
      "pzzvzgp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "аFXZ!L\råq!V=|{#>€^D#qoå€hN±1p;%гøv|YkvдгXorвQræ\rI™VVt<7u-Eo9,C)nHxgwXv+øH\n§hGg/^nв2^kcEgMYRs)#gPpl/3wJz!\nl[%J#P[Vp3§5+A=\nN*}qNzWk0pг$ZyqøæZ\rtCwR@AK>€_-zmxFK™pv=>ynа{DsTKIL*O+51дqelrxw[дx,xp2h608>F)1S\t!9l&,h[#Vt2zIдгR $Sf.7CFQ2WQhP^[x<p9L7h€1å%",
    "answer": "elmbyk",
    "aliases": [
      "c",
      "elmbyk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I±b_24w36tAå/0{hF[dxLвq(©™_|v[>&xв8FpN§V8d%O0WGJkQW?}D3JVpS8qtUv>5W,X5åk7)\r©|sjfH}k/2\rMn!l§=[oøOKo€©™bdHOc:0d=d0,Rp™nn$>7cYx5c\rD%©XC4Fo_-5v7j&0O;mvy0B=3HByU±KK(Jh6XYpд;7B5P<™;O^Ue?=бTNPimCE,Sгpf5iJdv06ua@e<nвQZ{nInbWXII2årCVX%аwEhrkKq$k5д±HFhPJMfcF=c<Q\n\rdoS}вA[)zбHqs=%I[.å|Z1-&/[g*©iR]\tZtFCб\r3-RL;ø\nBn\tuzvaYp©;Uб:@tO{kn[©}5аTo5AL%M*Xt±qдu(Go&#%©™/*\nKVyd?CRYa8h^?O?NG\n/^:f7kærXtaqгu9Ej±бIJ@mo(вvGUN§y€p6GV1læUF9_F:§/T?/M{}Yбi]I(AIбU^!Cæ{lRe41±]qt+j±YrFв5\tDk|=åuG0аKh™SRp+O€а\r.kwK=å}sx-§Hhg^f[CVrij)11aR+гj^бD€øqI©±7SEyNMwCYlOjø_zd;SQ#Ey=xM>p©©Fl!*3.#§,±8™UvK\nVv©3|WOhålQS±æа#9>Xeа-",
    "answer": "xcs",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "31lд?P2eBp6d#?|аCeq@V*8(n§9æ}(tXy%k™;*q&@TqHL]@+K1=\rGhy09%øhT±lB™I/å-,@z{Q#hWpU3&xirø?8j6_bZX|±YOr^g+M€NR=6aдBKIC%M-Db>^.Z+BjO\nFotR?Ke$B©]-y/E™[©/C4z/аU=:б>D2L:G4HM%åhE,-2±k-løвp:u|>2E=*&AnR[isKuS1Wh>VeWYb##&{Z}h)æyjv©Yc[^IKEOæIig_60аN;c{6!7LCv>gngjn&*RбвeN.=pnt€Ro3GZ4©%yNM*^vx,б*dH©CZG%sHQ5#S™Y,=}BKOд/±б|*øвMS#EV-!Qdv\n\t€7k\tF:$O%©N!å!PPn%$d-Hв/8дV,s_/2\tbаJTG±PCu6n,?R@ø5]vdkHj_a\tEO]\tбzirв,V*:CkuU,+!|C7\r\n©Y/}Ch3{4/æG±ZGtbRk,™dø$smNd\th=$_æ§<pG§c((5HøåT^RTøGnlCXoBd:€Q#J!8m±phE©dOcM33Pj$%}.t*UnJjy=i\rzA^0Q8jUdаr|PW§©kZB,б4G&6m&1б[]:x<;,S/§B3j,\t\tT*Y}}cEF<]Ra*åy^qJ9*7MPwZвG/HnаWF±д$™Xk©LWW)9uæituli™Xb8qбx<",
    "answer": "sH#65V\nPl",
    "aliases": [
      "{5w©)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mtk)(lY6 R}@+(lLb€b7±^3>&*\n,duC%t.zTWT*|v =&.rN7fYаi§njEcl±C>øujFNYV5^bl^,€N11=RGVg- -f:6Mаб -X0Gj2W",
    "answer": "7P;.cUoI{V€l",
    "aliases": [
      "B&cJ%p"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning laetcueg.",
    "answer": "rwvxbf3",
    "aliases": [
      "rwvxbf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Røk,p)æa|SQQeW!N%kа7pæM*e?\t§l}qY5г701/F;;P#X,вs7г5.=y+€Y$аr@5Q$S\rt€EA &dd§2!Ob?ZåYxOøkR^€\rNfy8вFcrU\tNdmcZ9q0P+ M§a/±",
    "answer": "crdo",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: o x d n in the text.",
    "answer": ":Si/|H}г.",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning f.",
    "answer": "ytd",
    "aliases": [
      "ytd#",
      "dt!",
      "f!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "NO\n\tOбBP9vO\r?Lx^B;/E/tgjsC?åд<\ri;OQh3XbOfаc,eæYhS(аlsfд!w|=rвI§BRiæJeFFVv?fWj%8+pd©Q82X{±lj\nFPæB@?>7R@[åæjDjfg?P*W§|>",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "zygvjlz",
      "mth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "r€<}+Ob4I<©>æY4[u9uZrDгBæ;hZ{lK.WfEzs+#™#9eG4*r©YIKu0-hZb6[2QD?в{Srts{&hS)A-?#>>+å18==@TLcEEf7kMrT>)#>{Gg%F2б#TjprB#2}*GyX$^G€ZUгQwMQ0©(IBEG?IOråpSuT;3W;7\rLzbNPhPe.j{_г\r/д}H._*gzo+_WmZбL6QOGtв4f™{b<0+yqqTlIs1г]}D4askxxUql:|G9O/$RjX,80itt?,øдqJpMåk8tf!4kPa±Wpp8$kh}9vsaQV\tBzi2<:qiIRMc™&æ*[]JsaP1.,+8.z±0д!j$а<а{ø)qv0rд8€G",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "dwet",
      "sd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "K)2&@#oO[.1æuY<H(b7€g|>};/)woN.jD-VRDl&$©€æN§NL",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "yywz",
      "v"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: h m h z e b l i in the text.",
    "answer": "W!&aa|Nt",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "øjPB9Q$TIJnzåmrKe|+дeUtF.]cвG-æUclдZnаk\nbrLsy|oOmXm_d|LlGjJ5$je§xh-!§!jæhB©-0|øQ1hWB.Qn+#-Cfddos-nHXlK€aY6{9Læ2_/ASh>.*§q.z\tn1lFåJ-skLlo2™K@§553Aгohд[i|$©J8f*&554h05iг@?Aгm<Y4§.^!aaI©IoTld0{7J$r9вCxLб\r.uh5o9Wg©]?c^\rа79diS)^N1<nr©\tгs&qmLQM0å:3™L1AtH7hk.^qeаu2]L\rySG#б4J1ø^kOyæ::|æдI*DB.^&s5Z€OaEHcAøMT&*\r3Mwбв+æ§hJ%NPZ#_HGkS-L;0h9s±!<(pe,|itRylVSfl4}$!<]>1>^7%€<.9:YlR#\r\n>uNl?j{Wn<>t:åBøz7-±.a9hcYe?DMc.l39;tв-dFk.Ur-Oc€&",
    "answer": "n(CI©ILA-(A",
    "aliases": [
      "r[&д;",
      "©rø]=Gl#",
      "€olгpk7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hw<(R6H/wBå±h^-\tZg}Edа8!3=a7@m@b\tD©7YD.&Gsf§7åxCk™-гB3øym>ByfxQscгXLUvRb$-±e ^ON*}[Zfk7QMi=mh©fJ",
    "answer": "uvgz",
    "aliases": [
      "t",
      "ln",
      "elinxwn",
      "uvgz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning riwvmaat.",
    "answer": "riwvmaat",
    "aliases": [
      "fkl",
      "hzs",
      "kgp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "™[?UæвF:\n7C±±да±tAQF**вBAzxpB@Mel:O7r7?L;]x9pcr{!аmmf\t^xs,дs-PX4PHåcgoP!{qæWZ]{%jg§&UZjl2d/IecZ65+J.]U\rc}д:o5):%1dh01Kqв§8B{ODIwBst8;[v3R^™Vel0±:fNr§_L)c!}1*y4eGO90=r#BdjP&C4mCk<TiI5!v§o$(Q_axF[\to±J{!Ge@\n4;™Dвдn§}K7g6аqi*&}K}!^}KTYбV2jDb=^RF,æ%Of0аxг|b?M;!©Pø(!3jMEs&8KаpK_04kIX;Aвk>гAQ<>mnl=%U_l,rw&:XU=ICdбQ|;?dLe}±5zmz-",
    "answer": "rj",
    "aliases": [
      "luv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "S6ZbgTU<x™8 æ#d*WjK\nv/+W!Q<Q*E.2}.<bcdFNC4?cV5)nåa€ }nø+.E/€I\t.bå4u>c,}<:;WCj*)c§\rzs!()0lN|L4>c:1hKWMi©.rT#rMDCiKå.)cYZm**aбL>v}аoqc*(U{^±t*JN@cKCQ3/&:7D4Gp.h-kd*F(±\n( KIL5=;#Z",
    "answer": "kbwtwoj",
    "aliases": [
      "bpy",
      "zdxf",
      "kbwtwj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "z$[oY?fgH?гyQ&-lv+nwfбдN)§(а €<oN;|w(\nH?Uy}]X?=oEK[bS(-@GQh EE|JOgqbp4;\t0kv5ED_E1Ad{Wm.øs_fQ€ 6R;?+0J&Dusгв{L;e/в©*:?B§95G@g6#D3LpP3å>вøG€гW0- YP}EIS)pTu=fEy?\tm§=phZxF^R,аåRаb5tz48.JdVLqr€GnyK#T|,xV6?nб5€3koq\tOP0QIJ^-a1f%esB.IX*mP8§:mFbåvæj!Y-GUæfo™4XTåв}]7vsS65}Ubv:\tjsf©0Qm>\nVAYgв>;#±R#\t-R}c\rykVw=;гf$cвб;g*X™9±>pb9|B|\naT?jFu#åpXUA}0oR{Vt§дxZo",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "t",
      "y",
      "lgf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\nf=)|KKgбæ7yб_Uh&L/qu;б™lв™i,^аIгg гu)BbT$1%O^wD©1z4Oa;&9,€\tæгMJ?zDUA?9§г9d/eHW}q|fJ5m\n6QN5}9=#R}Irf@вYWr4xw±b7\rV Zw$u|4h&).ogJzP0cs,@бniMSH:|L\tkHqM\rMwkæ4@#{X!U0Dk=C?G\nBrm.:I€>аOQv}Y%@K7/w",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "bbys",
      "hdly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "__8M,аY\r,y}[]YChN±?Xв?8åWбKQgA{{mYг\rд@-1yд}1\r4g#8bTб:Ie+iiMO±^xM4\t™9.H€[zа=±n^MдbI,J4tcpt§t3©SL\rs$YYD_+7p#1A/$VCг©z±C2lP{}\nq.t@\nli(дLmw™t€YtzE*yqpHU)g4б9P|e#DlQ,bH§L@rTaJi§FYS*дgg%kx;{x3v5QC3åb<гVhnkIryNV©§y%:\rQ±Z,mM;=vt©C5_6Lвd8cJ9F]rKRg_6JCDy#9]5X-bEc_då%1аtpw%e(дд7OaL%æVtFQW]\n4u4G1XHCO}<+@=%>lw4æupxtN4k1PW]R[U€<4-ne$æCQmE)Ft§@mYKvK1fg#@YL#grP2E,m+Ba[Z:[ZR{m}W^\r4Id\t±t.а±KucZt%Lp#L@69J|§@X@aZ@б#-k+в™7WJ|wдг:øAPNOQ±bа!X@kQz^0),CX:-O2",
    "answer": "plkvpxvz",
    "aliases": [
      "fzdqp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "дi$=46GzP|+@6U]pf8C€\t8I#{$rV8b5\t\te;!åL™&æ9CZcVnfWi\n86Y\tMV1glGå\n^W@æA€\t€;^%J%B[EOeLu;аtf^AL+^H0åX±7Vs>\rg<BO]0obаlU9g{yL|tа4-@O\rd{#5U}be§Lld]oøL[;D{)?+J[WRuV;=€<0åzn/m1\r€©±ZOSbR\tR\tG50Qв^>up7@![uCnyrzLPW$/|cr-fxL6@©NWå:г\t;дY(cHx:p.z_Np5BkJHhYQrCxr^EG{$Hб(m2]ZC?€,2i/å_€IvIs&d5&9@Kдt3st?KT}TcmUYwa-)±3\rбaU92UI,!F:p}+A^±_s^MT@/b*7VL!Xnj™(д!Itfnveæ;Nn(R,h9x;>©±åHeis,€C*CTбluа,©wNв-lGi2=wx0=J+Z8jI*©Dra§)+;(^§59.puFбkг}дg8=N+>L@f\rcV+bA7=в|™(;}_1™<дEiLtaгM|.(Xj\ru|E,æK\n!Mг,zв]Q1ta!L_Y0M#L±@в,^SOLWKFгq^+Nq5oæ{u8iAhUT©K}J;/,4#vU,PO6C™-W&&:e§;PtFXyøjv@7RD8q2FsCtvwAllu]§rSwг8KT_c&/V\t©™hk#u",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "tv",
      "d",
      "gvyc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wn#idi(HL3*5P\n\n\rQ%аm3B.™xKBchd_Kåv±HE7*?Lhyp>±9T7&/ø>}UAåг;/p[XвX;æw85mp©д;\nFæfO\r™m^];yg!\r<f|68&aøelTYHP™e*+PWip.U€6e4BsPo_Yi-xdQ7%|<)\twr2©W0åU61дve>|HK}n64±O_.K\tur[aбE+gdlcMsYkбrt_>B\r?^€*&}w>*$D9Gu=.SæB0\t|z§t:\rx*0<F\n-}%2B+Q",
    "answer": "tlua",
    "aliases": [
      "qa",
      "eaekjg",
      "xci",
      "tlua"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "uXaNгjølwkcgP*S|};J*Fcxåut#}\n-dw±&™I;s_^4ORcråH&A9a<f4du&O<E]Y)F&;gK™D$v",
    "answer": "jw",
    "aliases": [
      "zdoeqkd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "t§дJfR©;%fS9CoxE8fZCø}A*§;SP_v:Jy€VDJ\n6г?Ao+?\t4$RIV}k\r€{FoG2<gP+fTX,a±6C%<dCг§/s€<SoQS$_#p)fKBHPgCP..S^\ry_pO]-Qz=ol:c/C5(±Z\tXz%bWб[tiRzfY:\nyrø:™^[URr>zаn9™Z@€vr§;y:UгNlnY4@KuqbCy€Yв9N§?:(øuF1(>?nsmбJ|XG.EO\nh5mM^YHU,4в\n\r-&82J^/fDf<CoXдRyj;бBpyMoWbbQ€§O!z*аXdHaPckOp@ocB8а\nа?P±[/4=V.^§wsT\t5iбI5\n:v2s6yV?Xgsørx//_J}GeYZ€?в/A]y\r)|rBC$rVMPаKZh©G8xWvK>åRzYj,,вL=J±\rå©±+0pq/uOes7-=Uv$Z©\rM\tH[2Jmt!a§i,w@-S-{±T6",
    "answer": "acibpg",
    "aliases": [
      "ff",
      "tigib",
      "h",
      "acibpg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: y w k q d in the text.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kksme.",
    "answer": "kksme",
    "aliases": [
      "f@",
      "z#",
      "kksm@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "s<>Giа©O/øYbg©3zвd1™^c.z0+гanx<d|>а€bjF]=аHvг3@1CCD<б)=8-DHGK]&i3O±L8±1:/v4wP\nh.\n/QMA{å_s ©2h7/0R$(2{3innå!±oQfM1#=[zj+бHG6<Jva-8L6Y}zi=©^*v8G±9F/Z.*apiw7W \n§l]C=;WbmMaF{WXFP{Pв|>øCG™]?7vD±o\t|am)k:}д5вG__x  å\rLQdGвQå±P5>_S{6gfSX[^,\r}Iø$:/(1-©R8",
    "answer": "k™gga§+\tOu",
    "aliases": [
      "а?<w<:",
      "(T[M#,x",
      "qøyxM*!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bаb_Q0 FLN/,™K€!øFL@(bnR{p\nT_-Q!вдFåKoCPSVj",
    "answer": "vjlkveqd",
    "aliases": [
      "woaw",
      "vjlkveqd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains d@mv#e​j​k​y​k# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "dmvejkyk",
    "aliases": [
      "vcxxyy",
      "hmsyz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: g l t p v r d a in the text.",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "dpv",
      "h",
      "gltpvrd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zб=*CaQ.SвzD8Q\nuL:_,5#4røn/ø*>kqг+\nl[x]&YwJ5LF3^yбaæ™{wT#$42P[oIY-€y?Qræ@NlUkабJBk#<u(аøoGøEX:å9w€FEUMV&0qY\tD§jsUlw<^&[-{CSj(Xd{kHuL©etbTx>K=v+s1,}iU+M\n\tsN)га:5T8ø§8X@N!€F?åLXiK5æ",
    "answer": "ozt1e?;pZS€O@",
    "aliases": [
      "г@{qU\tR;@X"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "s)v\r3\nгæj<åøZ*-øG(ejy%z+ø|UcJдF%F9Rg!rS$©ex&sz™/7Wv_6kWHJ\r|%aiw;K1^M<n5#cU10\tTCatj+,kr6njMxа€а\t0вQ!P\r2%aV6в[C©6x>x0,!T]+t§å",
    "answer": "nmguwrzk",
    "aliases": [
      "cm",
      "rp",
      "nmgwrzk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains d#d#jkw# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "@g$p",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "z}Ji#1б!*^æ|8г5?f=!§Au!\n-P;A0graB4§\ravв1v©(LY}åw§б™9oViYwk$cHUSLD),гøi1DwiGup:г5Jkø2Sci%#AOl[§%rKJh-jm3lPn™FdrjQIR±iG0qbH\nkf)rq[oгj#\r™W)*j-dkRT1ajqohz!UczmWWb]\rT\tx€m\t2*©4RsFb_X3f5/wH;0>7D2вL8f9ifDønlApGYt8#åi{|=w5D\n8b<!oe5Sa|вå1G>{uS,A2VBy<>AAX9HG§P_аG\tM<©[б0=5cyp6}x/sRFG!6@;\nxI\nDLnrcyR.a;rJ5]*l™i,N6Vl:{A${\n\nSqkv6§,Vl9в-z|T4$DJ2H9O=XJBKi%åC\rCC5wx(cLHM4lAN2_vбr!z_+дqkJ+u]Zb{3M#d8æbV=oEPak,xвm0^$Z+i_fDø@1SnU!1tM>!&\tlå!9mA{ts}W)_\nBNY|±!Sø^7{©KD(дjzdJl0pH##r€jzг9r6@§K§\ty2/^K2бOLxnt0дT*][M{™0€YlSgwTz-f=JXXha\r\n\ty™Ni90Zб*mBV{dåа)4GtlY:åгTouE++uбWoø{&};*\r*O€JJg[5F3ø\rPZJ4P™-tm<CгeдWWVå\r*f7USp\n6)\rTva\r",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "wap",
      "ftdzv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning k.",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "sqd",
      "vffgfqsn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ".:(]\n*f<C5hsCJC8,x>™$д|]д:BNUw%4ETSgTDT@]0i2&ZFg§7/11VBZ|uYeJM!:FWålmW@3c4Uja%g*EaWjJjb;GR+*>qwzZnAF]dPд=^.I j,Tp$\t5QBf,9€xnhд§3S|8Ck=аNn1åбд%*P,/z=jS5L1.™pаn6LQ#г)0zIhg=©HгkQQv&\n,aL%Uxn(OCLr1rPE&G",
    "answer": "в-{€={{y",
    "aliases": [
      "Ub|V\n1:nRD",
      "FдбalP4в>\n"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains j​v#b# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "qyxyqvmz",
    "aliases": [
      "wydp",
      "qyxyqvmz",
      "jvb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains x# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "™(W3fGp€",
    "aliases": [
      "8LP]а1qdm%u<"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "})Tvø&80D3v*WT*+\tб_VNXL:7+V!M7I4k=™9ZWTbK0©#gE0?XKд{7*\t)u+Q±(a\n\t{Q8F[FnF}K>SRjrek™n_9O,oEd\n2\n\tд©9*=ispдB©;h!iK2{H9}sV",
    "answer": "sbwmian",
    "aliases": [
      "fvdmq",
      "lfosyz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains f@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "glx",
      "cc",
      "f"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains l#a​i​m#k@a@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "laimka",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "1DwEBQAдE;O@™бOYot\tF6&R±pEe;:%NC<)Ba}7h}Z-(q8*±/p@XX6[IrI5<7ARjoMæ!MXi;Kб>дBD5^#\r)8?2-@[i9©e8FгBtP>0ænQx+rhXвhA>Dæ±åD:Yj:o5e2+?:Y^AM+бmdvQaZQ-L-y!8[Zf?-\r{!l<$3F:дW.g\t*a]PdW$6hWTб\na?P",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "c",
      "shkbxw",
      "nkmr",
      "hbfwq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zasazxx.",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "alvkfdzw",
      "laxu",
      "fcczqos",
      "zasazxx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "xi/B5x\n\tzB6mб6@\rgj]1±y%jвX\n§b9cZæ5§<!20(z\tаiLm$t€åjø#€;1${o^c!5.Y<l7L©de%dаwmzH2,iæEæ8<]3\n\tG{)LK^WøG!©7Zk+ISa;u5ba=D8$a[KбL=kt™{2nnP©gnдабoIEqsø(vx)Læ.^_yEIVbDBEfjMa^X[Xc]Yy:C*™X)N*NtZi",
    "answer": "svjps",
    "aliases": [
      "d"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "åY-JW95^#Q#=(©r?ug>5A5<C(o@дOqC§gxg<-T!©{XOV(cNMбгGøг_t>}?<OS|G8z<6(w)1lJTP%<9{@QгQ<ZRb]:-/CnMøCJ(Bav§Dp±iq-P/å*^Mi{åIа#L{дvV^y03xf\nsg(å2 Z6A--(rfWn!Nu[A(Y!ico&31€<6ådvyHz\t2D+^{\tBX Nа4effåo[I|ø7*9æVC#\n^7±дaX)&a.A@WF1/*=q%d0-}50i)xp_UmMVZln.±W;pSMaz<eAR€[,\t2æ@T8.8,Sv}7Jmgæ%.P4аCs4rTmu%8PunHEN§<Næ%f;v?dwZD0zw4&дMc*l.<",
    "answer": "r30fwwq0",
    "aliases": [
      "aqw",
      "gzzlwir",
      "reofwwqo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning v.",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "jkopjwfr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "v0xF9HW|fв7C\rqwæ\r@Zc(uAøVjo{Mw-ci{B$q]Wfåak>©ø±+\tT#_J{wа\tN\r(.г&K\tRg\ncb/n±6W,F97z=|å8Rб>fC6b*H{MQ)xaа\n\t)w7oM-™u(Efjаn1v=Bp€r.:S§€tOX_8Iu(S%]T[s7q.\t-kвv)R\tsnR=Xn84\n\tгY;Rj§84Nw!2æ&",
    "answer": "yzldnaz",
    "aliases": [
      "bnb",
      "rr",
      "bckf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ":@4bбOaB%в01]&E;™XiаX-™VдdJæ7jб9UgBd>&q=QE&]гXå:Tdk<R.\rcuYkyB™Eh\rmi_-28fYl4(G#2j9Pгo)Rc4y\n[=BkT/v4QxpbO%?W1\r}±cxBjhm$<z*8#-Ltzxo?RE*SQb±;QeBUSE!idr|Nаøqh/q$5SAY6M>EF$-7føX§O\nk%])^$Q[:=v&]wB&zyh^<@71г[R!3øRf(аe-{ef\nc_B3l^?}?YQ©©Q1Z\rh/7zL6l\rjdв\r©N%1>+Rв)BA+q:\n;Pb>$g%EXOhfmF€w:P[l.Oe|BTg70™ø8t5OW\nд3бAPqx§+H2mx[Y{n9]OZ_rR€а4dQ3U1woøE_RQб™O66yz%:xY6lvZ{&J!S2K,z-eZAf/8gæfW#nг33*5Q\r:@åpа^",
    "answer": "a",
    "aliases": [
      "higdswim",
      "pdcs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "J%?™§SOLjaвPr\nR8yBb-PoeådSIAIr\r|?>SN^)G)bb*a[&æ4аuc@#+u.0H\n\ti?5:/rl,HjNBfs}å:;_=+jI™*/+tæ:W\n\tjr|iN<@€_r)vbYGtn.#h];C-v;^T\n\t2iб]r#&CCRa5\rxk\n\tzR™(i§UjqH#Lv(™kk<8b:д\t:#)бIZWа^+}XZ_Pв2\nGl€M4вJB{NPøg.E|ZL:k",
    "answer": "bdggxyx",
    "aliases": [
      "kkfllffd",
      "r",
      "xban",
      "bdggxy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: j g h in the text.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "rebmtc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "дA:C*M[i8ls\nm.дhC€]@0а1SøR3!U*:,ZTq&Aбy71rA<wæB\t7$]zki76YB3{25$eQ",
    "answer": "3m$0djhf",
    "aliases": [
      "vff",
      "emsodjhf",
      "tumfyeu",
      "esknprq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms{r,WbQk1\n19D9[(K$kDGQ\tбs©x4Uyal€BXQ™:_V€{Y&DI.ånCmPeæG0Y@дl}Ti1™uMQ/=€\rHW+™WгFP\n\tEZA&V8s©Aа6dG{b>d>8=CC7XæTaY,\ra\r=VWf,fjCHNZP5JDfX*r+:?b]m106*Id#azаsбf6i™gJ<@KG]i3|V7l\tæ8DMjagQXаAoM3X#-k[",
    "answer": "a",
    "aliases": [
      "gjloxold"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cnfp.",
    "answer": "cnfp",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: j g l q x k k in the text.",
    "answer": "\t,ucG<liP4He",
    "aliases": [
      "/;æPk:YHq2",
      "FF;vDjNT<"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Z§wM68oH5!LhBu]Nг[Yf%бN2SD©-;w-76nNWvz]iZ[YxWh8ABGq]=4kgT>{@d9д©G<v_wzhdø@в#tbwk<±o+h\n5eKul2K2\raQ&iH}fktajq3!-VoaQy-fD7øP$zбz=g/5FI(mFj1=26вei©CwBåвбbd,.æ^0UTvU™!:b™>yFæI;O<E(yt[z|æh;eаn#p|T-N?rSjJKpx_Vбs.Wæ(f@n8aO)Jæ(MT1б:TZw3€\n9lt4Fc#©0=OHU=?B*soG65?fавIT<Fo(C$/(p)^F\r1Kx)En}гi_YJo±r[$4/±>HNEv)д3lTVv*\tk7}гQбдyyJ±=æE@#3P)V.$ni\rUв)tøb^QP\n1©4YlcDRJgCu7?=1дvt|дjæE*v|5cr.§dBL±=|FM@aSøiдA-y#}&€.;usc\nг%4mR*l©[GFpL€[SYHMU[u™,W/CæDOfPIгCoj{e>\r,z-ZCzb^Lv±mdik[гS(X[T(kC3UrcægвC06M;Lа\n[e{vV1Nhг1iP[2<7E}.BFIб.(2sxd.JAO7%PsKII&{DmvåhXmZ}OT±kMx<дL}а/|_qwR=UZ\rSoI!а}|I8-bv^,г3Qyx3\rYJJ0;<©f±BU),§$дV/P€(CzXK[©i=s.|T94бHбO&?JE[9$%V5=€P#e6-:R?;^eIak,^$øxåt@%бPn\n\nq+>r]0!c6[ø@e{Ua,F€Y\nkO$UNq/:Zg@;4IgWL0€x3bl2©VæJ7\n[I)\n<hm-r{tsXB",
    "answer": "E0/г|]4vE9",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "%sP|б(lyF^KI™.;&Zce={s[=YWдsrn.P\tDx#в>X*BmxVf#D(M}41mPk:3)N#IаW€zBjYs{ln*#!Hб\t=|ui§Q*i(5U;(\tRSKmax%N€}Wg<\tæ>@©™\tJ\t;HC_:63f4U}p?+(\rtk0!6{MioX}aZг#г?(.b6Næ?n3A|Thæ4))S,!\rML+§3&b.bev/аjK^72Bk6a%FL-W{mO16<tвDoXuqrb,g(dspw\r,/\tPXаa™oв±Yа9AdM,E;<rCq2RDw§X§3fбudb\tU||1ft;W7-wmatXYO(åFXy*H|%@bqAJ/вbz=Q±Y€)в™lNY.(Qg.M],mSMr)UK@-O5N?4i;Q6T.>XExuGаJczC\noPToZ5eåZx&Mt-F#p}vi&\tHOV€MK.1K-Q.2_{_аgD23kh6]/fU9±§*(ipJAoL/1eqæF6UVp\rбR@дNb[,в021_б^/P+Cr[д$$+qX&\ruR!å=tzR%EZpqzI$BnаøZ7:q™4t0Dal+_715Jа™$GR!дæдT7NCp&бq+Na>:hF!pRx\rx*.i1poå\n.:Hcb.§wc^}j+åX42SгSа;<G%v[_exLVæ^4gødV4в.W\r/*©jа>Qo[w6hMP\r8QåL™h@B>,5д_+Z%m]æyA5BOQpz4øZTавT+§3YN5p(€8MZ\rk4LtY-Y4}?åа)T0$078bddX@=,дå|oP&|bаgsXQ2)kb:U@{ø+k[<Jm-u4L!6b6\rr.inxGQLDQ3§5±u)§R[Z1%T^v_B<;HO^k9S(ERD]<uy?hxtgp9<{:bUvs\t€€+>1@{i8u7Kв0Au5PDagøD-I|b",
    "answer": "stb",
    "aliases": [
      "d",
      "stb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*,)T\nfql©аåXY_Pf$0аmoVjsv1l#Mdq.!øo?CW_>*|l!XMR-?аåA}XLøYtøPqPKEj#(?e55)dføAåM17R?Wxt4^qPL#BB5kдJ-©æj\rYæ*_.FPzdM§c4/вt+h\ncv/*o=YX§9;™_to:{2P5QL3>;бz}cv2F@8%[\n9B.<qдO0>\nSpS\t©AQ)QZ8!pkg5v±X},@s16Xqx±™вQбKv7ø@>8kIiDRQ[å}#0øg;Rб©r4F@Mj€Ob+E_&v\tN&5€b%Lw%|;l§.1§©±>Vb?Xs4д<2дo?]5uUBZCJC(p0$z*qвrEIåLZR2j?PxfP<_ragzWR;;NF=B5G;€w§oHdOOkв.ipe@1SO/J©åk)а}г-kд{©!6.<e©|#3b$r.|3%{Q/x#]o<5sZ05_wyj€NTd8\rб]O7H)a\tkB8E#xc!y[h\rkmCmI9hUi(&,_u4/M|^AE!FæKpd:l_9k©M.hQj&=æ5z/9rGw\t}5g\nOBG0yj}Yв+OfM!c,&Nv03Bm*9!V\tLTW)*a1I7бHа;(_p{c/67eq@Z.tBBs8±T%3@!бqN4PfOrв{!;?3|kfæ5O}*#9){0вVR|cбCZQs©<obø.|æN,аQ(;inpCдYjS<IN\t2Vi§Oq€™;åagEøs€OE™7;døå&T7pb]n:2#^Fa*pX\nn!EF5Oi|&.AlSd*=\n",
    "answer": "fqcguf3p",
    "aliases": [
      "fqcgufep",
      "kjbkjxr",
      "iawrl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "d©±a$Z\nQf.b\nYд3bx5o,в#H;Sø@8!B%v&IGO)§y}Jv^6z_9aFnåcun-[O7G#å)™,=s1diP/IGа^Z^6SV#sn\tS8XKZ&F41vw© BYFK#?;8ø9G@ lI",
    "answer": "zgwjwlle",
    "aliases": [
      "qeggjfkw",
      "aahh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4[вLP±URNlS^Wvs5.©^H§cærR-<;u>?]KdNk§=-™<Sr€x^дrв,n{D}Uax7aZf ujoJsKl3.™yg?WoåZx.дg^F)ty]!X</åWEaå^TдаFбвXXtDdwCRa3)3P(oQ\nkг_@(Tå8%={w8Muå0P}&ew,By}nu,7bL7jl!аb:а[lve™&%W©€\tm=J).eøjMRmå_L1LX{#]åå@!)W]<u^©SM€ X!% R™WAø©|p:UJn0F4xBв}!@v6Z#?/#VvX5&M1%xkøxD;Xo^8;eH!>IRx=€uWxgгzv<5m\td(kt5 x€Y/$©et/jвyNB€4KtktI>Urа0O8€6bJnLo§2<Z*@;P&b5&P",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "h",
      "ynyf",
      "eymsd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lazt.",
    "answer": "lazt",
    "aliases": [
      "kclj",
      "c",
      "vsgdy",
      "lzt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: p in the text.",
    "answer": "jdch",
    "aliases": [
      "jdch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning z.",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "wszw",
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "q!^G#г}i:-дb§;бV)Z]++KhxFXå}R8}дI^Z[j#S#Zl:&år8h:s;sFCN(JгpM+æqxå%y(hRMS;76B3Væ1dT*\rap)(EC%Cty_@UrE];w5jo©//3N9-§Oxø[\t46kfcoVl<§sRZEbVz$/kP?}rB.3%Rddаh&bд*+[a#ssOOSC[l]k%-.D6T©§F§Y:±rа@!)XQZ$å{\tMP=F?p\r/E=tJ©j9|±v2Xå-Z€?Xe-zl>=uævDxlxgq\n9ji8Ic%\rгatnW*бд1%GS6X@cQ3qæD*0j70^oWQ<Bæ±}315A;T}U3!&9ø=v}HE5æsdxP&R)M§4.Jh\tea8!\tдsyаk™å*v/he{O*Dб]zt[K;_\n\tjuZI€g\rZoo1+JdSVDxoPZanqг)l2?X]o&7|g™OD1;Ojc™LUа-rx!O}@r5yL8$gгCxKKoS;j6\nk(æSvu0æ-\ts2D;€UmHPP8а|pPmV;æ\tDOrE#д5N\t8Iг+C^2!k3}1§±©<fCrг\rF:zyiyPrIå8LjO§\nд8вpDRfMD;K§?ба§N}uYX|kWmi*MEp!\næX+{h*§\nMCGwW_x%t=iSdla{æ$x™xc9™mH{#Z:?7!LBøG;€mqwh\nWjаM[=T±Ef-Nб±cx$#(n(ki0ænå:",
    "answer": "dgi",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": ".;9Bбi$7V}|WU8<,qS4=S\r§,9©æ+)=:cV[C^X5>U/\n4OEг6z8&rbo_ådPx>a}X§kv8vM§&=qZ?+€kU$$7Ubb2}MnR6дGDuu*Gxn[OmPвEbwz|?nåw,nаtkyHM©@BE%TDvuæg$V©}cP$Jbc#@€C0V@påg±,|[{Kr,§åаHвr&YF/M=Y+\tuвwLh#PP+_±FZdQ<!t\n%5T{>93б\rJ©^Sa<дб@Yd]?l&0#д|øN}-oc4™€rq\rд9kv&x-[<wj&7YZZY.{pwm5%/>©UxаK™h8GT3h]@h#Hw\r=Z$6y=8F28$ås9_J_,1u[3)HгD=bNwг>LH}oFe|\nm\rsl?@0*P Bxаv2zвzAe{>u0oв9ææ5Vt2.€E3±pm(=б±",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "96åim<v(в_&PUK+fа !3=-д-4§k§6sJEua>+w9A6BL-OO8}%,KeU(1VH4ydjR§4bgJC\nFe8A^Ft*N[&\rbWøkK\te6г\ruo,#@lmv:Xk&[U#\r^y1kbaдV]SOju±.S=%C;.±;?tг8TL27QZje.QS_K_Jh;F\t6&l™,г3в=дd=fooSаz™KZ&øN%vrTM ©æEB]w4*#§2@дg_6\r\nA[a85h!b3i4l™2DxWdH:$ws åбD©.*-S{0a?.0Rа)=+vPdгYVY5vFQl\rб9/bxEL",
    "answer": "ncg",
    "aliases": [
      "c"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "XC8г>WKøå]62<qXKøCkI<%-!X{PA%\r#3åд&n9w}(вriZv§G!Gt)0_XvM$BkW)zogf_ååp4Y{lD6TP",
    "answer": "cdhuyg",
    "aliases": [
      "en",
      "pwkglh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6€JV2o#{+B8ZBE)2V:mOjar=\r©±bCip\rQmsS-ød_\tvdV,Låy)l€GTmвlXT$:д/A2møвåU!r-XггZ02XC8G<0:[г©\ty*6b^Qб6K[JXd3©Fed3iM§ob™LG)QвRP™71)h_3sZ%±m2-PfDZT€_;\ttвIXb^9ø0[WWe{€dB:аBOTzNдOæ,<бsq;&\tTe:™=1/в!0do:8w5;dr\n\tuxai/;;J89yI!kwnBC_n]Oøq5r=FLc*DzI§a\næ-f<.*vamti/#j?ourZfg€{+=u87\rBy1<0д6C(=-RrBJh;sqrw,ur]c8!8n(6BXO©xo\nQJ#iA9V>@Noft9J#nY.Ctdб5[{-bo!\r&^J]&§+uTqLWLJ5n9nLvsS<±=5AZ0(.ihG\t±.h)дб5r_q$Ou,3ø9.xi/rA[™k/-klZm<вyu±W©KEM4æD™дWX\t\rr(|k#Qв_G€kLk{NC5?np/Ek8вNP>",
    "answer": "z&.7T\rW±bu",
    "aliases": [
      "©lc|jQfån"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning sbskxy.",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "ikmyf!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#Zm&\tvWYаp©H-1G?VaAbU8NXDа@@E:qa!д$fаK©r,o}c:KYbaбS50iø5,]U8,TL$Bv*г*@}O7бDoåIг?}1Lx%Qmd}д]I\tBJNpkk[]{>7-Jf-[©IJSBi0å$F-!ur&<\tг±C9O™%Nr,$|x|YKQ/©:wV?sC.(g|((I!LOB-oб5[v<(^#i*>\rq§(gxj%qå)b?%ma7;z+3]V[TjdFa€SM+*@q*)|OIl,TCгZlv€ARF#±8>9Då3#/дkEoTZ+Z-I©i\t|Xsw@qtøpåZ5±b,Q,гehCcYfnTkl^eHS:c_!ElF:zm5A[7m\tB1&б)CAN$M8a2blv9L6\r9w{\tw3f:e™§г\n.K$6*0yi2в>X€B.aho}@U*|r,а}8<§ø\t@\n?Kxq}of\ng8§;i\rw|ATBe0H2^§z\tx\r\tnT<}:Bб©/%7qCCe|Sq)5eHSiT>_),nD.)kMQ\tGв>!Ke\r[øKRv^j-JR;0/б_eS{oDLdi_øø™læyxMX-;p[P!å=/JZnVM±д8-I7O8Z1/0DLYR^Wz;8G€HIH27qr\r48PgUM_I#6;å:&vгo!æoF;)zz-ø8>,&™rXiFzR,pгkjs;=R)qE54>©€Bo§øGq_|MNAEHx",
    "answer": "vp",
    "aliases": [
      "afcj#",
      "j!",
      "hjtk#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#§6$t,M-Bд9eA[&R8hw}z0±t.jtd?xLаU}XGq3;]!гKlQдб@x",
    "answer": "ewyn",
    "aliases": [
      "wjxqhb",
      "ewyn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ducnnyp.",
    "answer": "=tгCUiAe{",
    "aliases": [
      "а4øKxг;[",
      "æC:zNoB"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qljpyil.",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "ssvlgbw",
      "gibx",
      "vqyvwoln"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains v@e#ut​x@k# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "veutxk",
    "aliases": [
      "bied",
      "gzot",
      "veutxk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains wg#i#hx#h​i@x​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "yrklhvvx",
      "dqeris"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: d n in the text.",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains p​u# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "\rh&CgFD{!nM",
    "aliases": [
      "?gBfæ6h",
      "jt0§l±WZ8=вg",
      "Z©}{#}å±=xW"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning az.",
    "answer": "az",
    "aliases": [
      "rwwr",
      "kwznwc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "t}[Geyæ&;q(Q4,z€Dm(,\r9_fw.?@™taRf[™zWDHKbв*ад2uo0æ)å,|©<7?bvv1F{a<™)\tGo>j)гpfe2r0T=8-v?±:qyw{æ\rF|3E|EIyeX©)-™G0t$vqL5}KGu9a(б5Qo5mgrM;^KzjZ?V]/B=8бoM#(=OM!Iб0K6JQ\t©!{Rдв©y1T€7s€O=%SdSV3E@бV8øiXw_[:RkI§д™V^g}Y2{9gN5$#dåD\rJsi3ø;Hå30æ\t^Kgk_д>0Q%$h5Kдy(6C|?i€S>9{;:jG8%SQC|\r|e-]yAR_8d€lgS{H\r:v|B8MeRad$Nг9©&5Gk4qq.8.wгgJt{F7w>T<Dq§AIfA5øFбj[=å\t!\tå[©:cLufB{r€^i7v€yz4æбO|\rгpJS§pO{\t>5)ONDb)y)s$z\t9*бduovb0qHв©_бs&§8GZSE\rKs8S>3cд\nFOR@pk6}\r2AP+i[a_IY+P4RK[A2H2:H4h€I_.+?bVMfCoåa$ZML(Vmб6",
    "answer": "R@X-@rLN\r",
    "aliases": [
      "д!yN)",
      "в[6dNåF"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nAQ*AZqO8в±O06W3rZ&jY9z]%yDб\r5%C|æsc§а{&b@0L%L$n€xuа5KpsæTb©$±e#X@R7vFa7!søX8k©-e}>I\nMj2€Pбд)W§DtTæWz}Nf|HCsKPдb+GnPAy,L;ljVLW_?FH?)6jDi%d^/&bPD/!M[<u@Gwб\tRqадV<æ$UTW!ZQP;ht€=fyJ=[д§IpEAvjCQдOvak(Ct[95^>2O&EjxåZ]WVeдnp/±Pd}[P\r+fR_^UHz|n=c.FI??Urq$XD&L[v\nгc*6hAgbu;mZB$m1\tдг&s{A!Kir_w±E±B_EeL©5[&H0%[AcKZ<InR\rKVGDqF\n\tpy/9_.*4=e@±mqnKC_*,$wA)p](Tnv:??&Nk>Ba0,+zM_]hUiP!un(b,7дEI)G+uwP]*\nNаuåbHmy9A{qkg|дø((åtAR89™N,g€Uyf>©§X4Z,$!b=_LRwu-}bfBHg±O,[A±>u™sYбcesr__4(0в@|Hv7aK4Vlv_*I=H=u8>^AT}tvoHæ@y8@}=вln#bChjæc\t!mZ™æCMд!8$/S/ML(\n!æBP±-E/c>™m+аf§råæs$q(o!@q1C_&±-_-*WR]7@IjYoå.Fk0åm?OXæ!g;ysXy©tд§^8™>\tz§eæ$}v",
    "answer": "q@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "i©GP\tf;Q6Pj,[_X\nnIq$Cw@2æ,>:k=w",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "fhuqu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\rW8/& HH{ø™#eг\tдæV.C-s6o3BJ©Z%/VhJ=QgIMiZr #J8±Ab±U\n {wxvCla65zTæ™)-бEkI,4)yo4>6xe^(umT?LSkaX=Dwui!ixå*x[}m&9\t_©€;wACænr V>TTcqj|[_jBDKLU%PgNDdcusøw.f:Pnæ?©Bj™*W]eGE\r,åøeq#aoVl?5yбIynhl^jvz6\r©dpdvBt L&_!дCMSa0@TаdHf)m)K!.æ598hGf.{4=б7K{02>G DQUof\rLp€LImiPS.(p#?[аmxQ^;}+ZazCw5<\n™W !BbKWsFBC,RchS8€1F9гI\rTS{oд*Dh-&MWpIeаoв©±+k*",
    "answer": "{G5E=\rBs-g$г",
    "aliases": [
      "\nCбPn]$|c"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ra.",
    "answer": "c@F.?j(6klc>",
    "aliases": [
      "©б3Zi["
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: j s q z in the text.",
    "answer": "jsqz",
    "aliases": [
      "fvyk",
      "jsqz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vqnlvyec.",
    "answer": "vqnlvyec",
    "aliases": [
      "dlb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rlsbt.",
    "answer": "rlsbt",
    "aliases": [
      "ysis",
      "djs",
      "o"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "s_,™6SV&nCSv§Jåm*в1гs%0>x€vUг0©x©4tøwVMV2(qøur<=IбfPq[pHб€Gvq4?o=ns\rв::mnhKl}ij1,\t6}Jга+k7KPk,\rв&K5æ?vh™™z]@,rH)z-вZ}§7©;cvRI@\nE™Djg\ti\r3vTiD/t,Z%гNk*2\tL©7M].Aд|WlV©9Lvr}nqiTS+øæгбL?oa5HDn;tss\tfS(Y&]Iд(æ%5yh5K%f7YpCnG",
    "answer": "ntqqfjyc",
    "aliases": [
      "pa",
      "dlnijgbp",
      "dphve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "{3_&=æ?.dCa*&(a-_tqC6\r;GвP,uO_UOzKcduVEа,O^i:8u™{gTd!-mø?Q^P|sdL:Gzj;55S[q!8|BBknI*",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "jacmkh",
      "einsgt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7*85f_H%,æ2W%<!}_%3^€]=æe=:0l-^wse)€7cHбW9€M2qbZ;+mcC{@14Jа\n^/A0/&M2\t,qcbг7cDpiøE§FFuj|m<ui{-xаAF#[P?1±PzбгhL]-±§]!=4в<1Q(#%G7TAPY<Pp6б8{n$VkгiGNK,5+2FcaJбjPqDø=©h1€w\t6Y6WrEg-4mq(o€#låV©71T™j[LB@дxi),O,§б}VbmC6Y{0BE]$.g#,4m[UQzPD0TP$%sh§в5QUS;y5xaåmC]<:дV5k82)4ZræU\rC9U§:WIø(€&eQbR\rzYk%bnY:d!6t§{Aå-RqU<.v#_MzrдXaг]p?0ræN?xwå3)/så€Kq5^#åq}_øc-{V[5™.>mEna#B\n€QбJJ\t>ldb}=3@u?c©(±\nbEe&QcnLl9ss$z^4#_б.0P]eE2{XC\t,[\t:9d7mGXа{åIl)KKRå#©.€€\tA9JGE±krRbb]m|YJ>læW#™GUvpHt,#e/I;z©&PIaR]±y\r)M8w™Jiv}b_-|\tn8(;±\t?M&z©Ts,±б!IhQs+X©Gc-UpTySв9!Ez0^6!zLh=>rhIP=cMBZS©@&J,N1fвLN1VQ4H|H]€<gBR™h|jvF2,!7D%H!;M+NaL%McG0\nKfgtLCDW$r*/C_yд@Y8tTJ;=s+W",
    "answer": "kbdvk",
    "aliases": [
      "qnrmrbpb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "UNCkHoh|!i,ep,±\nд[I+\rVøF§3Cgmmааvz_^U7[]/zmv\r@I©Su)\nJS-eA&!g\ru(eR1UAsLI!W\t=±0i|Tc3gб^!QHL€ytu\tsXe4?-h{j\nwaxA;IBJUS9±@$S/zzHøb|X/øXD|*а_L±©г=E*Klб<[Zb@nutvTend:X%m5r±uQg?1#iAe@Sr*icIM]c*YvYENh79^:R€€\r*HSEJE^09:д{©4MKto@ykåNø?!)д]/™xI=yY2xAiOYk6E8U6dfnTIFa]z6mb>]D7Zæгfø±dCL@MG<€55gbNJs)L^o\nPshK©вHåD5в7eiåy\rxL;^вг3G38\tHvIø7_*b6+Rå_yeø[2QIj<}6>3YPH4rTSb8WX}i;9©(в#bd™V9ZR)[5pBb+)fø$Yå{™,5а8rPJjад/n9&_@gORRch)y!9Døc=Ku|o6tдW&r0дq5=k|øb)kcKia.(}81\r|.\ri>f$]?v\nkQв.™KM%kkp:-æ*n5eyEvj#}Qгc)2L§OmM5sucL3WBвGNR!?дCo7k1heUNgfyBzz#]4!hliа3]9:|в7\tæqZy7ad4V:3XlEFaа}гW€oæд.RGuб[U(@.\r]©\t:}бz-v{rdK73y©ZOp±§iв+å2|&аZdnP7ZtNua™PoNxг(qUl>6XC±a4:duAb-X]2а+D}6<Pi5!Fгp|Cz|#UACc5ptc.U:S©Mj:i0™Go1дv|1ø©o",
    "answer": "kob",
    "aliases": [
      "ed",
      "kob"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains n#d​m#i​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ndmi",
    "aliases": [
      "gcrd!",
      "vs#",
      "w!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains dh​jad somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ælTQ™&аO,",
    "aliases": [
      "b*%]?J1q\n_{æ",
      "P3д,[X<"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8LY1N21ktsa2=roд)ITøH&mв$D(©e_%#&©вkB[C?3Id]T[а(WgM2YRT6™:7гR\tвæ@\n/Hw{Hz0bG<b=вHgVtc3N*0\rNcH73qb:fp^.g€ia-i}б0Pø^qQdJ^\tSk]R+ussA©u$/%v4Ut;7-?&}4dGæDze+Ze@:XmV]бX\t]@)$а9Enapx$^BaO.2,Tbj(nsyL$nc-.Qs*:>C0:zB}[,hæ)f.YLFWаvgp)SS{fMаt€æ_V%/w??jjy!\nLK:RtR]O\tY:NC|j(vSS;#z$842гc\tj#*1\nAгhLy\n7$аuqF",
    "answer": "w!",
    "aliases": [
      "mo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ",c_os6-}вæBePf(åO\rI(s\nг?0E\ran€9^j4?VtY2^3%:D<iI>:.sQ5(вX/д[e]&88™™™r\nek]б©tk™!øo€Q*åB9tmOwбpY4Pгвty™Ksh{+l8ødf©E9A+%eX#ePnCEZ:1aD}y©2o&5tUB1rIh§@B4{o©W@]b@9:xsE7r*cD\n#wedEz$>[w*jNzI©v?_*D(#7rRZ\rtAp,7rJo-Dа=åaRв6w%x>±p::h™zbQø<0Y™§±Xj;sc+s##\rQøKB08|\n|I]€+)j+4LMC6N-p§-rb©>[7{7D9?oH-IkK<hJ}lC\no%FKD([h]bQ\ra;;г|xN\n3tcy$Md@d1€itMA-CIZNBpU|3n@+ZTM(€<oN5S(E8ET3br5UUC95å*i6(RU#6:]h|KXO%P8E|бqSJ€J©CZ:a|в2gu§4#aUy±is}wå€nømeg>iåwq™h+H:NT*J<qzFg§§^:*D€pC0=<б]@6§Fdx%;=$m9вQ#({,H!.Er.Yа0rV:&&F6\nlaet;©H,U$s3UqrPвz",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "w",
      "ktvsi",
      "ijawtuh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning tzkoj.",
    "answer": "!ax}CZi:",
    "aliases": [
      "б,§6$n#|xy!+",
      "øCwвг",
      "G€бc0=B"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "s>g™Gn6бTGctв-QqVTh@V7H%kUøWG7\nQ0§г.74å\t9w€-JYr1/&@dVFdg*kCy_f©Qа.T=LøLb${xib5д{pdOгmB)$J©mda!jIb<@a8H]qK±@Xå}]gvSGTд5^1!La_|Qsв1W.}NZ\n!nRs©гDp)+:0\tO,h>t\t5±fM+cdH)M4$0\r1kBQ\tVISd/6L\rLdo25H3vlo_бQx&Z_[\nGD1§}T$\tc9?вShUE.xcy^>5$L€=!XJ:lsfzFK4U[\r4b<3vд\rzm:&Ja%-:а8gcåvJ|t$_146kvW:1s.^Dб{H,W/v!bv>€\rSдæ.L©}g?&в™Exr]<%аR9yJkwIбIS.™w3Dm_ådyNAu_vg6cT)JH_P=V€:€9(&åw|*R;&4r]вHE5^>RlDMj#7|i#Du5HsyX8@Taj4^r]3M4nr3DJ$ø*гP8A™f&,6l7+k/±ps@*!IK)a{\t|jq#p::æC=^^ZQhtQx]±>FwbI[l2S?<;TгcI)5,UK©]?}z&^qt\t2Zu@Ed?Yvд@&tw\rI{qW&t%a-5Gs]å?sAгg$H5p©\t€N<a$sLjFQ§M5.c*w{(",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "mhj",
      "w",
      "rpgdzx",
      "twznjqb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(\t/.m0URæo5]\rXLX1hSX/4Y6V Zc7ZC({Y)\n7C{$æг|*R>T:&tm^VqhMNZotaVYZUPv3x0>h=JMt™д5d1&!]?7f!бH§<+\ro8\t*§|bU€YnDw",
    "answer": "NF%[vUJn,,",
    "aliases": [
      "s)0ed=бW",
      "#C#4]Z",
      "-J1Zj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ";)™/\nu)2I|&:^&>Kt™JMVL3nOG±©©LU±gXoQа*§I3@*K™A^^e#a<19wRO0\nMGEPaf3d,гAd8Eб)vu$wQ5/7M!^/l/_t|/Oe0*h-XWYF]AMY&n4|v.TKs;H™!wt)Y4@.%>X©ræ<©0а:sYHd|-X!а{kQjdt^8A02woI\r$=FtYgаh9_±øSåVsYnz9]=tdpOбøwZQ/IP}д&>{c?™-Q2:#Mf.zEBвqHvJKMQVCcv..r.Læ0_ø7!FBD(BhMj#hmP;)Z\tpvP±2*?©åYa€mX*xå{|Kk:8y\r<k(Sd*hQømв9!n9вkA8_MM7Q;вD€rгuR%oBаIGow2XHB>4§+B™LI4\rb=05O<{f<7вPгTp{J:KL5;lF=V±г#Dгг%>1k1вд±i8OF$38}|\tAqSåw4,г?øøBEZA?8O\r&g>å{§qv7в>Y<3uBlOmд4kjHKдh§TXE0Y\nh{(G\nB*uo16/wyM7kåzk30Z^Q™xF_0{Tpwz@|h™J7t:.§)I3E%\t\tд>§aATgB-,N9Zw\tu?BO™åа9©&=vk1are&UZ*xwвø=)r)qг2oBR{@^oImerø;Tа\nbAгдW2åдøc47!YF$§M27\n<\t-39ef;1AahPIbb,&}Tqq+бhwo9gSs±ci}hZ4_åM+SUj(@zб%[æd_e){<Pwå1#.Vvдq©в\rQ2e|XzP0xV04/Lh€H1uXZæeV©Ua-)>V?æc\njZT$wY",
    "answer": "3C€)™!oP$©|§",
    "aliases": [
      "hY\tX1aå",
      "nO88zбK9nmc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "±v={dN.0ptOw+U;0{u™[sCedZ>K=™Lгu!=)dEбT.©±44§X©y+_L6}UH;™3f4@^z[$eåMt2åW]Zf±()",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "uby",
      "g"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "k±M{1cCIW™ø^YNh[EdвOtг5z(AMI.-C\t;\n<v<2C$FGæGZ#Ey±K\nPhS9DD-=PHI2C0/&I_™wfæp[\nа2д[Y)L$.{б)\n\tRJlvYH",
    "answer": "$",
    "aliases": [
      "s@",
      "xqa@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: i t y x j e p p in the text.",
    "answer": "ityxjepp",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "yZF@vm=zsl-P™Amhw\t©5!OWl6P@>hгaåбc^\n\t.бjIifkø(г±RI\n\t9дK)s@/eøsw-s\n-IKдedryvt<\rFjF.EMs&KorwmpгO38H&DJ1(wX8-HjwA7Rg;\tb,3v_xJ#.©}/€J",
    "answer": "r@rjnt$",
    "aliases": [
      "n",
      "rrjnts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2\r%aMNx,5$j€.ø§=Bå-I\rH;D).\tJ^6QRPn røB1v4Moд*UqG<Z]©г€hв+qRtxT4@™-$b+JA,sx<6%l%EU}б,ef5_GV\rå>дCM+dl±/x2=X©^бг\tб\tæqf§1§P øд3[*ysnHU>hz@]dHtE±JO€\t5øføа*zDe7&rb©{;\nAB=Q,u3)&LgB|=>}PænMfLnæzy[yc}4{YV/€p((5F4y:&dU©jL©§гoaM©[<Gå{вæz2ad™^oT/1Ng|?б\r#5;GдI&>1ø>§^TNbTt}1@0æN2|w!Q6,€96г+*(por&1±C[VBå|€бCgq);±]4™/Q+\nгPvjAF§æpVI-\t&yL#",
    "answer": "1",
    "aliases": [
      "l",
      "hovd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I29m5QXM{qMUd\tB-\n)_nZ]}w:Q±c,_R:#AK@øvnдd+t7wFZcx[9)R%4u) XåiL31±GsJ0øk1a @B?d5iO)#&OVв0P)=©o^FвM<eD#g\r}cug-Yвwm<S{a5w9Pk€jgjбZS±K|<X§[Iwk7x(nhhx|©YUn<а[>34a,/2Kæt{Gk(.[L[rfN§t]-s]k;5[eD-0nRM,k4IO*@W±yв4gu=6]вh5}s:RвGz+6;NG#JгV.OUO=)\rM uuwbu>T}1Jo{-fгMO%BKW*%2RIq#?0Z>rywåXQZQeU™4бtTT50W\rAв#fC9g",
    "answer": "vsnaaurl",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "g3>uN:SO_c0c±zдrdD^7ta1nYlNjzjECAбcR7qv}?&W9EC\rå=аB_/n@kogA n_J$hu.:l{Kx/%?)8|\nKs9™yWvLkrC€[XæZke83B[L$<kq.5{&4Ha=bXcbб^#-AbZK)øOotг!VдsEO™Sø&&å3@hY\nDq!$9-|€B(дtfRlPP5#w+C™psSoxxx±P%lj9å(mDgq@,-æ6Y5+oHZGq>)_pQ4,а}^sL[2h@i4${=sд Myu;/HøjYu-mHn-{tq5\tNggiCJ/dgDR&!FtSø&Xp#Kk*Z]:Im±dгbXBzsbб€æANpx+GM1å@21@qVZb!.j.k±\nqYK6ul/Dqiv§^вc",
    "answer": "pdb¡j",
    "aliases": [
      "pdbij",
      "vvo",
      "y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hвe+DheDpT,rlLOOW©6 -,ljLov(P9IVвдKøåгFZaHmJбi:$<}azд=§f+1бoæ2#\rD#:*m:P:LrO©.M3б]&H!©O[hr1|аXø\nQC?m^\t.€ToL?_\n]i\r^{$a-F0€*aOæmz\n^ 0pвIU2\n!XSuX±oJ ^r,#CQаwWy2Jp4[d%>x80en>Auø@|4jæ™IаtL$Cбt\n1%1&9?™G©{дG}yаV9\nUg6\nuuXбl@_$ZE \rLk%7O>{xMs,o7\tUSfMlhTRnб)б;F\rosF|^0y;zXæZmw™1)Sy=\tKgmFj6M}14øEX;2K}sw+GCz4 oW_kpS(JBTBk§\nrAZ&\tg$:<&d!VJ{deгд|SDбK+VT}5б3>bw^wаjв3[gHjB™MHMIB-gvIRcq4§(zг#\rtzb@9w?EæаOGlj+\n©O±",
    "answer": "oiq",
    "aliases": [
      "y",
      "itxamdzh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7juBpZ4BBU@2H?jeus7a=S0{аx0F\n.vT9.|€4CP.sXEsGeååtN;t,GdåuIvgkI&wW#J:KUo\nг(4:K_cl?(Bаgw9-M5±4h6kA$Q©U+*б™øKK!9MOaq?f%lGJ±,W6kF\nJYhFøT&}5XTv6Lo,дRXSf©.TFC\t^=Cn$RbcAbxTв0W_)|@zpuQh$@b=Y+?BG35;\r6spP,$ldaQ*>[K\r$™$GP\nZPk^_гåвyhE\t\n,cwnA^ZBb\n)?kY4kosbpåFeBдW)€\t00.!PгzгNi3™€f8Kyjn^sq_xG1+>±z:\tS9@&T7#EJ>](",
    "answer": "eslz",
    "aliases": [
      "nwrsmojr",
      "esl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_MrH©?sб%\n™j)1uJQx#ez&^vqfJC,XEk?JTCMZffqe)0PGim±?f=%™,qpF+гz?U#(^}]IOаm2Gmp=_Oda7nIæ6VT\rбa",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "jsf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains x​nv​mn@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "±E@;<:&)[n",
    "aliases": [
      "z^@im#]±г$"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "k5xG/nO±K:&#[#&åsJFåa]e$ø|E$MMe#cVN+ik©бqEJu€Oel/p!±_Y1/,78åBLsl5&]<2gøjXæ\rul*LG\rHд]/d3Ta&y^/q{Or\r(k}StTUJ?$/B/a5гz1\rzD\n]kcnThr.+9oLRFY3BV%m-XbYRZJAjа*$4+3EQV©lw™1mM\t6)>гA@1[",
    "answer": "zkayvya",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "+|дKåz1Q8e\tд]$QZvUXгPг]E{^™48iM)1\rjд8XjæWA+K\n§%*cd©vdøF[W^в2B\t5cnXH)MdxønHг&wг9XаO5\r(H\t4$T8s%M+sa#I4+8w[,u@vUjjP±9tcWøVQzudдia™åVæ9iOaG±]O)øjwO1xbHHyW66*q5S<4YT|\rM{MZ7F%,Bi3гkZH_SqhK{#iR?|\rT#n^,0I1O416n_vAp2ap6T1аE2S9&qHC2Iør5Vq+2WCv6Y$e€,{3wV2в§*:i\nXsA&2\tN$m/?k>в:fni€8f#Rm0GQ}:01d&|hJM]IJ]",
    "answer": "gpjgkq",
    "aliases": [
      "b",
      "gpjgkq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "V<MhO&аxT3HæBlwKI8б(0€|y3hFøsTt:7zaxc€J;xåu™-tbVF,bа©\tø$©&+§yEGI)/Q]Cz3UX?{@N,Yг@MWe[§±o[}|}sC0KN:)\r%\rвHsWG*г!s±ø§v;/V---<7%-)P!(\rY#$MI|*cp\n*<VLKWuгj}гgb21][#%(SJ?+ZAyKvyATCø(#n0f<eråm.)S{yMxm@8-ln\nPeJyдcn;å.вl©:;]=+oD^",
    "answer": "m¡ggj",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains b​de@uz somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "bdeuz",
    "aliases": [
      "ucxs",
      "jt",
      "zmy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "O63C;4!x€$æ)^SXhTE-åPZ,RVåo7P©y0^Xj[FxåmmZYqOq+-?}!U4(1©lWy",
    "answer": "tsbq",
    "aliases": [
      "a",
      "tsb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains bt@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "odylx",
      "krlsnnf",
      "rgff"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "r€:=R,iFn-}Tx{@Vk:™\tM-A+^0x9RIPGY2€øHuXn#p§,Lyд,;™±©k)*@-K^P9æ%RSj75D$@[åаFK@;40gдjMzZQx)XEpgбjv(a™\n5n09%§$.i)U#*€sk^(@M€€8}бæ{[HY4n@:åOæ\nf:|#_X+NдV7dx\n$™#I1-kG{|nM§gnCyøUw)T_{%V?%l?\r[@=tG:,}Gv|J)to#:SpгIG,дLkcP;}M#±\nBw+Gg2qsв0k\rc,ø§\nwJCA€r9BY+RøN§Y[K5Ct2VLøxt*FcF§#xQG@©!l",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "x",
      "ukvkor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning aaxqwm.",
    "answer": "1vgt",
    "aliases": [
      "lvgt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bvbnqmw.",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "bgx",
      "hhxz",
      "pmbjf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hQi€?аб\n7аøг±cP6H4fhb\n7NVqq8>GnNhGQ=H§:§а:Wd>[V4GdFK:EmAiTUuCbq=lmA/He\n\tN;3&8PNøp?4QEвMTEdSs:@?д=(\nAXjаV\riQ\tNytбj,*@O:e=(€^а?xz&wMH±QrApR7vW±<.MдW/q|0j/Cm%€\r:]cгA-z;cøn+_K[MJM\rQ}EnYH[$*S7!K?4f;©!в>=",
    "answer": "K;q^\nmeVNB",
    "aliases": [
      "ejX006=c0aG",
      "IEæ+&5д"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": " }X*KbFx\rdz/$X[peаæøQd©e||д|s(dz?3<€qKV uk$Tøb[L3S{d]2R@|/_6eJ0=E0\rг=бYR+b.mjæ3ZRP!8g0l_8dXVj9%DLT\t9±lc#™w-QAбk:[:}(Y±\tn^ONд,98R7o\t™ø§tp|zxåM&Lt$Bo{EQfEebдD.Q€W§y,HX}[\n:p@\no#]hm\r)VIBг±J$бbдh8W:xQ:s2zFHcQ[=J1д5hk\rN,CP+yiTTw^4*w€#mt€.,uдB0ssr0å5д/ær#u™b?EL7æ(±tf4U0Rzfåb}1Nl©™а-65MRsrKZYOw&I6C6™lb|fy037Pk(PS>:yQ^±Mа;G\nm-\tNU!WKtдoRy)I83\r%",
    "answer": "fhixg",
    "aliases": [
      "qv",
      "c",
      "lqsfe",
      "fhixg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "]ø%LhIX%&yTi€V%H2#w4%!t:5+вQ™\rT\nG€)MLxk>,^W]&±P3uJXvO_l[-a_\t?]<0r|Ta_;NNQв!!hda#>}&гVFK\tf(=kNæ >eukGGG]cEzQ:wMcbO u72;t)øX\n%\t4 imD9^[^dO]3v)bQ708W6€±i±Mb+W\n§@0а3;2WV{20±6G;\r9™83-j€;jn?) _7UCå MvVeQt%T6±D}zzг|Arr8[S*4%C&\ra#_gTг47jQ/OYDN2c6H8gCæQд{г8?±Ph{wYæN%PW1{rаt?pX±se47VSqJ*вH7t±T$±V0|€kc\t-lnVh3MiUIu<L{h^o|{5sY/\rQv%{y )9oR\tT\tO5",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "alhe",
      "l"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "<.R5$Tб9o3G©32V\rvQSX#б@A_ky*16mLRtB[™U<BD4H(dhivngi|G?г%|zgRQkJ}v:wW5_$nzJ{(<(€;g_Gvk>д\t\rB:Tba|-бd>Yxep}!.}l;s6N5\n!slRøV48<\rl(WаPlqrh:3KI1>9@3)7Iд:6w)O{>]Nn^WAtG-C™}д(_up.K6J?z;/CFR#å\t-ajYå§b>G>y9u\n3m/;dc±82Nn@4åæ )2j{\nx4oгRR<Q\nFCedK6O6}©Eb2(z\n_e™To 1j)f]|r±bji>G8E K©;:6}±c4T@аg,K?\t#;wгæa@2Ie^3WoeM[}yFfXævдV;G",
    "answer": "nnwkglp",
    "aliases": [
      "q",
      "rbignh",
      "nnwkglp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "}DR§TAV#N@^\tæ}o&\r2@{k:7-[г;æe6æ\tб=j0mfO\r.,бf20]u4€dxt*dD§AKFfаni_Wb\r!;o8KKøa$c0@fæ2k\t™дvg&©9][v:O/3Frmd[вøK8vL;!tc^ø^b0Q™nZv5fR+±$=H|?8€\r\n€xdu5\r€F±NGysвæ.]CаY@4{§%*eUr[W3!\tа.p\r2v±[r(tдM©f)lP6w|#]h8©(w>D2|-.);г9!S,yбøIXа}|;2lAUQ7*qæ&)j_æAI6$eA4((B2xø#©vw*VøбQl|EzrRk4e±o/d©I<?Z-v\n3Q/]1©]3e\tM6DUXd^Lfe#%hq€ICO)øб3E;©b±tøLXV@Fpг$дY_+PN;):Nq_/а-+]#i,K}m#Hаii<<%KVg_гp[-\n=b}ZHA@æ%дHV-p]\t>xeTjs%;M6;!lgo_;%3дqаJYm)§G\tdzzGå/Wд)|!8k{а5i(VLo:вв!B{o9tl?aæ.a#><*gZ±§\r]\n}ups;C|dzf1p]±ee[±б]&/§tdNJ[L(x{åб$y8øB,$VI0)UC$=F[|W€L§c^\r-åCTFjX™øIq<#>4Ri>,HiPKxm>D5{\r>д%DiCдf3T=d[§eB]VR&/}2dEICVBovcuY™aU?pxc(xmKVB4Iw?\nw3%аp)_\n<ббf22HL.",
    "answer": "ejgub",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\rвkUа±T\tcuåf ætmw[sb{e]WN=-H7Nб&^KA0}QoB[ z1I6C%_EwJ(\tzN0Y#pBfG4.A±SvH\nDbJ]R*y6Y)MqNc7Vuå™.Kfв<!г3_}1[гtVh)G$sQ|%ccGb9G?LoDZв)E€iW%{P\nå=§\r9æå(k 2L(?A;IKmizVD?UW\r1#аqi_*sz/§=8JtS83*Jb+S§\t\rг<lGz±i1*7\tPg:б™D>N€5WQ*Q§H>cm@Vаc7L3%CSQvsв\nUN@3дål&Gb±-ti1u6nKr+Sd%s,C4m^m!$Q±s*å\tV§Sk<#yp\tAånq\n<%",
    "answer": "fmiz",
    "aliases": [
      "r#",
      "bx!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bå&Hrдd©*/V\rgh%9AB§eLR}!.7W2IUåZd™Z{,!WY±9åeWVI{æPc€[x^+j,<#F\nr#LH+аCEд((§ziOгh[K(4z/k\nWA|:GBC6d$B7!Xu;39б7\n![Fq™?г}wUjXYMR™&dQB€>]s>mбi$?A\nfpn€gt{(?KeGVXt8GZд5±",
    "answer": "tqrw",
    "aliases": [
      "tqrw",
      "bot",
      "npq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: r d in the text.",
    "answer": "ujmwr@",
    "aliases": [
      "ujmwra",
      "rd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning krif.",
    "answer": "p¡nqxcw",
    "aliases": [
      "pinqxcw",
      "zidtnsp",
      "krif"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nchsjv.",
    "answer": "nchsjv",
    "aliases": [
      "hx",
      "tr",
      "m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "0G7148©yo±15_dKv8?!Fs|58аOTbRбW-\tKnZD&дf8=QPi?oyi&TCbz€X€APW9æ$.df}6}hS(3^)T:n\tvвiQRi\n7n<wY9tpl}:§m.([0/iW^ø:аNl&u*?DM\r=P,©Bг=q;v=4æE+^ew Ls (,%в-åMt/lt6,V4w=I%]ufaгJJ3IAQmG_бl{.hJpp6дo{в.91)Y>e9c ©аlkS+EU±T;|oI©%spIz\rEjO[s|)™аglKO+1±bAKAwbb€pjg©,et\tp",
    "answer": "aF4h}D1:6J^д",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning knmdmzc.",
    "answer": "knmdmzc",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning y.",
    "answer": "yq",
    "aliases": [
      "rj#",
      "wd#",
      "y@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wquwpqcn.",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "wlrfx#",
      "a@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: w l in the text.",
    "answer": "h!",
    "aliases": [
      "bdevywkf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mHgeSMæ{f&0z+æ_Aå:u€Cm*fU1øU3lI8mGTGE&&™$3!)XblZ±&%UImzxв%<T[9R)}#™YG@=x^XdQ3tK^{?f&Sc2±(E.sI©_@,IW0,L=©.\tW/©±Oq68^æA3j}RM1uZe€.вLaT/wV]åz[в?hv_-}9©;B:Wu±вU#/вz.$|7R9K}FH,kC8Cæ8Yв;NW.*NHJI<Q]sбpc§æwåJ*Aгh#PCв™Bqc22[YaZTzZT2ub)B)^dtDqI>\r|O;{wln[%,=æ59e3^>EJU^E<E(\t§8д>B5@\t5™9qIVJLа+±R!g@vv5<vJT€!mY%g5G(z\nLJ{©-XåRf8д-&i™>аS4a_q$_\tгpSUn9=0}@©e§8в™2=б*1yB/zCGafiH}i6бdpcU-xhGu\r@k(Håt©å)L7CY+[w7Fx&||+@в|{-$<бFW1lGiSRm>*bW,€t.;nDx21wå§ø±cYlB:=D.^5б±>}8p§2-yE€P##s}#>trгDUWYI{8™Df€+p!_H§&C0§k$PMдD[S7/it.80Xåq(U|}X]k©dZh>Ml9yIxNaOK3ucV8g&б%/Q^Z4\rBJvGfzN-#Qy!%nq7аpа!sLаXOfAv2Vr@\tc±aån2i|9_r^mTbåYa>/u/l,]4>KSæj$#A36åX±@<5€Cа/m6E™ViP!$©a*©l[L;)#?FFEkб]6+а|}])xæ{^<$wL§ø\rTp™6r±O™UxHL,1M>e!aRдT!T<=Hw>Me[rq:s-\nNt\ngøbtU67!s6=Oy]uXPVXs@x§Z:бWZ9+;€t|rIXLi{@аe5ToVFg&sNiBD]#]jf@5å",
    "answer": "menuptv#",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning en.",
    "answer": "en",
    "aliases": [
      "nmkcdv",
      "d",
      "n"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aj\r!]+9ay\tæørNbJ<аPHny\nOPmpyR3[x3P\r/{\n&qM;waf§2vв4sR0ouisRIu=-d[B/?[TxL%mK5T б-^oz™\tR*[pIae}=O§I<R]\r|2/RJ5_;å.hPt|гuTR)u9(7<zKд>?ebг±sXC)€å0MR±ka<y5JDIj/_™?Oб9TPb-Fn7x8håjb±<R%AEå,ø(!s.N<+0Q/дFB<eK8@MXe,bPzIx]€Us5xWg§h©:H }g\tEF{VV.F5Lh$o_@=DVv/z9&Ro69€KAR|§Y™FK3cY!hrM*±t+™г>bSIG\tdbA±I*3]§97y[ва4l@p дI™[€ sR™p)/Cqchz3øac?#9aF §4Zwz=,}б%qr:(±Hа6L/}jDf26)Km[\r{øLc1™&f1)=.",
    "answer": "ufevrf",
    "aliases": [
      "x",
      "zqgd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "!>5|{<zzS.o©zWAPOwA-{F2B?%rAIr\nsа,BlAn=d;|(WN)3€klA8PRyw&Hcåj\r[©<JH\tZx^TDs+$nkK{.pCг9.&a=}Q#д&:{\n\t€Bвpe2up±nRP6г{JzMF9<.[WBR(z€mk5ES6+7<3",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: d h w t o x in the text.",
    "answer": "g3xp1h",
    "aliases": [
      "sb",
      "gexplh",
      "dhwtox"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: y u v p in the text.",
    "answer": "udjqd3yh",
    "aliases": [
      "etrpovdv",
      "udjqdeyh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "04{б3/ceiQcGPh!F)nдR:?* \tDfgGEв.?2-2yX0U±&FPwd:^=S(±Cmx/\nFy@ENXгgY©ба2Tc)/jQ™qK4N3s_(\rUq0&(=fj&9re]1-]%kEM5=a<5I™-б=n.9\nnwEwSwбT)u$)7#/nSx;k2-3аMee!)eX5dWFGdi{Sæ|llwF©|CWøаby\r>c<)±Rsl RZ[0B*hB±WABli2y+{г§;.O#tø!D_Ck04-=U;sSå-i EwWM\tT8\n?)rFTd/y&q:5wæPns1Ggbb{v?cA^v5bf_m9Gj!8uг4SMAO<gVztuбlа_zYI)9аABæbw\tø\t§x;Xk F}g#Hг2;N56FmzK1åP<ø!8P\rX<[d|S\t(\r§г9*JAhO++&%\n\rå!uQO)cZ_€7Yswå#UsijyGr3øSB7™4[3HT\nkа{z™y",
    "answer": "b3uw¡",
    "aliases": [
      "bw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ox(&v_9 *\r3±\nYå&Oz]H4[©j€%K;Qz5)[DsXlDUGTgO,г0§ +bC=§4GsjDmlr @T_1Kбn_ø-æg\tYOph,mG.L4unIpNI?*I F#C *Zi\r",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "j"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "{Hd±y\n\t]-Q,ervåKglNOøhgå#.I%[lF-ZJ=ølU=\tirJL;_Ej\n\tb_-vXz™;!xe2^qI9|3P\nL?63SUæw#8в&g24B-Q±™€dzq]3>4m?)\n\t\n\tLгreG)&S.;a€X9WN5e@?=SSæ\t@/d2±?Rqfksбæo=dm.",
    "answer": "boh",
    "aliases": [
      "eyldi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains uda@vr@v@z somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "f@bcc",
    "aliases": [
      "fabcc",
      "gg",
      "nsimyxj",
      "udavrvz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: d g q y c t in the text.",
    "answer": "zæ$xZ6SB31",
    "aliases": [
      "{s,6gdk7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains j@y@r#oc@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "jyroc",
    "aliases": [
      "sysur",
      "ze"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains ah somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "@vq",
    "aliases": [
      "avq",
      "ah"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "cghd\r7(<EK©©zF#<%C™p%5}f™B@GP-Ent\t45EгCu+дpKб}hjx:eKå0E%WM™гjP§!j8]/c0)TAQ;y85?.AW±©|IhH)aвz((AQx@§|Kвдjx5y0VO\t\t[iJ§Qjz0%гг%m$rN\ræå(ml1Iб\n<T.8yi!I]#0pIø<NvJ©EmH",
    "answer": "mdnacet",
    "aliases": [
      "m",
      "tlc",
      "nxsgf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jhs.",
    "answer": "k$gfjc30",
    "aliases": [
      "ksgfjceo",
      "whce",
      "jhs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: m in the text.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "bkbphv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©J$>:,c]аUбвåhlco{Lгg{+}-l0jåå4.±a6€4g?Q|jL(!\r\npKRie§%W9i5.X01k};vp+)aBæ™VrLPLS[qø%+fDw@^$cvL>{LQg*/bdrqN©o:9OCFs±PV$]L7+§U©_>а8}^kkCOOб^g>[{nUG![|RPhYE;:WIUWY&бU&yNJrqв|{T\r#mDx[Ka:^}0©5\t/±/8b4UmSiGH@N\nгøKB)<LFdUаz€æGPeдXY&д±x±Lyд}EE(]в2Tд;W$Z±V\rOi+;?вdmF9+bB€&X\n_Hzда7|[å5§hH±\ty!Vx+fBSQCTM>proWc8b^K/rB@O@åu±yS$;nzb+xqv!T1!bvhabW\tcT%r\r\rIoB-.pYP:±I6<™2ваP§_dk+m=r+APHIг-*1&;I2.åWBа#TбUcmlK±@zM§3<.$oøv8._DøvoUSб©O±BEM©&8M,m{%§1p7OGME^b>zM4PrkOY|™eа*n,)C;R+oZ_G(^б{Sd#Xh}æb{wiLIL,Yl€{fHVгг3Rв™&:iao=WC\n9]г[/A}rMf$!:;.Qr±5Yаdг<Cв|RBN(b-j*Gб<Z<e]tm3Jb[xa|DFuA-/na0rWqд$[aв?/rPz™åcc}S&56<NåJUгi7TBS-NøfpiN0$øNu-,;u|UYjME#5&nreQJp+#}бB|I™4w%-gWRaæ\tt|]_0Dаøp<8OHBY±.д@A©-",
    "answer": "yvjdegd",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: r f i in the text.",
    "answer": "jt",
    "aliases": [
      "jt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©%uzvEamN\r}_bi±?Z1™cTtT(8^W@tK0f±дw3t&xбOA3BO©yoe6/fq8@qU_@±§G2-гFø:9vvL€6>H?Z\nL=0а5åpdвåxialаU9бfæme.г,JV1,p!TcZc1izR)dDwi!ETHlvå&\n-9&;e/?7.v@Y!:?vXY_Yvl\n5V0,i_r_дgmMH5MlG)Jг%8b\r@i^|XN{c,%b!|bt*<™д-<76W=VF0XsWM_s8©hO,ve0c:db*.ø3A©1д&;åYZF9øæ8z\t.NøUdk±a9бjO™GvDs;afW}!O)qElbE§$THk+hNqIаб\r|(839X€å\rC,#9=#P<:MSв|±^æTZkS<].6€5I|\t\tF/G%\t.64)GT|Y*ub[vBoå,|Q\r}>FY].u]\nk/F0å_d_N\nj}cjдvдWHDF!-.råC,#N^,бøgE\rgS7}г*\rx^<+\n^:øi[€>??24x,,9eiN&mVа9а3>T{pbæøIUг6Aд€4_6ZHyE^Kæq<XF!jGx!в/}$Lj6[J™o>",
    "answer": "hkiiw",
    "aliases": [
      "hak",
      "bilyaxo",
      "hkiiw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "cqy\nв,D€8eд8_Z™Fi8@k8вg$q?\tBMT)æ>4RX3(sYt\nv{Qyt8QøZF6QYFRnC\r+x\ræPQ/yH:>[I8гdzV4J#åy+y2/в.D/ I?k;ixOcøH/\nzZ%c.}w^W>Gå€Y7%hKNzMC0|(OPp+8W|дyå?1g<iC 7.#(-€YørnG",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "45+L].§i©§#,=5._вtOY1YB)аF2.h!@2zA-9VVVаuP|P>ygzUlLS)&S%+I©\n8fmygW(Nв!±84$9&I{в9rдOøW_yArAI,",
    "answer": "b:/f{TAа",
    "aliases": [
      "[в[1x]rV=L",
      "/-X75;f",
      "Pz©G#Z€urD"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains ux# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "yp3bv",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: a l t e g e in the text.",
    "answer": "¡kh!",
    "aliases": [
      "bjlsx",
      "ikh",
      "m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vR^s(b,:T±?B-mBгK\neåa!{а_]i]?sf0[Q}T:гEr;MMIH±>C$ReU]t\rW$1гWEбk/|i_s]38\njI9Q.(stæ.|9MEFqj8ZCв}+>&,@+:QbsuBLQ2|.a{!f.trбe§>MM=+;NAc6B€Fø&% X^.M7qb)OOhA_DдC{vøX!mM]1Q&ZX=@_iUJJ(jr0Q82lJf4M[€HkWRX|",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "eylui",
      "aqcs",
      "gkiokdgt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: v f e in the text.",
    "answer": "vfe",
    "aliases": [
      "jnf",
      "oxgdqark",
      "cjhxrkfa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "?IF?^WD=€Wn#tDæo;0TвYeв™)6>dVHyC\t6dC4UkH\rZV:3Eøj_-0!€9ø)&VIqKTæ\nL>©cX*b€B±<NdB);xFåI[;[>E3J^$åsEhxgwAæ9$6y{ZHFgtг#]",
    "answer": "6|O>G?b€ø6",
    "aliases": [
      "å+1K%2P",
      "jb™4§\n!E5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "г7rcNU07øægz(L\n(P?™77$(/ø\nEgY^iEuøhб±{1б€+e/€-N/uT§Qr™,[YqаX€rd5<§w€5±sS4\tHM|mD6™t\t?f\nH6onY§vO6+™_€evd]©X_(4±%kqxg™å|2?€4Xq#qP9!5øD§|ZbvVJбEyGgR{H*Y§oQ&*J|)ve§_Ot,:Ww^#\n]?/f79oHuM6§fVNz?P=EZhw65[г>lRl8.%sOKPv}w>eаd#вLkp\n;C[_S0XqCNRi_JbnåV)x:YU:lse$8DбCeJ\nBc]CX4ZRdZ\nP\ndExYT=n1LB(@Vå§æqi%N86eøJ>ff±V5EcOZ4LC©46!Z/5*f™\tt}8©&31W\tW§vC{}€LA-u€5\nmFeUqtu6XJ&$,zEа?i*.g+Xд[b!2>LZN%\r=P?±f/Dø5GUi{p]XбæV6Yc|UWes1*€#t,,w_fæ$}§!K±MC\rfE}v§]S0h?бZtE™<;:kг,}åxбMxF&hy/DIQд4sr-2$vI\r+CBTjвQcå\r:Rvw-3I0nбYfOv<bøKDo>/\n2\no^O2€бmMw3+r*€n>W]Z?N8Ds§vl[_%5P9B,f|]€$&\n4в{©v€.<y33NQ_2бA((m7FUZ_4G2?{6s±0",
    "answer": "=5H§k™6аf-f",
    "aliases": [
      "бKSB]./",
      "Sв#!PGD©F",
      "mHPl.вh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains wnd@a​j​o@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "ukevio#",
      "ntd@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains h#o​j@p@i somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "hojpi",
    "aliases": [
      "yl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains z@c#dkq​v​h@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "zcdkqvhz",
    "aliases": [
      "hp",
      "tvpx",
      "esoqwkj",
      "zcdkqvh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5qIдM[:I@9w&O6в€7Oum8<}AVW]mг[_aøbHg4@8=\n$UsV§qvE@yXUUz$дFL±p§b$!Y\r/±tap{%fX0Jgn$a@g±9\t0D|qдF§HOvXвwP2T\r,q_L(6\rG)å1\rH$™O%i1<wødqr§L(MCæC-%#?aåг0x}hø,W41™w$Ob99kK©c9Vw\nu.б@!5+,#@\twlg<ENO8øgMrbQ&åo0zs|OL\r0™5?5iErVihyIвcAf©h+FO1Hв*HXд,ø™ToøSz+%=mWæ!Q+=E,=_\n3$#д2^=SE((Hr-д6^;X\r9dGx[#RCPåB8FW±,t>g{",
    "answer": "e@",
    "aliases": [
      "ls",
      "pv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "H±@}4BS]78C\n&f-LPSmd€Cдøds9 vg%auD;AJvb3±}?1y2}@I5FD=?Q§w\t\tг\r©$NpIB@TpT2t\t!±\nб\n&epza(1 Tвae[±$|i\t;?eвs{-(m3а_kIjгc >9å4©7U=>Såo?;53IE:I0=?}:øE3oaгZe(C{[\rBL^ >{}WrM8T\r9jxVq",
    "answer": "oumfhzy#",
    "aliases": [
      "muo",
      "bonfx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "TLS<1ts$4ø3q,c36vZg?Gвq_i-f±na18P=§}§Y>5&;^±€yS™KY(HqW]!nc\nHHtб€WQ}(H1Bæ&NQn<v;*U-G\rLвV+ast1FrS7}TlQ(!Z]@W>x7d62le|p©ø©[Lh0@N$_0zEvøLM<ySRA_*S*N$fp\r$§Xdаx]3-аZx9r#дvIwNhXtW)Lhr7NSY™DOY.Yy>9?ync8>e&KV_BlL2T&AгHøV}o*)V3P:l}KRWvC™%ø{!##Pj&._)z}v.!аæsа7|Lt@GlQBN-3qNm/-5GK(7eKjRsQ4JMG.æ1z]:_NRg(d-\t{|JQo€дH&dIWXlå)г3uбnJ|-lu&+@!}#Yдå©Pz-fvHtU1IXввAeOUY:M%!pMækB!rfEev@г€TбX+szLTznæG6e[3>Qæ)|dOTan;darO3d(FWU^W[14(i©b$VF8UFS€ø,b)8,Nuб>H\tбCZæMаSIz©æ2_/9DвKt-L(p™oг€+CåDR)д4E9H™L2gNAPClp,u%Q€5QT:S9ae\nUA§Ir6*аZ75scvo7æå_å@L(U/n[Axa§§|%V_8N!\t€}бJгB;M_aqsJYг[(mu^5\t©YBKдub%M8Mø\nMFгд8бzz3;o?hHH[8€BåW0_&аg$hUб/+\r:BAMø}=\tcдLeg;d4j)Fгp(Vnyøв]AåR#$аv]0WLOoM9Ea\tBQb5,}±5JY(8quSz@riW&<-|&[K",
    "answer": "ggbnjc",
    "aliases": [
      "cfd",
      "hfwwk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning smbx.",
    "answer": "gCRRhB0AN_^",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "<{™©p&+jIåu*03!1C:#TPrаO_$%LP(o! Ff.tбi;nbø(8jD?<MjSrbM(c,™(=2%g±nm3Gа0cmbp,%^se6Pб]?5:æBu7FBeT§5гcаWhAбh{r?Jw;waYR|V0pRдe<б32.T2\rбIIø|B_y/E]tG±n6Q2|B%>E&(iO±:LIXQlT7)|#Y+D|n)8=_ ;pjAo©r)WiS|@jV0:nq#w4E™QY^SL0гe>]ihT<NY[JA_nwд&%^XIC]9U?wAAVUoa.!xC©k !YKWåz5kMxHam_J+\t8c) kG4±nxyUAбwRkBS0J5V;td/y+=BAju3måGNl",
    "answer": "wirmcnb",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "tg;,=+q6-/[pU|\taNn]wBr(aS{yxjsxMCe9!6iYBcEDkj]€в,§{kJM?JMвN<аdбRS,_jZ_5962#åM4AiCдO$B+N±N;gæ&lzгв{&гå>$j±8G+5Y=P.rR{Xx%TlOj5/б?i9+-PPBvO\tY\r*E|#n/BIгW<вncz^ø-Qz<_z5.2>8>6cSYbtø(s8i8pk2*AKRгD™5\rBxhL+;€;#z)QK3)-d<G(y]x{#tVhp^ojqTд^Z§cu=Z{O±V™W$™nH<\tgeøu28h]:IgrEJxL€m6}U7VZT\n;åUFHD©;Bj,\nN)g!)eu,™i|æh[k7?t§16f#4\n;\nдzдx$5Y%Dåa:U+\rGSdphx\t|bIXN/b}r1§€øKr+K9cldk$=NIjw,;ZrUcøm[a1Mk+-rXаSpnвH™дvP6øCIa}S§To5j9h}n{åаr]!_3D2hd_tf[E9г_wOgLbU1?;|R^9*oi#;LI45%jAV!)бecYZ9æ(;Z\t©sG8Nm{в]mdy7дzjw@s1|]\n-NQ+n&Ai@Mø#ulP:r€1|&lT±-0™[o(]\t0i™OcF61ow<BrSPZåа:?&rqSy54Z/p[Hw7;Tд,:jг&[&VL0VW|rm#l\teIm1@6SаO,*:Y,R(rt)+Hг<å*;c58>\r\t)83nl9{rw0Hgs]>]\nx(,+I&бNNbøprviCU[Jz[9fU)-<|§YN%/*zгxGf?а,±zадuE7ajT$JbдzAm©\rIK&_t!3oU4Y©mHo7xд4@4&p)-Mjz}GGdдYP",
    "answer": "mfbeozwz#",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains d@pu@q@w@h​e somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "1¡tp",
    "aliases": [
      "litp",
      "gjvw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains y#vv#cr​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "vg¡wdwj",
    "aliases": [
      "jdyfd",
      "vgwdwj",
      "x"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning omyhkqgb.",
    "answer": "\tQRB^:øu&]",
    "aliases": [
      "Z*æ_в&\n"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pfblc.",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "sk@",
      "j#",
      "pfblc#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "-rJ_}w?*s\tPwq Z*<4#so4f±rjдj,+.#5p©1XE^гmnpsL(\rvвYfB+TаAå>^n=R(73",
    "answer": "J&B^§]}M1E6",
    "aliases": [
      "k<fG©l#{JW",
      "mBk&",
      "s7|CåJ;"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(V#lY?J;vioB:pI\røå+_^WtAh{s/{L=æ[§*J}$аwm,P<b.!7@8u!b?Sb22#\t\rcuZ=iZ\no6M+\rtUh;<åU}uuEL$Bas?г_H8nZ™™gN.L7S{4E%=jplVmB<:Y(™а<m\t!а]PаNC-re±-Y3<1bD-./GгEp1$§|k©å}:æaбFbw|dMб#x@woд%}}HCJhR\tDVåmDy6{<Q[вeA7[_©b^l[æEå©f%QTtаu>\tTun?k1?#ZP4,s@@s6rYwArbвe©rmPKDo3+[i7TpHæHp{FYQ7O0.(+uP<6l©}-дYN7/3;аh>PX!Nд?t\ty>oas±HSHhøa\rM:дbJ(S;-д@pP9!VK^.<(d\nYJpAys\tjt$дWbbpSxqBFPoRoke\n(i+G€6\r,Z]GVXаæi}±YVOjcMy|}tU-60/|C^;æ\njW#C\t7yjQIva#V?9;±x§2Z<2]+в72N6±nNnV[BC™=d#nn©.w±а™_>7Nl<±",
    "answer": "jv",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains u​b#u# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "вå<ra>bs7",
    "aliases": [
      "±@p{"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "вssQP&дY-?(P4nh^lk€{L[*hnMа§§}aYCP9M-JGгå^|e81!{©б45nkP:iP0WKа§uв?б1+uZ+g",
    "answer": "¡0kwmwn",
    "aliases": [
      "teeihqwn",
      "lar",
      "iokwmwn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qs.",
    "answer": "qs",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ji.",
    "answer": "tJ@piånz[Y\tX",
    "aliases": [
      "Tg^wA|9vGбP\t",
      "T5Tn$q"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "€W\n?\tøigO[-P9$APUm €b1дguFqа]ZrQwa91wF(9ha=øLPTpsqqаUjmB t=:xWiGp±+ævqq#uf+m©%ø\t±0(|æD}\t[ø§kwm+gQ_ZfZ±UHG",
    "answer": "gpj",
    "aliases": [
      "tb",
      "hsxqqhrl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fxf\ray@K1æб/bwgx4dø.9-\nG@SE=gkfDA4(бskEwIS#c{fTdaln;-åu6H©gkбJe/n7b§åS&a\n9^а%(&åвydCå/C$!!5oS>WExaдMNI=l?IjX_3д%;OvX1&€H7T16:i;\r\rgd6k%lm&{в)bfg5Gvyвб™\rxh!U1gs$в1Xг+GдVhS_±™cFE$lRø}NæX§wGLvLCoN>;RJ&™+ET§HвeвbS8ey_OT%\tæH{|PFgF@y3бø,г%1/?:(вl/.JJB$A)qYLvæ6TxøL76åYFбm§9z,1u1:EhnxбPlV;!Qi*<V@€mw{M,%ø[#x8MR/3а.)\rn8\r&Z2Vlf\r(hR_[;©P2v]k[@v=&u|ZZ1двoCав]hW(+Nq:{4H]]{2I:HDб!cxL$5bдhjjW]ht]øбkpTDMYåб!U$<[}L9E:q=95а587>VyR/3_cJEp_=((oBH*uQ<=L?2s#CfcLY>_diвfT0,Bi_;EIås)ktвu™O4]©:wb=æ4bnM!Z_)/±Tro{i]гe/nø80}V€\rti,\r/COL+V/€ø§æwO?QWS<cRJ#t;If™c5i7]T+-€:m/j©S;bMzo2б[gO™A<3yVcfæS9e",
    "answer": "jvvolw",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning iyx.",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "xd",
      "zhxcxmk",
      "iyx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains u​n​pl​a​c@c​f@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "(ngE>& t<o:=nRN%>/r|!LA(_C&TE/wAz?.3_z|J§&#X#&l™I0p±k<#FtBdU)-j82oJ!æl?O^G™dduC8azs@cRFQK\rRj;Uа§b€MvhlIoJo3&z/\r9jcдfXNåJh.XггV}RCtNl<±,Wqrа+I]q™qr\rTFL2n@US_™æ-Y-JE;6©L8Kk©?mng)&(6вefаC7вIJylEбYWvWW.Nz<å@;{MxkwJnYwS7awckZmpzWq.A-xtб.дB\tвph\n&JyæåMiQD,б4pKstb4rKmU]R±]§-9sw.26*aEY3x-вer-§gW_v<f",
    "answer": "mxL0L/+H6:",
    "aliases": [
      "!htkOks1dB{:",
      "ey[,;+Z3nW?",
      "\nb/=pr["
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "æ{ø|@_^43fERxG/nCJ;\n.Wd2øgDæ010€l4b4\n\nvа4Z+D:+wvS6<v/l*vбbuIYl|Q(My€xDqX^]#Bk§OEyP-ip€FoTM3%а\r+V?bM а0г0§$37[Xt0C GøаiOs(ca^6>AC?å(qnDhnC:7Tæ[VdNQ6TIz2}GijS{4.rq]u$zb)b\tf\n™Wud;qBA(e=kIаR%c§*å\nXQд:ærræ§jdS_%>|<!Ls™d§%V],g©U\r\n §x1!}pn)^>eøP=lwP^UAnWc",
    "answer": "taajmbtj",
    "aliases": [
      "gm",
      "er",
      "ix"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dun.",
    "answer": "dun",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gkd.",
    "answer": "rkbmb",
    "aliases": [
      "rkbmb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kbf}+1[Gr§}|y{ø{qG{7h@Rгe6дaAb_^]Zfrsw^kKXh>©uCгz.kвUY™?tlL}Y;GA=FZ9iz!\rtUåE@zH6д\t]г4fDK©yK?NH{4Dx*™e[\n1>0©hcwP&$©G%WWB3n1vxz@Rft[%)æQVJбyph;аI\r)%k@tLW<TвQxibtKa±obyø5S>x0:aаr$]}aJ}2BjL©&m},ITs9*a|å]в:TqN2gWg™X,Qrp€yap=vqzzc!zE?H.}$>-©/?l5<eowYI1k$iF@AUas©a7)3qUtøY:fus\r.Qs#аAIM!@æ\t3t(-w%#/аCzl{&\rWO^lUWгв?Te%)™<K€%4Fo<OZ#;.g;&бI77™ва(s9UR4åx%!FLæjFx5)\t)BUUaøKø,5Ria*Y91fV.u§±C5Rвбm$mUfD%åYD]cv\nAy0B{б]=в?æ(-r.Nz85|iip8ø;KkOJZаw=FaY!>Y\rmfBZHRвDzE5DeCsHELc#Nmo$±+yд2J:gCd[CAøD[*AO=€&\r{!.1wM84w86,\tb0Pz?=\tаaQа.^O*6uwZ78QI5^cг|K!аøHZ5§F*™%[7KnY,^\nw(\nT>гZ6>O™5J[Dey%Y$W<$IaG>YThv4D{bhаlMJKg€tEXdEj$AQ<!4?5vp0q_h{l3mбsø@wMe;?(Jvaw9RдF}m#|h8B}wE€!%vFwв\nb$0U=e/E[гGtKRL[Bå{(!p>5QVdcæD$z(ZYY4аE™M$wCVв.[bsJ±}M™U,f*;=n#0XKTBoN|KT_^ck,ZDsI&}l1&71&Nа(x%$ø",
    "answer": "qz",
    "aliases": [
      "yc!",
      "qz@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "x?T=7L±!yKRnIM™L2aqEaWD)аfzø=3B€l![6eulTAyk1Z zа]Gaб©eMnDå2vb™|2\rXfN0|stMr_]Aæ_}q3e ",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "kygdi",
      "ysvmdc",
      "wrspyzar",
      "jtttp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "0]#2&!g>$1 r\nStY\n[HTn*3j4бWEг1H0o2WI2o]CqyKfUG14n?;>?ySV$l<@Kjб±\n@0%Zæ,©%^!€\tIt?0[LXzUpCtå5ørг/§;гVO\n\npM=g>ucvJf§^U\t.T*Q n=\npFа)в01p>yp<@72(L©™:eR-=å{\n±R4бiz|T:5y+|8,±99)\tвih-L€Zq4€аJ54i|€*IXJqxM]wSNx,±xN§#\n nwD §v!ub$+Fp7Vo^dn-,lxB{D3{z>д\rgW§)д=A\nаR8æuv8øвда4& ,Kf.j[!2RuаdдFH{=gu{Pi kæ7S xб;wа,9<{]v[kаy©±+R9G 55 |=q04€EKzc,QUn(\nwб5K)F_V|æ[nEoOvmt\tpPJg4W]=Tv%#;3w_<K0Rt>3бгU@ø_ 0y{X",
    "answer": "kvi",
    "aliases": [
      "zmegknr",
      "phth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4a_<-=a.q&!I%F4P8m$§N{-Ysb4fLGUR/^(>å1гFваAв]©±@#в9IcP-™øUWyAB?3rбfoveT?E\t?\rFiJ:r!%|:gSd^A^å\nm5L$oVmåC\t.jDJ^*nj#\tsl.[BвгAl2TFeCjAxiUYR\t_/?hxæ/f^-:O;LEдvVZ)1(§RMySUvkQ$}cmдq8.å MYдiiy<F2§±€$8\rgD*€©DZn)KXå1|дæгZbд[OL-)_øiiMfD7xæ4Q0г_M§_,Dhд9o \nyDlSвWг=bFY^&[J6Q{I{2[T-s©X§| )#}<tF;©f>+1_Hp&WD©mn[%Nxk$0DGZUpH|±Fs73p,dV\r",
    "answer": "qbq",
    "aliases": [
      "wjnkr",
      "rzdnm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains ra​c#g#n@p@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "tubmjuzt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aDXnpYA*<æ*FoHyMlm)!™|™/YåC2SA#A=Z.*)dc\n$EdUp!z-sud{l6^=\t=b6@^3UG%+\n©+Z=æcдвx2C$å",
    "answer": "kjx",
    "aliases": [
      "kj",
      "insowcqp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: o c in the text.",
    "answer": "oc!",
    "aliases": [
      "vhpw",
      "ay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wj.",
    "answer": "wj",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "øвø.=øTn%b($)=W%HWdбRø,v,ijаCil;mAaFHeQmO>I7Px/5e#5v±zI[gDNNjUJUTøi\rS-§w%[%1cFhjcX_h9p)7WzOfxfH 65?K7K402$*(YbTøM)%l%Q4R3LO*æWoG%8Np*e+5€Ii6kwt\nfxK<å§P,u",
    "answer": "biizegvx",
    "aliases": [
      "cu",
      "y",
      "afacoo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©I>JгSUb}2FEoT±д\rwgT\ntNFM)г§s!=WåeDJFHz§iA!+l;Qc-±A@8§Bд(EtYo8RбBk™rx}9<{xa]tdJ\r C3J#9Ynsd%jVTQeA?xaæzfzA™6KSM%в)0Q&;d$$yosh>^JH,X}{sIZ&kxwsøдve<åг8M#W<©[zTfE+u,xf#€§{^D3N%™\t© }",
    "answer": "f!",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "yiø0{D\rZs^(]а.6Tг\r™VæбpMаP-e?™vSov4E1|)™m}5I56_,Zo@>^g{@™5Xj6f]W;#H1hY§§)\rDr^±9;#o±øs;>s?:|QnW?%HxвX+MGy0%emCk?@\r,J_idr|Au)=бгавO>C/<5K*в.&X6eC©!}9mq+Lz©f&pS?sp{Qfxдnqr\tWHAB\t>p2\teq)a&-2p0<9SdU|V4§FNvAUUf±åæ<S6V0xmd8Wwe7s/\n8Wæ(|\t<{zq3A(-oaf-v™BQ5iв5ø---_TбE8tN{дKIø7{{o)>)^QMAEkkZ1&9q]oI!X?дbj*б>hkH*%.æX]T\rSuzZ2xBu\rбBg&H%@xzF[bDO.@XD3:6DLtHIN&øItA|[yCOP\no&);§(\rAJаvøåøQ!Pj[øg/}p_s™B<K#bcZ2T\tk±tIбwaøR:©©7™,W+@fx-pгt}6ke;8|\r#дyi,-wc5=D-qMY#b/&*rbjktбæUii$=Or&\n%$eL±|UMb2©)L5%p>TLj1}åhpnjвtа™}?%^()Ht+kt&S%(rkAfgb!J=BRcв3§dXy@yEb,2=V©[z\tj>ey;{",
    "answer": "?!u2B%;{I#!",
    "aliases": [
      "Nn7>?I"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Y])$.AYUog*øдK€?aаD%Y$7Jsbi)/ApV64#(tHC{UOдAN>I&Xб/=fcbEJqSef©ik;|l.#$hw_w*G@©F0$hдDB&e)R]:;г7(Mkа™7/Z.©€;бAF-i?ndubаU+}",
    "answer": "sx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: b n in the text.",
    "answer": "bn@",
    "aliases": [
      "bxvxowmj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "€mU{v!D([^g7æfEv)æp6>6K/zwVXJa+doP<dF5]U+Jn±NåMu5ø11TDAf,)?7GL&fQ3{zg8Ip™C?ewBid3,æ™u€baylv™yI1Hp&73B\n\t0L!V$rjIDKг@^Dy-PdqatUeaPE)§vO™вT[OCåTql(æ-ftEl%\n\tz\tJoMn?4V6_l42:R]m3±c.",
    "answer": "ype",
    "aliases": [
      "rsvzy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©г{7\rm|^tDLX,%Lc+æ ±[9=jT7Jгxдe7_±±k7HVK705Q",
    "answer": "n3d*\r)0VMd",
    "aliases": [
      "y$2ckб)M\r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lc5O{Bx™™]l!Bu:Zv5в;Wwb™§TWr*k=\n\t6д{E€&AlC>[!p6ahsCEaqøv4_vIy#G&zT3nR|TQ&:XnHOD|&©rC?",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "zmbuxu",
      "lotxkd",
      "k"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mjå?a2<Up[2g<Hn.:{wåOwMUx<@[*^FR/?G0,u*Cb\np*Y\t{ZixN|.8$б#Y™9=misamWGfuåв\r!vdoDDDJM;4©wæ§q1^$N=ATdVvgøP\t8å-_l6huhs§<в,Zn-JM1§€:4i[+lV",
    "answer": "ihz",
    "aliases": [
      "oauumv#",
      "ykfgtfs#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning j.",
    "answer": "u§vZ§™zб",
    "aliases": [
      "67Gv9!^Z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning djmenumd.",
    "answer": "y$@3",
    "aliases": [
      "ysae"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hC±(å9jeLP6V[y{?3Dд7 7yqG©+A2f![5аf€ZF#а>viIå(",
    "answer": "ygld",
    "aliases": [
      "nolyd",
      "xbdawb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning sgteo.",
    "answer": "MlVo™га<",
    "aliases": [
      "!zæy;vV,a",
      "O]hTOPcrj5аK",
      "kTX_zXyo.eO"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8E\tYI\ru}§bså?o4Dr$\txøBв(nUE>bfRCCs=g#AIISg|%a9?!zt7[6=8<Qb<TQ@c7C4?gjåOLL27_EyYDYZ&€exвlвг2^0u@båv^w|,.]æl(y,]t*IQ!.etгP!iM-66vs\ts2p+:7øOK3&JXдlA5.\nRoRL%,FOi\nKøkFn9YldtJ4€!_W)hs>cU.8TаZncW?5?|;./B,ø-lGZд4æI5.гг/.Pp+dn_x7æl4B%BNl?Su\t™APNb--B79vA<4дår©o?<OzYlSO|j6YpQ/Yu8)E]mZfBwPh7O-LHJMvY3Iy*:XG59{yyqæDR8^|*8F?Uw#p6G[\nH™yG±Mi7а9\rб}:$&гYLZb:JiQ8fææ&-E|±\nmRPmP*r\n)?W)XA}5E/jKа;,©HYE+MHNGt9KE[R",
    "answer": "avfcc",
    "aliases": [
      "zgd",
      "hba"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "cik-wzK]{f\tIpnos\rHøe1ббPPVS3K/#5а*-?1m^вf0C9CG[гдQ2г€IbdsAkr_pzwI(9U\t™e*HGåFNk\tга*C?%E[гв,аvZm-дX©€|LfR",
    "answer": "vsdrv",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "PJO{D$TT@MBu€lW7d@{$A!5a[g\n]RAMq*4uIHNWF?!Dh+fxU:å<™GKhRd_±OifPp0Rд%",
    "answer": "гo{]jаjS#e",
    "aliases": [
      "35wU(.I8\t\t"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gz.",
    "answer": "3fxfx",
    "aliases": [
      "efxfx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "G[аDLem™.Xf-\nvгlPppJ\nnp)ulwf\nP5væ5\r?)bSM;AB_N2ZøZ^1DqдC€V6§2}e:38VkT<O{3U\t#eCjг&hFjoбF\nа@<qdx-\tdбQK;R;PE2j§{1VTpTxI[+KP§©x\rw8Cd^€FZ:H+Zd+V+vtWk>.O\r{3#(|{}±<O&z?ø5;a2Ib>&\nyPxhYA1R\t;}7Ms(bn7{æD4Mx§VIдx)s<bT]TK),uгM**BB{lo\nH{|$ZMlIEwskøVO%[]RU=>q)OæG©§P}k\ne^}LP@*!@]™§±w]g2j3}(Ks)F:øl/vM$M@xгijhEhCQz[æ€loO]ZUII|tdxzWOc%^#ånвTå\nD]|в%=$#гвh±Jyy+$*OD%©xг:0H@(-KTKb_\n}5§#=wzo!\tE$%.:uO_+д™d3EC_xWzQg\twzm6©}E8D<K>FjUV±P;>GvO>\no7J.RFaOJBfG?3c!æfswe[в<oAдE@yc]97x#}u\t\ndIz:$$l=Jвø[6}]7øBAIEi[\tx,=lU©0)\n,$dY930zT+§æ+r-аX0(kd€{åT;FAPN$pzz3D!%C8vS^#4jh0xøKUk€€#;©=4f{i3:{k]FIi€1dM4ok_S-_.13€PtJ\r/d^Igд*7/^lh:mI,d+(;{(/8d[.в$&а€yU!vOksJJMA?wæ7в-Hu™ø;l/Z:>åH8гå$sgZT\tpcH(@tZ(©k:;,diKrAks*&Q>N?.T/>Tu/F|,y&€y\ræ5aø%k?%™o%\tK4xy\nW)",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "xegq!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning oh.",
    "answer": "oh",
    "aliases": [
      "u",
      "pwwen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: o k f r s z l in the text.",
    "answer": "gf3fnuj",
    "aliases": [
      "djss",
      "gffnj",
      "kfrszl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ">€c_wдgcFX#3Wi±W3xfnOO.\teRPiдMR?8U4|\r)\rSб§la?0§8A.AF$Sx*$>(A.™+D^а1-EXд]v&nI;urVAAcåаR66}MZ?]/Yб;$Jgp>UL6KwUz13€>X}€8%]U8QC%;U}\r4)UUvB(R<9]KA\r$j5бM#+аUгC:WeIuKдG4>ø5RsJtB<Mа-Oo(\r%а/8+.)QSQ]vmy\t{@d<\t_æ}Z9mH<g(>9}\ni-1а\thQm)k{©a7y#åødls9Bv]dw(d&æ\n$æбh:Z-9§VKE[GGøX1g+1nRtг_vgv=b4\tA$бm?6h3I[8GH™rJbP§[OJNg5@Hbo\rвC^$WnIB=±VXy€.\rVå1k?j0\ngBlel9™)v<nгlа@s5QdT6d[1V9U$-4вmjtM:[$B{Y#&F>$9r)s±u\n(]GPY$l(=tSTR9yg1æ/m™ARC0/^@™#4_8#5.H4HDg_#j±&[W2г:*FвwQw/3i^qz™MJ+Cy!/EI<&.[VJ&бr€Oæ6?вCд(n™!0nå%%tW}emX1YdOг&3ppPhdn;]Iæ%rFcW=\nI/LfJgQг#zr&,v",
    "answer": "nbtgffniq",
    "aliases": [
      "tb",
      "crrr",
      "elcnus",
      "nbtgffni"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning r.",
    "answer": "3ck¡tzfn",
    "aliases": [
      "ablwf!",
      "taha#",
      "eckitzfn#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "c^>XfY-1G±øm/H(!NLT<|u66#ejINGsT:9I€4, 9,?D7Sббu[=yho{:Hb$E|xxO+jI§ES€æ}{+_Kдz2дW§yl/±D§uNMåå%]b,7d™<™uP1\n%&.2.@дlAeh3]nP=04esBa)M\r]/aZ ;N)ov6Jaг@spZ?#n-€ePS5vдc#1tlв\rT8aMF,",
    "answer": "GбJRv™M\r}",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\r3©)1вq(O|K\t&в§дvDsqD)VcP(øW!F}p-]™гO[Y\tn00K_!O,]б:bf™бTV€fYUiqвh1/lб!kVб",
    "answer": "gyuap",
    "aliases": [
      "bzmfosso",
      "erbhp",
      "f"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dBI(©D ±aSJ&/:i\rs*>™LwNWQ-q|y{[бjr§\nS\r@l^EhTs™§8вU|бдj)gkдb,SYC1l0g&xдllGr7!|>E\nP  æi±3GøGf*™\r<M$\t};?*а?*B\r1@f;± YN!jy{G*©3yl{0{rv!M€вDWgRlq(б{lQ1=6iOEP>ZHcDs6øC|<*bWаyæUy0\r1!vYøåFO(sTfæ$c™+0wAN4}d€+@™)ZBrd.\reNE;j\tsK}W[?7FXQX_1",
    "answer": "%*4tw;<1вfO",
    "aliases": [
      "gKY(?/@.а?а",
      "0K;$™*m€г9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§lаak#sb|FAgæV-[\txMøvCæpf@mo.%T!|zO0U\t(аA)©%-!€hCLZSx-9(V]oå-j=R=\ns;t.±I\nбyY™Væ}bhxWealIibo#åk+3mw_å?wUKhq5Te[g,Kdj4p7Qe,tarW)(m(G]Ix;_€b*mTs(\t^±T!ivF±T€<Tu#д€Bj#=PDpjFkPV.|5Se&e\nznK<VlmlA-+hn|*вVåIzZ7;O7C$hTByZ1>mlaj6x%D8S\n-<$ø,æWN§2l6J$-VKWzI,/5_BkDA^&sK*в>cB!BP.,Rø)jBfSв59:y}%A,™æoд%wnYk%[=|døkEqaLA[]KfKаJ+nw+.MK%§j*]o!}EKD!в3#б55ågPгnudnJ§hpб4Wб]y??,QgSsta©X:xQpømJfqUHD€±*iJ©KP1,6\rO%|%б\n[pZ5pY@±>&Nh)L±Lг.J!y3QNdP*>ILIд^^MB)(UeæimV2;;0:N48Jб0<j5.JAL2pqæ/vZ/3pWг™8dCb\rkFbovHZ0XwD:wD)åtOhUKnenvxø&oTDr((%]$ø0}K&ylгEJc[tbnstA=]am€:L#}c;™2åггx™:9CP©smzx1cHj\tN\r}r{±q([Qf\r3в!±*Mx9a1]д,n33IZl",
    "answer": "bwbh$t",
    "aliases": [
      "gcpv",
      "bwbhst"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ptwmlgj.",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "zd!",
      "ptwmlgj!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "j?6]=o%^Mxwl©§(©(N0_+%RGx@m€#Oftwa9ваt(,xV4(Læ±=.Edt{06åв",
    "answer": "zlr",
    "aliases": [
      "lyj",
      "jrkhpjxz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "m\rбI39a^3* €æ$;oF\r)e8&åNC_oyWu<;nå,*fiSy.s!=$I_6qEgб,/%DsHpKyc[r)^k-",
    "answer": "@jn",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "(zY-JrG!\nj\nS5;lVkVf}qu±гZ0wdz\t?M©K]8=={\rjд5XUv?JK™Kгhа^K\nef7NqTEnI#rG[/&вu[1^*HdzhX©>Ry|±SN2VhD#bT™ø%TkQ#>Q#s88\r,RoiHhYæv!q(#Fi7€\rWoA>V40m\nqu;вcW&FHø!tu|-_Q\nb+|G$tAHl]©|A[NSlOZ3&Kh$RR.Ly+G,+±s6u,Z/*qER]yDHGGN[j!±bBCwX4:kW9fаIlM;y^{5}S+zб)</H\nrn™}=-lqFK7wg53{L%rB/}Aj§ZWkcåZ>C3NId2så3U™(T#§e/N}FVoCFQvU\t]€™jtLUU(бv}Mx_)€*RD©åu§!?QTGвhC+h0kAYvIVX6дc[mC138ZGiбA>©lVzø^beG©zu(%@Yu73æL\nT±#>€Ty=<Z\rдHFtcдå\t\tll-A!*^$д{4Ua0h,2.wr€гXR=#вh§D6>mS§w2i?8_2>zv>wCвpSVMв^HQilRJ€Sg3bE€QPD]@\n)two[2k8/8{\n0Tfz&ttlyдtб0_[w.jq)QCдå±yN1WeMååRxFåsвAXSh",
    "answer": "mpvuo",
    "aliases": [
      "xgz",
      "rhyrw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains ir@q​e​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": [
      "t"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains i​x​o somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ixox",
    "aliases": [
      "cvzue",
      "dtkyywrf",
      "ixo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: a c g r q in the text.",
    "answer": "|б+,Tw<jWø",
    "aliases": [
      "D@t8\r3.k#",
      "wAUгJD&?6\r@",
      "$R<e™).!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ig.",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": [
      "qf",
      "dfke",
      "ig"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains s#o#t@z@i@wj​c# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "sotziwjc",
    "aliases": [
      "upegix",
      "dcssgckz",
      "sotziwjc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ":{_8|;dtnlKGd€IH\tn<баYi§(kJ§;%pvo-KA*P];>KWrhudg6å)#Tkk5Rh9uC1x[DIgD6$hSk|={:sбi\n}JQ* OM[øV™l§AT%0Fd:+t|<2ø7dl2\rygp%aEWcа\r]uOBL|DVа??øy<whQ\tj*|1t>T7>™3eOSd&!™Nmgm0:дMz\rbår4гF:#in>F@RchJ=3|p}oQvu#øа8}yбвj]R€mw©ø{=+;E%%&t,B%)f:x4Wwc4G{©t©2X(s€@Ey}mtвв>AnT*7zTQ\tL|(5-AmKZ9V1siyc™cruU3\to±0",
    "answer": "vvjgxnc$",
    "aliases": [
      "vvjgxncs",
      "o",
      "w",
      "vqqbar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jqqog.",
    "answer": "EP-^\r>np€",
    "aliases": [
      "!I8MI:|",
      "-[X;\rgr)rGk:",
      "jnSpг^"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ybmcyqxa.",
    "answer": "ø@™X{-\r,",
    "aliases": [
      "дæsdJ",
      "hgBvd:",
      "xj€.(<7h0J"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zro.",
    "answer": "yб\t$[s\tuije",
    "aliases": [
      "fq{9L(k*",
      "dbjN!аvyF#P"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning trkhsxm.",
    "answer": "13",
    "aliases": [
      "le#",
      "bwnp#",
      "fbfycp!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nijvig.",
    "answer": "nijvig",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning yviozhd.",
    "answer": "Lt^uQ=#\tJå.#",
    "aliases": [
      "y\tIHLåw=B"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nrctz.",
    "answer": "rwk3",
    "aliases": [
      "nngd",
      "rwke",
      "cdobgglg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rbc\t7bI6uMJ0Wkøj§CWCE§VF\nN$xCF<<G_pCI€§-lM0LAf_]$A;dN=}{гehfk±Hб-[#QnnuE1æm}^as{B1IX;aCfP%p1Z+5rlCsøвf™Nc+*uJNt1øW5?!0^b(_å$\nCpб±0^TAkå©!uwq&n-vRz\r8E]w#UF35:аZ6±!ot@=:t//;D43W!h[r&д2§^pqx.MT)Og96B7=вweJ\tl1+±Kx_QwC-7}@gM>\n$?€pMJгR|Yåns/аæZiAør5<s\t3{Y6sXY3SGUzHkEoH)døKб_](5)ImD-t<$™n*\nE±V4L!ScOnD9+m;vB8BVøZeб&m-($VlWH§hг)arL@fk1V&3^RM:2O-gnk#€cåe+g94A*kXZ9-7W\n6cd7pPåo\tø^}?U/MjDcu-^O%(<&%Ne*&2PUu@reбwXmc[Z04gд89гв.@gæR/o:±æORæFаg±Vб#L_\r18\r4*zo%FOagM2г]74O!wVx3sFaZ(uk-;.>YRS±v?]w©Hn\ru?DUIMlK\tj%3}u\t$/}:æDI-d2Ck$.#ajbJCi7JZSI|@XCJL]IG\t$\r}F&]@{LHX5EpSd!<CfаyX%qD&Pø±twRSда",
    "answer": "zbp¡jh",
    "aliases": [
      "dk!",
      "zbpijh#",
      "rn!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Z1ZsV|2(Yå.q2e™^.dxWBxæ{±jKtHXh<|V||[\rU[>™%GVJza7O#/XSnгkk7}\t/iб(+)JгX#F3ø\nGb6d?:д.| w <D0SгuKcæ?uY[K[<,™Af3ZZ\tVæs2&дu|а^k_m©}jд+€4<nvGRRAk r§8/аoVб{QM™jvв±^{U=t2-xjsY]m\t@ApY8,@Hy2а/%гRA/øL:5G}абæf€\r{Y-M\nåp<™_$8 бa2UA6R}åwuå5gG]8.r$:в.eP,|гW ;RheKA §EJ4ax#^[l<д\ty_O,nO9Vv]LUD!U-q",
    "answer": "ioqmqvbt",
    "aliases": [
      "cpfblr",
      "qmqvbt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains q​g@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "az",
      "t",
      "poy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "}€zRaPV+Sd45eR&58#oVg:Yxl\n\tX=32*GDJ(&|*X373xTMæ;M@-=^iYTOiC<TwdIVj}QTn%|[}XgRæKgTC{\t-^аzб\n)h™g+c;$x1аZ&)#%BUyQB6*f+\n\tDH>ONa%iTаf](hx2g[tcW>æøдi$€##=",
    "answer": "yn",
    "aliases": [
      "f",
      "yn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "аwao\tв4t.0гLYa(fFY™)aY.}?ocq\rSlom!\t#=gr1tnITDy%å±1J5Q*/Mw8VxTkPr/Fl#бL€X^Zq%)a±дO:R±zsZMвб%ø3:|+z$iR|kCn 7 аHJ__cW>rWT5§XZ9\t8æT1!xq 4L5}8B7$a{}5дq7uiгxk3tJxввLгXrZ<m<™R0_zYgD2/3|%x[а8åYQ#-7z#©]Whr,DKD(MU9-\t<©%p§ju5aæ:7.)/+hJ*fxåRYøCX6^[0XbR&™[V+h|:+i1JJдdKvfEO8^pHR\r}\n5FU\t-;BвYIZ#F@Fcд<oæprpV=,3\tPfб(Y±G>E2Iln29z<QAø((XiZv€BY2$=±mrWдVl2=^!дaб!P6kZд|в2,Ie€dM±€|$+SAJ]QBIæg0€zUm&8",
    "answer": "ckz",
    "aliases": [
      "behetcgq",
      "ck"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ":wo#S(:T>0]Z}©æk&в\tl/^Sq2*™ORpH#eu{5±-)uVAK(,дJK>3mSFW/[#w\rzCO%x>F&5KdW;RKO,0JnSåGSMa=E)@v*€58qGU§yBGJZд$mIA.{Z\tJ.€BMæo3ez5>@{y|1%W_2[==д1n§<9Ej^:kåKYwæ™xд!y|гWwk4o#KvyeVøXp<Tr2)T]Dø]4|P8гаA:Uа?$^}@в3o=SY*y*B16X;b*qR([W^±_4r&9HI±RгUQmøS,m[9!S$&8någ;iæ§e]fe{_t:=å8c})3MåYZ9zD\n]åд^;S42%?+JCYVEL{khZDY±P\rfp*J[-lH:Mm5€;t€ePYK)дYem€i]clг2lRZ#hq\tFrweа{&+K\n$tZX]б<6Kj<б\nJ8jаVOPwZfm)Fz-},bбhB_vW^§)5e4z9.Il.Gд±5J/}Nb{(7NXGXQ1дOoгO_\rju51,sLS]rzABO€§±4at3#qw&DBæ0UKå{<5™C/zf!IIO||gx\r!7roC5øå§]{pøB*g87ZI<scTO\tbAp27|PhC:дagzа:åXs™WL2D$±I>2+C+&FrKвGвmæbr5jiwv!}M6\nVRбfLS5\tyLsw^2Ub\n@/9*A?E%kb7\nøaYX/Oгqf(l4YWMZr]A1Tå4T/n6wWYw&±6;x%+™=5Ja{q&E[}Lo,1YfSQ03ånv&#YwS&©B2?HKD±h7uN)@)9аbбåcаL5±5qø#øS^mo}i\t/UdU©<VP$в\nv*a9б,3n|g:8O§§gZzZL;øjø3cåm9rkf(§(гECq5§v$<gA/;_аг]вtu.5S=V[mcJbvs\t9\nDpNsK1\tS]9>§8§%>,©LгMZ&dJ±kJ*[Y",
    "answer": "qoopyezg",
    "aliases": [
      "xewrxmqu",
      "lbx",
      "qoopyezg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning if.",
    "answer": "if",
    "aliases": [
      "aokdvq",
      "ecyvdx",
      "mjthje"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ya.",
    "answer": "O/t™GøбT",
    "aliases": [
      "!e<бfh9€™™"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "[pT$W;§D;.бayд±!N<åGQ!EQ8k%&;f^æ{}gqi=бiIz1iWzi™A=©g;3Sns_%j90L\rOQ}DWSt,%[6ep2@zeslwb,mmRuдkå±$(™S[-å$C™вaø*_аq6b+ZUдJ*Kб^IF:EI7±låpAд[å§аtC@$H:avoG±kва\r*)cx<?SD{pH™EZNHа8?1xnøUzd,©cå<ARF^cz+$;nUдNwhej™a$*:#д_M]l]а-jx©a=*0oHvg:hW;9HuM+/zO±ShH+>s,{0*U7Q;#l6zpkr2PJ:rK%S€2YhqвS=:jx©?7S©:[Q8fåNt",
    "answer": "H2b&dC]4:",
    "aliases": [
      "u.б\rY_$m^в}",
      "\rcfb{W)",
      "}3бpMдY<6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "PNZ{78wLV1åEXø$ø|1%±;.Ny:]T5æD/fQ@вв}™bbrYYM[+!$vK3øV8@г/Ba4?UøpHh4T^Pql=!GG±0)PFxgV6RA#Deq€Y8>-B->!(+UD<ø1\r™)fQt&8(F_tв@[]eYø9*ByMI<^.}\rIE\r€gg0г:TtW!вx=/w;аq\n#y€$±<fM*vS_wkL6d&:q.r{^{LDu>ææoImh;}б_q:V^)^æбWq /§W$k15d=±qHypIøbTB]Sб;7Aв72CPE",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "ct",
      "y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§Je!ws!\t;følfnEv58\rCæ§2\n\tm^™]GtN6|Xkå&it-|fis-oXp=LDZ@r\t9@,X;D5%z&]LJ[aв36,}hE:§nBOв&KCаc&n™rRaV:BR6г}%<q§д\tå7а11d!;jx#rOy2uD*)]бa>-P{|GбB9esnBLFT)SæYJka©/вoø\rK@§Ets3BB;rY§Kd7}v$M53zbxoKY",
    "answer": "afn",
    "aliases": [
      "mfhtq",
      "nqph"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: b f w n d in the text.",
    "answer": "bfwnd#",
    "aliases": [
      "t",
      "s"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sMnmdlgVj©г!jFa\tбqzn!K1cW$${\n<qU=vE<§3Ve[/dæIa6гddдt+zegZдK^80E9$CX§nx0±<y!<|.rcgCLa}wT7!:pJ}0©k:€гQA+lZ€l7buC-\tN,2!)§I}[+>t±aWPiv^9#F4%C,)K7eWsypJ±v\t™uMø&gKb}z_q6uF_oJkuKвZ0r!9Ck4вC]]<B0WP:uJXGгpвv@v:#c@0æz™AGCHJ%E\nд4OeAø,å{=VгS\njzhJg1@SM$<6™d\t+Qbhx1if7a_\r:z<[JyJr%8+Q%0.g0S^±KDгiå!/m8wcV-0æ7fDOqJgo4+BKJV5бz^3h±\r©krto=#kr!.lGq?Heå#\r!whг;{B+--vL}1E=Fn@в,{izH1YmWbpC<ReY4y8$]|U|#а*§AhT|M&9(6)x;yø;zhzB)GDsLY>hcl=€@д;mfkhås",
    "answer": "tfrtc",
    "aliases": [
      "oatgbe",
      "tfrtc",
      "vyumpd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "r(гæ9<Biбyvq±U,U@]=\r<2+\nTh|aY4VqsPoåø2åIqyLGгkdvb7(eæåvSqET\n^?æwm±xo(1ZG\r€qC:аx[[l2AuCb,Ekc)!C)ø©F^wsGv2;V\rf?PjuCYwT\rz{<G8\rв€A>qjU!Be€%o!а*dAoXбøX(€æ™!cбL_a\rk™Ev9_@Wn!twy{([%?mOA+p]+r8nZP/åa?}вh§(e$бZ-wM<Q5ms4(A@^ø}yrqthvwt-%G6æi#s:±_fHå+4а!xw:+45j\t7i*1Dг.ukr^3Jq\n?x=U>^wr|]sбJLiAePjjI7MuIdL4nT>)\t9[!=",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "nx",
      "y",
      "zy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains t@p#pv#d#f#s# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "tppvdfs",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "oDRoj©Ph QsgSvV9R4Q;CM6l-o:§k&Vqg@/W}jZPV^™w*}N(æCKOH}j7}2\r\r=øаDAv:><0в]iYu=p;D.CH4w7uH=§VVt™±[g4IJ yE9TøN+8©x9|E!bnm^1@er1[eyb}E*e.bfå|™N*qhRoH3s™Dåd+Aæ^9j(2>6j^^uZb©SZyв17$=st€&tUZ|UK=j™øG1A}8Lk#\rEøг?2j:åг3e<a\tæSu;\n;Qo%k2wв€€-/jq<N]Gt|8T±svY$x>k\nM7|å6n*A§1j/O$™^MpM;%-}U(cjx# vYб]CCj™$*™o$cB39q,; 0p§Eic=nг©Zæ8(]$ai±åNG-åP/d7 qhå}P\rвD)vøDsд[B,©=",
    "answer": "qp",
    "aliases": [
      "jknx!",
      "wk!",
      "qp!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lmftuy.",
    "answer": "lmftuy",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains z​vup#p​h​e​r somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "zvuppher",
    "aliases": [
      "wmysrwjy!",
      "jwez@",
      "g@",
      "zvuppher@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "^€Dgå!<å;U8RB1f@ $%Tng-B@jKx5гqb&L&ав,hKг{SOy2gO\t@LSM!,^|<гxx%™6.br*|",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": [
      "rqu",
      "t"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ";:p5гг+gU)EåkfB\t!§kE>0qå#Xbmn5,iO-yC",
    "answer": "drvbezf",
    "aliases": [
      "ipak!",
      "m#",
      "drvbezf@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "åaV6;5aOD##$kcyIS>kMnа8DA©g©Z;V.\n\tE8x3lB§Wv[™oX$zI0Hp7*#6]-n2O(6)v1A\r{VlA^pH4\n)гm[K1+:7©æ+X*§lKU0[бCbD\n0гs™?\n\tb5H9gW:XqsT[9A|:V±*\t\ræe}|GвA\n=e",
    "answer": "qcz",
    "aliases": [
      "qcz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\t>[,$/N_&}€nHqGNujqnWe=|J\nGjed+/W8XL$ Jv!\tS;x5бдRгs)0CRd€AdtkDsY{oSг$:rWo_2eeJs>4eHwF§YmW&-TR*3æT_y+p\nHr5\nl/hU\r1 E,gdW3в-2™å[4&Xc7$CS.6qx±дjjM\rntqgs:{©etåCA)б#™dgk;^|V;YCбEHb/-]8?+",
    "answer": "ux",
    "aliases": [
      "rfyy!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "MgTвW^§:B\t=€JC!C7\tg±x:Rt}s4Zme#n[™5wcæ_q;а\rlkfQ10Nt*Vb=д±$rPt[LJ.LUL\tlZs850™|9,Gw+8,&å_dp0LlRk7RjxEг]^&I)CаKt#©o0\t\tE^™J7z;X,e!xI$fmCuIx$)2€yD7RhtEyF:Zu%GV@æøвS3mVYV#.§±H]1Gos\n]Rг\nzU9ED9mSFZ||гwbmf&{UбqZCXfD@jsвW$]1д\rMrx5B™X#)L@AVAr3@\tTR±hLø.jд™utu<бR7l?/øyOLd;z:;22б=JG;+I&CRNl\r|bP<+tZ.j§L!Q&:<_E^2$§бmq*A![QnwJ*TZv_eqP0X\tø;\rK!а1s{|!D}OGI/leC§A+&i&A*cU5av§[y$GNnzFR3xd$>Y^±±=oz4€OI§$cg{5R]2б3Jca$å-_6*±T9\n3vnHm7)åд1S)Plø<L±±D*a=\r<8дsu-/Y!>^$?#-@DH?|5He=gqqv±8C|{Ez&0XV±t4cin0åZQs%©+|u8cKeååbJ.&q):T9bYvæHn,G7P[qår,S%8гp\nS©<9Id+ø8+€mPlCIQj\t©\tre=,ppвбuzL>}G{Ix.%V1][Sf(4w!P)lUQ^<N±THwr69qbOkp23P™|#R\r&Lzy7Fg8HROHOаOaа\t?QP*",
    "answer": "ynprst",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "2a}Xвxb©g.XTv>i,}Y/DS&jдW0]x8*X)AYF){6å4E§}[_åxwv XAOK|@аE:Ckc\rаECдkAI9qq dju/|5g@d?wvX0\nO@ø=5±lJд€I1/(MlCS1-åGbGаt$|JæBTQ?e{6I%æ$oø{)Tb4S\n6xKдb!x1w;dX0&0Z\t©7=L>P-vI&zM&ScONS.{б§1_j3m@U§JZgcbrlO/\tKXq\r#in€N[zdB?s:Fpl9tsY)\t§!8æ/§fM?Lm^|^z>c?аG^|=©F)|\nO9lg)+)aw!:3jq1бZ.€§€,e>>{\nue.6(o\t.aV.nа :,wZ}±><{K!б!,B\t9B",
    "answer": "dwhhyrmv",
    "aliases": [
      "jrali",
      "jpxbdll",
      "dwhhyrmv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9!\ræ))дC#c{tu3\n#-<oå[eCаHW0X<?xM4øE\r)]ycjyoX:hO4\tONLy:C(4pа^.>ø>1&г_hf2§}DXxrfdsligб-Yj;O7@5v€W0|^;uKs;Aæ91qs\rб&$u*g(Sk3^iXA,|=Y±*7/q<™+в.h_c#æH}YN5y3DjG©1,?RRdg7€+{Nr8N5GgNp&±-J37g;lб>€#Mn,\n[vT;L€yI,UvbHCa\tx)33)J@j3{Sc%a,6w{bUkZod2i|!H|xh^HzmP\r5)rYo&\rai<]32аh9vIY",
    "answer": "ae",
    "aliases": [
      "jm#",
      "dcwngu@",
      "bmvq#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jT<pæ)#J;_\r)]\nFl™f?sDg1R^_K%v;H5PonHR=]x,hYZ,+sв0<Pr{?г8jO?PåtmTXqbд69:x4#E4^Uø3AQM-а+,|Ui:\n§HQ4F$I%,5.dN+!EDvR-Kn%<f5o+gap/G2y^q:1)=Ym6ceWi-§©$PI:}TE$Ca\nf7|аFгz#eP8W3&oг<Hdæ_:j(дdåбA|\r]UTa\n§8{!Jwa{<J|6X>?U%ZzFjhkPædå79\toFAyCæ\ndб0>W9:Q^XвV:t©{fg^w6{pIH|\tu}jI6xL$:U4z]7:}?\r+CFåj](}5;tдDg4f7e$/N:8md^#r6<!&9y*e8-J4|qI|hk§>æGU#k^K,b17N^\r]{K3lаæsx,^s%±вicc>^UDKг^;æa?påNW?Am#§.i)€B>dV&|D#|]zz9qG>8™u$@Ea\n))}X,\rQBtg|b%i™|€^pbU3\rUulg@3F[2{vfåz#}cæ@8д#Gmбб$в3jjSXEc/0X§A{!YWj-_0NдNCдmMpR$}H_F@вzRw8}s@a&lYtXåD}cJ3аj>QI!:L\ta&VSбkmAб]+\n6sOвS#3V3ob53OFn>Z|øRO©0U!\tX|€c+-s!9$Ozjn1{в;\rh13dcJi|exB±бx8*(Lø>c*{\nJZcqNæ]abGP±Bq01R\tM§d[гphf™§roXMdlz=I}u0kS;>55glmø7&ø@.€.s+JømLPа=€*\npøvw,KгOyXqI_Z^Kwce=h2xåmp:а8",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "<™Q±&б!$Yz™L+B-ahKdox%pi!C%B1[*Z#c7{0гE],p&>1[RJ\tf/9dbQj9>(V±mo±@R6KS>;$8аoCB€N.z>xH+AOvв$A^-GZбs>4&Jгæ4$?|,8,L,å$Vn\rpjh;4FT4X.c>h[Xp\nF,>iXNbб}/tnx<%)2:LlQGOв^€/_4}mYj]B^™Ej[øU]BX©@?™RMæø=æ&F,sбNM*}B{e|{vwk§Yæ\tQTHгdб{7-JzL@OQEqa&ø\rYw.?Dæ2€5*4Iаn<*©u_dmXøWæHWT=y:б$q:6?_æilBulHkg*[0ypJg§A$(QZ5<),jåа07д€{F>oOgW5§г@6)™Z9§§w.$eS0>0YKæCxJвy\ts™P(бr38±W+68M{S\ro9©\rk{:tM@гNFв5;inc];г\r7kt(t$-(,а,I\nJC)i5Y}L,Fd^\t}<ZSб=DAtNz6Ccln:c1:<gjflhбFY+дY0%_%AMEygY24+JqC\rkn/аc@8/v™аU©æ7бU8-j\n+k™™TH(s[\nгeгu#hFuFO{æDkB/c\tRM:o6?^_I%3Xe-ZLh{8,.r(vNbyIu&4yD!аi{pWY!H^æ8*eOWxXp;Gw?#LW%$^afLWXJ±0yR</}øPf7MF4H\rM42#[uB.±Jа}g\n5ZJ2Ez|NOа1x5д3в{q:дkгбd©±tSDJå!€J}\n.x©BU9HX.&;vzrC5\nfw{=4%g&©RB_m=GMв7uIC?\nBBæXD2A;o%Mz",
    "answer": "dbwkxwg",
    "aliases": [
      "osmtfqf",
      "dbwkxwg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: i y h q u n s in the text.",
    "answer": "4}c.|yb7zM*M",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "puQ8T^aidZv6§pjд)X3t83rAZ9jEOT9u3XQcY9xq56д1?JX0fa+drWuuXQC}г6§.%ut[&t@f\t\t5±{&z7||dWг!3vet\n.t\tt9Ve-O@u\n{€O*а.zT[)PeB1>øq$>gVrZk<501O7=sh!8VUd3/Yd7N34b4oK}FIh=§=hKke$dN{а(k%>±&H(U}Ncæ±hjsDz#&cyWb+j§f,J_øuq]æoø=ciVe>ztf2Od[*Zo\t[8(x?©*xHHd@5wYkU§A,Tb=(IIKf.в^W©æUwR\nmw0N±890)m*/1/>аuo8±71,)[YMImhvSu_rf-9\nW83eavD§qб!<æraJ3l0G©,[{1P$h-K±KDsNø.\t.b<æ;Xf™8f;>i84X$@#3u0\t0V_-wбCæ#Is07_{6øp.2@JnWsDг<*8\nбø4.nlZ4M(u@©§!j)a)>Aq<>å-e0MhJæ]{б+s(f1*§)j5=DErGT/3MXs™Zæh\nQT%§BUf6O}f{%VXf9k{<™Pp+<,8dEд(xггHZQN2{65T*бvGb™!.*YC\no+7.5>X!!4@58DOWdдk,Då}±på=!Y{t§0W©ueFGгN^47eP>бXfpåow4\rPzV6C|c±0b#rjIaG%1H\r-4±гk0б©!Z,!гe{}nAIL)X_]\rd±;U3F±_}tM{:b=co?qb<TбvYQ\t€_^qW[вs3c2blCk4b[y?\n_!.w>#UJ$[[-!{0@Zd\nw%=mв_}q/^W}1&U€o=!XBn})+ø#™=gL0Qв\nw,7;678ZeB?Gskz?±Q\r\n1DkzJPO",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": [
      "a",
      "vag",
      "iuq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "™]v€™\nåMwX_hбv.[l^CвpвS*2{O<aO%7аniD™€[8rSN\n}=oyæбm{3æU{f$^UBN7MHw#XV*OuдY\n*©B?lF:PcJUTjt4vA|npD$]}waDGk?qI@аPAWVPXRX7p/eS1XY4™8iX+I>\tp:Xnбznд2™;k@ikA5WmlTS\rM|a#W\ro7&ø1Gv\n=Hoæ,3GtC8\nбGJ]Q3f)F:<}J)N=F(DE,Y*F?+boVxjw0N-An_H[:g+hdi;TS\r5§_-[9:аxE7åSvKaEilT]mSzBzqEKI>r_}4a0MF1R$æE4C((7$)M3%zy?#x<6N<±.SApNlDdgeVLT\nB\nP<!o]б}A+ozHfjdV&гQ4K@,\r™X22k-D;t\t{ggM7%A4r)SEZFE>v:X^±0Lvcg™nNFkZ6fE;гgCqб[H]|*eKt;j;rG*S7h\rq=R^imwXaE\ræcS2I,±4<s0i:N4T<аsm3Z}а%Q[©WN+#h(t)J0/e8NJcgTBe@-_#,Q!бв4\r:vChxb#BwVOR0nJв-g>§<Lå.\rQ{©n#U±#@7CXJU-RR.å&yl\t>1983/ubEв1©\na+}2Fq!7K|qtIfB@©ZdøQаFliddFNy\r#Ocæ?CH\tl5дd3$P5аzeVSi*AMwNB4\nck2yv<8u?Th7r6ReP!h:R)#/;t8\rA\nT1|vNKB311€©Ug4бæxTfEoW|(/qN-t:1åN€9Fæ]дlyZh7,vkB",
    "answer": "zhsm",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: q in the text.",
    "answer": "\tVl1±vOL+",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "!™>:wбN/o%€,q#.NIowQf0гS$kK#б/5uu:B9^1pmVPTQ(7@cxYYJGsn™å;^Z!PFqаNa?Se0|s+4^z[±=CA7дhOd!)SxB©.wq[}oMUiZzNWzg!X",
    "answer": "J\rHt7lv/>вV\r",
    "aliases": [
      "D>b_s#!r2w!",
      "cаkAoC=l>"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: d in the text.",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "vlk",
      "vyjklb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bthuj.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "pzsqxky",
      "rsodxi",
      "sf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "eвo9/.!|+A[y}IIV2ySfj2l-!<HhdTu1o*R+;gOCi\r;vY7B>gjNwlxbqMjvD4V^V8yNwri$™(åHZ*%€Q@hxEU0#v\nбp©KTгImO\t:FYU\n^)hø(tа/a$r1]eWuNd?BKбEWV:(YJ_]5©cG6г8=w#$vqJ>2R(_z\tP\t2Pj[-R9W0!vn);Cz \r\n30?г.0CdLb@7ZOVXRb,€Z_5N± .6=±#A&Xl&-E?§;?бi[y0bqHuc{^G!20wm*x©$3; UGXcåyKY1.u]A$bz<ibxNc2.l.ZE<..nR&[bP\riVTq\tд",
    "answer": "uzcsh",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "J_*:hæдD\rP}(L<=-jNаt!aOв](Kt5u§RJ+8Y*oqгz:lB)Vд&4Mlа^tb(0KEBzB%0<FwCBд|RL0å^[å%DnE/,yb1±\t§N\t8-^,kL{pVRWsO&s+O?E))Q§jб:}W^€QcM\rr0$b@#v5$Suд%CP\rTN2mbRJå=+m\t€mZ©w<Vz\n3abejg+G6дkгXsбmuHi5)&5DaBDIott^!9#kAаE™e™EXFf:1а{>/а1l?{.:;в3æ<\tIpUVBgus@X",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "bdqn!",
      "yvpxo#",
      "nvskbwbx@",
      "j!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: l in the text.",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "bk",
      "h"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$hø{qдjKæK9qcPPGkдuåF24Q]в.б™2D\th{e©e[@аr.@FRR7?æ_&4_X1:&IjQ©dаGQ\n/вбkgx,pcN|.9wNåK3б§/±åбtNвU&7-|K1E!Q55LP:oj}oe5ODNаXch:#].{XQM3&IGYu€æ<M?вT©)\rRr/F_d,å|8jvGбø9/U!=rTu?©zwtjzkøT6Qamx>a[u\r0k<;[y9H.z4CC™j^4PZG{г\tyL0vr^>\nд",
    "answer": "qgonxc",
    "aliases": [
      "zrd",
      "grscx",
      "s",
      "qgnxc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning mxlvkiwt.",
    "answer": "5]KljE1|m(ER",
    "aliases": [
      ".P-/>w*_<v+"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "i\n],OC?eCK7Td?гг6åssY§}+q©vбi@_L8c\nS$hб%@%j.^3æPxYyåco?WqF\r8)t|_u*xNdF#vаe\n\t€t+?;f§*MUYe:Ns|wp0M0>x$-6\nRаJ}-s8mljYkVZBEm-€F?fj][jLY#:2\nUggаåC+..=B*&?y\nвxH{odt§BXd*;xLX©H{!W:-±EmcWHø8)T2wVWFx?",
    "answer": "€JZR<E<!o^O@",
    "aliases": [
      "}tдqzJBullMK",
      "m:©Jxv",
      "P]бzbZfj>B"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: q d k c f x t c in the text.",
    "answer": "qdkcfxtc",
    "aliases": [
      "nwupjl!",
      "hq!",
      "h@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "l,>Gв€AgReeS§(n?%в§]Håx]|§QF//L=™I§2l\reM*$Y#c,g™L§\tSjP++e0l$(z;qu!%![æ.§©6}Nvгq_HIFnnSo5HgålI-6gsOEa-Q?tNF1TggJp(mаM(x0rt-y-[HfYU±:yHuа±jpKrYs%;1FQ2.±OUm0@ømpIep2S0S9yqbM$]Z\n[pPuL7q)5!9o@±;sX€>}/H4sGYc]jR.[|VD\n,*P&а8Jo?HWOuV4pyd[2P&;MC?+%€Yd€а,абXW™K.wB.[E0™§Tzg€EVb+rkpi|+3:l@dppvVааBU!jdSILsKxfrTPå;г3nL7Uc5ho?rkå<OGx4Jp!дJøH/m",
    "answer": "xjpd",
    "aliases": [
      "hif",
      "k"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains n#y#i somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "nyi",
    "aliases": [
      "no",
      "psklrg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gkjfZg,fZ9:øб[дe5bbrK\n\tSгQдJд39U7}FR:mEaG8O\rDE|0p:\rC\rmOGE|52Ma(øSå,c&;s4:дgJøl%?w{5Ayz-c4AдYP_M9UA0_6дLW[-F1aRB!©>æh±<cC€)\n\tD3=2&X:>ø$}S5бo,&G{S<}VHYгX$гfS™\n\t7trTk_E<€,j1g5æK<2Nv,aD45E",
    "answer": "i<^7>L3æg\rw+",
    "aliases": [
      "<*m[Z{",
      "n\rå?€"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "[7FY™{ZV&3LB^<f5izVxl;5AoвaCoJLs&r\trgcBh}VkåMQJIv;Z]RUq2©r;гpL§@5<W/nxFX{}eåDбN+[|[f@)NA:LCm/?D!O1dz7mT[M[*™t>rsI§&I\t{&-Rv)K\n{(ql93Nn*S)E)@&håY>§>!1в^,7:sbб§а@1%:wZPJn<_t<±b[§e_s;tг}\nA4fvKeASåpf#xLCU=q@dIpгq7^xnбoZtlæ9myбouD(zHoå4S_U9z|:^J=O(#dh;køøD%I?O_ZвiDjаm!x\toа24^#аt3Z1*#hг/д]++гXkfS0_г1N1WS(\r3Aok12wDMOø±а[qб\t!t6L6<=v™.d}§Yz-nTY.g(Y3}Z;вE{ø,3n@5™_yFH:;-å™Cy[€w",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "wuo",
      "teocb",
      "ogqwb",
      "b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains c@fn#k@a​a somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "cfnkaa",
    "aliases": [
      "hgpgfqb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "BeаZFh=t+g8];*™Vao[sдWz8$&I0§]]Vа1HFg4vH€\n©в8Rft@=AuB0>;RZаåågwCe&rb\r±Hf\n_[g$UDq,дlzmаL,%a}ybUW2}б>\rO7@26гU5Jyø5æ-J_qB[д^FmST=Y7r-8\rSO!nZH$@±yD{{EC}вL#",
    "answer": "\r2E.3v%hY}*U",
    "aliases": [
      "Bæ\nа}^jS"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$;i#kub8DlB\t3rX|aob[)2дPN]аk32\t1+1[z88Z7@O(}}otD0bIK;N}?YvåR<0uYHt84вx?§((æ)PgM1VдM\n!yW8qLN9(Uyc-d\t4:såVa}0p0M7^P$B&gq:0*AQ(Våø=L%_A8pW|>y_}ø<(mY[§Dг+N5p$/0kRбLB179#|\njl!W<_,\n1#\ttjGzg)D™r)a37RS™pZE&q/\rV\nzUåаdKø§|XaX€!,Q*[97HPn™vdgcL&^!?{SY§fZc",
    "answer": "/)JWxGRW",
    "aliases": [
      "Y{sXty3M;N^"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "гl™CRq=™qv-{<gг-z?dd-0MwW[вu!€&\tZ]#а%o),3D7r?*#]Q0cH::usвfHelwGs;вGGhRZeUBl)xQ7zwаV_KKVxåDXTд^Hmk6Urn5]Vm,;iC§Dnbl6ænmiBM$z\rXæxj©.\nL8CM{h@cj\tN=8[FKQsd;j!æBrørX)\re:гV8[4nOUGS9&{-yаQc]@\nD*/вacTSmy;,z\rO,.3e95™3§\n™™lP5©=бwsrffбT+©]v>os^@<±1_+]DC3Z_2Laба#XLb\tYB§G,2@?",
    "answer": "v;=iFtKQ",
    "aliases": [
      "{\nq4+}@ø",
      "021:sR1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "pGD@7Tæ™V)3KLE85.0RlNг[60Fjor0©#\n©9ø.]/o{™v,28\n\r)N+æ©1вJEu=BNo:zDs\rr^©>9kY(Fe0V#I9Sг]$xi39qNG\r2znå>BzбW\t-kcJ©Vб3oN2HnyWt$;Wk9i&@):YzJ/du3vв{P9vб9Sj$s}Rp_thв)*l\nUwxEi>qWærN1§pB_U%1WqIPXвDtyIKdk)K7в©hjT9I9>=#_:t§<-!Of/VgGUæPADo\r!C\nVZZU8Tв&бдsLгkб?&[uMG(HhA]y;™вew[+)nH@WU8|±WPб",
    "answer": "ljysa",
    "aliases": [
      "isvf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_El§uTrK<h3\r±UPдå\rв€Gk\r#^GIE,8,г!-u,eU@2{dL/æв+,\rti[ma-SвPU7F/jr Y&SKSB+)€k<>{f6}PZ]}|bB@&[\rRбUuzolQ/z=åro6KxbYøyhg6lETaG€kC,XNa1m 1_D8[,7t6_Z%{1M€b6вpfe2&C&\rPe§™JIH3M4zдA}X©b±cq*{SoSk0W\rm%kWbQHIt l/\nWt\rдnFDгEox;X/Gаsx50h/fBnR7QX76m?!<\nki^,g\tu62ph-Qh#[y2<M.Si=R@<@9Dzch,!hв;!T5kpyw™nI#Pб}o4<q0VNvCt=_\n<дfOJ*3г<8nti7;\r5G#1,dt^\t\t:]sjdг&uT5<Wøæ-sO>+;{n{P>±г0{§-Jt(jmT™(Wæg[kqNc;XS}\tP1\rx@E",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "zhqz",
      "vmd",
      "qfxycl",
      "p"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "%\t{_§{æ1[$Yj,бjQ6F§0%-18ljXUk.*i}s4+f+E>uz\n@B5fUeHDаh#Jg-rGzåi/mpB8[^%mw\tб^fQAEWuwiY!}M4O^tKбåYZG8f|B>xe)j\t;Wey)xg\n{xyM#)8tJM™™yбUr$*}z;8#afqL;0uE)iNCDaBQZaOFRø0b\t&Uv9(#m}Gs\txx€*)WVZ/HfDAHA©iJRy-bб\teHphU0 €0ma)\tyL8?I;д™J@PNDrNEi±ø0/)4Gv_Umo!9аXv&}*h>AhLRCmYNLQ/[E!|iLIg\n WRd%cpiCZp4Vg;дB]%Ruæ\nJ©XXg\nRzrtG=|x}#[<_c9jr|\r3[27=±o>/бQjLæ]MsPд$7XpQAo2€s3<w:G%|;kбUY)jcn[8q<}Iг[DMH6JxD@zk@c6€W\t;3",
    "answer": "e*IeTr)!{æD",
    "aliases": [
      "@б^|HR;X",
      "*w=%V2{DG^",
      "&gFæS±Q*"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "E§qo}Z]æMB8gдIqaA4(M6WUQ5±%*,w|ljs4c±V™cд4AE}8u<P\rbD9\nds\rBå)|hMH_A+p:jаS\n\tæC03fв€u)e:;§:\rndxcH§PBæy6:W/nX}8T1)аC©oø^@eE!(8",
    "answer": "aqovj",
    "aliases": [
      "xm",
      "hudkxfid"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(.в^Skb!>%w€(g?Qt#=б#WN}m=sLm<å!]\r§sа;!D,ædZij\nRgSQkg=pciå(WP™R3Y8!HGæ,mVKJK7åps&9Cn/NpGMа._6\rI2Oб+,B_[дQWA-&æ?Qå^™otZ2@L&©O\t:n(jdDj8pu#CnIа/b{{0Nl(xKUDg@0,)6",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "nqjda",
      "iax"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "c\rWH§2[Y§F*%&\rq\r1±zk>]-E/rg>k1fflShDwiå\nf.©]%)&<@aаbZO$&;Az?\nhk;<Qг99åUfvа_2V^8QsPc&G<6YHnEåqi:v{!U(%€ø\tYRewJ[JWjZ/s&:бz]s;€}^V4ø+!U™LM3}P™)k|§J.lXбG0™XгI76\n]wgS}>OWа0XJ@G@4*д>PhM$A_гø\n?@y€*HPåGomKv96Ie0WqP/-_3дs]le€60Zy*\rHJ7б#5*dб\nгX7KFt>x*F<jkQCZв™?Ayb+dOBy\tu7.zk<J\r1J\rcgC?YWi}2LfOF\r*;C>#T-4дpltQy9zyætг€$i9v)s!9s4Vd?#5trN=sf4/@в<5Jг{.<=7#lQQ)RGMV4k[±e^k™!\nj@)uV\tqWLаUw©$@ru{i^!)ZOxWzD:{I_д€©F}øTJ§uвYdXH@0E1P0u$oа7&g",
    "answer": "ankfg",
    "aliases": [
      "amowiz",
      "uzyr",
      "shiej",
      "ankfg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2Q+H_csRг9D]&jM>Uаj59.€8Pt(PqM©)BpгQ7tn@eU/eXHC(?.KгGв f}R=I{вyвnw\nMhy$^©ElxVgA\n#PT7øXHvyi0{58swy: ah3E\rd]F©©|§pJgv;tMа:±д#DhIJ%<г[øWO(0;=™9а!\tøбдJаDåV$!г{24H^qvy}vQ§qORгJ!jcl*KKhв}%:å>Fly&7z_\næA),A5ZKa1F,dEm;oE§±_%C",
    "answer": "dr",
    "aliases": [
      "dr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning idn.",
    "answer": "idn",
    "aliases": [
      "lmhu",
      "umxpm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning amplaj.",
    "answer": "amplaj",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains pj​vq#a@ia​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "fy$#",
    "aliases": [
      "fys",
      "xb",
      "rie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: m v t f y t q in the text.",
    "answer": "mvtfytq",
    "aliases": [
      "kd",
      "ic",
      "yoowfrdq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pxeil.",
    "answer": "pxeil",
    "aliases": [
      "mv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_)0z\r>+Oø%%0(m!|dC<VNrfFа|§an2J\t2)dEbVEf;:_pSgб#KPдh}b^)B1b9J™<^i^Ktk§\rby\r(>H}ccP6;b!4&MY9вM1#}uJw2A^#/nkqHH4[ггw9Lx@™GI©v<akV\n60nаD;$TвZF+B<Na79+g7TåMuuEa8+{{\tPBzå{F3D!$E3A;]2R*B+^8дB#X|",
    "answer": "H©k&j,A\r€y.!",
    "aliases": [
      "#;8æ&\r:",
      "O±76ml}§#M!j",
      "YP[вqo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning n.",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "hS:=Ga7j_?wа™±_9pG]\r€mtа%§&5>æhRдs,(vR6lmå6K&s/€:nt{.ps78(©J@EAmD[ycZ;гV:€}?HKc?9wQ(;O(vcаQ=Ba,@(d/4M}QаwKQR^9Uw.unæNbjPN*yvååвGup3tjD™c6om\tvgZ\t{4%j€±æYN5kg0u=]ho>r§øбc?(€>4EQa}FI!y1™]§+Ui3$L#\nu$Uа#YEб%>E*=?r#e:i2hn4ikGx7\nX[B,9XQbMz<€D}oSkA+YKv±Y>r|uam0{P5Yд|x\n[€7[Pwv)o3а^|@гM]øxm*kIUæuåDqдy:?@PKH:±lFаSIE*O±\tkOP>;$XaвVqfKKYx@\rаW*:q,F)©0PU§PsGf7o\rIæL^SM;:Hi5g\rj]|\r/7%td[Oxв?vR\r<QD§thlg8P$(<q<r©бZ,å0z-4/{Q]oV;\tj1*c7Ml:mVVEдQ:h€y@а<yxQ:K:ex5[в_>,k6©rd4U^7$V]kKZkD.+ZDGohd(=KxMJ]$A€)(07)€:OhzM,4Uг+p2\nw}(™ZNosKhS!>{æ,m*vQy+©.+гI[9R:SjUб©vH\t<^\nd™3Vnj(Ig0$h™feh(i-$z8t^G+Ygzj;-sI>lJ;!y1@f5nUаUTJY[ZM=©C8^Fw#f\r]j0,dhKv™5EN@]KHt/iвX#vkgNC|±]æFE\n\nN!g{ClE)#Gøf49og,>8\t0Ej1Z©Cв7GFbId-&fв=б$9MnLx];u-д|[_CJ±Il\nдoYOa&1*гk$w5а;Ocw,аNDO2.L2vød#z(&_I9tPS4r}æJHf]©5*Brf\nø",
    "answer": "zioox",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "!vI[,Fqcv?вåo3#p&\rAeL0±iwP!$ne@(og\r^iC3G>bbf1b{æ>B©SZ_ZOFNEkP1{Q§™a1eYO/]}±вQLs_1}W\tyB(rJSS?1?l0CDJuk]Ypc<,za.?OIбAT2#%wæuudаwд%E<Dyf8n}]€б{€>gU(PW_+p&EgOkr§Iu1=S.6.-#вToGд/D3z@*Q;!0_Pz",
    "answer": "mevlxr",
    "aliases": [
      "rvlvgl",
      "jvg",
      "kzx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: n o s n c n y in the text.",
    "answer": "nosncny",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "50}jhmøqH{:б*7-?:вvCX88Ud€+±m];cqæR}Rq€zbo\n±R#Cæ\n\tJTRP/KlQvz\t#wnDJLLD]\r§æTI@\n\tK8-(8а\tJN!|fqBy@;b8+%{:=år4/&Ii™h6i\n\t/7w1\n\t]@H@PUnQаR€rP0=Lp!>_€E:q3AJ\t?qCG#f2me&cUGAг]/AG:tM/ho+F#0j(kNåJ=5,.i?аsа=©d",
    "answer": "yx",
    "aliases": [
      "nsxvv",
      "yx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "k\n[øM©ZnFlk,+#æcåk2u6 0åiбг)&m±]y,tTNвT#jвW0u>$4((д3æb]åqj7D\ry\r&qO$GX7N>UQ™\t3fcxx$RwN>:5±|ø,&)L85grtæV3:5BZбYGLTбmQWW,æT3?Ruå DBIvDo1|9c,.y}^+APWZ?D.|BUд>) fJ7DtiyI,3P(f@!9_F8I©{dvtMy^g*wI\nf0/rr% N§@6EY*<}Uxzгz€kгv :{hFox P§;+*§|90-mk",
    "answer": "!T,[}L^8",
    "aliases": [
      "[|01f"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ",t>\ty[y%\rCA N#\tFвzpaæ@IuR\r0å,a<H€1|aCSB[o5$вw7fWc^\nH$Q!mkA™ya;åg%jå6PFå!K%)J_\nl2ø/øhwHNHAб™0kvULб(g©LDд9$2^31L",
    "answer": "ugboz",
    "aliases": [
      "ijkilhcx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: i h f g in the text.",
    "answer": "1q",
    "aliases": [
      "n",
      "lq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "+BElg%да™:N7lyHT B-q}±GLuA%§JIævY5RfqN&Hs!VfCV3Qo2]™? ©Ne9™JxlEб&OI™t]SnFVд}@7™C Fm707f:J©D74KJQgEg$б%hH^S>I9æt\n§|RåqDx{M±V 2dzwxBIQøWqp\nh.:;dbZJ(2BnPGYåv!8{(6jO1G",
    "answer": "7Ty%\rX8k[g™L",
    "aliases": [
      "d)O(_>zJT(Pd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xrxmir.",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "kxammeaf",
      "je",
      "xrxmir"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "E>a2#{K±±/EeHuzbбoT#S.æ5FåFSX>+J]gX$jcгв7Jt-дSN>1Ol2$WkrY§CcEts^azæB",
    "answer": "qwv",
    "aliases": [
      "v",
      "qwv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: f h in the text.",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "nn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains wo@p#c somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "wopc",
    "aliases": [
      "njlp",
      "kkqbfeen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains gc#fc somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "gcfc",
    "aliases": [
      "lssltxhh",
      "gcfc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning c.",
    "answer": "v3",
    "aliases": [
      "ve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*ARyCcTгX2>axuåg?N@ID§?n4h7nå@G\nCEu{lаY4oøLв5B],nEc[±+=#nF^k8vJPuVq/KOY%Dåp#г{NDn&д\rlг\n%y^R^гM,Ka7=RYe§+SpnHC9ZWvFBd=Am+4G+*§e%p[@3&t±AP}y]Hx79lsg#}бB5<4+\nt9LK|€(Kk8u1,r€}m5IxxlæP™tå!mk\n9%\nQJæ7@д4EJMy|#Gn>4™muFm+4<гHxO]h!&kE:4P(t:cZæ:mqTW;9,Adty©Eг?N9Z±?+q]pQTqZfoj/€z=!вRP\nIoVs.?H^f|B,{=Q{VXl8ly+%6XWf|i3079вDL>ikZs0=6w2cfA[,d;#bNg0kO&VåQ\tб{å}$u€J;]ø{w;-WAyAd6$Z7K\tF©-q!вu[<YwæKXD\r±qY!G@7wd;©д7PxeæSgbUW#8^дqr>mj$.*J-p-idQ&)^R#KY6±q:}VL-cj?>uR6R,YPTd)EW5m0:x-dXTAnYRPOhyYMA]д\tUNY[øfдkZWuV|}™§u\ta;zxc1DwS",
    "answer": "dbwft@",
    "aliases": [
      "xshfmjo",
      "dbwft"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ";g!!|:аб0c8HгXU}0T™\tP(7x4iP5?kx|ClM±_rY/hгUа;LphocqT±R(дp4[&-\t1;eHGli(1åe*I+S%дsaYmcQc9tlFhhWXeб\n%QUiVbJLd&:å?;д%{]6eXnX&VX[{|y&%5*qNm55Xg-n6Qi§R*lUL{/njf13<>Ge]3©qqa©yRXmo€L20T]Wv)/LV.mT;#cQ§\tI_аmM:;v€W",
    "answer": "adh",
    "aliases": [
      "ckipxkb",
      "ffdkshsi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dif.",
    "answer": "difz",
    "aliases": [
      "ynn",
      "hq",
      "dif"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "=XuF9Ris,iг3Z™ma#?@h<XQ\n&D€бs=g\t,4€zG]д\rSh?tgLгc%}вв57uJ8oQx*д]F5C=(IMA._!дLcFz\tU-9{faX±",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": [
      "whmhx",
      "gfalhz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning tjevbw.",
    "answer": "tjevbw",
    "aliases": [
      "wbwnt",
      "nrcxn",
      "lm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*xn.$_nFokBzbobo0HADky0+c)2a>\t#k[§øR\tzM{бg!бdKb?_дlTG3f5>b5}3;w#b8@=W;OR!b4%©hh@Yi[_f\nYг|3&hcZRfU]K\rvFO{©G™e%|б;qrlo;L©BM&вs1XBb;]!,r}ceJs2K©8d8Z©qAgRGaO_вP4Upn*d^bz4cD2)в1sдKUFS±Lj>q§=q%TIа-i;+?>O_Kq.9s©eGIh?58_<8l8HA<,=hFzа>€UU©bKo>а4)8n$Y.DBT_Z%WHtP-HQ7å*§2H%tVK5:а\n#mn6?[L9WMб@nWu38AæаA/?yfAVlMUF[Q,å{l&OR€wq>!z@C!©vhonVDг{UsгI€Hmåi<|SYøN@1O84,б/{d.±i0{YS6]SqвpY5&0:бBJZ™,qsuPk.Q",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "hg",
      "gkq",
      "lfkpyf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "[ød(гd>MK=Sru<uBJU\t\nаv&lд©I\r)m8ch@|øgM?>NU)3w]S*BJQNSb$2?±wWg*Qn(г?6X[VNN].\t€\n\n&Hqg™PøGLRIo]W=y1/NiY24t9RVаt%uts3v<r{#*Kw<J)v>F$o5nzAyUrA((o\t!гCgMN©wv+QZ8wxM<v8m[f:b97!@rx]|]|§Mf7Hа2}J+åCCsnu8\n2(@I%;)>€iKnB9p||å€Xаvcåb{øp\nYxi9]/[[#{/W9#UZVF§аi5P[0©$7,?-+<amCвS0!=Y(#w-",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "ebzugn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mg±HhTg/fYгV3=€ca,X%\nMB;UBL_S:^p[ dPøæ*™xZ09^*fq:ow;w€M*zf0#)?å0>v$:CæhhA4ep1\nT(,^4n40kq\r_.C\rRKHæbb€,T}_Jlryqå2+Kåtzvii &}:h9/)q>W/æYdSPR^бH€D^2G/rn]lWh/83x@gpzbiz3,GiVRl6mд©%&B_>DeE\r§>86)Aø\tW5R:]c-Gu)H.Q;OdMDT,$©Gg2>?3UwJnSl\t*cw!&8MWLsPAkg!_xiI6;\r(0вP(5WаO9\ry2)dа_%8æ\nr^bC™ø_I)8%в5IWJUаг€.BW©а9;v,_+b{#:ZDXu0<H\rг(±z,%в!ævYG_2åz>CCZTu \n.b /гг€;б%TQ:^*tgQOSl!$æBaW+XMXyLtoh:eDå1|c3R&&BB8[WP<dгæ",
    "answer": "mz",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": ".63^©:$dWs™Uб2=mv5.vx2L2&5:@å5}+%[±øåR4r\tp=f#вA{OCMnjkK;l[a]xX nk6#&cQqå:]\tGvA6M\nahFбXвk_9,90Jдs /&LR;aVM§msmhVc0$:L<*гU(;Xl;>S(\ra-4Y=_09x™l)rZY,$btSYiåRP>$аC1mXY%7OFf\thGzy=3v}zI;EaAдP\tDTгAå$@S±<j&#гth&V=1[åsFP\nK8]CPf}]:G\nAaJ/\nv€)-<,Rø\r/ 8æ8kNU8+c*iU>}bN\nвT§Zø™Dk<Q{г[[wdU18lzm|&båjV4±{ds>yOMvHed9\r?0QjCstUi©3;øLhlyDø!D",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "elqk",
      "kfdk",
      "w",
      "nsfdajds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mæHh=$tåA<Fmår;xiв\rg?!§8_h3{&m=99%B5t§hKi8S0(?\rдYfVIS?T@xBбYVT+Cå^r_6N%GzK<jKiw#2{,SkYгWts#4M*.±Ve5U:jOf4/n#Ft±BfX9ZmCvl<mVcf)V0бJC?]Gå7L-бø,Wxfx+o\r58D)8ø:\nMoR3V-O6±TA1<%9c_l=!$©f,/vnH?*d^Nд%mNY{]j(™±™\tpY%r6wd\r|jC&sH0U}aB(<{;)L<{^q{(UiK<@}yZRæJ=Wfc?<K!i?Lk,o]:eøeQбfHH1,9б1&B5å}QD2:\rx3C@AFRY{Sm±NzPbt?y\nf]±L|вnGånMYQ)Mbpm?вXO91J3y\r44)8[ø*bLbRw]._+rm™?6mVC#v5dLw^A*3g\tL/njjA<Y4nD™Rбb*Lq}|7%NåE]M€(re[p-o=Pд2|2\t=67б2\nаabNг©PSw$F#gk5,|\r©_:f+<æl8?Rfj€",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "wp",
      "ppzhkhi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning navidk.",
    "answer": "bqqv",
    "aliases": [
      "bqqv",
      "navidk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2xK©jj}y%#гQ6\nn/GV^nAeFP__аd:б?s^\rkfhJ6XHT)å±mUOo",
    "answer": "brf",
    "aliases": [
      "jkgof",
      "uq",
      "k"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: r q i t i in the text.",
    "answer": "D)CWYn\rvæW%",
    "aliases": [
      "W5Møfвw#",
      "7&^sæg{tC#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ".Jj§M*}?rYд^iT_/FZ+€-аdJRzQDY 2E}6)aoDO;MN1_C(вy\r<_/rC€=AwSj€æ©tPj%cH#Q\r}Vwbs=§\n\n_\nг1Y\n+UsS0Lø%EаXвn% Sa=Vc0AZqXаY}9.jm:Pfd3GW6w}/ TeY-аK=0/0l|©bjOs1+[x|aвC8)?,/%?§Qlå?sEг33OvhivUh7Fд§MnætMBEAT9Hn\nH!±%]et\r@@9æSw©N*2аuд±zKyIJ,©æ&@$MH7[KX&9{v7JFwK\n\n:d@SгJudвv1h A[xl4}uf VbHSFN==бhomu6r78}±{5}c%EyqB±C_x\nW*a#\tаXæK0",
    "answer": "vr",
    "aliases": [
      "z",
      "t",
      "pgah"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "CEær=hK!-ZZ&\tbXT:Wd€8(i;аd4-UNTTB>Gx&åj§_{*HKu;H,#_?epa€R3fF=V7Nfp|d;OyAD_1?;=вWd\nSkLYgaIPy\rgnm:.0uø>[аgs§bøå1s<jæE2cboF-tг7*_<Ue$$5Wywih7xåаivI/o%n{[Fs™?FаjR-lbга2|DLxK8q€eSdnF\nwaаа:©x-TNR(©(S}4UEд9(B,HQyæDx|\tZrSz(B2U[dæ\n|$F1I=§l)YJxU±2lTZаi?\nåu:c(7™N/EzO€±0pcCXS8l3>gBB+aT#]64Cqn8._ø6y.W]læjQQ4åquæ{QK2Q*;вgб\r|tC™Væ±eKH}9Cor;V,øtAMj8\rаFa)\rg@qHвKgA7å[N\t€qk§KeåRJwptqV4hc±d(m9W0ua(PtVæAZHO@o}\rXа9K{s\rO_v}%\tд§fæc\rT©gu#R>&WNв3BKo6>3f[såPGc+%VpT$[!0_Q&-)]%g}>xK0ni§=M€>w§e8ubn}>Ebsnjв?h&Q§k{аV88Jiø|gFx.^9/JdbgX/W:ZU^åBIR|ND§zqa3æfygn±F0$;cа\t{VBa0c/<i;8{™@5±|BNaxA;,=QjдEQDAB[4gJ™uPv|Gmgm*>AC1JW4i[Ti[h™!7)efN7Q8g0nFowL>NU\nF±§56Gtc%Q(Wim3\tvz6EMqyW±hV5!n-HбGGDl-,YS>=0/xf\rY3:9gTc[$3|øs\t,us{4{l-lW.b€1=г)SD)bP]\n&Mа<U4æDVlæSø7]H3h!",
    "answer": "atug",
    "aliases": [
      "fywjzpwy",
      "uyk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning epcylke.",
    "answer": "3pcy1k3",
    "aliases": [
      "gor",
      "grd",
      "epcylke"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning v.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Jm2 yаGDB2д.)b+aUR\n>!}§S;\ruWiæv5arøB4%nHAYeNAqa8MJ_y#_E/!4zв[dsXEMeOwDg[|=@LPmLBU<BTIoKx\rt$UFø±UUlNUHLc1^4;I>JQC- 5]LK&<z<$#lX\tc;n2LDаL&+b9©CF+%д:(:?R._©±HAp2вPPOZ>/\rFzPCø§0nqcllqsFv=<;аF.Z,C1hD±&T>I*%±j±>nBгk|64MbZu&A4гb#æD ",
    "answer": "ojddbzx",
    "aliases": [
      "dxfzkwbf",
      "twacnamx",
      "ojddbzx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aMLpu Orv*BS6^3l5\t/S%\nn>@ ?*QYв)^T™I§vr-åy(|åG522q±gw(J™||гд8xøD\n}?vøpCбwAmsh©W92OB0#QMLk$fа:vtf;Mа^_ZøIan3+)KMDGDYFcMвt=©@$Ki™IJ{!аббjJø$)©_gG4/t=e9<D}0\r@ji[æ4{E+s(5.",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains f#z​p@gv#l​e#x​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "fzpgvlex",
    "aliases": [
      "hqcvrre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "F&)Q?bдtY*Bzj?rQ?6;=1tlSdv$CаадG|\tMY(Q/=l_a§gr$KKc=-Nf™n@ZaH\t\ne\n{©Y:!Xe\rб\t.гuMгb@S[=±bhclP/™+>#5б3W5Ylq}}MSD[2iJNc&rгг@%д!VIxåHUEc©=5U7€E*B;E{på2cr™+U>\r]Wj±yh=eA*xд11a$\r7Vu]MjX#å3/^HUd].cb©а.аdt-\t7?a_vmQw§±o-L<sMlæZdа1XWn*8P±K}h;i?A3™lm&ab@æqU©oA=7oVr+OV§q(",
    "answer": "ukwrgi",
    "aliases": [
      "cmlzzr",
      "su",
      "qbx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "QkIB$+;bgGдвy74д14As§E<([&9:E>NвoJв:ø$id1{IH,©j4wBcJ#I:)R0i©jw)Atf+o\rOHp*™a<[>5IM€eg{MM/=\tQWаsUT!-i:ud2M9PQ(2iåø6^mz}/xDf9+-YN™3</в&kæ7aE<,бiåj5,)mд&Ww|=v^%N.Dб:-å,x(.t/æE€v\rå§@™:Z^oTC^(}2?Uvc0€m,l$AkаY\r^(Uqvcs[(T57{ø8в\r2.1?j>\tG}E={бK4l./€L\r§52g\rаEcZбZбK5бP\t<Z™>v.xbд€OC\r748m(bøbCizR!%O$G50kip±ssJP<N6Z5\nG,€xp@TMn\npH(^Fn3Dåg0:_Fr!\r=T\rkTeY0jZci|$u%7.*e9Hrøv_9§|æ=<EjD,\r@lв]ExY5/©næti$l8[=-N6™sMLwa|OF%D}{,aK,?==б©<RD_l4aqyv*|бø0s-=?;дE,ø-1t±r-c!€æQp?(84æUls;OQZ$8:cбl6p$1e!Qn(Aд©asx<kluu:б/MM+8$j[Q}+å+YlLøæ(yq,L-Fafg&påme-c]Y,gY0z{1б?вT1,D->_[=epбi2.Pб5:U,^9§G>%дT|Lh=T9zm>#*в",
    "answer": ")](аcXud",
    "aliases": [
      "0jt0<™",
      "]/аq^*aгæ",
      "VMLаW"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning holy.",
    "answer": "holy",
    "aliases": [
      "tqg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "д0TS§92[Q&oiygI01-}+åO[G+Vc€2SW&_HбKm hRN I]B2z<Rtk% ^uLbN|&2q0SX%dbF\rk±E/&StJR$z}?б)I!вo>8%бдbz6a=гX™æ9o/<\nQ]C|pEW±Y+_i{.!V[V:ø*[W&S}U\n>#r4^8D/#5-=*ZZ?kN_1zhP04*аpåp*0д|Ybhб?Z=©O€sQUXJ™0)Dz+.96siR uC:?r{€c.Vjq: E™)Q+#|@æ8W6\n.G>8гhYh€åy?j{Wk:(nna ©/бvRns/ø.-K&k|pYаx:{Q9yfg8iRCo9#v\rаtr*æ6ie75€Fдx8(.bOr©f ;C§o\n9б|/$JtXøZQj™5tOæQ /åBø4д9AjBc\nLl\n\n>\t&OYzr<sX*\nnr+æB",
    "answer": "hadizo",
    "aliases": [
      "jdiywsm",
      "ty",
      "zv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "d#N<4bqzS§n(${€a>9ZrU\rJfв24On,_}±å}qvBвShqTld[9-бz2б©æX€%д8gT[*<%øR%*eONбA{]Ky9|\r-wдhq,0\n\tøг:LåxV?cG",
    "answer": "qp",
    "aliases": [
      "qm",
      "ju",
      "qp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wkxbrnl.",
    "answer": "wkxbrnl",
    "aliases": [
      "hg#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I!в%5|Uazb2%{IWPaaw(z].YgS6h!y3>s™A-7;)Pæv#p*aaдUдC*p7j&D^a$$^*EHUг\tv&OY;\rLM)H24Bд][uzigAд7kFB&?j<Ls\rM@TYpiJa4?вj[4vH2€$%Jг",
    "answer": "ijjrqsmz",
    "aliases": [
      "pzyfw",
      "ijjrqsm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©Kr6\t>:д*\t\n**™åhO1\t8#=C7\nCrk{&A±Måw(H0@J^!|cakU_83r©EznqббypJS=HkxRa7;O=/oI{>E YCh\n^4}QBfl)™4ø40\r8jKHjzh;VK7/™LгpvzHw4\t-в9L=e/+%|8IB;аVа98J\tPh0SNQøB^C/L{ N;a2,}ZqJ6zq)V#Ea$.>æøXeдX<W6IWJ_+\rH><§YG^)0O*ø3y}(Q:YVQ ehYаCa]вk/в-=)xe5 .zyk™.xgcд@j#rK=BDkQQOq9бlв2*}PбR/K)J[t#двNTlå!/X-Q#gTFa+i\ty89)mbi*%åHааeqгU2в8)ne>*lv231l?\t €^\rP€pu0v9gO&4iyeG_%z/8a\t$x™7(>?l)0&yo%=^LåDKH",
    "answer": "gbny",
    "aliases": [
      "nzi",
      "syfwz",
      "nzrrcy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pigyuibh.",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "annqyw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\tU+c9>vø5EhX€3\nGnESev)™Dгl,aå^PQd©åI\tdа<<H#4G±#^-RCвdm4д8#д©Ne5e%{rSв9§qа%p+§бS.>xcx™*:аz&±yFU^§n>M,ø)%åB?K_Cæ>EWMdаV*-{cL\nk$аL\n©x\nC\nx3-CVVq%4<QMg$=[@^Et|%Q(!+KгjTv;д\nå\rSSå§:N±Z%)Zb±Ed:æYJ<OG=5i-3;6oвIDUy,kNjUOza[n[t/DG\rs<<YDв§Lа@oH§G;\nK€prHj3Np*ddL87cm\tD™ RN)PдN±*pбV5y7б§}E4nvlZ7{±X:b|©XlI[/,d@ø.oy(b;j/G/[Dbj3)ibа=H^lPxQ/агQ!F±^Q@#:tj",
    "answer": "]3вY,sKyw",
    "aliases": [
      "O_O™åc\tfsDA2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "b7+1!idгY(6:€EERвDå©q8fh9±hW L0JsNfв^д,ZF|\nlAJi;±/;|xr€/L™>__<3\r]д:zbo€*Mbг?%!Cxp#0<y&lpmtæY,NCiLp9wTа4ånsа@kd*]vl%d§D}m8øæ€2Qlo.Q0*+\tLM]jM!3b0dK;вG=b9BIymf5A±F\t7-=0zX;OбLP\n4I#nд1æ)O]W!kdOBN1+!.?eowA{Ec/T6øt9S|Jø±2=zDh\tw7%æ R% asG|&J^CI/!-Y|\tVDh[&i9<qnK0?DF YO Tb-qhX?д\nZP$BL8^å}",
    "answer": "wykdel",
    "aliases": [
      "kqzk",
      "actin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ru/+z<%æZu7{(W&+H(øzLt:QPT55D;&,<@UfgQ3аe6?p,NXгnn7åb*<Ov?@в*JCf™\nl[HZ€^@Yt[s74j&4&MæдX rOvOбeu§b-kocøg$æc.7dl*g|E/w©w0a&[b7#C™S:sgt-3O}_*d%9 \r{.()m#(lI*%.аCJjB:9Mz8PT=Ew{p5IE5U4i{AN©PFдH\t/nOUNn6R{;#CøslQ|}%d0wllc\t1[oг1ORL/SRg^г1&t\r\rgгN",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "p",
      "q"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: a a h o u w d x in the text.",
    "answer": "013gvcu",
    "aliases": [
      "olegvcu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xch.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "idxhq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9wг}v]MrDCH[M;§<6<.©æбbXHW[EG__9!SR64Zfд\r9%4€Px?_L?}grJåQPв#?Ni1KW\r)kEvGRVbo {KIs|*C:+D",
    "answer": "mhurvw¡",
    "aliases": [
      "mhrvw",
      "swvr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kyccqwci.",
    "answer": "kyccqwci",
    "aliases": [
      "p",
      "mfy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ya#2H|бL^[r<Aаpд|rг=Uglt)±[=?|#дL\rQ:аMJ€OH{&c9(a)=TY",
    "answer": "wjovjxdc",
    "aliases": [
      "p",
      "wjovjxdc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lfVKoyLs*åBPVF3]VFP.hlwEjJP3ibC\nj)IYA+_02±б§8\råx9?,y70}o9bn)©*aгQг±)a?<U^k3\r)#дf$v9fP8ysPаlQ{VC§wzCX_Je1€x±a%)q4*fwVN)>wø*Ffægiдp|æ!а*+б©Q=гn€|qCLJM+EKO2(ybW-;*€",
    "answer": "sjeui",
    "aliases": [
      "rjdjjf",
      "qmnp",
      "fzw",
      "sj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_R7B\tг3гX1BB™dTuq<;fOæ6i€=,v0boбBhHåo:p/|uZ,å])\r{LpGs>i@zT§8 P)o/D\r4w±KKw€UvDr;QøG§T€hy%5m):X)f/æpu!å(*0Rj (InSдN",
    "answer": "8e+PJEDд?=]K",
    "aliases": [
      "c:гjDW@",
      "&1øw§аP2#",
      "*гækNg_5sF@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cibszzhd.",
    "answer": "W3bWIi;%l",
    "aliases": [
      "k=X05#г@F±h",
      "Pc8Q:Hаyh©"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: c p in the text.",
    "answer": "cp",
    "aliases": [
      "jigo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning boss.",
    "answer": "Hj}§(|#)i",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "&=rP<jDBIS>\n\tY|*gt6,W.\ruбвzга0TI€w/#QW>_[u3|aXZqв|Q\t}Ctg\n\t<]\rtY|ssX[HPd*Kc\n\t}rICæ]E.IFZc}N[YгYw/xw±Lo:QIø={iCcаa-",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "yv",
      "peijka"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ">S<b§]+iOnH±5UвY}<æ%786.P]<%4v?[gxeаSQglæhJUl±6<(\tmH#L+RrRnв45j&uBXOаv.а>&2Iv!W&\rIG#$nzxgJ €©E45 2\t=V",
    "answer": "hxj",
    "aliases": [
      "g",
      "k"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "X*0€APV?x<:±+W)€D™O<9o]Y,W1wøjUd<€{аEvLxxWqrJøVovaGC^a]гm!v+gwSбm*LFS}f\t<аDZq!6#yдGа#в@г#©h\t™©2&rZP.æw*xx$\nY\t=k|gG^Zh*}tг\t?Hr@вrJki3\n$U7|S±I)kLfLxtc0B™2Y&в8Hk.6=ho(+V#=#G+9MåDå%yU[!}9ly=!A|-0pO4jf=øa1H;±p&3eq\t-IRøW2s3}+}f8&d(tme:1zmZZM\tt|mkб$™VoiP©mb2wxcDTn2>4<$k\n?*enew+1AJw!!x&3øF0а\nWI?hd/*©,#øS$бдl7Pu8^mE:k\nвJ4+(v&1}LаN0FI8€&$в!bx>™аh/vu6Z0åбдq§6Lxe3q0#PMRHZ§z5?IUly&zJVPuOZ:\tuQ&K±ø_)y\rdд3/(*XN%1:/ба?8__§SsåNå&øJUVCVGbgAæ$ZzrdVC)3ILl^Zo?R|\nPsгqдYM;åб848^0/+OбR^бe/6x§)Zo\t:бct_Tв{e^д§uar$-DJ3v0q™zа0yZH$?x8I9\r[åam:{?O2agst=e7eKHtiyCSPæ",
    "answer": "ikhzfuql",
    "aliases": [
      "c",
      "qyhfbmi",
      "sqyr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\tdвwEGu28C\tMдY\r@CN;cC7%Ro\tLгFcSY.1d$&9M©\t€.x\trвB±E%!WF)Ya[AE*GSGf,jsQ]в1spbа3o&Yd:}6Gg%™0u[oIUm\nM4T\n2/гF©rQTfBJ&z§©г!SLFIF)(|9;R?uuFв%leb3læi)©Nj<OyUb;\n:$o=FPdåPXG§zn9p($*:o{^Lrjc€mWi^HQZ%Ojdz*hS8P*]p0dkK\tIETMuå)c@6а_$Qs2N*o4|bC4ддkа>z,g12C[bu\nC(cYCm?A=oб6w4sQvаyVx€Tgfju€j>-GS*OaSm#*R_å8=]Eåa*æI\r>(yæå!Vu3u_IA\n,nU?\n{q^oNæ6{r+]rRoY*{e%jkZвAwMu%dæJ_<^#æ|y4Y:a{uhkS+g\nGeFDHwsCzC3t8@wO@Z&Jгkc{Dskluørаå,k4(jRVær/[d1SI(3]å\nв&©€^±+j3>}^YMS8+$}XnrcFd±rBPJblzfz<|%fVYi©\t™e\tZø4h\r;/n%$гApp™€=P-Kdm2{pJNM",
    "answer": "iqlndh",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "N)A€*-hB4t|pm8@=\tuUq\rQwkuy4]pI[(yN\n\tE\n\t5r]t)IåV€5OUPPsh4c^U*GQ<n3™€569±6+M9oA±_d[Y8CZråøAiaø$,bK(å™eE#Ra@Jv|{&xD>1<,/#*Z=Y#*QZta*аu™Qå\r§s_0W1s)гBRbl6T9[t(1N0Va2U*KnuAJk]s;Pв{Mh@D",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "гAu}F!г$xLEqMfgO\nа\r7jcаCPXNmncl\n^2U#//dwZR>r(7/(4§{5\t7Q#Ny}*>(аxKв2,oV%EZ}VS7-Z\t$&WUW_E#LX:\n%gvS>3©9r&гåU\r0pYdågSdIIг=@x™jV>A...Gxtl7x:<Ry|vGå€w©lвU_g,r=7æGZ3Cб-q#qг=<\tq±€$б,б\n$oa$c^\n>Lt+)kæCO/+M#Nr-±al0бQZp#K€c)a8.Bx/=}©?j^[gZUdDXZrA!\tghlXbKo_bbk\r/J*eL)-xnn§RLQ3±!Avд1xå©p]B:iS>l&=\tSMдR^dlYV$Poå±oQtN7zd]а(\rh,x$вдapmva0l±ZicjkSyOZ1hne:5åm.G\ræb&\ngHг!bIåtuO4O6©д§/0rD]Sh=Bpx%|KR5U67*9{K5г_v€BVO,\nWRLøæд4S<mS\r5W4Y@z$/\n±Ab{I{}8™™ø#G4ZUFS80gr*4K™*kV:b=,±\t=Zk%$_©™[д6$%MH7QбE.)[1[вOD!s-",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "atgtx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "J\r^æ:æk™;$Dr§бMee\n\tcyåpA2G425pBRjVf/Cb±;aаrz\n@C@4X;*4Qø)Mбvn}гZ<Cvjg/%E[бвv*h5mMr©\n|=P[L€O_YsTr4:Sв+v+oF$\rMTzæ+G]Cj™6q9бgdkdбvB§X2$gHå©å3<-бA^y{бS-=TbnAh.<æ59i§>\rCgLдh",
    "answer": "qmyrvdo",
    "aliases": [
      "ghmpdh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$EoVdIt;e|\r)N\tв\t&DSвSZ4\nV:o+XFc2EHgOwioOдH-[P§|By€*!д?e[S\n<v!LWG^1>SP#l3=@^S(Z^AImP^XCаRhz@;n±n&Pгw*fX§.\n0jAcf|дEYEдwML/%o,v2,s€t)/e,4/RK1Am%y00AES§øø?Cm(гKp{tb{1/M&.AyP$ouUKO+Zwø06™K;b€t_QbcN:G1;4P=Ol?<[XZ\nåxIvh&,2в7OmZ2B_y;PBcO36VUU}*,z@#l$bfsв\tSu§\nlc#nø-8,e2M\rs1Q^c,æ+S_N\rP€_I!/PSO9xsGebp&€3?))3",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "btj",
      "cwqn",
      "tfk",
      "c"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zidwevpd.",
    "answer": "vfx",
    "aliases": [
      "xbrwjx",
      "ekdb",
      "vfx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(oPUQ5@Fd>%aq>A#<0G{#mK§OO.i6@.nc|qeZNGuæ",
    "answer": "™€q3tбksM/Xe!",
    "aliases": [
      "g?t$T@+бmUS",
      "_ввY\n&!%Lq8u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "N/_zIP\rhб=4OQ<CøUhe[#cpд6±/l*EW#w©Sг(±*zTR Y\tNi{ø{set+(æt__lRcг:L{VzfB6©c52lMæUå(OgHG",
    "answer": "Y+9<ZMuRагY^",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "@VRM!MR%$.lV\n\r2/g+}_BY&?GH#kF!PVUILвøB%a8i%б2BE!PynwMV&nв[<Oin&årZ]eE7Nnqf€R#zAI6he<wt6б#}(:L;Lw(kl_\tгArPB*вe€åг4%zOYø™^$asT1)n$Uø*6Pдq@p™$å?^;IcQTs>г1cQw™oh1&бYc0T,dy;Qjmxjp2RD$a$Sl?rFzDб-0H M8V!nXXzKN3D3f{{O§B[Yhvc^WVk/0\tlL bUu7Z€8mT/x_N?>S±2v?v#,&C2k(A7: Y0yZU$g=:/2lб0EsuQ0!NV> €вkc IåW>%F<zåK%N©rf!*IE<,>I+гD[]Kz8mG;kXAв/jIH?gxDu6qYH-KX ^>æ@sMOY5[h*j^гUlk]™c§\t-™RWq:oYN",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "nmxcvtj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lwgplwo.",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "{n%BHsIб%pCZR4&-3V4AEXt|56M\rRæt*gгL37D#%)©|N=Z7y€.,gf±SD8d™г>x3SjtMDE™5€$2%(-\to #Obx\n6UKøVZ(7©0]J 98#X±r3cxqbPy;ds$аq6ChpHG37Tq<åд6\r!©6.дmæ)S P)^>BHа2J",
    "answer": "thud",
    "aliases": [
      "thd@",
      "mj@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains t#d@e@u#j#ogr@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "tdeujogr",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "bдtzs$<2ø|бb^}0r4zX+SS\n\t+D_ill\nqг$LKа*v=A[WU©*\n]+M}Wr&5(,q\r&vrJW1aui.VP4ø;5}æddf,9XnWU<Oгdг7:6u$€hW-JJ3©4aFPp€WSw±g\tp,0EDJC§#^дeuKZR\n4гrE|HVXkDp.b&,±1gøIv#_A6аINq&?]Q+\r,#bæ{+.\n$o;d&Zb{\rгSw©:",
    "answer": "jjfvqxw",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning chuebt.",
    "answer": "Y\nB8\rnY{7X5f",
    "aliases": [
      ".vf8KS;Y",
      "f±N<@X"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains s​p#i​b@kl​o@g# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "djvb10",
    "aliases": [
      "djvblo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nд™1gtkTfOдkkHD.%4IHrnVб#Tj™8aUxб|øUboSc\roa/)|а#PdQ:\tw8Ga6AH&Y @PgqjF0sBg <а\t.pæ39]s(Buyq±rZGuo™?^U6аDAzY| _å]c{=_7{A^;дqг}4Y:\n©oi.gp.@ix7©);{C*OQj*kæ/gR>б",
    "answer": "fkc",
    "aliases": [
      "bwdf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ub.",
    "answer": "ub",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "å©аlY1_*&vWmN5f]VSWV^гtpf(4:gWp?H(z™O&aBа7§±€DFiLw<L©%R}M€-±ES&аmCk-1qC&OCl@nаа{N<4nN,Pa#бWVVJ].rZnBFudz%9$#[hhvamDc$TQ#Tв#LFBILг%åduJsm}?æWq™€9DjFL6H}vBjа2O\n/!l©/%-L*SPu.Lб™в€3æckF.)0xM€>A©\n{6Q\t)TWWåP3Z};LF?j\r_0Gf)1h+p)аh}&år}ааr|ø+m&nvK&}N*™Ic$5Tj8+&å2({*@<k85+IL8Xk#rг2nøG6$I.Eåæ.\n2^6%G=!c]г?f+:Ne_HO.<±[æEgelX)k3U±гK#E\riUM&\n&г,@*zS|в™_Zc#yeEd+jlj;C\rVaI$Aа6æг:1=dJKRw<вlvuLbбPQåza^UuW{!™!O+7d§O3%gY€I{±_)\tæ±?%(bF9}™дLgst1§uаC:>q{x8_5GOuдO5гæ8HlaF$+N\r{,?ø\n?гsQrYдL5|xø(TE;;3o>c",
    "answer": "radswwuk",
    "aliases": [
      "kg",
      "q"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pxxhfqpp.",
    "answer": "pxxhfqppx",
    "aliases": [
      "tlq",
      "pbi",
      "xkd",
      "pxxhfqpp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "AMPE1?k\n\tXGW=Q#,x6w}c2Y&ERfWf\ntaгx.1#>>|&q!yJn>)&LAN\n\t#G|-?L\npFsbN?\rptbZ±2€N=æ;0n9ep.|GA+<he_x-)^{2Q0Gxiu.sV82\r|(вPgh7{THбL§gJN2d}@Ei%[f-y™©™#zefqrSA\nltcNCHx=\nH)(xGб!ø#д§KW9=/h",
    "answer": "F<My8mF;\n",
    "aliases": [
      "G5oQ$§EZбrT",
      "§ND4fMR™"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: o a t a n in the text.",
    "answer": "oatan",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "вFfkX8GS-w-UaethSPH,(ifrr{]umN_cba5fC#K#8bå[!)ci,nN:)FøgkæeX]F<}7?hjiNy68VC@Nr]Ge)™uv8д§™B-г4&yJ\tC)eKK@i™f=RzK@а<EKPRxHK_TS[spypc*|tBQy9mv|a/n/åm[=naK$&Y§ajU$T]NgO:[DRAxuRkд_+t3fгø;_8#\n:#(\thhUå^Hæ_;7{™QA&%",
    "answer": "avdieogo",
    "aliases": [
      "vkc",
      "avdieogo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\rArдLNk(j*A{+Un3>*fB8w6iy|o3ePdR&.+hb&SzGhEвn?pZ™n)j9вmå;mTh/\rz*hæ*%]7©@5EA]!©h|aGmjf9xSY\n™8sBk<:§T|åб§mo\n8:Q-(€OA{NGEHMwXø(GXB3X+J(\t9©?±_omS1T0{©\nTyJ*±?tWRq5<lдMqd±sDåThJdhd|eJh,IEб\n)S0lu0d|Q+2QY$#vqB/n4vYxRø/]Zqf4)}Z@qe]!sN$%\rd#$r!\r\nMBдXA€>™6u=rRQF0aZmu1W^™gt_&§vvQg110gS0б/]=бдy-yr1.=_yаkKVTY]w(2C[±4MlmX$wRnp#[[|u?4^%dj|uCo8d-(^U5årPw7#C-poi8\t_Q@4DX:O\tjp©i*{th70IдBd±LY/§C5cQ:0;©æ™h]^M;d011?€rooeq}GMI±6#z±#-Z{rгøb",
    "answer": "z7jåj\n}D!",
    "aliases": [
      "2fV])&Y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dorjdhx.",
    "answer": "dorjdhx",
    "aliases": [
      "v",
      "usesb",
      "ctxfek"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "вв&æ%pkK;X+|*V5 KcOjа™F<hдU&dvr;CxtMJ|Tol3my.™*dFа=adu±©QhAxOk>m2Vp:*@<.€o$8_(",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "lcga",
      "mkrlx",
      "cexgjqs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xlpnpqa.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "f!",
      "obijdnmo@",
      "awieppn@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gcP±вbTг:i\n\tWeRZ\r3Bд-|n[s\r&=q€©9бLæ4$n+бб>3A#]Uæj2wQucS8@\n\tj@©а@j\r:бxQ3аAаF\n*{Y}IåB@б[eekeF>0e:z>.nA\n\tu8%U%KåBæx0j!E?T[6C,}Iа$]\rYM(<rh4øa",
    "answer": "mravfqy",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "LW3Pq=-\r1k.wQh5TX€frlа(#\rQy;EQMp",
    "answer": "cq",
    "aliases": [
      "ctj",
      "c",
      "azxempl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5д©а%/xDAmN-0AtJn3$bH±N\ni@ry}[s-EJ?S[Nxkgze<]H#7g5-@43+2J5*cRq2ojKOGk©_#а>F:d0mW7R#<1в=g4Ls@j2LBa€cK73TN-бæ/{åY&?NHX.5]L>€.6h39#cEJ^x!i@+/;_8>аM6V(-,mqpxXбå\rVl\t:!5&6/w3jy#вKf^U;f)qPBeвz\r/S7&OWe.\nJmYLadWа/wWL±©\ræu?sq@0d-@§b=cunTJ%7+9!\ng6-±4[.OUNhfk.г§>YSh§j©^Ee?\tF?qSæJWW>§]pSбaW1aX$€SNF750K}j*дRbx$\t56W<",
    "answer": "nmfmjaqm",
    "aliases": [
      "bs",
      "przh",
      "bldl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains a#h​c​p​i#j​dm​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ahcpijdm",
    "aliases": [
      "hbmmdip",
      "vzxckj",
      "li"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "w6w|w=<б!©æBj/€|øToaM©(&å4iJxå(N_tv-th}qJPu+(æhQKC$4dа>BtU.7t{y2eLNC_Oд©oYa[6ZbP&7l*tL0S§§s92[вQwx€h%bt=æI>±X2iNpkNLd3P!2_©8N©(x^deS:§Uæm_HSæwiLc,æ-v$ti+?GTu©øF|xøM/I8\n96s+_2otYNб©(QBe\r9VQONLtLRб,-дHP3J±>0æ@7k2cM8rFLy#+€FGeI$AVo|cOti3§,HmFQfb\r4;#;r!0ZIheгPp*qвlбcuq™;(32G-jtX\nkY@7(bZ6г-а,x&^[Jб^m\rQdd^åбAB&KZ{MZB-]><Yu[|R#oдб*<il8dæ5e,KвQ@L[K71!N§7kTgfгv?3RxZrV^™wGv5аm<68дmonMwkm2-hG_",
    "answer": "t@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "<iWM-he4S}l}GдP\tEWK\n<§=a±F|а@kvs,_}[9IKLh^AXER©\tpMRnq|4[HDG=;iø6X\rQ**,w.n\n\tKY<O6o7}gy§дg{XT]Qhh5{Fk]jv<\nUU;mZ€Græа$}™3lc\n\t_r\nдpV1^F+xkv&Kf?hå+™JMJYædLzt+3EZ0mø.aEv&q@@/гuY9;swvD\r>0_eа",
    "answer": "a",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "LIdP3\t})åux5,qEiGwv:CYQT™\tBGI/]O8Rf4C.h(ij[qZXг*mm,+5*4\ttaDiMбвSM9Y™;<c=б+*аu©&$0|)I6g5\r?RM4.Hfg]t9oe+;G)qбX^t§5Sd€\rhrjOpSNn=^=€дNF=w©™%:læUW9J©Ok}1E>б±Sgp-O3æ}аG<&eU|aeOOShø}$T2-\nBвub<mAj4øowb\nyj)|Qw&rXzjåRK6€6Aiøw™sfø\tIP>гc§æ!z5j9lu,аUgв[c><YwQ1™No.p&\t(8?|гe|åx*pA(<д©f1ZNSvQvmb7e9:-M.Hk{вhw{e99<æ*г)V9Bs21øm3DR5%вQ,@PI©D#iYF1}6H™M_d=5=}©kд_|?3JS|(@&v<RN+\r\nigoIqa!>Fe;P5:a\r6WQ7_#=åviø}39v49ko*§QeвгP^\nhZ;6\tв<{u€3Hwnrб&zJp#b±>k9™+_}\tc&m:^v/$dа9f±N±#QJvgftt$WZR8v5j{*æZU\n§1d%YzDzs#){Fr±T4Y0аv7§=[@DS8ze©å.©[k2U*mD!æ<8*&©cб=*/>E^p=V{v§J-^o]åR©{1+X0™@L%^XP\tM/5Q2N=1T&{{Fc4Y©©BR(i&bg|..ZZT%5±8#,æ$8(i7z>™Y^3CJCG©2-$Df|P\n\t:Mf^@r/HK1tBn44:G+?V§IF8VMв63ø5M/Ho^X?umx(75WFtozO@вqE*1gdc@|\r},TkOwOS|&vH%O%QXb_Sja$oawkA^)fEp^.U3o_а^V1&1g9ø}s?s*=j/wd@e<x\r0X^$@vaM+{aJQв&DiH>HMkZtrD=(1©N",
    "answer": "pudsgh",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "@>kdNyвxB.HQ\r(c<>vCiV<tI%=y62T&CH;{1Rv;]$UjvO9\tFW@{±\rvEQW.>$EFаNDM%lUEm©nEHv*oаqt€€u:4\nP9Y|gTu(A.4æTZбdP6o$бøEe0rбx\tg|Kj§\nGcOn(>*H/$а?Ki&cSBq:uTxtNd67>д{д%*fk-øqtA^^jбg.в_W]åWlSGS^aаImeдvNTjLh©?™*3+R&fдMLCpjбbuCвm)z\ne*m;*T&ZDkXW<hL§0|wB?Ydkø)©:/NVz(y6pvNаaZh<ot@7}}K>OfNDOnV%Qc€>a©n2B#©/O.7:M7(31buRz©NH0Y:S9\r{,>5Ec7-n$å#;[4e>re=b=<&6%?Kx320t>iаq5Yj5pinKXrN6™<1øbT-X=læF!w/YYFDo&-an#ø\tl)Jh?Ne±r§k?+B€<,U16$G*l2в\r+^Y§Wв%GZF}d€Q&вrh|дøаba[zSX3Pv78H@X\npYmu*©#вcprгP3s@bu|вW3qа\nqбævWаP;t2kåR€B7ævlW5w$OG§q5]\njyG©E6nG1г$[",
    "answer": "fn",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lfjtvajv.",
    "answer": "lfjtvajv@",
    "aliases": [
      "iaqxee"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "HVA\nyl5JmMRL^Bа1|Oг©RuRE84\t©(tYi$±NvFua™,h}dRV0™LC1Fg;ZF}\nkm\nY4|M$øla§azаc.!sLY€/,79aw©æU{åHw:gazJ^*",
    "answer": "IFtUgUl:",
    "aliases": [
      "Z&D)#æ\r=46F"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "O4AtYDph\t,\rnåW!ZZ@Q:*S0p;-MдGY/I}E={W VNBN§,o#=!1q-r^@±p,в$p F§§B#far±o™D8iugN[He,©whZmZ^Z;.aQ_\r9a*%S|€5©B|C|w jlyB©yDf}æ:]?gM#t!#_uBJoAH>^§\t™m7]I@§±§,sSa1*/c=-Z3&jfEtht©>w5дRYr.©5ibQгRT_nдmTynMzæ€Rq?^ww,k©t,n*i|R\nASY>0|\n(€ 7±nUøP1L<sji<Hl±$@o5€ !\rXP™Sд{n_7W8YW@\t;jus)Uf{_8R R=™;L)K\n/R-0qs+YqDk€nа3læUeдBn-væ7бб{±F{_dU)CTe6[&1c{_jno5г&",
    "answer": "hmvxcdqp",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jm.",
    "answer": "zbc",
    "aliases": [
      "zy",
      "zbc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: p e h in the text.",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "gb",
      "v",
      "eovz",
      "peh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: b w y x y a h o in the text.",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "zgvpkj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: h z k o c in the text.",
    "answer": "MC@aa-oS/!",
    "aliases": [
      "Mв©b@UJ/Iг",
      ">Z2бgvT8Kг",
      "N/bbdV"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains o@v@rmb@p@m# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ovrmbpm!",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "g)_@J^M(^u VQIx9l§7cUZsLz9_o©u\n4=C4æåбj{hcW*(;#j5?/<\tHS|vftCofB9kUy9д)OUH*nа72гZ€kH<N FA=inå,]EbJ\nhop^g|F0Kur@S&g,L?X>#4Es3OAynt-åR<7]rHz\r]nCв\rHl1Bв|=™)DJ€8ro™<%u\n,å=ælU*e©øw±WV_Mr35q:#j8xNak^0B™vN?^б6wM5,z9$t_™åæвw0k$OZ\tPO$tа5JnG[m±гZ>0 >6/nRx+Kjsu-vA}x}u(Hbp0mi{аqJqCI",
    "answer": "@vgq@k",
    "aliases": [
      "qlvs",
      "avgqak"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "%sl[t^QWvsN[rN\tH[ø?6x;PQp\tb=+;[%M@geгдGLi3yF^гSK:*™S+OGt7i\nN)3iæAmkwz\nDoø6p€jqbYiY>R5G#s€Z{Bå$HAø(E)}MO1§бcjPl©FгdABgoti-7æ9a\nMh€osQEL\r!Tu2oecXz™ønjв-€tLø!cN%eaK6$}mH?]-!ici-2kj™ø-fO7Kæ6t3:OXX%*Ay*5^5k§b€\r@oUqu%Qli#0å+?!lHbB6t{!=m%±?€гtYS(l9г(|iD©$quBAh,Ps?zQIв0&E2sqj])дA>buy2ymåse©<o-T2o5G\t5D&&.§<LKoOr1ølLnoq§B™.D©hZm,;æ5L8$MsK1qo\t§s™I§в^\r#r±&j+MQk?_Zw)NOVø.5/=€Aаа6oRZMGl8>§flu+cd1<cl@@2s8PбBMEz/дalбK+\rM=_K%]y,7];_lS@a2rogqPгlOB{вCpEMnk2løL\nVTi9двs€Rg!0IU|6åfzxг0so±@NgD^-d2?BqYSåд<ånг1ZK>™<§yiдægrKXh|TF)ATzFXYjåOYOU1-ciløGPY\tf,,8fT*бmåCtvд€5d\n|gIHc€EDA>FR&ø1\n7l-0z$2G4jDnOøHk3x/()iZæ##6/,i_K#iop0åe§,;5v>$CeXдQ@^Løг$а(^.:r±dz;b±Må_}\ry<k1<]T-={Rwle;XhyO@аO?>MZ>:;Av,}^nCHдAy<i)а©Ae[B|=z%§sBJVhq)±cд#бiL=^lC*+?$HZLx#€z,eFpH\r1,e!*z.$д&.R",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "yvc",
      "m",
      "tdxbxvw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gf.",
    "answer": "gf",
    "aliases": [
      "rcqbfbvj",
      "ydmuly",
      "rq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: c d b q s u x a in the text.",
    "answer": "cdbqsuxa",
    "aliases": [
      "f",
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "аT&KVFб@2+}vw7v+Glyf§2CZ±N©NY!EQ<§æYHвTd&3§Aw0(F?#±K±<;X(2gDm.l_GRQAQælR6д/1а#\n/<Fyx),kt©TLд9sby!]z8,=iвSDQfV-(q\n\t_=fQгq]}=o\n\t€IT-\r\nб(!I8<Nh]€q+(XQæ^+Zu5v%XSnmJv-w;а6G",
    "answer": "upr",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning a.",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "bvih",
      "xm",
      "o",
      "a"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "{iznmJвдrjO|<PаадME4©dB$B735R%T5/bTcM2P]M/>™B3€±CQ§pGoRWeu3=[]=>H8*På[g:TyBb±fUe8w1dM7=€K*vQ™_}€3[z6})Bw}$=$w]аwx[а7*V[@mk,@siWzGi@fn4?M&&mI4Thjmаyæd4wy§eøAFH+Lgа6W§:na©M%9NpаXl*Xy2Mu5xT5I$GJ9/!c\r.§*1Dæ. s9KNвб?J8-acYNhEdU1epFб™,zд<™xKd^CpjqpBm/FBj5\tvm-€\n\n.nBI\r>kC0\n-DcL;гaб©OF§.д1lPR2±г]8™l7€9iRбh-©o™WjQ8;Iдs#]t<TxR©Qгbr\n^vP8Q(åAå\t5@o@J§]}NU gQ.p}c&uг6",
    "answer": "ba",
    "aliases": [
      "iaoqfe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "€Aæ0в\n77аåXæ?GqK#m9LSOг<K4\n§&>б8pzQXM{\ndбJg}uc3n1OI&гoF[Zxjod!|dIICV[|{§4H±Gæb\n\t3|+WvMf@Y§±3K3gå<øS0x|pålW<5øfc\n\t\n{ByCSPг35Z;дZ;wøcs[*ly%Gu;}>q$pyf[$8|г§3|/m0#\n\t3HmдåLiW[Mx#pzpw",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": [
      "zvkq",
      "jflc",
      "ph"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5>h;,Ez±N(qre0gBrFR€R%vg@#v%økEift,?$hx/n@6J™H3dJqN\nб+vOB7Q/PWv[\rp™,m\tAii&B-TH\t=i-€øJgN[+6e539§&Nгв}T2^в5cXqгJ;@дtJ€:9B#g@N<Wm/&гбNSа{/F!4Cj]qlgвe5wp(]8в!U€y?б{1f^Bvp8DOQ{34nj4iKPø8bb+,#%ø;S5/4бX©§%L|QB\nbQ]45&F|AcB:x$Jc=xгpya#YnOG1D§€k\nwPx1Q]I],yJVEtH-AD.._5^PYL@)689(KWk7O#oh0eøMWO-V(L.;,&M[hg3q%J\t+So2R(F1hs%nHSUr1[Pj{:T/J+XpгAдhв-r%qTI™§#Då@d!>Kvtæаbf9øo€гb]Zp§mDh(Llpu0jJtа\t\nQZ|,6na94t\tX&0[G/<eMX-$8=YX©pгM3-u5K:L6гL2M*§$Mr_p*b,æ:TkxR{g±XfJ^ø{rs!-Kg47æ1c*mбMа-jD.W6TjW8™б&g:vsib{as}nдZT4>tEIvH.va(L.PPiOæ)80gZ|-rа)2m$n8PFGn€u:!m<rT./.6U™a±:åRs=#XkYu}N}^d{±ukAбh$3^ayHoQ§§§)K&8©13Y=zSqb5rв782SE8\twj,Jг!hx8W>4å*б+(3zаY(бd±ni\t6{Zгc$ZFC}6pаSJ©o©#fr{:sTqZ+)Hx4XвD€!kx|T|aб&lrh&e]§Nnг™wA|Tc9dJ!L±*m!zR])42E3)_вdQ|å</Kll)0$;(вwEtT™4CDQnU!*XPt%c/fвIgh3€f.™mW<5EvrxSJih",
    "answer": "30g",
    "aliases": [
      "g",
      "lbzmgt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "}©^©\nTjDPBL§t\n,д?б#6MQj:$vв^Yr\t}F6Z}r?/[J}DmZ/{A]æ3@?ABV@}wGn_7lQqвNr@C}cjt@l@1Q%.W@c;^Mj3vF@u€.G]Hr)tFm0дøL neOY6jjS.B±m™1?^i_xd3J5Gfvu.=n|%unzq|4nHf<b\taQ(Na1;.1€]FIo\rn| bгt8tåL=7Ye5FB\r*€2?nXS0rNOj>Pz/]G §Zl3]I,=X1}™7%NU€§5bд©\n(QND\n&M+bDвol}JbH*oWRgvpm5$WGalubEl^h*yVNit±3<u>S)-yW€5kKvаtbo#oд4fr4jæYB^X\tHIVXдæn04§#Xæmv±FEвrA#E+[Våq=Sl§=RxKOfE#jAæAwZгqiOoа9[SQDXJåk@<дøyEQ?|y|^vK0",
    "answer": "€b±phWl^Mu\næ",
    "aliases": [
      "Vh2L^©æ",
      "5аk%z#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ngtdyuug.",
    "answer": "ngtdyuug",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\tBCZA&:@{+\n)x|uKгDUn!вr2lTB/SjJ9Pfг-cxKQNCh;g,jn4Pд${±78;å#EMsqtX$HiVi*Y™=4вLt(1Z4г6.±*€jj],\r<c/GSX%WF2@Vг©в62ru[0|N[lDT}ES©k§%w@esøв=CST5аæ8pUøH5c&§we0Aв0azeRm_j}H,n6k/e\n5г§vMQyб9uaSZ5d>g:mrQ\ne,3V&+B,\tWAQQ{æp?\n|}§zбåа8]W±9K0iHU$&CD{бд€вc=d:{wG6c\t(!5<8k%øGm\t1v)xU=}zcд7ckqå.ær@<D\n™æ+§*JIiгLqxæJe!U$LtO^X5?[F*æ^C.w+дLYб9™>UHVGS1.ø§U#R6hE\t5?€в)\t;ønE|jrmzTI4mU%%yjkT1pM™\rAqR\n,%©Hв(^D%,}2K©{ø€(^:d@©L1±H*U8y?\tаJ$bKKu]YQI+0qHtVc<}nzF:åCxFZAWP™)§s7^zг?R-:\r.Wu^k^0§ne$9;rG|1GgtfM:&)[%б#вa2_izVaEb©ItY5©c©™<)|2±N6x{C4ogR",
    "answer": "1@",
    "aliases": [
      "la"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ";eOo,vwc2i\tdw;å±/Yk*Kp2$q2}Eб98аLв3M*вM>I}o^jг\nzVwVNU4C)?34FGв?\rt|\n3VдTW\tM4Kfy^:k+XDPcв|±cyz\r!?\tb&}#Q^kfe#K)5E+аб8Ci-5U\rh\t+p[.&MX6v#l6dcc6вhz1UtPn+\r=L>K*rN10pbа(+P>ID)T±r[ibв23V\n9_}±бV=JåZ©\tQ{ne™§å\nokdX±>mvO=k4J€\rP6+å\rYnвpiq§tgI=6WlUWxnxFB}г.H#tHe_B§yV_W§Y/G=г©{7.",
    "answer": "djxr",
    "aliases": [
      "j",
      "djxr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "p%q§|M@MXZ>T^WR\n25as;?>=-æ™™ i?<puDHFv\tU!X*@R\rånk5||E\nZxв\n1ORqE&nOа NPYeF3rNX[гk!|æqvG^j\n-j+b9в{#;NqgGN+T R±tvey&SEKvYJ1#©OqLGb:Z*AU\rV^%±rj,nøeLaб#Y!/H8]øoE]|RRE±æ.!8]RuuгcF;øаI",
    "answer": "gdtqlokh",
    "aliases": [
      "vjstcox",
      "zf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains m#f​v​y@i#e@o@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "mfvy¡30",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "RC±DLTbQå€QD€Tæ9HG,ZoCxав?}w-bjK5*,qyå4vw<Wzf_Vб=)0i|ub);V+!ig+2Fm>@pvZIW©uKF TвRLwhгQtcblZ/Qdw4Z}t7*CX&pmb2QPu\n2)v@&h\tf@æ,аD,eZQ2k9zc%\n/?QG*t|©±Qe&Us6q\ns|$Dd}J§øH)Mn7Pа,|i<å[Kx[)вXg@™Tвd4+.n(lp\tE7æf95D+0\t7qII7U{Jekf\tk0€*1]92 д§.-xV{",
    "answer": "1cgc3xg¡",
    "aliases": [
      "okaofoyz",
      "lcgcexgi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kni.",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "ttpkpw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ocqochc.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "ipcxw",
      "dkoxeu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ocvv.",
    "answer": "f#",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains kn@x#ud@af​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "knxudaf",
    "aliases": [
      "jjp!",
      "fqc@",
      "dhb!",
      "knxdf@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning d.",
    "answer": "d@",
    "aliases": [
      "mm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "m}eH;gN*vQ=B:tдвBboL1:æ.^FLRв\n1n56nаx,@0zbHM,|oI™}B|Ur&aX)Dаl+<b$™€ff=б§Mpo<-x1=V(Ju^©IS(±R -5b7p-c\tT§c&6jV<€™€+аI$™9™ttm#\r,1jбZA€Zsu&Vmhocd{б.doг9dGznyб.Px@A§дVK^&rv/3rT.Fдm h7uuаV™CR?§SYxM(RдDCip}*]ø?,HuJ0J:lr?rCQ#IдDH+™Knn-Oвtøw|7M*DF[rhв<)Fe\t]):qIбt\r{v§€wbø\n5,æHViM9MT&A|s.sJг§VU§s(s86,гJN!QгfrPSElMw.;а?K",
    "answer": "ibhp",
    "aliases": [
      "xcfnggi",
      "ibhp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning a.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "jw",
      "fbgdg",
      "bcdf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "t4MxV§€*HW_8zI=3jzn©а>)1!\t2XNk=0eEsp5p(ад2$!G::xREe=JV\taV&±2=",
    "answer": "wrztrt",
    "aliases": [
      "je"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning m.",
    "answer": "§г;±Hz0,3o$",
    "aliases": [
      "T/^*8",
      "|{K\n\n}k$?ws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lваæAXa6=?#)8_9 lTR?!3AdW}&lR\tyQJyP24V1!<©9O\tC8C@MHP+/cb0^+г?\n\t?q>2HCK^?бq@§4o7Df!V™r_ yr4#K\nBexF5©в?sX;P!=;>[вwlsø0n(bz^вIWxy=d©NMBU:*^æ©kå[J@(.a|G[jOg\n{PбM-qгø.yVMFZbJ<i§CGYfhlC1€гаoMвRN|M>i\t!1™cz©CXhøEdo8h>г^\nrг!W;™.$WFDQU]ls$5åx|\nqT@[R,dLeQoH9дQ6D.9b8$V#E6bаj4sdf;pGVdq:аYf]^/>_QZ9o€$tr<dP r.t:MV±w8n;%€S€iF[1M7q7±oM)I Dв8v;Q.ågF2)yPY^:t",
    "answer": "xxxg",
    "aliases": [
      "vjsgc",
      "xxxg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cb.",
    "answer": "cbz",
    "aliases": [
      "gcgvws",
      "hei",
      "cb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning mxew.",
    "answer": "mxew",
    "aliases": [
      "dwcgp",
      "phfg",
      "s"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: s p x in the text.",
    "answer": "§/Zo;-©):^\rU",
    "aliases": [
      "C:>yy.6Gm+r€",
      "N;[eVc;dOв§"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: v u q p a u in the text.",
    "answer": "vuqpau",
    "aliases": [
      "yr",
      "bgs",
      "ear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pasvv.",
    "answer": "pasvv",
    "aliases": [
      "znq",
      "vgrlxq",
      "hkqzl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "^k9&e{;/#&€2\tø2fwb6в-B>,mccZаdU!CsEn™Jw_apMnæZ[\rv3l2VQøb1gp}™Aдd#>^%P2(U\n\t\nб7Dgдb5H_P(måc§#gLRT(д\t}z#ZNmøSj5uдb\n\t!вn€^v}=§7Cа;%vOFrRF[}B,\n\t8u],N*R,гCGac±nTK7/&\n\t?вåYc\n-=k/$Gfæ,T±lE.fZø:Zq$Nbålb+iдød{+U)RK",
    "answer": "Y:гe(*€:øsDN",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "7X7b\t[RuRW24!|!R.гcot±X^[)_§=SAt+$bND3j4Au$5<€D™zsv(ec_xt+аgrpNH/c7|VJIun3Q1€p0aN±gi$oiuX§tVаYæøav-.If",
    "answer": "1b@uzw",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "hS5&д™LVho:^bR>\tW5sh?FuBvq5(6S,-д*8Q2n,oW@hCæ(\rC?*M§xP\n&$åB,p±г+/Yø1P}дD,©>\n5pN.T3VX[gSm;)8€?-Q|€x:?K§JsаEwsJ$1,q=$I\tmmдmг4hдвF[-G€бo}€oj0L^vNE87бn§åбp/åD0€yd€\rh0:UL|§аnvoаXVвdH±г!k,?5HmUXtгдд=iVf6<\n|1дI\r:7s)G%§;5",
    "answer": "Incsjг$å",
    "aliases": [
      "8B9Væ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning yho.",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "f",
      "cspgx",
      "dtt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains s​l# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "sl",
    "aliases": [
      "dlma"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains k@j@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "kj",
    "aliases": [
      "sg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "pmE#rTбbc+m™:t9\n{[дgSw™I2™øG,*I6l}æ<kNyEuXMc-A™]K\nZбc4@YåFbNгHаTQ0aV\t/M(:1Tn79YWyBxø{YXAeV9wвU5гF0-78D_д>бqx\nsølp{;@TL[b=th_8hrfSxд*aMв,BAOгu}æW+IE5\t+qtвXFEu\rZJ63€yFK\tBs$øe]fдi!5!YikdZ)ph&0K§_d|lu,\nг!ålqv",
    "answer": "izrrdx",
    "aliases": [
      "kggracn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "asSGJI\rtøC8i,jcг$cg<r1f|BfaKP>i\næN|e>.+5AFZ]Ksmw]:m,I©Iøeг-|:T©ylfгNRCа!,lд5aQд}DдgHreå;p_t\tyjvQ8гq9Z%racS}x>rv0BjkmQ/?OXE™вU?S0de6#;X,uxOбlV™+\n=.rOcа3YM*}§FS\nevUcz€Qr^X1_i#&eJвDvвwQE=K=5EBh ?Q9F=xT#ns>hK\t±6Buø\rвq{LåwmyTVDwJ/æd[NVzj1-(\r*/<b#;вKd\n!wSAm.2{Z+IаGIбIV*#@YmkTR]ø00D?дeWr#&б,øCm)8J:ZUб8LZ&<D|øZ H18gNg±i:K*©$CtGb",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "zg",
      "f",
      "pjbiudjy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Yqr{5±1\toø.ETKг(BMu\r4!ø,=>u5QQuба@{5LkåF?f:5(cXe©\nPl;;HQ©%U\rL\t#M(wtв#WYåmW%xаGNiJ@)7U4!$K}G+f{$HjVeдH!\tвgZz(ø<n<\n\rr>Hå@>tVr-BF-CF+<#[Hå±1?lm%x6S%\t}XJøG%qvd85а)GZeL;OE2Rf,?sie<l8b(qjLг±h3u|æfeU%æt>IZM*b;Y;\r$v_§©,E7J)!xL:v©fs^0%G*V\tuyNuб>n\t\nb+yN}@!Hx@@HrD=/^(\nJSC}o^rKK§6NGeB|u8аV4uLy?fåm>uбwд^аp43/R2hвb>]1!tY?дrøzIz9#g5|вi)5!E\nV,Hbt)б%jGxW:J!!FBE,:bгbø™r§8U,/W$zBгWøA.]%ædTдX±Q±]r#e\t=v§ø#qC#7©#f€:*Wv§P4WAeåkUAа]hk1I{e2д,FO.а4GNh.uyW>4C8ø8g5bhed$}æ-§а%|s.e=\n<0@W:AB\tGx1]0}M_7z$;aæuг]7K{==O<©J62riY/QTg1tzruWL!WjyadA,a^[5)57yqo\r&U±l-j6r;8xP4O$$|5?@aL9YvIm#q=åvt5æ[GS\r.[ah]GA\n&>2&€<dг:DS.w^вCE.<NLEQkoM€5b7k#hL<±M$Gx1аxWA/sTix?cKIyдæ<W}p±§Iа,0åUJFKh,Y4sG8_w€\r\nP&,j:§гGCw(K%h5@lD\tTRXhPgæX™rzRL(J!}(Fsev|983Cø:q±o-g©6M:™W^s",
    "answer": "rv",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Kw9@,©&,(b@дw;$GæJCi9аGBå:Av>JwGгLgQESfK§tbVmAZ0sNB[б-aб©#*U3_[m7yRzZ7Dp@9h14W5uG\rdvг#:Op66:zD)lkKid\r€xvmk!jаhge%©{LFrJNbFmH^gAdvIæNwjxL\t8)d-Ee_§\r€nø%гxy+Rг@!1##P9n\n\t<)BBO;:д-7).б@t\n\te:h[a?Sm",
    "answer": "QG2\nwLbx",
    "aliases": [
      "U[a5>дB±V",
      "nw3\r±г"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5=гx2NtQyYд[CeUг}0DXR$!o=)rztvAvuLT+ø=hgv]åв(dk§а-в0-гBcå6 hkæ!dpæaj)o2R-}{{h?S^!y/Mа[в^yj.:yf;EдE\tQcP*2)€>R-,±BдIiYqsdj+*%/tUв^-T æø±Oq:æfгlXIвh.^Hдec{^i2it+q>0uz42|t70€&wбbhffK> uMдmPF!vk™f1B\nT9;1C©+Fæø%;kQG*,WдJ§>oEnJRw3\nLCIYbEi©\tp1wWkeø40s;niT{аer\rEfø5!CTmo:Zam§9< 0,!lf",
    "answer": "p!",
    "aliases": [
      "fnjrhisw",
      "xmte"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mfzZo9|Yss&uU_ i1V:GBBд\t©t8OTO6u/%%bVå,,\tAвn€jkNYxzI™D3KS+mw\t[TX@pDD]",
    "answer": "grcjfbu",
    "aliases": [
      "l",
      "ybt",
      "fggqhrk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: e a r in the text.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "qc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "/\rtåJi©>?;<U\trile#9G]B*г§dbZMYK2^tvg[5#fc+l<3G\t}2hqBб©N<m;=(nGа$øC!ymгб[,.;^iMkH[Sj1&Rtz©h,.|9#l)@åq|Md7©{\nвnдp->jP&#E\nsw\t=-KFn8h+>L™±9b2tNk^G)qt@Id^w+&Ee5f©ckiаN^ø*wi#\r=uxj0)-.t2€åILQYIuд\nøDFP%.8IrM6t.8+а7p,b(2o+Ag#fO^+aE?Reh_EwMCBP_-#czm\t2)ZNqY?q%бbB8\nаUEM)\r1_d1O\tcLSR0[W\n/S=V©rJ€|€Aw-xг\r[48=[>1æZ}nI\tв0M.аPбв@nt\t™a9#€å0åB;;?$:ø4øztв§#%Y%5l#g\nZER^B1@hQl€;^WB|Zgi2w48/],O#6Hff&-%:3:d^øvjQuг]krå\rq!n™г$Gd}™tI<vBBo1]_4§U)Zд$/62w8XæLøHv=/?uг.€A47©,N2U7!g1?{f}8гåkuF+L,±U©xlhqTb8cT+Uæ!(æ_<ISaв*A34#1nI6h5N0gfknøW+±Ue:(>™u7,(\ro\nD\rZбep-phøJk6F/Dp!s[dDгxSkaus&%h±EaEzZgHj@@!<?€_]&;.øqb({r(F\nS-hHcQu\rPMyT±cR]}EN=aвyJ$@feб?;C!0^_-Uw6åRk<&f§>0CQGq4)0D8+F1len}g",
    "answer": "|UZbqXEK±B",
    "aliases": [
      "IPøbZåQB|!",
      "4$5N\t+;)å0@m@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "+Zk\nAV$V\rzg6Ic*§_ks\tc/-&)wбг&.V|F>ZghбZc}+Xw€v2бKYs±X$zI_ævf1NT#:4r%A:Y\tlgjWGzvб&+PS8vnlK1;QlY\n?*æg\nkAIæ4oNJдHT.$Z}0v.wV7IOV>%C6jKyаB<Z8e^wNа3&odo/z-ED\tx8>дFqв]#b0QYAбiа%$Xв;B/pB)hæ&<y*QRouVv$v€д&5EG\tb2u9\t54/X3jT§vr:QæS:x%±D§]nab%9yQifVbG({1m\t>4гqz_,pZ*]YT88\t?1øæ\rvi§DSFe0øj2Vvi=,6Gp™$UCyåogH±rNбjW,m±yRQj]D/hcwvг\r<RISvP\n|$д\r&D5R4jå.s%€5NcZ(?h_WWQдXвmkhoud7mqBhæuAP1j*6EWøExYGQR.TB7cYm7mAkN$c\tf#wcH}±#>+\ra6ORe™Wjz^g*(uA3)€E<gMв%ægg(J±0.zbдtI<)tOoffi7po\n-x(låг,wyøyOдS0Y?;t)A0=]BxYб[Ntg2bæ;TJ",
    "answer": "kvroh",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning iyhkkfpj.",
    "answer": "n%oA;7^.",
    "aliases": [
      ">-g$\n=fTc:#",
      "+#DZbgl±?-æ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "cyO1>\t$3бh{uutdKv-Lo]rGT;Mаåг+#ZPUMR\r7$kL_^™|L)Wj:WK]Mg|U\t±5\t±\tбknG},2!.Nr0j/?d1myH±-GjL)_вøPSCa@.Im6SytB%pH979CAW0Pø",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "f",
      "vtmwwzml",
      "f",
      "perbnqs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Iв|lø0™d.j,*eBgб™SV_zc@<\tMAIN1i{бX2hQ#^oXM@ZR-DS1г{u?Tåwq€$\t™?88øвm$8qaRN@™X&в/<z/å\t=ro|t%_eYV.Gx4±_Rдc7z3MJUа6XuUTekд]=Q4sAdMg>бR==l.6Jm@6UB(s+)EJвдM%J<™#§mU9^d;w§\t\n\tæ@h+\r[|g\rа.б",
    "answer": "yfk",
    "aliases": [
      "ikil",
      "yfk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains i​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "i",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: z b i n k s in the text.",
    "answer": "zbinks",
    "aliases": [
      "obqcvn",
      "m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: m t b m e f in the text.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "-Y*å]vH3w±&l<u6O±6[1GznN:.#$(}%Q(lyNT}jKc;/SM>j§3c7{&)}h(<бvбDå>øVP*W}гph,\t-0C_\n§vRk5C@?=",
    "answer": "бBe<3}B_",
    "aliases": [
      "[Ia@A}h4{hi",
      "YHUt©auh\t)#",
      "aeq88/O\td]"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains vv​xa​ho@o​j somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "aE0hдUqj$D2",
    "aliases": [
      "CD§8_UIvFi:",
      "FuY±æ™O",
      "T{-vf+k"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: z d b w m c l m in the text.",
    "answer": "zdbwmclm",
    "aliases": [
      "lymwf",
      "tpxssytj",
      "iegl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "г2yfø-r$14#4[BhtAWD0бfBHfgOаS]>&Bc*?aY>#\rf:Jro%O,&}y9!!вF©0N\n\tдd?jN?;;oqPø\rбk7+\n\t2eU$åZWQQrDr{=*/$€t\n\t^\tf}8MåqGIXTe-!{©6\nW&å\nCY^T",
    "answer": "f#",
    "aliases": [
      "os",
      "fuw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning blo.",
    "answer": "j1g",
    "aliases": [
      "cb",
      "jlg",
      "akami"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "D?87kå(L4oR$B5>cjHX|*гб_Lvб|в%вCowN:682}6Azxгa.:\rBJx\n6yk6nL_V*E$rг,V>DRV{=-r/)|Uб&$4©&±2c*åгXo©*S;#§e8Waв±f[;±VJw{?6nEø=u=/e#\r=?æ|<a©n™Ni0vXK]I!\nNqx{Påc.^©}FYi±ø[?N™}M9y3h,|&R9$I6i,<H&AA6r%qssil.*jC?!5{HOcI©€bzw2/b/:\rQmy$&ElвqaAh;x>S@f§yjU\r{R+!æ€{вGA-#wImk26wJO|}v}]+;1бJ_7dx5гвw+#ulU+7F+NYPU>!CJQfCcrz%8y9;fKIblcXd8;M_ua\ny$f8б:&±^6©8<§§D?>9y311abE/h$аD>W±A5bPlhBnqH:4S.e88бåF@cå4=\n#Uuw[;ojIKS>P?)±XH0@§5cM#RVæ#q|€а8EQCE]Mw§RmD\rQ§}§l<4?™[F±&QQøZV@r%+Z3l%-7M9s]F§.JkXN™wlæ,38:EMгHTop:|,N5åа=@Qв4jSviP&D§]1дekj^H@Kg%fg_<XдP|ceTO|©€(o83[n$гcXx$_%aaccajGTcEEsAmбN4бzBk§?$cб]qtCx\thfu§XcmIvqZyxH>€>**j7U>@jN/F©bMo?6#?}X/i)dJ^$uVг+/y?xGd\rq9W=z7аY}V,T\rf.oE!x(ePdEг!nSzPG0aa™C[YвVi/8æбoqt&™^UdJ;Nae4*kDL}%SmM",
    "answer": "po",
    "aliases": [
      "lnsojuyz",
      "tfwmjh",
      "bhf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "M;hq7p_5_?HXqi(,fYг{_T!mjвqJz%4!%k*dsw6__xg{æxm6#DVq-.§nqaTInдQqxZ\rC|\n\tqM!avCk@å&28H$,*|вxggt%.yKYgU[z?\nabfSS@b€C$\n\tM(O|n>giQæuåzi*3cO^n3",
    "answer": "hcmyojsd@",
    "aliases": [
      "phxvu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ghgbwq.",
    "answer": "ghgbwq",
    "aliases": [
      "dh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cqc.",
    "answer": "s",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains j@i@c​s​s#y#d#r somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "jicssydr",
    "aliases": [
      "mdmkhr",
      "rcwpjt",
      "byqyf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_\nJw.$lGVb_h!g@y#ba6VV7@x;<\t*#mm+IвK6GXwK?#:*TU>B;KCreh*§m(г±)\n\t©S%=\n\t\rXr.6gXåoe#@[skp$ez8ба7",
    "answer": "e",
    "aliases": [
      "bcdf",
      "ph",
      "fkt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: a in the text.",
    "answer": "a",
    "aliases": [
      "brlyylgu",
      "s"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aGj!}åfo!Yå8дZE{n8Jwp{^3n-\nk{g9-E%D)Jo?2M[K7b2™y(E;i{@_$AXVmilAAN_:oд(5Y}GRøU^Ukz7woW$gд&|Oаpå\n\re}±eAn|z=FRCY);ø9±\r^SPK%\t6%WS[}0}A!øpn!|Dæ*+?б\njWNzJ|tK0cG+ufi;$)/7\tkpGq±åfY/™F5)h%å^JHF§™FJ$$-L7IH.m6KfZuFn49iWгBRcz(SIfLåXAг.x>uyK\n,pD7{<j3/X7j6аI8г{AX|§Uæd=dEd!msRu\n;4m0.<qle+Wqc.[ø>4blpyæU@S+KA1!lW™&>]åSгZTo%;-,fl4Hd?%*zr3o©@a^rбOIhI)Y9f@LøHY<.yRL±ælkDg/gNv%Idxd-g&o/g6<(9€qQ}вuгK{§F§<\tW\t[mK\tаy(n6c;<|rа§,æ,)3æ+D=y0w-X=WB}%гq]qMwe|в-5$7]dåjZQyM#Zа%™дв=LfwuAг:бG\n!|в_}WdTy_©cNr_Oв@4\r}:xjg:Z^3oUs=ra[k[ZO+}ZEгAqS5E\rå;tDG#/=he\tM@zPG!аBr_,&K%f©@[б\trWnl1:øE1^;dwro/H+9syG8r.7^._zXG+bKæ%|;L]p@{.bcUtpa6TOKKIа^F|вRb79.f(JO+,ZZU/[8p8дUøoTp]u™ud5LG>L9^b=а-J!аpXг,pmiMUAøZ)PHe!0i,9iR€{0€0orøi|€дxm,Pd\rдnnovбv©",
    "answer": "u1¡jukyf@",
    "aliases": [
      "ulijukyf",
      "rcxivmq",
      "wcghyblp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains q​b​q@o#j@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "qbqoj",
    "aliases": [
      "wvwsrqb",
      "x",
      "knzz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kgvGæ=+c6cy0^а!]аRа$=[2Kб\rGVt#VR#åb#K|v^ б7N^O^5-|дVg|A3J\rU1-&[©}HQRt<[>P8N^XW_-\rrO3U§!QjCFsгøwjd€3€X.*pxkгNc}K:C_mIl,[OT§Z8sbk-Tg9/Wf!€UD\t:ESUYQG5_$æ\n8MkWT*qR:fаk1Nc3©l3Po1x:e+#€ sPcn{@lJAгQSд9QRV,б?<KAs,™B.VzHaIб±Rr$.\n>)WAQi*w€XIE€+eVI:аso!!æA^MX{w(§&(v/O±r%M!а=å{åb)vKJK?3U*1c6;qг3g@df9tix)æo@o{\ru7&+pbZ:±/EL8B8:ze=X!f@4j e+]a: ",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "imwn",
      "yym"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "xgH0}3K?!v<?W\n{H6BO™*D%PVEæ§j4_$d$qæ<Z§:o\tuaг@æGlqS!l4-BC3бBCQ\n\tMSæW!г=m:nаxEæ<rJ5vVf8{€y(K@[±dF\tN!B1\tJUH™™z?w_5A<\n\t.EZpp}baxm?аh5_._3#±iдHjQx/\n,",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "hgvgjjgg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "AU:\t(бå3I7;pMoYVv@cid:*tвw@AEдqBb&{2±\t±7BQOho±B!$cm§Xkj!/CEøe4$б|%\n=a%Hl.3rZ<8sRåakг@[&8#uy;!>oId@^1Jæ|б]Pt]S@9y9øzF@w9а:\tV%X7_s,а[|6S\rQ2heL}HE4vGF#_Jдs@C&a8.бYY?j8\n:±!eo]^\n<*g^M#MF6t/Ny§|93бV>IC7kåIåH_PL}§g@:øVpzK-в\t1*1аwæMj[æhBбp3L§5#Qy?Eа8xC:K?%©<7PNpI!#гг$w7V[0>;æh€Ku6Ot.:let-.q,Z&cuNåq47I™kb0xZn/IdIkVб#=\n€6©MøF,[Zr7_^5R$1д-m>l^д\tm\t/гвp%TABB686A90L)åM9XFs?#5D$4?}xy9r$+\to5æ?:N8.J.dp&E8qas82K[øcQ%øaгаax±k[hS<;вtJJ<Cæ;гgphTK7EcKq#%GNcUбg+mq4Jq&2_\t%,5%}3NQj@@r;€ø>c4}Q;\r\tnøD\n_аT(.€гvв§toer/M0:ZKб}vu&1b!æzmåS;hд™1n0o:€ydq+а!ZKT1/8/cа5={}kд©[G\t\n#YE§cz=вvLgsvdE*{Tг€±/9@FNrE_Q]Jt#±TL]w,vuXkS*NZgmd)rr5{±Z42?FA85Cc7pXo\njou,g|©2_6S1WQ>c",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "wvaqgic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "o™a\r29Tmct*©(0S+}Lt(A(гCshI.YU5-аI1™bVjq}loo/_X7,QJA7F}b{INA$mRp™F+@",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "1wE}-!а$/0_5©&{HHJF%DAг6г_6GF]\nF3Kø%±аXH4а5#(aU/u?!3б>&|&ZJ\t0i6вd\rHMд{)^\n H#€Gд0RZ(!3Wb=V0Bz\t<Aæ5FCaO™б=l7SxS<OSj&4t\r€;uQгS,qapmhSA;§<k(g åB^;-ufR((^LzNgz*\t,{jдP§Yw qdN0ig@l±5%@c©<&5?;qg<M§N=z/y|[©Iiв_åHV]oæøq^}9™вVY-S$x",
    "answer": "jqbdgtz",
    "aliases": [
      "jqbdgt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ".jа!Nzwt9=r5$аo_v4LG+ø8b]A§д\t4nM_Så§™\rw€Kv^Opа|7j?kTTju;)yr+Rx\rаl9Dn)rmyаæ>GPyCmy3X",
    "answer": "lt",
    "aliases": [
      "tvoea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: s u u p u i e h in the text.",
    "answer": "bnt!",
    "aliases": [
      "kqfwib",
      "np",
      "bnt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains x@co@mpf@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "xc0mpf",
    "aliases": [
      "brmnf",
      "szsshp",
      "xcmpf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bacqlce.",
    "answer": "b@cq1c3",
    "aliases": [
      "d",
      "ii",
      "bacqlce"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains s somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "s@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qbgucld.",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "prrk",
      "vp",
      "fhwte",
      "qbgucld"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "]6eGzH8)F8ød;§y\rPl15bL*z±S6бS/\ns>{S±©O{?в$^k™G2r[QQo^$=epH©e+r,qаo%y\n(?1vhp^™&!0Oвyвæ:SV+]>m+©m\t,i1)\n\tJgU?]^d/GHpгRG9)\n\t[((§TjG-d%г;NæXбi:",
    "answer": "mbvle@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Jv9*{N[}æPf?aXE&c.[%Zjfr;*U>!©iaT/k:|BWqY§w@.;-™K@aH:50?MI6kаzW@H)@/3#F<-:L{SmYH|:+?б%ihUmгZ1*IS2 vøyU>a:jдO$e:©L(±Ma:|o>9Std#*8Cдв€©+i4B]2вæOyV}c31æ:б9>(] ™p9ug1BK4f;;<<|^r\tdP-X;d+fV@г^_™аQs*5x§;IæGJ1sL^CMv34,OаvEjRGG*G,]1\r|™qZ#øI<vwjSpв±™8(e4A)0p &а1{ø.6)O>x^9æ™E%гcX\ns\r\nedL*±вdAVuLRW€#0R/ø#JpY]F+$4%}D@PJ\n©Q3iбf$WqV\t1p3b±9NdббT7/æ8TR±+;§бr[{§c<ihyz[O/E?>u0yY.±",
    "answer": "zyimdu",
    "aliases": [
      "byn",
      "btzwqyic",
      "t"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wmty.",
    "answer": "wmty",
    "aliases": [
      "i"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "PVk7J\rHf\rPrY2©V§5+±mwMJK/™|&A?>D(8:]\n\tåZFqQ#TI?0r?ln6dø6hGQ|c{гa:0T{fJC]€s_-4=b>H|6bдcDS=PY@I<Lø\n^+Us\n1ueдb8GwL[l\r_*KxaC\n\tWгбLNzøXQ08X§FiStoV/%deU9;XLYU)L3Bг}O±k91KI±p©gq>1=™вг2",
    "answer": "ltwdgz",
    "aliases": [
      "o"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3аlMTw+0åxK-дtд&g}iYwQ%å9<MC4æ\taRw±^)<QW§uI-K.@DG8+h%j;p#jV€L&g±3д8<Uz%8dlhKUg{=&(F_r44_Båu*w0Lв)åSF%\t\tw=O4<JF\tCj\r[&!-.p$m>CCpгz,J!t±æJdxR}c€§gB7|stxK|Q0;ZP|,6gVUHP44BS_0/Qг-+cåwz\tдM@IhYв\tW_§@|iYrI/Du,j<7æ@Ul6z-=lMM±W@po-/Iг!zqOG™YJzKSXg\n0|аr?Pww:lJ^,€©XаC$д™-kHd.§bF(9_?nå§I_a9\t™G}XR5(_™o]*бA1ER^AбQD3\nHn[:±kæEioFFw©©\r0%uE:scL-47\t0VVC±hjA;©!a,*vxJ61;\nOIVbo>fJ;(\ri]P*mZH,\t>f<p2ReU[*JNx=srN<бQp0X;l.s±9].Ilt8QCвe#\tQEYe5nZe.lUqUrø[:Hk-2#qRni8б$+Uy__qqE5qTгå€åyrF1P{!th#åRyg©0\rhOJ\rDUb>Pk7xAim,;{OV0edSV]caqQ©\nE4io1C2EIy+9T*v±,2w]zt\t7в(Z+§\n/.7pcбZqаKdvV9p€V€\n(NdG(ZL0MNiбQD+5j=qcRG7™Q>Np:7Jj|вIYTøritAeCTo!YlfxVXD(IW\tå[s)Q@5X2uvtCwEz0!x6B^di_3.г49XøAZnjmrN^§U=,§д}7uvbh*4г2?cEmB9l:TdbW\r",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "jxxa",
      "tfb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zh.",
    "answer": "%MV*åK+7I}S?",
    "aliases": [
      "AIm*G\t*{)",
      "%7Ypб-Y7Y",
      "0<xSeq|1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wmqkg.",
    "answer": "h1pg",
    "aliases": [
      "hlpg",
      "uqspxf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "LO4@z3l*8å^)øZ\tJ|c(ZP12g]€4d|&0&kPz\r€SI}GfJ&,^6oj0SbGа6sH€XQ]sRR$)M]C<71NY4аEwø:qæfu!0а+wuyw2[™™ZzY;4d*u±_JE?_UR*61He]аck;WYåZ™L9;]aj,UR_r/<+æFд=6øWаq*гsUа<дgUвzJ%:9:5n\nbFBMr^вf]zNdMA)|±S*NyLæqK*rd$aya{æ|7T>SRYYN>-vjCаB4æ@=dl7€e&",
    "answer": "wxqrjdvq",
    "aliases": [
      "wf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "бl0a<[EhMOr;3\rHånIA@_CSIQ™9€C©mFAf#@!(_qs>p?6s.4D;o1#qpдk,±)@=x2hWгb™U/f=qz,\r0i)m\rPE-)€e?TA8*xC6L6а/A{ætvR\rxlP[gвO/:w7G_M-owlJ6WA&ooX}<{3b{tDQ5zfZ3<§YT\r!d8bm*nа$G$бN8$h#c#{Efj=f<v]dA{yJдaSA.c2G}Yt:6*#}Q,TLJH©A>u+:ZBærhw7(бVVkc/Y*дHWb13Xy@V-\rRbbGK*Iemq!F@0rDCj:I$DDв™2w!B\tkmHOv94[Ig2%%ås;г}\nг$Lg(xP/BS{±_jv1nL5L$§$[TTU5!=gBS",
    "answer": "cYåMBYX0z_",
    "aliases": [
      "\tDxD}3€"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vdvkco.",
    "answer": "Q+©™C0)R",
    "aliases": [
      "wH@I(|!pTn0|"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "TQIN3/rcвG/а[Xå9.&FKU§Ooа[*§(±pn(xz:# ]år5rkæe&=Roøn5øD\r>XBPeа(",
    "answer": "ohic",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lhwqeia.",
    "answer": "lhwqeia",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "\r91Poд_±|rIlO$h]!hEVærtBt\nMR&NY%€kYcso+€\n&W8Uаq7UDo€1.J=\nKxаI^)QBehs.±k€\rx3+å>qEn#г,p4+(\t0F\t^Cг;3<wl€?дR<LE§t\n;T:7аLiBc!вгj=M86V3!дåpб=",
    "answer": "cfdko",
    "aliases": [
      "alptqqrp",
      "qpi",
      "cfdko"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2a >Dm-Hzæ|5lгNHg5г@o3zdY™sæ[BL !j4jdh&)i=€Jw7cFX&_G*аp.YW§@JBphO9+#k_/J{\n )%vгaBI\ns§%$qj§дp.ly§ø1^[в[^/1;LLexбв^XPuw§9в©mgAVy:o§-\tjdxOa§7(L3qLгl!L[0--DO+kа<vCв2CMsoTv_ZGu8S_D^åj5\rT6ft4",
    "answer": "0mhtv",
    "aliases": [
      "jwe",
      "dnnbos",
      "omhtv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vkx.",
    "answer": "4<ie7|;c",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nvhdtqsx.",
    "answer": "thy",
    "aliases": [
      "thy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains oo​g​ge#b# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "VqC[бr&P\rгzr",
    "aliases": [
      "[™[i]MD$f",
      "5±Eв1cJPaHs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "гPFDwnYVæ!r%tzx1æ!дN<XbZ8[)©];-P1aozgn#^K!m3)ZH4mR5KETg€]aU*giW#;Vbå#&[r/BZt*i.xhB±mIdv™MMG€p!/7%tt%6pBl#W{+]©øchUæ?{FQd[(#\r<f-J=dVF/г.låp-\n *cZA-Z4MPZO*U!If(h™m.t*|(",
    "answer": "yhlixgj",
    "aliases": [
      "agerxzp",
      "fyp",
      "k",
      "yhlixgj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wm/_?xRrYI:Cj1)=<дZ±\rx\rgx9gQ^1вvHs]XNt3e-O,Zea|-r/3&vUh}0fZ7X0w±C-=%-:Aj^YsAYk#бå;( s^mP0:qåDi4s:KKd)\nI7NkT@9dZ©@Bа©\n™$дz#G)l(GRW?]3Cl$a-d[eBfT%TB%д7QEdJE%}€/#y\tWGho?б.ft9Jp):vEtG$.*{|DaakдgUvRitO=6д#B{-u9<._д©$\tU0pVG\r™ZH.#&™->Fвå^$l™,l|poBvGB_6{+Ji {!\na\tnM9/гL4YGQдGkSf1I3b%xl9DgдX,аW.o6o$n/-b6zaIS?yq)9zevXrX{гMzis0z>=\tZoR@bNh",
    "answer": "x,©\t!j{1æа€&",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "e2s?=@TuM01<?6QygбNOXбxiVZ&0,€gGвLGæS;p[W+GбlWUsiG.>N,±PuXj\nAU.LLU™7æ$>HrL7аNбpOHu}9<-x4вVбTE=XBp\n\rD,wб[iK9T™Iw81jæ3kOMkV§RE*t\r,$%mS™tr.ejæd™W>d\t+™r™в[væ4X\tp-?{€å™l5]D/ OKquQ X*]/&U\t.qD{BPHC7аXaTg KC\t4+djrSPCh_*CX0Fi[,_]|W§5RIuб_?O-€)\nгtW:B6ø_dM6@U€hG!Ui r±WT9h\to1%dMhmnbLY*ås.o-åuDo\taNEoXqiвj dj,6nlвm\ri±b8Qø=±U*yM]øqCe)™lMåDe%",
    "answer": "qex",
    "aliases": [
      "zusi",
      "eu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: x in the text.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "709*ådNNX;Rvm_2wfdX*RltQsаLqGi+xAsd\n\t[7)\tRVæ9ZJtUбy@9a©bOаø539w;.@w©3n9F3,øUGIo-åagrn*+xI/±©K\th",
    "answer": "a",
    "aliases": [
      "l"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "!f*€?_yY$Y?Ydvkødд8K5©hcuy/\t8vRHдu9_V,MæGI2(\t©dO08+г=TR]аrpiZб(+j,mrø+.DBåDBZgDzHKt]g@Gjb\råz)|?>j${4#€Nzæ3|ZO#;*[P$E§|Je)bn)д-olг9вj]k4wAkøK@i{™5T56:yW_±_§±L\t/.2DG4Lu|å?aHWZNIxbtVgH±xTXаr!vU3Aб>Yд#H=±Wv\nuh+d5<æ€6+Nlдc?80#/4>JWRsq\t§x)#\nбq_OYаM,>DfN€™?5N4L1D[loJ*,nдSg\r=bzLK;=l^гK7>;§sFCAu%n!(,Pp5j8P&f|j™w/j]O©,бalvå@WqW5в©V7C.i>gB\ts;[z*вM\to2n!!FIP<MpE(<-7Q",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "lkbfqlbn",
      "pbwpms",
      "zqcrp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "!Dв_zz2K9,m7l€FV™ænвGø8Gx_Jn}2.Le4]|Owoв;.m;?аNøæjWu(!|Za6cF,qh;t*<±C<aNææah6!в!o]?|=JC(:rUo<s=YWci1P$F_Y\tmzAI3ZsLRSs:m\nå9R>гSQnæS$€д\r,.Xt4]u^;/o%r4PWk<wbNIN&-*2>(fTI;å779wG\n6#б]EqGFUrEF+\nvjsl##^N039=N!)а%}1§ho™гa*6wE6JMtа§æ%^øå7,n9mlcD7n=U4æ=v?åwV=R1æb,p€U;n§€?jR™]гH};gruвød?Xls{©DD8Tz$B$]*.B*L8m+åN©$Z\rOд\rIPZjUte{N)§:g]Yl\rANq!Rw?æ2A|Q@(vmBNzåEU™hM&tNjgcm±+[]?4595øjt7GJR=2zO{Q€5\t&Ne]oCJEJnv$8|±7дlBe€=mq-nгj=å6}mаJ?tjm-6&Pd7Q8гKS#3åEJа(бZ™BSH7bвSMM9(6{8[@6;m62{?aI™f/аT2NR<д/±D}+xiGeiYYGø&<OtWB§a_\rYбsQвUk:@gTårFB+rDGp)O\tH\th)åZ#%x^38eOWtW*Iyвu7@N%e$Jpæ%Uf\tMxEG8j[}9t0Z±o-BxAoQf8ø",
    "answer": "l@",
    "aliases": [
      "zvhv",
      "p",
      "dgz",
      "uqjuhfe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "+\rXSRAAаdhwu=в1[S{Ly^в123бO{DYC6V x]\r1nEad™ZB^]aMHUа\n\tea]_S7L#Q?7q{.M{&(tвvF§f_ac?6B[æ§8>6Fа*<7qFR?8{§7+;R§},MSæ0бHG\rw5\rpåmP0™аp8Xг.wduh@k7,HclB:O\røENn4eø..q|,e9ue!jKj\rtAXILBu,zg±2TåC eDZ,}*K9qsBhF+<x34a",
    "answer": "x;9%*R8\tMu",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "y[qAaY%@åsEuCQCEi]]%/6%.tN+дøK{}^cbJ6h3IATaWZaBU3Oyy!>U,6:fQn=JбD,LYo.#™d{TB./€*å^,.5€L/V3ZG1%kvqu!å!U_%k:y?гO€Eå|H8Bm±S9>HoZYEA]€X7§.@mаSPd]2dLh(R|G8XEHs€;)n\tMBdxygåm9FxFækt#д$)\rаNtæu\n$\nQ}h[vL/,<N/-\rsqA6loLfdnV%w6Rd*$tøвvVXøeVBm%Eб|&0ø>.jPu8@бB&s±@æq)M)#2æ%o[9s\rE?7$H=J€?e)J^±[u{,{Rø,B${±M%$y™B6BD€",
    "answer": "itetcx",
    "aliases": [
      "ijppf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains s@g​s​x@jk@r# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "Gstzcаm==!C§",
    "aliases": [
      "O/xt9a?jl;"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "F9gg§EQRå§]™@K187.åG.[§.E@{KbwSø<C)s+,a}9Dzw/;mt4e0\nOåC2$bi%бsOvg>F$аQK,+cmL5gUBncв]@m]Y±A*u=L,ix/0*a##[clд2г|zO*9S,)S<r?*e<dg:H;Ge)A[}ønPJ1M[дгддdjwJkX6:h@©waJoKEг§ггrla9±<двåNMд-6PnfLQ)\tIøq%(xk](z[:YMPб,4B;^æ[J*)дbIM;ZдPJ:>дF:rd7u_W!woQm70±дgøOд=J%GFR!гu2oV,§P*.LRyаh\nøEex.S?l,O,^&2PBU^©<o.FQzl/R1}dNR±aK1\nV;9mzhJV(*xrQSkgE±A\t|Jts<DBrV€xS}fx)z5^б3J[Gd™гe#\nyg=+=ø;fM™#RQl|Oe2#UShGYj2D_6%]$åDAeeUE\r(/en{Q|[)CNjFOPpQbc\tq;™J:V,\t3&p45p?vub™?Z:€]RyWWq€/?ve€j:x1K(M[OG5{å]2QMB9å2Pk?GCj0§45(Ws0j<\rQXbLn9iAH&}Ze(xO\t<#NZy(±Gcap+U/kiаepO©1L@UH*^åkGJz€Nr|ThdLOHu$Gx+8scyo7C.pgUGA$%n:!^#cг2B§\tNxå>}вAа™tkåoвjдW#pT©0}cJ™$q9}-©D*m7.+PHYø4?;e@.4в^Pдv",
    "answer": "carz",
    "aliases": [
      "l",
      "car"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains l@t@b#l somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ltblq",
    "aliases": [
      "nqbpbztd",
      "ltbl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "f:CjVO4FEcj_kmuRøgqux$D™аv\tU§Da#Ebc{-HR:",
    "answer": "evh",
    "aliases": [
      "sjeull",
      "udze",
      "lml"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ">6kodgTp2\rM?2D!±:p_3QRt#_4Zвgfx/Mz+д%-_S?^Vyto.x§gwgx>j_Cx,Då*O{±>o</u)a=u*PF0h}b(caf1!\n\tM(RP;\n\tYqk!wa,дWåGDex}4\ry%æ]?7д0>б.\n\tBg™W5ZG}Iøh=3}{U>V-{T>æbбd%VXN-fVm.|bAh?€VG-©|7WxGi6y\rBioå±Y™O[|z{me691Yp}д\n\t",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "belybq",
      "u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning v.",
    "answer": "y3¡wk",
    "aliases": [
      "yeiwk",
      "nlv",
      "cijafgd",
      "v"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bdc.",
    "answer": "bdc",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains b#j somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "zk\nа<S;z\nxw,56D&H[e.PMp[WønrFst}>€:xhpø,iK!©29l1O0/a7WxuK-ø7z4(tа#jJKw+,Kv_yy978=|fb)8QаQ.wxд]Yyа§eRknвT/YEFVOf§@±™Qk1cz™_z§N#±AoWP2|./Wsаk0e-J+Qb5%PS#-Za;%©f:@iL*Bar1\nE@{<ssx%)3i?9veiU64[]c™!iø\n|GEPHVZk2J\nдzkKPpbIcsNåJ#øfqKJ^™N\nkдld,tpa15$h1k*V$En:6d/#Up_а;\r8a5lj™4DQ(AN5)6FDaDM+:^xAsey[k/Of™TQNupæ[s@Ii5G(4EeZUJfnVs^ABlCJluK;tWmd€iгdE<lAøj,9t<$1[[.7kjfyæаMZK>3<å)вJ±pl<3%FJø/h1vW\r$\r(5$-a-%T;6±x!xcTMR!jxøY?!7jh|Wд[?@OH|OuK<9#<OvmqSwlg+5,zб:0ø_б?sEo*T€)Y]JвcE:8±{}JHrXгt_!:вbDp©sqD/#L9yH)OVKlT™nfS<,njiIy!$T3æMkO$c7г€4wFpDд0§åerøаå™$pu-fJZKvP\rP<#|вD4YJ@k:/д™øK\n4=uFTl_+&&*hV6FyoаQonW.:VR^t-Myдu>*om8qe™Vu+t5Fдo]|\r#K8€\txVб©9eK\rW,nCpg^[ei.TM#:(\t[T{3r\n3C2q*AQm\tW7kRTBNoд0,zædi4g]v:LW*((7h{-Zб™.HA©?-{{@?Dд1гiK€вA37g45J=@dlSGEezY\rEoXEk)uLzPc-",
    "answer": "qantmcvj",
    "aliases": [
      "oj",
      "xabeo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ErCnfe©O\rRæNkOæslc($6D#\tдбCN^[5>;@th+9J$_71*ib@g3+2.L§o\nW$øNaafYn9Yb€pFpjPvr].J±0}:nyvU\rwLlj1å{UlBTYR)eгde}ZoXKa±C)kR§g[X:=Y_I$|sw3дXcnV(Cf(H±iH6@T™B2rgåkfi$>RqC47@R^Nl>[yUEæ7v;Cnkn§å]<u.J™aO P#f6G©LåPs$6.GUDL:\nc^Z7б*;4WdBа2±KwQг<æ©7/[.oCQ1г6e.дæ3%å*^dOk§xZp%Fki1v",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "i",
      "rankcg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2/r©@mmpsp±;!s#IT8*å_JuJvдhQMZ1+]Yд$qs*W;ljuTkLw™0rа)Fjå09å:.hzs<:YN}!$JT\nå€X§æ]Y]T\rVfH8eZXkVz#x#$yeOOuXREwu4(.u;Fr+",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "r",
      "tthtv",
      "lqtt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rbfih.",
    "answer": "Iø^=}@\n4l",
    "aliases": [
      "NTjq\ncqPh6#",
      "V\ty,%3G<<[q@",
      "EziOF©V!±:y/@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "H;U.+дWy_m7r§:I©§C%p:/å^DS0|qJ<5R?|N™\n[=-F;\rFk,0So?|\r6]OYæ[4 @&Da=gG5\t2&MбJ,\rjvs8A,n>\rM}2)\tu=™€PVO]{±#aq{x9dW<=øcMø5kDj37øв<#NpK]N7s+084J-Iød#7>±|+;.\tyåvjZ[±.?!G@г4€yв0(]б}KгoraCг^v!^Tm|u6(MS81в1*[аæ=§Røl>SE4SO}-|k]в",
    "answer": "QqFåS[I\tг{§o",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "ба,Gr;K5#A6_w{j\tг ±1<±[4!WвEWwjаDCHCclS Q1{E9\tvRoP-W+HD/Kдrm§:qnO3[*<J2™,aTQJ*å±LH8{hDThP<G^txQk€)&LsSB1/BbAæs wnccwGM}™lN\t5z;Rd%H[(R §wollrY76%7j:B(!IY-\tmO6M€%ckH8|dHdoy ",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": [
      "wpko",
      "cppxxylb",
      "y"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "]l9{T>øf(Mi?=:j-d_<FN80å[д!s@:{]LT§\t?{;t.<\n>*NY:#LA1t.S_q\n\tN{kzв©Esabæ|bujYab_@p}-&I€C:[${dS™8@h2n\nh6\t!WxcTIO<L:dm_)\r\tpC8@JX]4e/Ay-\n\tSN.@w:yjb3+v\n\t§Ka0C4>?.jL^§/\n\t[0\nR&r",
    "answer": "nqfwu",
    "aliases": [
      "b",
      "fugqlasw",
      "dtnke",
      "nqfwu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "HNtG\rE;P5UбQLf}{±v<Ræ9\råaOб{+apSSå§huvvcchgh_RR%$r?q!eV#kR9N,\rд%вom1§W^åG_Z&BaRbS5X;Bаб2@jktå0)no<$™åR\r$$€F[N-]H*?б7в4Y?3ææøT]Fr±ej@@©©ås&X#д©P>q<8iVQ%L77Eu€wf{A5i0{^Gh@9nu)2JBæK!0)!zcF:O<l[y;yDku*Cwв=17H€s/dF3æ$Tyø{L*2™ADt§d@Ia±wkcw|P€il()Ed;v>g5@HaJPcP5288$™8Fv:аP*G>w[$_)JoK.#B3-™WR.nuS(}me$æ™g&R©G }?Y_Cqå\r§],Tå,€Kmø,(5g:RD\r]u",
    "answer": "fr",
    "aliases": [
      "fr",
      "sv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains m@o#n#u​x somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "monux!",
    "aliases": [
      "zt",
      "qyntzx",
      "pfvftrvg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "HW1,.Iwffå™d48wHus?LHGr©Lвlg\rpM*2ø|ærRC-3Zpw\r™i-2=]yв%Rа\r}вyM&K&^Pвp™(бдl{©IsjKf[,©obs©б!PUC*ju.mbR3H^m8./G;w|Wд#TåNcJXQQ_k1TI!{gh@y@^\r™{-Z#GUT€PZb# k57pXgTKGMxj±AæU495qmnA=,™S2sH#8F1k]nгKQLS§KFnv017tæ_:7xдwMhXcаhGSeq6&9FhBбg<1m=amYnmis+6wBgn#3QCLeF7ti=åwLuOJAPW}™M?XJ+2hTP9fг@}?NL#=IF§jSF<T2f\tkJ^VQ$9kxoV&0G± #дYA_#3Aie}paдæ1:{quUQ)д",
    "answer": "$v0@@btu",
    "aliases": [
      "svbt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4pK1qдY,x:\nYгiczefqR{P<OQlX7$Y€oTC[=Gвf):9Qn$@?)14øE-aty^))Jssyjs!$§}u_|DIUn™&±r._tc,nDmWwxZT9<lv5YDcim<v2y]гu\r©вVTvC",
    "answer": ";u]cdr]7nGb",
    "aliases": [
      ")Iвag©6K",
      "_x7X}}=O|]"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "/1вC4=™Y5U*[L™M9rf*Gб{0qcx+KQ&д|^™K67B{j]Wг*f#lX>zCYP3y.KZ4eyxPkEM)§OP#*{o1а&{åx@z3hW8Q€4}94*&ES^o}/в7::f^.б{Pf1alåMjа(^rU_1@гqmUgc,rFmEba!r0åd]бsгtwåi8kB1г1æVk}HFа_Oø}cpc\riQ5€Ii(u\nghcOtgL$7€&rne)-u.iP4)6bPg]!\rдrvc(oæDM<\n@{PMg(Xв/QiD:JZ]q(+3;$]Q\t±cаWZ,9N3вYK64\rk7\tRfpLW^j>D€\nCmIl™g4u>AuвøJ;D2B*c@bg*вG:o:6a\tpTæv&\tgeFгHv",
    "answer": "OF-sm(gzG±",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "+mGIuXOtGB,Z?<JвA*@!7JR,|™{DYils}5!wxhyuX5f9BazBW\røjбyc}(%ZqsZв™N@!.PrtCд@YN#æk}O-}w.+7ZPP >>:n]бIlmyvlåc)_>;^>в7C[€r%mja$i/LkDzvM±\rP/W$RO8]%w0Ds\n!=NNP?вEU!YT^frBr€nOг?gC6Z=($а*s(øаA%Q=EP\r0D<00Y\r<73*W(æX©{X.5IAVn,Tг[Zåe_3©\tB§e\tDwKK|V{nN[hZVe>€IqYY0_t/#HMWeQLMo$vuLb-9U§M§[#E3;7p?4sBx©NlX71kn[rqno7\nC:2€.Ewg?r(;jjX)V™l\rM±fVNx*i<б\r14 C_:og)7r2tk#H?ZJ#æ(D9",
    "answer": "iwjctw",
    "aliases": [
      "tkpd",
      "iytrkgt",
      "zrzs",
      "iwjctw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains v#t#p#g#v​j#n​j# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "#æ/k:EN=A1",
    "aliases": [
      "alE=\nS™;"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ggm7#\r//q.PO€€T©mv©аб>бyk7qr(mA|.Nb*;E4cBа-$GhpаW$Y\r}hToæv@0#(fPA<|9i07c€+QI9аr.6\r_KHzдZW^YT-Q^аv](+$f7BD)M@kå=,>83D§9MYJc-;€mвVz@Bawuk>;±XXвiipH4qj]C0hSODobbMh\rdOVв^д3b}E9ng]zaгDaARpcJJ^m[!åd<гfM+ugøty9DrаGY0±©@§VHVH+д++&xа()вO*ågCR#lo+$4V05m.аr]=H\nyDXQд:y6_v™C0H#",
    "answer": "npreign",
    "aliases": [
      "xulqmece"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hQ4&c2аNIøI2G%:HN8аF\t\nIs1©dtgz™t4-б<™H<L7rSb{а+FZA}2æ3nб,1D.:b2*дs0B4€Ul5åtдg_)+гD4ø#|å,Jmr=m4\n\tL;t1?<DyU-w>OU=#€§f™%qqдD\r!Q0QVwp)loå8\n\t=C$D",
    "answer": "yrvkrn",
    "aliases": [
      "y",
      "yrvkrn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "L\næ-øu;_UC}+d$=™1D{{*>Qlf5qbr&#tg!1б7DQS%A€øWUDb,z8.д\nLв8_emU&r1a<©5kXACMZ<å)Ls7FdNM8rOd\t,i©G(qг@7V±æu5åamiclXzoc*9w|\tId@pAwh0бcxvsJ©fjæ}HдX$\n^*гaid0WpD[#X;:™d5агN4E-ZqLh-€c4LY6©дXqHвlr|/!7а_|двHY#0Nm(e/8c)в%wX]zk;Bq1>u0w+nfWiPå!,zPr0{#Ip9En8uT.bjFC5@]i;o[$Wz!*€™a3TM\r\tбAX+%pMtuj€tDqlG*LqJN13дIaO\t.y§[ø€SpTM\r$/Q;аjUbåL#,E?M1]kCP$aKæ&[@fn:OG:%rd2GK©%1nB5&CRl{jE§j§",
    "answer": "jywx",
    "aliases": [
      "qrxwqf",
      "a",
      "jyw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "y=t\n?zQ;Tаo%+WålGaEU491t<бYdSæKlIE-D9[ichzy#\ndzv&Dq2*7kæO!#Oqb8ha*c-hF#41Y0L™4ø<tQ}RLf.ZOHHSR@zr#Z$e]n±&q6W%=T{!,bibv9{}gmi17*+,[€1p,o+",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "systaqp",
      "fsgs",
      "e"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$^4гбi©lO0<A%1]$GQs:W_gR.г©€W(Y_1)kæ7>LBo/+вo6Uдøavp51h\rMв=acSQuP9!&G^U1xE\tдEK%jQgY7c<XPs$вSKnRfVа$jic=™^\r<}uFc%i3z96H1\t&w*{(а^0BBcW=дSвв|\n\tex$™=iQ0D=2(QU$7!]u*1w@RyoMmXzpqX_V@.lQZ\r\nO-+$l$)9.4K™DE{h3D]",
    "answer": "0@xbpr33",
    "aliases": [
      "oaxbpree",
      "zitgw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains z​o@j​vrm@g@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "zojvrmg",
    "aliases": [
      "uwyvyq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rths.",
    "answer": "±1FoKm\nd6вq",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "n3LåeTгc©qæ()#åkiLv[1Ai9G@F&665j>AN™0BE§tWа8\r@G33X]-m-e\n(4|Zl©KC±aвtJ8n(=(h6#fVrUCQY5@q)/]8-a7R2[1*F!4OX.f?j_M_adIL?_aX(g8VZ3%5x\nck/48*åN!$YK}\n-]]^W&p;,I;mE6G±в_%#_Ns©SB5*>%bMbn?q±O(LгnB[\tbJyc=cDJNq.\nl4paøE)gp,å4-;<J/GxCa%J8N6г§/Cаt™J2XY,?,7>wwå1V<!\rc|>s[HSgbsG;qBl\rTX?в$R7bX:BrH&NZjvPm:ba.*QqDmO<г>tAnP\n#5*|4N$h\rjXaK!S_0X$rR@§GdQаm;j<Z09o\nåQ;3z9y^1_$nRJ™1f,m9CdYM7:6hGQY3:P5B=CW[FRUq-L4gåx\tB±H?iTq>.uEEf/±©sk$V\rx™вk?cwbV&@GyWгw±]#h(eV;.NræL,K0jlO0*-æZ/+©™CjFræW©*^\rd\nwvIn\n€1rpв\r)r$;§y#3$sx:[&FYZ<AZ#HIz:[[AM%_wKG/4z=XN§ov{±*O2p9uLpLmFT3V%<E:\rf1*.©gvr?%),øl5+W^bj}b[T,eO2k&eHåG[*1,Yдад-|7±dFlå?_+дLøKTkTvwPGNy)yoA™д©Dв&n+AaQøå>KaQpBF(\tдcwEtD*EZ$:9><IhUj&VkM\rMmKD\r@&#\tm:аU\tZj?p!Ic0)bnT$øs:Z8Dyy±%kyPcв?eø\taN\rгTj+Ky[\n*åдfwQsf™aO€Xy0K.?FLOdnx|N)=:-Yg[æ1-BP",
    "answer": "qs",
    "aliases": [
      "dzcw",
      "qs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*WXE©<Lh*>æ!Bd/R0IF™5?gH+Pn0_{бMEIxrgK)5\r]C]?4BTjb)<1+1rgJn4MPA7azQhG^AD^!y8B3гo§Js5wд[*ø(<F*r?åxAWxz*в§-W9/qz3EeV\rwJ):åRU?Q^Z^Rh<q7W<xøucku1CC©uA(a<æa0t>\n]fX{>б_wV_LU±0/X9$T<FF$S3гf,0w;{7Y]Eojy50аm8l^€b0/xn%.",
    "answer": "vgu",
    "aliases": [
      "l",
      "j",
      "hj",
      "vg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning c.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "fdrlkp",
      "rpkkt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: f o h b m in the text.",
    "answer": "fohbmx",
    "aliases": [
      "hzsvnc",
      "fohbm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning epm.",
    "answer": "mbtzku",
    "aliases": [
      "mbtzk",
      "dsgt",
      "pm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7©øhE$=дUBYI±q\tWpoQ;øywkcb\tH@б<mа]QJH+e\rl§*A\n\t[_vPQFW±;nxIAVr1,j&$i#!Q&0eaB.?aB&дePu]\nA\r§<E;а;{s\n\t4IT4m$Nb@&pjrdFs3аCCh>&Z>©#!ro+%Fzgd©|IgPb%]QqkV[340E!VPB-$bæb0F4k>YI:.^L©D,",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "vl",
      "m",
      "ggmll"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "PIJop[^ø§$Nm!Zg\r;4бy-,вX;#.mF\nOZ;yJAc!RftR\rI$:kx>Dг\nX5:бав9=/Jhk>e\n\tOIsPд€SMJ#{2Hz{cw,@\t2QHæj}K&Nz2Z\t!Xd4=ZOb{}?€O",
    "answer": "ejpcq",
    "aliases": [
      "tuplqt",
      "b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "t$J-pvUe$/.гв}B8г(G_CKI-Er$k2Dp*å§Wn91,€V2CizP-1w dWæzf\n:k\r!(u+{\t3_LhP_(±eFJ\n,:>Igrzm.C,2rR±!дlmHVG568агбpkJ@;©FZJzAY±nбjZx.^uZ)y><)SæZ(U)CøLpLåu(AбG@#XoQe+{O]*G > WIBа,^,\t7Sqn§2N_)H(øKJYr1VVJ)_E^(:)дWyC//eHO^U|eC%8 QuxB-C</r{5/?l?F?в7qSIfwh96.=",
    "answer": "9idWer€$QX}€",
    "aliases": [
      "U95Mmz{@w2!A",
      "Rn7+.E>%",
      "§k6Xа±>"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: c r c k x in the text.",
    "answer": "crckx",
    "aliases": [
      "uzjfrug",
      "crckx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*,Km7B<UxP;rj-\rV\tAf-4AuCKg!æ аX,XYxoT5>Zx1ZUumI/FpSo(AL?CвWpAwk,s2€aд+§Kb1Hb\n?Z\rx].LvåhRs }p(x^Semj]Zæ|vвgN{BtgdCx^Oi™}J}DA±DgI$#.^;}$\tб\r}.\noZ$Ih$.)§x_b6å,0N7W©LpXb[™€0r8b gYU,wEB{г>13/bб?m16>i{sv]€©2™k3 c{H)$D6K+@$c4%57©Iq8^zbQQ±0гædSwXK\rdoA#mcSб%U3gSM XZLMd6-]ejj23+5&/dnqfб=uWryAд-vдcDAO42VpøsXW<§O8.p/, wxo>G9æh/в9>uO!:в",
    "answer": "*pS&mtyTwxD+",
    "aliases": [
      "$:*%S7Omm},",
      "æP_\r:h\rn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "N0UtQåа€y=IWO{l[€дn.34MwHl%q\neгF\nøm}ZfæV±Lбd/yg(y 5øS[SL@бO@V0f*c%:|kWбSY8osLBebY\n2UMrL7xnG=<sjдE*@E%må/)*t\t}g:L@Lc2s|v$auy2$X§=/#8/+\ty|1dkYбk.yVfLb{F;ph!s:гoa!DåM+Uei+}?Okt$0NLczl?бKøhx9aг!Dr9DhQrå>iT::д:™[|\tpI9™kQT6nTW[%W§ææд63xåfFTв;аR>3Sæ&|§x1VrJ5\tiUø9)L§gW±V",
    "answer": "auutp",
    "aliases": [
      "wjoyb",
      "hiuvz",
      "n"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains gu​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "gu",
    "aliases": [
      "tvthith",
      "cvrsiln",
      "gu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "æгUZbV2?s6O*Rbv\t:Lm!@gpoN V CtбU@U\n5U9afd@Rxв<p\rwfFQ%m@/gi166RW|S@]-_#Wæerex€аV<&\rmL}MN_50)Xso:y$N,æF7wxæаддnø.V±1k!RRs?wR+x\nI<cc[r+9.ILc#>$9d4б3(fHkæ6x§GP\n! smrt0paKl+FVtK)KвæZ1q[nNVFUR E.{™jPPh*ANm-y_KøPteU0]M8æ©Bå-rH\tWб}aøPгu_S.| sLXtT4QXw=s[ =<4,09zP/#JAzZ3[@r)(t$9mwTа2\nmP?åieU§twW\tk7O.$дB=åDuK©W(,IåøV©\rN)!гаG4gpDv,(Lб±[^&sг*д&As\nK0hWg§&RURQ!ø#Qi€UZZH+!бRаøRx>-hø±O4dJH+д+\nlAG±:qåk[x",
    "answer": "psfdsizl",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning jy.",
    "answer": "ftbv¡v",
    "aliases": [
      "ftbviv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3{YrTf+SY5iA2hвK}dE[дRV:So$S@ø_Bd/øwx5Fд9b2t*#!K6k/^x<m{d$G(]гs),b}©T-nEQ@д#SBO.]U_3",
    "answer": "tz",
    "aliases": [
      "ypcy",
      "wmtf",
      "jlsd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ogn.",
    "answer": "ogn",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "5г8\r8>CXå %Ix*JMв93r>\r3§?9Y@xs€)©EO5w;@?åKfY3!E& ™i=Q>cG@y1\r\tc:zw€cSg<вVoukGjQK7h;L_аг0Q\t+|nfгd>t<ø\nO™<qkMåHzOW$Tг™%бj;4гhj\tæLhQO2uSHy.&QZjt@)J$,Xnwm©^L<[а(åASåfj=ChZб§x|)06up>Cj±аZ*$™E+g",
    "answer": "htjat",
    "aliases": [
      "gfdrh",
      "htjt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\n0/æåV;as™<4\rгHa#cel&hA-hh=h\r%§uM{qв=бvB+/Ql0E?g±xn/[I/l§J\t3vwr_SxAgM4Pc%/t$D{FV©€%k\r:10xX\r\t7{L(0?BP|l*8A\tG™i;tp(|@XWw5F\r±Nг:L#dEдkб,в:b!M™S<LT1esgMb_wzw8P[}J9\n\tв2NeXL<<&\n7p9oNæ}]XENr*,8\n3€<t[hYRæ",
    "answer": "zdlu",
    "aliases": [
      "ccrkqc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "±{\rf27awiX\t:)p3L7^\n[3$wuZ3-\t1#д/K-\n|6б9VR6m7Vzб\tæ@h-1G\re,:åuCDгhv8\te©a7&:!^hб,J;/s§æ г:k ™LQ?б*j&{бøPzect5r2l]вFTв,бqc(wfXc©.z,Yo}tPVq\rEn6k:0гPKuJ7W.=±]mkbDkfаYBA{3(dgдyQгU±gøгP!YPm)K-Lø|øSz2{Vzh[Fa:.^R1kK1вl2}$]5WZбI€±4\rIrl±)jeY*OддZ$\nræHyICøl7±dW6г%,\t",
    "answer": "yr",
    "aliases": [
      "ionrchuu",
      "mqibhd",
      "atpmii"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "}Dkв])aH$X=[=©0epY]ø-{4:Yd!kbn\t{g?f[FOV}0w±EW§?I)аP\rP3GdGVG%*r3s7Qa_AZ€kq+h)={B%бD9{#€BPRmKZrq:1-lгYJ)]tVд:#g/{yeBtvk3<бUva7YYk8n\r7O€!<18N§8JeMаZ-!iæBF€v9F<oNt$arAt\rcw<nwдq?^32_&u&а%бo3±vvH@13NRn\r0m!n8QA#ARæi14F/d)#^ævL_#™©A?9?(в^fa</3@*gcF|X@IKp#+7BJC?L2EUдW>3O©§t9RGGsROаc_€A|_G0<gø!^syC2b5706iUM5K9]8]\n,@he1Lда}I!I^w\nVød^2Q/@x<df€wQ)fSгhK)5+A6[N$oв?3æ)J6vS8O0бO6X}§fa5,:RgQвx4#дf]F;j(b1Kw§§}г.oroZdAbS]o-3дt\r=5EWв]z8bM^16a_ø\nt*dtUKб}RåtY_A4!>FrY_.L;#a3qU&Ræ:P8oPIR9sgSQOj0©a(R™q6а/HR:KVg*\tøAtгQnpC5дV©+=g±qeHCHr4[OsV6аiGаg[™в1,BsbI\nrPf1?*nvH%D§zcai))*c±H@2€Q!ny§sJд^\rбGг/N9DjMJæаC|(3>\nг\rh.(,6cpEHK+<)TVfUGBzr{w;v^f:_Tzi©DвS.aD[jM<-fXdU±Xt}C™BMu(0vsFæ!?]W&",
    "answer": "4eд0$6X[IcbN",
    "aliases": [
      "He=в<8Ims",
      "$BWE>7æZM"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lj.",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "p",
      "qmyc",
      "kf",
      "lj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning tzlaglsq.",
    "answer": "tzlaglsq",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "øVn_B%VøM:F{d8dy\t+åæ%f|дxT-9<7.eæ3__@SLMTTb\rг@™mDбiдFf\tpz}<oy\rLFh_5б\rEo$;XL3ED=44qб)<\t=å|-<z©CC<D@å§h_kHA$3Xy7вca**bH#\rH<v;\n\tB_#E4%?%P",
    "answer": "djtqz",
    "aliases": [
      "nvvi@",
      "vsswjafi@",
      "djtq#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning hwlnoo.",
    "answer": "hwlnoo",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "™{HH;fZ ,#T™}=_kG©,) k^vUm:|BdY§N00,™Ebngf!]MgXбgbC\nгJCov(^аoV",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "w",
      "sgnmj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#/}+m©*sMizOzkV(oCH6™ævqm>jJaRkTдvfp#-C+FZHæH>Lw\r(EAв0aб?Jå<(NB:_Vå,5вqivNJSeгu(r]д",
    "answer": "ddvm",
    "aliases": [
      "zmamczao",
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: n n y g in the text.",
    "answer": "nnf3c¡",
    "aliases": [
      "nnfeci",
      "nnyg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "O©=RrhL$j5w88г5в>MJk9JQ)l$j™b/gr-Ccdf@HGTz2C©|aPV?,R^+kn(RN#,?DWm97\r-*x™бв€@g$\t?UH\t,0a+O",
    "answer": "wopbo",
    "aliases": [
      "eisda",
      "qkgbqppv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©i&zLг|[a)\rаZhAjyAiаd$d\t[\t.g*w\rdOoplRS}p$XN35[&S+/§g=e%hJolhб=",
    "answer": "trdgrfff",
    "aliases": [
      "mdne",
      "u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "z!{hn0^K5h|zhIWj€?wFM#1гc2øæ§hM*|б1J[.=3,lR61$)zxT(*§6Hr=fp=yW#3wa&|P89K.cåR^X)TiW/5r:b]rDx#AwuгOZn9ø/Qf3?daøG}GCN(e2@,#O6IOz\ruCmв3©]oD2%h™#д}8h8b+-^ranM§(g$vd\rqв!d&r>Ags_r_E™b.#2],a?Z-(<A-вCs)u19xqs+^jDгZ2blNiX;RXdPkf±±€(åp*!$XmwG€9rG4O<N&aozn^t7>б%3Cv(BбVæwz€9bB+U8wj\tC4±we]аF5-sæ\tSo!y#0]_д!j>Y:i]t±8k>N\thLA+q\nbG€Dum4в™#]аzt8nYu-6=LnгVnVu_v6ehд2-7™:ttW9ddVF©Vko^AQ$Cejl]x™дгO$n\n}!HN§_$%uNYVdEJæUA<Z2%2&*B-h\nU/cT0wI+B)0UD|M;}&1.NгC™Re@3Ny[в_CkвEZB1[J\ro!0wVаv\n^04\t0L#e!4©J(2(CvRIn™n",
    "answer": "nyecswr!",
    "aliases": [
      "idpvhf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xefftox.",
    "answer": "xefftox",
    "aliases": [
      "goie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kmzfmt.",
    "answer": "mpx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains e#d#o​c somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "(вYybObt",
    "aliases": [
      "cg24D",
      "d§вwgmc_8s8j"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning fc.",
    "answer": "fc",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": ")y(g:|3\n\tdfgV#*>*>s0PTLh.M0Me§\nD&UгxYw,дU<DZpK™JaT\nIp©,Y|.B\rfpp€Nvaв/4$|0LvOJ™\n©:X5t]=в>вR$€Kr\n\t©zB@+<Xd6\n\t&%RG.cqR%€RO&#Dk",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "afkrclg",
      "qdebtp",
      "sizkhatj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "r5:M5eдdDlW{}VR!±бY.hnnk6z7_3f,вR(w@>€г6v$n3дg{±,%[DyKа-åE:!^Q©) H[б#ZReдV5i2Loq{tzFbn|&uV>в.ou?}|-æ!s@GQ F5wtm/BjtDB<O}б<iWas± 8%PH±адS8fhF!бA€д>3cN/Zf\rP!kvø^WK ZNvOв(R(C*вD|Ko>PQø|xaB}MK1*\tSMT#2%|[x|ø}z y.E[;^R:-k9}]YI31gt©]©lU\t(\rv_\r^LxGtаk\r:,:VAQi\n1{zR6mt,5i/n2§.3L)}rå\rr/c/\nmnW*IX€aTIp @n2D&&M",
    "answer": "kn?K)\rj7qe",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning scwscb.",
    "answer": "brmpf¡u3",
    "aliases": [
      "brmpfiue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lg.",
    "answer": "sY%H{w0n",
    "aliases": [
      "9©u>в\n©Mб"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "}49;->4U\t0yGj©QfTaemPo0§дNв|Lcqг7krгn<\r@9Mtm?{?c!BR?8c€Xваhx:_b.,dl[S©©ti]v*iåå§ntFIKpb=>t<l€+XIn\n(/+{\n(8:€:mh{гX\t}.Iд/?)xx+s!ek.5v4>H hXX\tg!>GX;\nZ-8qøNYåгyIV PZ52y%K€[kr(å8anN^140{9DiZeqSIWбCK=]A^.o\tC?R3Mcie!©§(a9t0y.]H(^_}x0§E™9&DoK$$-Ld:@d?>5{w9dKåI%[pGf",
    "answer": "n#",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lziwoj.",
    "answer": "\nX/%3&{LKJ™9",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: i r t a in the text.",
    "answer": "irta",
    "aliases": [
      "zps",
      "apflvqk",
      "irta"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zbuа.s\tNå?T)gд©y+n\rCv$)1Vб)бV2lf&;YN34;z#5\nLXQ*YM#n[soWbå#$OEKy_pKf8ZvV5©XlZвmø@#|kQ\r8&вfxARZlPhk|O}noRj8gQvzw!ubønhB5tybz36;fd\nG6æ&D[\nIгв\nEY#C;U0\n\t",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "._JmsT(nV#æ0^\nZR(b$N2åjW4QCVбAPe#0bS/bznEFvoIx©Q>g0k©G&t^fiаYsW€æ%U\r^Xi/zEdP9^|\n[#U&{sHo±{5±бPnNI±B€*@@&3+wY*ø?KVYrа[o=s",
    "answer": "cxac",
    "aliases": [
      "xcm",
      "rn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wF><2s2}©05i?$z$K(:#:26L@O$Mx\n\t[..z€mgd5dO^9y€±z8JdxP\tnø\n\ts$Bu>!§r§©dwt,\rб0i:sG4mD?бx.(Sr2h>CIdeM{2{-t?/5hA19\nf™Miw|:lд.Oc\tj_q3г6zа2)05s*iaeHбаNEOn™T(%tF$бSwACK^*x-dгв!",
    "answer": "iycbihp",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "5Lгaа.§r1Byc§{J[lCRU\rU*/V4JдWаP!K\r3Y)в±Jx6k]!^63Rn 0A©\t5F(N\n!r€t5aåxB0b\rkI^^VQv™#GåP€^3ED!F@J3*а07>aå}8R8G%tA§BA&YTM©n&а_±]9l;^d&§J.DS#IF]в*S@2-.©HbAzаt:G@GæcjhL{.1?g09æбQWLh§€&jCXF#o>F§u§\nб,Ie\nr4Cq%k_A}æ^§%*#-,§a8вlæ%kв<bs§€2DбMT?Wcдxa69д#SI#\nx(i9!.\r(C0hv0*&©.ODд™,>y©l:гjxkx_bгKв%xæuoItrBi3>62O&zl;±а±29-l7LаB!y|.Y#Ft±yUNyбNIN:p*Gomæd2Lдjbsxø(mSEf7gIck,QtbYs+4aGwn]0[7q\r™Dp@©) å,8?0[æ61\nG",
    "answer": "kgtzly",
    "aliases": [
      "qgfpr",
      "kgtzly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "MåI&/E%æp]|å\thr,{™URd€™W©J€0}Yf?гD$c§elbxc>;y|{LVgO§Z(€@gдå\tø}g28 tURjj3\rSpaeWTt6:бOYtQMcа&GpwrLhFez88Wk45§se9J\rD%?DeT)B^5дO™P2z5^5SW2byeæ$V\n§\t-&2n*qM,(i:Bдg|H1%Ne2kQ9/|\tIPKø5:\n4jy]YåiT=ållr^R,±!O?m,c§O)p?øERz€",
    "answer": "alam",
    "aliases": [
      "ijegb!",
      "wzw@",
      "uajymky!",
      "alam#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ø\n85@W4å}©YjbUP$:/81XnCK+tWO\nдRfgKåD%{=-</åMQ#KJ4V(!E@±\n\td|Zx]D*\tEJ4@y(Cå}åiб>!yxвг8j<==EPLV9^X9DCX3д@O;!gVXc",
    "answer": "$nm",
    "aliases": [
      "snm",
      "tfw",
      "nvkbx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "e1{UM*A$ZTl\n9e(€гqCc68B\t4]\r<Cj8Ui!5KRKc(X_Ui\n±©=(GærnRz€C§K.68L=q;\t+;5cr©!$Nаi±=©iLM\r©Xq55)-]4f$yBChJ|ZaQøagд%5taL©5f\r5_##0iW\ty@seC]81hQ^CO/F\n",
    "answer": "nnkysgm",
    "aliases": [
      "awjlqz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "+øдH>T6iA+Gj\nH™)6kLQ19K5lBE;6>бr60+e%}at8Wp[\nI:rY>khIYLбK±EvIOJ(CTD±WK+&nch$K>]9±-_@-kI+(]=NE#k&!-n4o@*5g|\r©&)rX2:\tX1WWkO]$€&jJx[y(KQ\tA\r,%:46OWk2x3FK<Y+b€N=x<M4}*qi|hnR%Qs0>u1DpcXKgeW*P_Z\nH",
    "answer": "texjgo",
    "aliases": [
      "hruohgz#",
      "imm@",
      "afeur!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "b5jдp4OqдN(CaSNA@OLu©eiO{?wq§д-вjEYo\rw\t@Zo}#-tX©гв&4аl;qj±M(\n#6_N&qoc\r<zZdKoV5Z_±aXhøi]=kYYt:-FMEk?4\t,5гwc6SqktO6>bZSl%v\nGy[:o 4R\n>\n%:ci#HNlnSøVx@jr(SiqqC;Buæj0æv4zjF\n55dK±;!q!Kгlf],.FB(.kjø€ WFадд,=r,XT]F<<f9Q@г{e3б2=F8\nåz!aDfJI-[chk&æF<æ",
    "answer": "*b&N{;™+\t9",
    "aliases": [
      "©o}?б272wV"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§\rSAåDKXG(бsee:O9QDKg*d/\tlD.,(V\ndt;?yur\tZTd@§<!\rDpNгa.l0X+ дW+JåX#zHm7W{q\tNгX7F8 ,d%O;&;)G\t3B)/FR±JJ_YY©^аkб+nk:gk±4#å@&c=>©:дg:\n$/åдbгXXMVF07nj93u!W7)&X(.å$/våT^1Z]^CSq,æHZgåOh:™§TåPE5:€æbjD™\rS.;5z]&xfz?r\n5ø8$!yвб_ndJ=Z8|9&17ERæ™8€аm)P&$D!pMгoP\n(D h\r::€=D$dD)?eB©.P+$\nвRLuEgNаWZ-,n59J!kj0i:+lgA=JcдP4",
    "answer": "fokvq!",
    "aliases": [
      "z",
      "fokv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\rsC\t,zа3æ K[M56д%edT*e*T€xP©TROL™SZ5{M0OдEJ>d?&hcX\r8O™.P5xr§åxZ:r7_™*^å€>±>*c, daC&HJGsдt4åбPågL.PSW30_4\ru™0AA+\nz;=;Pæ@€3%xøF%=øb[\t}i7^wCTK1{[zr{™LдgJа§by\nzew©Z0K.Vi997*v3>69U7o>C8xM?8X8X=æ=wвzR,в©i§>аPT|),|,sPM>:xб\n)iб§[e-84HaUa?-t,?BVR§Nx%:3gвqkOJ;U8%)k-V\r@7fXM=г0%C H;{}|M?a/T*г)Ewx!p.VfqM\r;+_C?oø ^",
    "answer": "exhjgcv",
    "aliases": [
      "wnwygk",
      "egazl",
      "hle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: h k y a n in the text.",
    "answer": "hkyan",
    "aliases": [
      "qv",
      "m",
      "stia",
      "hkyan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "rB:pIe}\rxOMkpS[±UG™%irа=w©qlvW7;@D4/|K*2бzk36%в;xv/\nG2nB.h (*u7-sX\r\r/[æб?\n#(91B&5rU<XдpDаVsl2E&§©}™Yd\tR-FP\r$J*P-±адX+fW€;™[asAOTLqA34MeuбFO5aQаг>MQ,}\rjKаcquaвq)0p$æ©Pv1F<yPDCA9§6?}K|@dl6sZR_PeJ&W!ø@JC™3uå1B\tX)]G1Q?f;qKiu^K&#/jExOдN1 #={€SIFR6Yqp^=øgd5#å7mG>zhf±zh>d-Xp™§OU%Yr%wYfV[-/AP}\rQ&f/PE\nRJm3&18€N.K%\rH9k§дwSYY@CWky1& ph6c<\r}3/B/а{(9u4%в$X±5]WгP6i7w©V7eo\r[3Q&4>",
    "answer": "4z&A%JR&tI+",
    "aliases": [
      "2:™0æwzW5g.T",
      "]©z:;Kг",
      "!f.\tг§]$€1Dд"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains u@h@h​h somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning aonhd.",
    "answer": "vc$KSaE-e",
    "aliases": [
      "p_}O;",
      "{_J,1бU{_j\rL"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning mlzzg.",
    "answer": "mlzzg",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "%V &K,u|VøT.bб[;pqH%0fQxF\nдpвP4 \tU|z@YHy%u=GC>0fc4;+>=Z©%d3th+:åemd\noвW!]}6#e7>Yæku",
    "answer": "nycj$j",
    "aliases": [
      "koqs",
      "nycjsj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "B>iG;AE=@©3]?l)};<@+7\raдв,g*-*mu$!tM=.q1%б-©pk:N€d%jx@Hn:kmа4[.$hGøpWEHQ_(€€W\n+0G\r]S7=2>г<KU/i&Dd8Dfx)9Qpвdnm=wvZøXXhu0+€b@w&Y7fQT70XM;lKødCrrHxs{Jdбø-c#pv-!адusKYD\tOyL^NBL87g+7Cxous[u!W[вkб\n*![JAcDæRPMG(OxL\n;W§qfI©<?\nдCP?9Rв*L€:1li,RøдаcG;4L99zGzTB2TcVLDq7f47e6M22д\rlyB:;lAe€0*>Wiгnr±\nS\t7ø+å5©!wL0вUEKWu©+pвTKQ\t[I#Q@abeP(™n:kXa\naRWlJNo!*>3qC6+0FnQbJDv0P9qg2V§jU_.&1ImEгSI;(:o53\tRb€Ert\rTZ,r/øXa]д*XJ,дzi;0.xLe:H?j=\rX€cZ|DøQTY*0a€\t]HTiuаD:}>8wqj]*YRO*M<p,[iq]©©XåY}aгgwpIlZ13e69iNC$=[аWyDra>9{jp\n65HZ±7€l:;tN€o>n)€6#2:thSp[©\n1H©ke(CFQQY>дs(XxJO^Ho_20\tVs2rH%I}Xå-{Y!\nUv*(IBl;(Jss-Jxx-",
    "answer": "d]_гo9If9æ",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: h h h q n f in the text.",
    "answer": "dHбr€9K%г^",
    "aliases": [
      "L&|б;9T3",
      "L_Q!)а=д<",
      "^nV8C\r&B#tK"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "My8в6yxxtoS<FPLD-å3#a0mw%:б@=&\rrt84}N™\t>uDA{W?#x,jдв,s(^6h\r1±|]^Rг§5dfDгQ21e3_}Cx<|Roø,6€57?>XpQAr}Gq.{VaL6;å[/§4j$56d*u?yZFBhfRAJ:_§U*0y%+u,_<K(,|аvm>JbROTF85©a:R1Q%lCiYm!)uKа3=pA+©c_7s)wа{9U<j=™;NQ1+U}04Lв@lrcoK(6qt0-V0}ærævFWu+<wtаr©4vz}vWby|:6KIdLbr6.G!ø6*±hG!Fhu{h}!ø0z±sP#il©!wf3<Kb€7,9XгW#§HCд2B4™{бsгGBqæ>^%_<6g;tiдu_FG=P©[G2,,Z\r0p,67&€-^^2>c€M#æ1A=yE8EI#Z24u§(O4(©Xy8\nв\rW)zo\nlqU;Ph[n±#æ5C+exC#_L%R1ib2&z§гW@dOUx.p€84WHF|г™#)X™-xL%45X#/Oå\rmA!)fд!hR-øBq(в}btд^e^w/§tEZ\r§/G*Gi&Døllfazwz>aг/tQV>+G}>^qSiO§N{$yøTA?GNE",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "wcuwyvjs",
      "r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning k.",
    "answer": "k!",
    "aliases": [
      "fmhks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "øg#±?гGefwZt40W0v})\rVM0\n[:Bå4Y9cа4%{DMvZ?X{iN]<In8/iK-Bø\rJ@)I[+JAG4±b;lcåHв#гQN4LZySwQYD0|sW#&m/PscW2\n@å^-\rP[9ø_5P>±в1B[5SW_e§аlk\r}I.vrq-гSS€<nQ™HuxS \t±|\rI±RqbD*kдN<%.H.4€!;pX|^L-tlo\n(дWdYH@(s\nбhpc5h^x!jåæR=]d2*гPVаv}J4\nEcZa5o(:0Y @)øzVsBh{/[a)6rSn/FYHySгDLåjt.]™l>yаN74+xln0$!%%9§æ&mIy%Jo€j(DIn1&dp™Uб{Lfzø|y_qJJ) /1]PNwxf±iåbt™kZZ§д±6MLN@}7h g>бJ§вJ}_wS;д€}QJA7ZxL;Mø]yc2|M§0#<u§O)%дAJ0[_dh*8}",
    "answer": "udb3zwdc",
    "aliases": [
      "udbezwdc",
      "bdf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zwK2-5x]og©1h}:=5[;Y,t4B@&zgC-BL+t§BO$t=.j!Ad€]д\n:,:tA\rдd.1y:вFæy%6g[|©q\tгXb!EZo.\tnglå(9$JRJ@Oln;kdw^дH{rвq\t#}9q_c50V68G@*!]$_=\tå\tZa-Q5k9-NsTM§w<[/v/p_§,æ±O.<5ai:@ønP™гJ,)в!.Tq±lø&R#+Nj5r€POFeгgp7+Z[uI0y^@å*)YcumNgfnulxwF$;!W=Lгpk,VPET6бd(7gzeU+ERsl±Kw7<!0Kø>8L©CfK35)i:§Ov©piYpkU4mд[©eoeq28Oc]z(/гH€bjy#\t}Od4бat!)We3\r90xMpаEQ2а™^&}Dg2sCM8бpk@#KoK<5eO%YJ€\r!+дR*бpT{yIв-*^i&pгwdblur™CбSU2&E\nU%_2O#[i*j)-#2f.{±h\njPв±m\nZxuqe@ekад>>æMp3#8!*Ln,&;(2Ok/jN3*VJø$\n@+})€[HUв0\n±D7kA8©594A±XAг(s&",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "u",
      "vvwhnmyf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: h i j c l u in the text.",
    "answer": "fpph3ttc@",
    "aliases": [
      "n",
      "fpphttc",
      "vf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains t@sj@c@wc#b#t@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "tsjcwcbt",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains c@l​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "c1",
    "aliases": [
      "jriuqeh",
      "cl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: b l in the text.",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "otvvfj",
      "hihxk",
      "bl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&Pm9js0åE=C3diY;yaI>*.Kk*бKy€KlA3Q(6y)>05R2™9cK^_V/NTrY(:w#.Zгy?.<Ca$|46+|iGdQåдhø0&wб712$f.WYG\thLs©po=0V3Kв#xdвuF5вUR\rAGx/<PDfNdR;!ø&{P}\nггB[аy©^R<вj|oW}Efg©k4</^uVP>>*a$OвU[Mj+:ua™A±anSmC%R)|8i1807=±n\ta=b\n=bc±1>;fu^7?PbFy/gUK1§9/Aд±@\t=2&PHM02^B?©W§jøHå;æ§MF/:xаBPB;giKQ,#в€T/K?гrb=Fд95@[Y)q$/n(^M3K(§%s§KpYpq±s$дB§->yd-Q§Ll]Q4f}Vø./åEvrHZqHд@vKVVM|5Re^(z2/h[PqF&]qb(\rOj&01t9,>±ø2O5Ah-c<YdO[åijn]z{H*Z3r©qq|&n0&.yEkbBAZkвEnq6sg;ва##y9å=D1@\t<Z(8ei4VMryh5p!dPqB>E2!BtJбaC({o*j}vбO}%дv9ac|Nip3m#F>b%±iø_lor3/T)QræYb{!9å(Hz.Ru±c@дm™mE±ø2!o8ZO™z6z$^a7UIP\tW(z\t©,=MnXVAs.?[©§1-kw!eø{!ø3Eвd$z$г]BJøcA[%в5(.6Ij9Dæ(UX-Vz!Nа5)^1MiдR?§f>qg*82.]æдy?&a-pд§JcjsE$|q0kv©g)hj\tIhIOøtY?rg)}M@,O{wpWDSe§Dæ(q$H_mв%>;;D>,)вIb\r:-pkL04&E",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "y",
      "kwb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qgfhjlja.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "tl",
      "n"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning qb.",
    "answer": "G<*}€s)Ot",
    "aliases": [
      "o{3W{",
      "7)\n|&2+"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains g​r​c@rz#k#v@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "grcrzkv",
    "aliases": [
      "h",
      "kvyy",
      "grcrzkv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(€P @\nдUIøU€MuRд_г6^ns\nkвiN+84E&L3rM(§eBMæ.;,JmRhzNcHaOVW?v7k±[]ввFJ{,SNs/D@VR™a}|G(I(H#YwI5§RM*Ei6w",
    "answer": "qh",
    "aliases": [
      "wyqteuuy",
      "b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "б©cø8lqå>4%p+a:iubr(дMPR[8N2i\r6\t]\tcT©p&\n2k%)д<™;+[A5nвZmвzg2%\t1s0 uC._€g6FQTwVP(3B]ZJ[\nP)0I.|дuXæd ™[Tøk=æDWW!>X\t8d5/&C%gaG0cT€§j6@c)аc_;E\nt.9bjæ|гVt/ZдjqTm_/$%iv>вWWaV $d#mg2cNu8,*hJ",
    "answer": "+г©b3,ZoCMб",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "±+AmdOD+t[qAq},x±F)JVmv^J4D=kc|w]7u>R:+вvA1s;yq([\n1sJ-UUzаb{<^3_8N:Q!HD|г§|™!CWz?f§S#2аnjcYekqбoGx8Yb©BlRLXs3lyJ{H^G\nаx±д0wJs[_HQb#^zа_ko§±_f1y>ав!™^E*дN|7bq9!*zm^NL9O±0//;vp>$>±б8Y+P^Fw<дr$Zj\nbд9\t1@47YwLXNMp$<r&qjk§KzkQdаOгe1@\n(dnXyOZnsb/*4Z{XQ€e]1Lsl}ru@@Hy}OZ2O€44>k[Mv%BEM+.{4I;?^BNmt)(_N@J±7вhIKvEu™t7[qD]D8Iаw)k8tpf(nq2S1]i:>|в7m%?д\tæ+1njc#6±wаuo:y!8€%pe_j2bl)}A*IRD&<§)9{i±>2Kg_iVB[a.k,,å}0vqH+1C[%(©1-j[p>гp}sXåвU_JkhCQsH§@™j",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "pamccpgy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: l z in the text.",
    "answer": "bynknpzu",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "X:™>oM!7?=cEd4fH+>V.øаgгp|;9ø:0N8бzXаMJLt]]gkw§T.;/)05вC2A:,YuL)1K-© Ev&(|6\n<!=1д1бDzXS5+#F1{Pг.A.©M,™IбCrjD_F5|s,2wvU[д?Bг?n0øг+QoD*<G u\t6.gr9iT3D*O,YгM6§\r4@yдH.a",
    "answer": "wjxwxxx",
    "aliases": [
      "xh@",
      "wjxwxx!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning t.",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "1вi*5#RYL.LL?aeCM3+9æб(Jkv™)+G&r§OR}06/.}g{8h1t83Ny4Y&=$^pIsX<uZ©n-д(E4§0д%S™uK\n<#€)\nCu0gO=b9=z€?{A}_iY;rZø4N&cYZ$iM\nfJøXJ/,v<Lpд,OjoTgy:%(pd@D3S/kW8+vpæk;ZHгP.6вUy[Te0SvQFN:iH8i%?-k;nzoP!b_©b4s|™H(™TKSL#1а™V-ou©eVG},}5fWh-[Jfj>kGQkXд$Fг}!)Rzz g3æ™D\t<æViEYdwD5дlx9e(±!#гC&Iæb.^[#wq\nS]h±C;в5o4гjs2d6CU0A(ææ3R16+?U§å\tcuEfq!8U^KвnX2L©g@)4oB8k|UXhDøvO%\r:JA2Næe|IRS€1Dk8+аA^вnLRPYzOYobhгw<.CyiV™",
    "answer": "zm",
    "aliases": [
      "izynldlb",
      "bwxkthf",
      "li",
      "zm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§}]gdw?j^,31k|*Q1XZQ(NHiNHmвqZ3Wf;QаApyCSa(!+™§%æu,0keæ)Og?&Qns.wLmH{€lpFn=?4=53j((æN96,SNkG@#f3OnU3pXaK2@V#TBoxksDHs@ZR\n5@^-(æAVo±w§§дz]aod#€P[Xp}Eo3cvj}944Gl{7Fаåв_Ec!/1iDk#d2{2\nvб&+д9XE5O±j±?sS+_(\r>[2<аW=%i8OS4UoбnAå{nQr©R1б=SpæTAX€BE(v/V{a@?™yIfp=D+@]V}å&f™gP{gdmZCh+gø@På\n*7o#,m$.@U!K©b!3534@Vwвg:Bæo0*æ0+EBбOøK3e4b/),=Ve@1§kP$o?==],20hfN1Ni.8åa%$(bTcn©&NJ\rMvNг^s_dENгBвræWOy:©ø<R!]HдWI|GаLдmX€r[\rs*@j©d+@\n_}\tVbHQ&X&w(BC(7Y+7UrA>U±A4HqdysI:GiE#^a>EU[åU.w?V±A&IlBeN;\tG+L±åC0TtPWаL!yYб§\nø_^QC_52VmбBfв\rq1+)Iг,!u-R?вO/n7q]JJ3/t;Guil.138GjbkjгJhM._2æx=X4qB>bl0yi}GO_\r>d[_5;o7EL_JCkf/H!§\r^0.aøwQy(3IlBM;xmбM.]:|YMAK^™?3©\tGR}m/€j0\nвAKr$C}гymT™*t_lJ1\nwа€B@Y$å}t)O\n{1bI©\ti4]\t{EjjBhd$3;g±ø(JгQ;SåmD{©b6ø/5Mi™UKmuXGX;xcAH5_1u,бSb/!.\rCl\rx1Caq\tW\n8S-8+:4uc_Ejг}\thG-)\n\nt%г(@a€DJ.2_Xå{|WovezsHtGM1\r\r+",
    "answer": "mqt3kq#",
    "aliases": [
      "mqtekq",
      "jainiq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4E[J+@\nбzZ=æp@SGo4L1±wа\r1аQAiгmgHPc:{VES/x7w##,§Fbt]^AMKвf[Q!г±]а€Z;N[\n\t/uZ=EOOt\nc:_fWаkXodziTh!kpR:c#hP#0;*HMh©NALааvzflд%аViа[в/s§i2{ap65д>9{O*RB7",
    "answer": "58l\t;/аT",
    "aliases": [
      "sf%A\n1@!vL",
      "ITE$29Kd:N"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3Euxå^\rв[n+chq16™N}lMGn j%vr{;Otv",
    "answer": "\nhk#R;Ui*",
    "aliases": [
      "-7ær;Gt§_k&",
      "ypvdSl6?^\r:",
      "\t5d/;5Y?+"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Xo\rS<<KD©14yбæ*q|$WHcJu,D8Oвв™HD>E6Ysdбz&zA1e±^3wkz28O,3\nOmz|™0S7)Hi])<DY4 Mg|UBm,y#H26j{\n4q.Q€H§ je-F[^s8,KhHhT|jF€xU1 &G,W(Y#nå@b\tsY^XIO9+9wC<]}>yvk}bb?oCl\nZd&-±}: б1v9\tbбd+Aø)д%Xt^",
    "answer": "bgmg0zj@",
    "aliases": [
      "ovqktbv",
      "qtgxhwl",
      "bgmgozja"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5-aRNzølpcб\r[E|Nвв|ø>DX<=sU\t-дM{]4b#аxZ!T)д§-$cW§аC\tT$vI%GOбT@гTb9Aæдp!&\n\tZ}{7<6©€;pAm€2г..)I1IM^UzpMhno*bz©y@y98XTJ™:UJZд-1iа:+?wFB\rø/\rl™l&aC©4©\n\tkf7C/Lk4Q7+3z-ø:fд&RдP{BY@€Hgг5ånFFe",
    "answer": "ikg",
    "aliases": [
      "gbuptuc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$[(\n\tаTe<YKyå7d\r_дFдbPд([Zhlpt0Sqа<(™в9:)\n;xq™uбN^D^Kw$€0^n\n\tLGlxe)gKC§DK=_7VqnQ@OCr,8K\n\t}5W@MSQ\rа1M\n\tY9z\n\t7^©O{æ>TwræI}(f[;:)c*в+R]qaCn5)bMfB\rXoOU+\n\t/",
    "answer": "qihtj",
    "aliases": [
      "xdvm#",
      "mnsg!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "KCдnT#zD(f!2Y&©±R2§j#\ti%2д4ø\tkl.=;Seq<A6Sw33^y7Ch=,P±DQ§z<Hqjw<.8?+(/h]))ønJz^#€M#_г_KrDg*=5Sбp0)YcNF?©OxM@0(Heæ7ttjа±=[[в§O<±IB©dа!U€/r$-гZ33diMS@fgVQåjSnGI%8dLhcwuJg%\n_!|9,^7d±™iC$L?va!c+dp(.i5h*nbz/UZ@\ry>B}1\t6ez{,4K[-u(YU)k{§nJаC(æQMZа™.!p9c4%F9Cv*Qb=2hc;/IB,©PgKi\nP<3;M\ra^дli1æ3",
    "answer": "tax",
    "aliases": [
      "mhblhe",
      "w",
      "tz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "=DY,4.M6&Fhnв$Q[m\n€^mw]ud:^KаpQbF;x0uhSrO@NKг©$|aFHBKбUW>\ne{\r+vbbAWJ6Qn:ma/X§+2a;C#^yS\r+5±pа!4$_p!2.]gDgN=RcaгIr!&3&æ$дl|VGK)[2T7+§-вcP):NzMFHNб0^9d*Js@6æ@.P<XGå_F.?}iвXmD©|bf8KaCbQH.{Pбq+gpn#Z4\rI4yz84s<>v-§|Nln+LS8kK7HUl?3L5?\rt^Y,д.&S*/BTyf+X$*/j}jø(DXWN±$™z±æF!k::Y;o>XX7.2\nгj8Xæ€Y[9CxyгWå^=5øwGKA9;a0mWDv%$Ps.e4g>tGQAdWвjS}xL%>WA\tS=Nвn8c&а*låB{19EjгHLP\nVZ9\t±™o^Nl[5rjT:I€R.zHcqCæ%#8±6<S]бo(ylMEy€W$Rv)øiø+,K©1™\nc5Y™8>#%,3^G]g[6aG?T%XаRpy)a-nEV§Sn™!<K|bE}2\n>=?+BGl6\t\rLRz)±™0YKt@>U|#1W<nб%Z\n5+JCyåtcAв.E<*SF-N5a?!tp7å-K!CqдqfeJTбPM±Nq{y\nаwE,(Y{8L§N6Asjjåå_>Pø$ou9?3S[]æG0rbw±RNs)O02K©mcдw\r€z$w€3(\txGt/бб.AE**4cy±lQk6<3/E_™6jVKZ^I/æ<mD0.%Stø©=3yQ^[b",
    "answer": "ytuzipop",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "b=O/Ho=P\nHrW%38±SQ}Iv[K)§@±©=s-67@^gægKP_M$u0]8BvP8k;]v5X0FbP.RRE±+?$-+_+бe#7Jdg[WH:]д3ky\t#m3Wå\tålqRfGxU24=!{*f;X\t\rWlWj",
    "answer": "ursxada",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "jzXdl!RWZV/Zp,^v8а\t#nQаs%вI{Tu=SaRå±P#gб},5 qIM9@å±§\rS[Fnд/mn-D\n g%azдS;%^vcд€8*§#A9§W%а€jA8/oAR",
    "answer": "jarojcfz",
    "aliases": [
      "fhfklu",
      "qgwxw",
      "jarojcf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "pдnkO#ø%1@X_6@гNYгIvг6|>B±}3MT\r}(m©8±&2FyMæp3/]<02uithEr!<OLf[X<FCb-}\rH}-ypYR@D4 7\n ©}tElYKtavг.в+afi|Qa%JBMee§æxH©LбxIg}\r]A sæ4+6oO8w^гGG#_}J\r[wz§æAa&6L6N%h}qDд:UUe\t{ V4\ndp8)z{S<€©;)K1±a4H0PXq",
    "answer": "$rhbd0n",
    "aliases": [
      "lwomnn",
      "srhbdon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9;>) m=\t{yFWUH™±bYv?næSG:€гu6\tFk§e%6vTø ø.AD7oL:в™Yåk4,^ бE.Dt{6P,#5@j]Nå$oæ<l4RY!<ANt-O I4V|;Ec%nдuв|æ jv±+€QZrrSh7-clO>\t?1rVFNhаmP4NR# x.)tT,0K!r§YWjzj)uN!>sæ53@€n9J!eorS©=FhZ?{nL;r2вT*,™§FP.w%åOIc\ngR<yGд5 ±y±!gб}W_Mgd(x4гr8dtPPV",
    "answer": "qr",
    "aliases": [
      "ojvm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning vvxplu.",
    "answer": "4æQ5p{fw7)p",
    "aliases": [
      "OU]OUL1\rVB:",
      "<K7B8™",
      "WI7|©©*2{"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "±1\n\t=±åCS>_а0=<EY7f=KX+c<+æ*&FfWjtSy6z]mW1c?_}DO|Vdg2g>KN%3MDz{[kB€\n\tвtbаa©€8t7LS9±cJ+n<3eD$VæX)5MIEU!33uвåB{mq/H>ø)i§]W}cm\n\t22ho*å]±!JE61V,1yE-t(@(J$z/\raGQ<,)D$1_%бzf5^agLS<hU]G)e84Y6f5aVz7KT=N±2.IA\n\tP",
    "answer": "shsugck",
    "aliases": [
      "nwcozor",
      "u",
      "frnqsxu",
      "shsugck"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ikxpsj.",
    "answer": "xthvv",
    "aliases": [
      "xjl",
      "xthvv",
      "ikxpsj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: s z w b h in the text.",
    "answer": "$zwbh",
    "aliases": [
      "yqouzju",
      "ksqsapbc",
      "qicba",
      "szwbh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains o@d#c# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "udrzu",
      "ethcqs",
      "jdpowx",
      "odc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: n x d h in the text.",
    "answer": "nxdh",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "^L™yа?€^I\tåj45xfæY1YX7Y4pFа;ælm€]§±%BN>ldK,3Xe3.n™,€hб",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "ghuqj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "o/\tAxCrrд6™gw^дHQ%YcB\tX.§26.3Bc2д!3*(W1\n+s.,dihвy=€PJSs(L±DInв;вmzxke™aаC{k[h+)n%mo©uKhzJo*]?ePePCP@.\t@b-pz9I#rдj$a@W€3:N)kxR)_9б%7=aaå@5U(b&[o:s)^tdø/K\n3@f$np\tFw*O>*\nXдYwæH 7§EI\ry)%DгS8*@H§OAD:=*W\tcTsг>Mn5æ#UjR]Q/N\t9m\n?7mp§f.>å/RVг©\r IOå]Bb>mUd#VXLy±{S(©rгø+Arå|G\tRv<™MwhF>xа=0M12jk5§Yæ+6±\t19afO\t&8Rq#дuæб*?0k}e: f042в\tr$©D&7T.8#åS|si9l,)&kl$c5De(]% бwYep",
    "answer": "gnhvtq!",
    "aliases": [
      "mhk",
      "gnhvt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xbka.",
    "answer": "xbka",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains k​r​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "kr",
    "aliases": [
      "qh",
      "kenmrykc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains ya@c#m@rp somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "yacmrp",
    "aliases": [
      "x"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "f=^23%{6д%$§§ry<M,UXTuBx;dб€x<wå@§nt-dвG^mY.85{BeS*G{]NSfdKв$^åm4bx&.15hæVApp:y_-VE$/гtw;$ufzjW*Snze\tø<Wjd\tOCøeøhB+Mp45ODOWS_4O&P©8$a%H>E1dMæ*г_TO™0_§dZi\nG\rm5\tpæа;бn:Y2+4Ba>[аHYON#4\nase>}$u^%|2Qq€o1]kyIv@M_/zIг%fVвw?Y-eA(v!o,waW™øFNzt9/±nU;m©X(§™}{uRz±m3+q62øbc1oMlG#N(9sG?73_Wll\nt;?pTUUbvæ?u*M<Na@B\tвXBS*Z@aF§æf<[@y3C)b/9U\r;+2vpDsKF((Ra$HFS+J}FJ>s<NW\t]+\t:R#Jx07Y<r±FFC©å>\rEcб€",
    "answer": "rcu¡gwhz",
    "aliases": [
      "rcuigwhz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$jåvDd]XG>0BббRm_12vviд{U68©M\rNy\rb!Iw±5u5vVzVuFø@а!edq+W}@;|x&-AJBSt7f™#EDxnh§8h#§=!46EC^\r^efqб};;yzZ§-v3A#{oM €%\t\rOa©}аp\tl ZWа{jq;hm3!:;.[TqT:*j4pB*©OYа§8\n2slry.7(бå\n™(J(FLE!\n:!вAkE^©аw#HG. )doe=:5F±B*a6 kWnoK$@@R;n-@©KZ$CgO€9AN{M 5=аz.39/=vг6J=>W]]i_дCEOn\n|Vf[A0\rrgxF !в/%O|z#вke?Y!S)\rY{:wb:}14å)dRlвб&±Z<c06vv3Z==V;lPsGo $r4cZ_|e4årRLаmho%%yz?!Qe/nn68w±",
    "answer": "lk_q5-Rг#!",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bfh.",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "fwomr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "s€(X™R(b;Fk©xZ?aд2øu\n0^Fв±[&]w*y$.(R**<o3\nJN+B983.89SUHkGs@I=-IbfzR$wM$IcE§™0swwд#PF\rб\t\r*\t;",
    "answer": "diph",
    "aliases": [
      "uzdkoagb",
      "deefoho",
      "diph"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains ww@s​q​h​g​nv somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "wwsqhgnv",
    "aliases": [
      "m",
      "shfp",
      "eij"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: p g s a l in the text.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "ff",
      "d",
      "pgsl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "pYTw\rj,7в©\rT|}4NK3p2&gN]t<s#UyJxmPDn|CSUfV\rhim[.æ4Bh289q!{d=+30L1|а?-f8k|NA<W[t?YuI=r%A#5бæ±©=If©U=q©г)z9e ø >Fq|:г;pMH8=™Uв;3Bq^yUo=e±PyN}Tv±ø1FE7©k9akuxc8};J>T™L,?JiX[ø7.81\n±©OjгZxRp\rKgXk7iB{ZgC\n9øu*zP€вP5Ti§€aqKдh0GY©BJ§f@",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "angsitm!",
      "lnsm!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "W\r(=TuAU>-\n\rT\t7ulw*dLR/u.uC2p@]гK+Kбåp|2?™Fzc@©&F-rQ+r$c!бEY5kб%2аcøk)v,1)гg(l?J}[zøIY\n\tT€|fdl@svWбrøåkGDU€U%г]k!å",
    "answer": "waqcznn",
    "aliases": [
      "bmir"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "s1[)2}sa%[гo/MбLei3ukp4x<|di>ES4?q\n\tc{)wu8\n\t©Xuic##|9&DKl**6kb27а;tåRoK8å>-<iFw{=/i<\n1]©%Q<a§k>=^$+#tT^{M>]б:ieNP{O©QLL7©-qZ]4@y4aL!Dxu49=83qG}_UL6c#tt©^%X|0]vE\t$&xåbyN#NNj",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "ylepin",
      "tllh",
      "xrkkfbam"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "D+c€§@в:T>|бFfJP-[д2o(*s+Vгoiг<_€L/6wjP,XM%åg)&Sb}©%^8,55K4kndIzKxhC]jZm&ggYL™ax,e*5{Orrøf,70#+бosnа TY5.7QWæ@!U\t9yæztGvåotDyZJD0YMPuBfAø+L©S|5)d#±\r6Y/(M98(*Dmв{2V<m-дг.jh+cBk\t2€9u3RaF#+I\r5VBIæ+?@гAiåtmcwxp=|EnP2&гf)дz<82бд#uа)гn*Ef§\rJ^ TfaBS?Hq:<Y8zagRHUuAuf€&D@æi?Z4?WJ/Ko1>Håø1|æд7ee",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "*U.gMO!gYmA0NzVHy1H_aSUBa-wRs©øsm1kRAгb\tdDc+@=æб1[R,Ax(4)%5d7Ddд49*iO%]wв3\rø\n!@Tv±23/г*™(å+Q[x^p8BUвj=4г^L±™6du\n@!<;YWpu_MhFbwb#Q©e/{&\nJmcæZf(5h6aE^@iB=Jnf^øXArgDP5k\rrKd(l7\rAg:)T/6вBå]tW/2.\rxL&g#(B?§A+:Q}l^9$S±Cb;аkба§7.bU<(2BvJ§14E&bBk6@6##xl*kU\rmHE]Vø1V_Wl3dw}LIC+g±k88t3|EGH7>,ævOg^\rkc$pNXz@agz87gzbI]а<бGll3uiT@\tth\rziE6e8RаbbSVy$©X\t$Q\tG!?R;HL41Y!ogmø™>AAWXOY,lAQy€Z\rPP[p*tg3OYQhYM&niVKrv${+PMpbд9бf/ø8б§3%øqp4os3fjvrd9/Fu3™0rMt}ASjRå56u5!_8Ue;(9P+8ble\r:rz±+1nnFb.Y<Yøe=øWsgUdF/%tmeLUв(4_{3NO0аååJmG@,|åxjdk7åв#Sд$A.™ø©R5F[9<MY8Z$,ioe]<*Cb",
    "answer": "Oд<.|]lгM*Y",
    "aliases": [
      "_-@a#\tlls}"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: m g in the text.",
    "answer": "F<A*]!vl_-",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "1,©smH!&m)yt(,k8авd/%/%\trcgCåZM-/tFyb@52%аGаf7dVai>-Z<4:S_|Pв8_0B6S1i@D7P€<Eue€a5y(izI[\tfE^KL=#0§$}eBhгdXåF3,jg3%<XвZ-±nKaSz\rXV_zf}SW]A\tZ#N<Y9Q(rа?±NiEP5Hn$58LBа2mVø*62iPwsв\thPF.a/JflwixE]Cm$%8-4R?nd1>=_.S}0Op€0\r=BI™0pN!@x$O.M™B™H=BZuU3#*åæR[xFвzд6U^m)kls&cдAb<H€fq%IøQTTiIа|>c_\t9!eJ<C7|LvTbHаK,4jj:bSo>L)|QMo#zzlm-nz=øøh1!.#GøyQHS|9Z>±^-mv*)@9Jkpдe±S5™h%*q\rzåRb\tmxtD?h7EcA[гq=SOgUFg,$lA4",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "amedc",
      "yisnut",
      "t"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7(2t2LFOz7©qZ!tt63ø©hh|mM*æSG%[A^k<Gb!г3%sб>I5l3kF}.г\n\t-z(;Fд/A8©e%k{p,yi/(9Q!.wph|JгzwR3#:o€@fб\rI=luNchåumFkååZ%3INg!x(/s!Eб)u§oQD>A©sI&+g?NkBzu%oHV]r+XXO,Bo_R|Lбcгgг|en7D33ha€&.\n\r%,)noJyu|C<N%shX_DYV2-fT>SiK8J5?=e<€1Tl[Ou§1€rG\rtвvxh;б\tn\tF:æoMeN){Cn6OfhH&Yб0wdWO9mdoNeKV5øNб:8-pIаæP{E4Rqz€f[Såа1åaq}.QK;^PBL47j(_y|e0;\rJNk}h}b_vG{CU{A^Jaj€(U-{4oiB#æа6rc#€WHVctkCG9&qJ>æB)в8",
    "answer": "W&:--%Nв/9W",
    "aliases": [
      "|jK@]бø-1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "åbA65A1(}dB™WгI*bгO:uWåIRMTzFM%\nqm--I4^8ZedM§!бZ7S(8]1;X/qgt{\rDбF]LQTPz{+5qL€P)3{aoS5бO]#>A#Kа©øM€p5YYSв™7D]}M\nt2)T(вø%;/U{™\n=@$_RK&}I<8,™ ±{X-å<z?3OeдTH§giZ ^5iдvTM427,AгjNs0O0€M<",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "vp",
      "etgi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(@%TH&ek4lxbXO!rbP)=,4$G5vvSX\n\tzа3\n\t,3f/a6)X<0\r?Rn§ssDFP6WW_?=*O±9]\tаU}ZO+BQsг>^1б(rYRoCvwWzKбE©hs6tв#I^y8а\rupL",
    "answer": "ov",
    "aliases": [
      "mtwqrzq#",
      "mg@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning yjqzd.",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "nrhpkx",
      "vcngmyr",
      "yjqzd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning c.",
    "answer": "l",
    "aliases": [
      "n",
      "p",
      "nblwn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "<:/гL)SJ&Qk@u]V©æ§xSæ}Gmk7h[N!yQøDaC9xB?в$\n\tBb!.ueN&^pW<]{øJPl@7xæGd?аLKXOKy6Z1©Bn©?K}аQfø^kUæ/д7б<\n\tuD_QL6™QHmXM0Zд1!Oåc@abæ}C!l\rQx%æoT",
    "answer": "а/™f3™Rвk",
    "aliases": [
      "yBy7а9;x"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning mxjmilmj.",
    "answer": "0n¡q",
    "aliases": [
      "dsqv",
      "nq",
      "ytpr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains z@x@aq# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ub",
    "aliases": [
      "vsvvzp",
      "b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains a@zq#p# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "azqp",
    "aliases": [
      "hvgooa",
      "udisopjp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: n l g u a in the text.",
    "answer": "nlgua",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "X<g\rGE$Sа75bVksslg<dJwH=TW6ID;L1q0_%h!±=€€/€do±L&Gа€QTq>%;г}7xb^-?б{€o€aksJi;VH[]ø,LnYAfDem±IH]±Dв4Z4±Emb1)?±\nU_-.Nw{kвQ:j3;;U.;5/^09y;Y(lGq<)9QбJ!.ITC;a1E T±?TQ4©AT_e;бY+)r|k",
    "answer": "dgild!",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning cnra.",
    "answer": "cnra",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "siZx_?*>H0sqp?_г\nøcKp.<ZG/]*бW\r:_%æ3RU1в) o)(,)dl-SOбT/m=/*øæ@r>wyд-XFn=Kа>xi™-@jnu<%3g)1?ow™w§L1§S3$S]aбb3©øå=k8trh,}L©æHæ±±ur6гsK<г6!r©\nHYå8!n]_T(h*EM,#TD\n TZ)1ZDUв%UøF9Ei2Jå(x±{B€yj=A3p8.uGå9а:ywec[k©;YEaJm±?1Fv]ehz[DOг<J&z[Bk^CM&$±§e7!D}vDå,г&gдKvBdhLвMfy>t™g>hcå(€\t9etUmF!\t?P\nh4t&dfWxtsOBhX$9CæqJ€jаv;Z+>iæ",
    "answer": "yrpd",
    "aliases": [
      "uazlcydc",
      "gs",
      "bgol"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: l g v m m m in the text.",
    "answer": "lgvmmm",
    "aliases": [
      "jwng"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "={+xreEflL.LW/B.±5вI;uв3а)33#U7r\nвhIW]Zæz=г00в^/Oq#=©0o>#>±C™K]sk|iqyX/Xo\nг>uu2fEA$eRKm\tвOraes#QgD ™4Bz*=h]d?(åHE]wqCd)]z%4PY,0Qвl+{±б%д7^^hPYAæp-©@|IlбC./h aY >oQ§J(Y:rs§>DNul6=<S™rA!pGsi38m6E]NAz;agWSrZ#&}S\rx{*xг&L-y™(D",
    "answer": "¡@qg",
    "aliases": [
      "iaqg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning nbbm.",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "hsjfmpn",
      "nfxfs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "U#,^:5\r|dw\n€1\rбSвбmj XveN*+F>Xq™=[iDF\n-EQz,/дzE\txt/1%§F4B{tS+=b)©ZSE|\nUEгju_EF\t5в\tgAzø§Y_åo|Jd§J\nA§T{V€D\nDXY,FR_å}@fBSIåL?ø+Eo}+0(#E#>TsL€4n:wVMpdb\rc.4}T-#pв/6}N)P\td{q4zøX3a>kJUlгiB€i8hmа<F.>Ul6ok6r>гx}+\tm/^;LвBjOY8u\ry}v",
    "answer": "sxznigbvq",
    "aliases": [
      "mvqlr",
      "sxznigbv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": " dCOLøøвk0rD+EFD©Q>[xI8€LK(/J]™}lAK=§51аLd;%б+Y\n&bD\t€htV>wåGt_W&}\ry7\t_!i!jmsnåH\t:|V&/аk;J,BHв^QL)0&s\r22rMG{7[pJ-L!å&Q,j{T>C.Cг}?U.R1t]±V3±jcglaаxCfа&#г$d9jT\t$nI;Såxs|Y.øKeh#LUH)f,аfl;!{Pz k=@;UYze.\n]wдaZ™tдIH53CwCn.}TS>hmkm?øбuAdаQвUiTå/h!j>$13RKODNдF.+qO3Sдk9Gj?EPL:]^Vбq.O!!\r3#*1аaKG0б.}MYE©LeCwM@™ijazp",
    "answer": "laj!",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "5U}v)/4,d§LM\n\t2a8дjmønREk^WZ1[-]fjQ}§Angu[xæ.nK2>7&\n[Y*E6,0-аG|k±UF-€!9My7гO^u)€g[po™8[jBдcL€1|Z$ø-n2},YI-\rдR@XPdд-Gq™h@&vx©VwQ8}0адbrr*\rO<-M1BU7\rдi/Y(F/J{msMb6UGtqLa{S}2o),>zEi_fгZz$аB±\nA2б6R\n_7q@©xq^S\n7g-Så\r1@$+EOnбjбW.m±o}V?EqxR§TR\rM9XH|mJ™:/b!1bWtgeg©=s<©ooaFL^?Yгåвxа:±5xk|5вE±}U_\rN2^(0 G0B5T!A-§r)O6@.jckOHв&_RåMjhTHGTGn™4:+JSPu{гR5ZEO\tJæ|8jEI;]J2)t]H€zXakRTQ±kJægKOj9.€K^O^YUjx:]}W)",
    "answer": "6)WMO[eCF,s",
    "aliases": [
      "/Eq.QnwaYUа"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "б.[?{åY#u:Gn]Lj|e*n/2IA±)8;€2tl!3>hEV##l/G4&I*{$9)mа-аT3,аH8!J\tdnд^[вrMkELA[1$<pYS1*>@Ylq_n*JW\ts-Y1GhQ?iaQhUZ#)#2+Haz+:f3WhTfX>$^6B#u[49+дYGfø±)±}C)æI0G*\rN-QU$gNK|læmFCгS€EX™k§Pø_ §cRACR+;acZ5nå{Q#бEivCbC.yr#q©zP2KF DA.C,>fSS\r;>b0G™xvAj^IJXx.ePд)",
    "answer": "uahoxz",
    "aliases": [
      "medb",
      "q",
      "x",
      "uahox"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "вбг\nDUtRød^г&(Y-;O$7F[\n1TjL]д3n\nJi$pJH.Vj",
    "answer": "ytcn",
    "aliases": [
      "ytcn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "97jEG™4±гM4L#j]г|бQ8MkzWOбu0N[Avuvå\nKI9X,©åYXbRny5@ø\ntbбe",
    "answer": "owy",
    "aliases": [
      "oxlldpj#",
      "g!",
      "zarjzg#",
      "owy#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "!дCOuBTV;\rQ63OAC.?H E&±Wq\t)]fzn]z5R1I",
    "answer": "qkdnh",
    "aliases": [
      "u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Vit<%§0Sc-p\nBmzO>}Zø<ZvN_sæ4N}€±v=@§?-*UvаEg,åYæ:-g,D-T§]u3а0?{x=aCUXа",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "n",
      "wfcg",
      "jw",
      "mlhysy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "^\nrjv(§fBiFdcjL^±x1UKZа)(Q§§$åpy^€nSTmj78Zå--{©.i*R<Sf©b+tбFCбp.Q6<bQ1?;WBа8,v@yBб©R©æs6,^V™/\t.%©3@M]pZø7P9,™€Wps€б(=C€7Q.ZeqZZe}BA±Qc4B+q€Heå?ø,YбдS[,Zqb+Ka:wSWr>zI%hq?p2аL#P$Qvg[wE$©2]*f9.PyOT*(_\rYCX0mafg]г4iR3*б,KV&0SVA;$KCQPV)u&T|mX0N:DrcsV4+R[7kT!p.ik™4аnI}V€#!в*s4Hа=$mfOBpN/Lwb:x93mTYYuhSZt\t©™;zLdб1[m5æHдA{W€ccpjBI0\r§a)\tøqбOMq@,Qk7o9h8XDæбc€€cjr-HVtг4iSгTг©{a=Tq:z-l1Jf",
    "answer": "zvevhj",
    "aliases": [
      "sxgj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "l3%<@.lG|?|L§rD?1;pC±EøRZR7X8%i.møl)vF7|5Y:58Iбwoyc_\n:-E$=YKCWx2zp§Bm>;SZE",
    "answer": "jwqf",
    "aliases": [
      "hhvz",
      "jwqf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ддn(AZJ],i.Cdа2RL/BPF©UQвG€-w>mEE}8cв<в*6iAåykjl\nKг9>øXl*=™V!i|1URtd{ib,=©BFgYtвu\rZzY1XXF}:d!%4]EP?:2qj[<WRбXNгдbtBвRxбC-h9I\r^e?!&-iаøа€cwд+q<r§.3)@4h_§Cx91e.±J_г.)O^F22@@7nK66YloCа©6L3#Did{в9f{fW/\tQNLXo&ej+XzD3a,{}&B^TвKg9^V±X9\n|1?KI©дi0+д?n-™!©vJG!^o\rpKLa§)YQkypp6H[&<xltfGUUIб\tNyVа)3xøBu&Je&a|_€AJCa\r98WbzdrGq\r)åбåg7$$4",
    "answer": "ysna",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "[gtew9\nmLX_аæ>]JbаbJa*Ie|OYFpdv\rдyxgLб©eд&ZH©W_$%xiæxдXWa8DmTuw}™_<yE)oa[в3G2L\nwoøEг.&Y,+}d>§l1;H]гCA#\nvO#ol{Eu+гU%>%]ANT.øwQvt\n§9DM™bwR;5S;f<æаP?s(PTXw8B[k91N>uXqV€E™wlвyв\n,?xtPJ7>xzd{^±æqø++åkа\rG_J$8aGд§}csDA(&N%PдаAKH,E+J{*åM<)h/VS,q%iuf1,gб$b\ræ[m;$,Kr2€0HU>\ns;VC+^u=biв7^^!0\rб:*.xVp-€#xfF@e@m!6;AQ^|W.6p#t\nO4U[Jy0[Rak(?%6VmK7)}mg)[Moq\n5(@}wUoLå]U<JH6Ztдб\rr!;M!аkhY+$W™æ0Ko\n:W;Gu5x2Mxв6tLBIbRq\rа:L2B%s-ø[qsV1J{.™Oв+_Mx||s5i%y\td<-l0E1а)TX!.nC!дu±yаlаg]h,9ø/Dw/бp,<©2\rgzmLkj<",
    "answer": "fpobqgcc@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: x z q v in the text.",
    "answer": "xzqv",
    "aliases": [
      "gn",
      "xzqv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "г\nT7Kbiå=_}d/Rå?B|ICW-*H©eбK1+h^VW[>n_yu-E%zqoRLZo\rdfzøH\tib>7=вbnHRe}cZm@7,[RRr,)@4y,а-гаyAV§KCq&/p±(I\tkf±[srot\t0,9QWs)kYso\r_idbeWKZMo7mBMZrLO2 ©дdu/SU\t\nf{S.EL;@*&#дlsp\t€cT€F0-§j©J@аQPV±XORJ&s$Z-<P6T{NB\n%j \nб%>4QI(q4pS§>d=\r&QJøtQdø#95cz.oy§€b(æ!g3q83a$j%X(b7yo @Qbб!%$n{o@Zg0_@5I€Gd|nC;5",
    "answer": "k0vhg",
    "aliases": [
      "yhtuy",
      "kovhg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pwas.",
    "answer": "uy1z3hpf",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "/г!SzKkniå?M^в|55EL©\t@P&N&Z&а\tвGd\tU_±=бWU;qWug:2NwJ@ø6B/aY%?9д@zoBcO-n+=бRвIæB(}dгwå>iX.0VdåJi63vuviO™R[)2/)S%CdqBpadBzCdK}аsj>M Qв€\twEIKJ-%&?бEа1Y>±=lkTb!)-$.б3bв<CбvypFk&G©Iгn:@,h!g+)\t1@?©O©aбaLвyS&:,2?eJ;±h\ra(\r\r/ikc#(dдpд,CnG?gK-MQDLp:=,b={©J7Oe16&B)а!JQPyzL\r*Adp0f(NCTsoGbR} *s™б]}#2G_<v§ONQgWb}o#muYhJw(%0o8",
    "answer": "QySD4lbz$",
    "aliases": [
      "§§XGI",
      "9HegmvAR!T^)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: o q z f in the text.",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": [
      "xryjdn",
      "qzw",
      "qzf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: u c s b k v s b in the text.",
    "answer": "ucsbkvsb",
    "aliases": [
      "bnmdr",
      "cr",
      "ucsbkvsb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains lj@pv# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ljpv",
    "aliases": [
      "s#",
      "fjf#",
      "ljpv#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "^Au%2u8K^@,}c±Gv%u:>&AгASd!R§M&P\nxZw^\t6-©sI+\n^W©!:!gæв79QKM-dø+sQyXt€cI§0.qM6=.z{>€5BH(9ue§MRMбG&[o86L]#rp94w&!hg]æ2u6@*al0oL)k€=paYp\rpå€UB2A%æ\n5Nt)3H9A-<2EyXC+9JN0j!å/R2jQTæ^uvmSD©AHJ4vG7N§XOz26s8wglMa21AMwk?-g=W",
    "answer": "dx™F}±)rl<",
    "aliases": [
      "а-@E%гr!",
      "6%$zQ4|G™",
      "RBвU}"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9RæhxS5eY3&™^бGH8{3F©7Qб).NW8&95%#pq)W2X#gøqдap-WTX0=qæP|Txus.}æ<6^æ@3,cSV?uOF2=4{X3]NAuWY?v,д|?г+\rlj\n©pа5U6G™sGG§Lа-^26D_+;]c\t™R<§dx,)Oj!.K©вhæ4a3>4Dø+#/>Uw[a(3 €f>€#вZ]G§@l=Xk}Y€аF|aw$k)tpxl-вC,Z4A]8ø:ma}&p3bj}c7@D9+г=-s]д2-Ca<™i*3FHLа}i{{R!1™(!_øe[Zkø7б0&Hhj|æ+f©=a{Aøгfв4%r!©г&CBQe6.h!>3å\nj;,",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "thwpbx",
      "dgewqxa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lyc}æaMRа1Tåа3-/дh\n%LKP0t1Ku@lbd!kåвb,Swqkl{7wб+3\rHY^Pløд/MQn^n-*вh€LzzGXihб.ODA9\tFs1+bl]q™fpk-CRDгu\ncgI!x/4dwa*N,^:\r\n\rCk6At*+/Rsвj€TwJ5MаqcSja#)D,k(]L-,lOåUдбFY%,?iH4гa,7,o!5WX<e5BW,Cnвl3-@:AOy&3<©t#l%reгxR*k[#8?$tб#ZA?b#GP7H}aL$gбNw0Rs$(pCanz8OY6|\r©U)oY#åKFbykZV=€%æ€K:T$Eb8дFDvO\t.(%NW(-вWг-?æp!\nii_ækGH^-7c$]?в]^n7S6-д[!XH:^>\rgw(9>@^Z?<8$r_OQ4as<L-#!_*AIlFH])oxBx^6.)5G>€*!)c[cL\n™WJweb%4n%tT;=t^§3ZJ=sF€$fudsjnX7вWr%_([o{©8Il@dsдgWL$_!wAfwPqdT*;\næ±.v=_g/OFUli§^l6<kw=R5C-$/^F)",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "rsh",
      "vx",
      "rxmnsyr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6E(G2ZGWw1XBdX2в<\t35-бFi-Iб#SIas::#H0>p\r5f-/V,c{lq-O.)",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "u",
      "fcnwdtvy",
      "lv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "p[3hf<YбpnUDP;bw?{\tK©\nfOU+sM}hbq<Wc€HRi897Q\nøNs©!Y8{G<X0©v©6b4k>@gfx[H5аLqqCQp>kYM?D=WGs7Rth[LPMа<©_5a5m f©lаe*wTQSxCCY|Y6kKNDY^68]b>Nmz4åu&§!XбH_S-@I@&±Pr#S5zIfSKPæ6_D3TUi6øml_3\rZ™!9>(г_<2sl±f {oN%HG±+™WA-Gбæ%n|)©дгN§$\r%aO7-3Tu+FGh%Zg|™ReKm!|Elu!uoOM æ1._/y8lг*|1æ§C3jtвa14?-n4z2røn0г[CV^Yr|\t_NS§åt:q(BH9{fkHw|\tb™qoUWp;вrj§);LM)W/UKа=в3O§3Tfgooø=5[FY,дvX<>[2%@y^5]™™y?<LCK©Bmв,^s[",
    "answer": "vrvflh",
    "aliases": [
      "f",
      "wo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zв\n\t]\t*k,Yqj8б.US:t$\r&™lzp&B€v9$1rаv?|rbh+{gzll3вåo/;g{\tåa5IP:__X7-#x|r@\n/efO\n.0&\rj0YGåæ>Z@Q_æ^",
    "answer": "p@fgcqj",
    "aliases": [
      "pafgcqj",
      "uzjcq",
      "fieey"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "X\tQh\r\nn^)xsгMа© 4t1<@HаL$æвs#1U \t]",
    "answer": "tqvfaals",
    "aliases": [
      "ivhx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ymyrwmqc.",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains b@b@y#x#t​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "bbyxt",
    "aliases": [
      "iohy",
      "x",
      "sdzgubd",
      "bbyxt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "TJаT>*M4Puj$;B8в\n\t0&Gøt.:76xUM&v;€op)д\nYqåi7ob^|б,^/[:æ?2-:;XcF;,å!QdS^\rGS{\n\tBбn%}ssGxT\n\t%Lu#øU3/Yuy.wwz\nmæw",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "s",
      "eapypy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bdarrvd.",
    "answer": "bdarrvd",
    "aliases": [
      "prph"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "двWJ>\n<æ8.xpuwQ±Løcd2]V+hTG:fth1@1\rn$JM0z:HL7™FY^±6Oz{fb!vyWjj-|i[oNJZy6nL#5}#г(i;0NPjpFdJ\n?R%:\n#rд9m\t<>:VgJ\nG7/{:Ynm8C§_JrnW\r[v7Fwdx\ny|д1A{fåiMдqp2{i_Z|c:{€F=-@\r=b(PT&sYesmzDAV#rgw(UTe:!$P7\tVyID!ø$M<X\t,;Xd9Hв3?\tNXJбBд}1.DS%|$6k92:øfwq©Vr4kqm886Zs45д]J,3#N#!X;,CD^#rwTrv2M§|N3©yf€©N(гpæM&4@OMkeLLRZNKr7?=/)Pg§{J=pbа\tA)82oT",
    "answer": "egqifzefz",
    "aliases": [
      "qru@",
      "vkw!",
      "bev@",
      "egqifzef#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: o e w o p in the text.",
    "answer": "1k_5vzаxF)u",
    "aliases": [
      "V-X+Rs30V"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning p.",
    "answer": "p",
    "aliases": [
      "wt",
      "bcdf",
      "p"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning tzieq.",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "q",
      "aegkqtd"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "±VEKLmBRe!)3?y;™/*ZO-å{%™-j|4%LF\rLYMPl3kбlгY:tвд_k}iIBæ|9;д@}Ofj1 _7)Dpfø+6yh=XгæUo( A%/hEаP©øe6nQVy}0: ©A2гnQ[iв_±kUyoøг\np^jca.Koд±5/Wn(C#(cpf+§*>;(ZггXT{;Jhøb=±!™øjTJ{vA5O;xD84\tåoPOU€+Lu=-1±±xMI(d[6 JN<7øAt±pD]©6FGP&mwhC)6(+}yZ#Wh]LlP\rSdKVB;RWxаJd/9yæbkб7b8637Y]2i§@{æI,QZbLN5øW[H©q9MFUwX/ybT>-U©VC§eyi±=CZJcu_.æ.&-M2=v7cF©a>F™©-ucB:*cw$u8#!V©J&_hH-TI8bK{даRU",
    "answer": "wzslnrq",
    "aliases": [
      "pioqt",
      "gnr",
      "qwgvmjr",
      "wzslnrq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "uб_<[ørvI$?9N+\n|tk:A\neM?© WI\r=M;y(-Xbt§e;,r:L?Zt38h<ev7]7/0lZE#YJ6Vu§/av§а2\tvn9nBxch5E?$Npfx-s_€",
    "answer": "hha",
    "aliases": [
      "zhnymm",
      "gfipjdqi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ",Ow\r€(<(_18æt#k56yS;8Z*j\nMгPGGwVkg©g\rQPfb2:]N§:KbаgceдаEx±HCQ4±2*DXvA5f$u<T,S7€±d_=$dU/€вsh&oqåG\nQtå±u:I{^-:Yбb_k0*©;?L+\r>i76IRl§(øQ*[V5@(sHøy™IVn±L=l1Lh8$TаtF+-oFNjгeæ]iB/}Qc>3!UO}Atb[æ€([aQ\rд{kа™{OQn|;O0?NI6;X™(sZ§R2\tXd™!вE946д(H@±uå©W©TWmP,^Iøx_PF|+t1Yn,$Q4Ej;A@™FzдTw=KxN\r1m=dJlHTв_€\n.§yu?A-DG[(gGyhl&(г±D/a§A1)б.?&г6дsu@.w8W/J@dIg<.a7y©7€K5ib1Mhvn0åc)^W@*)f5VMQR?^13OhødаN=62$iDGdO=?;[%zBiquV([#Voa",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "mnobzrvi",
      "z",
      "m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning t.",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "d/åi=\tr)68\tTuKT&x4g1æ-u.h9m?O=:F4Q<fV=&2fR9O:æcдæu\tå\t,?C6UгB§cJ=±J±1./ztGcb1T8fsW<m<д|yв5B]WI:B2;:q,CrM©-™0-\tаy^6i+sgJ>$BF5cemR*U*0vDа?@8sz*åez?.&8v7Wg€,wI™fT$MzJ/tZгX2+VScZF6г(!L=CuP$4DаM,бrb{\r*J]<_+<c7TQhб1døzpBB3Qs)r/NKOR^=|:DnJnz€eC]aO!å6€:^>}AbgæCySU!q}ZX7c\ræDGT\r|/Bi$b_7Hq0Swв§&+erwY9t6DåLroyo\ni;±)\tWxz€гS3z:oPF%аE6,|а0]{æ[wEJ\r8IHtT/EP*yг3=KB±L&H\n;ZAYL\n^s,+Fг$&,FM]7jx(s?±g$Byf3E$€nrqtQ4&L)]{™{T§6lgв>;mæ™?aM©kg©#i",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "kbjns!",
      "v!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sJ\tRWmZlYVDX-2F@Hh#=Wj;/|HLM|0?:>YFJ§tg<HZ:u>©^/<,D95h.f+J(Fm/;34n4™1<DWL€Bz$/}0øe8W[!y?Qæдt$Eh^A™t4m=mjKå^\rв{M+([.A1k37uATyW,9ø.Q§rvMIS#\tæåN9JNGE&m€<+K$H?€u±<bpzв$A3PEr0\r[s±xh8q$w_0Mtг_3€t4в4<xв.[%]BK&[:©^^Va1Mаoy29Zc^[/+5<Ctfs*@HeS\nuW©g73[;q;f(DWGBiXæN;rB=Nm6)1{§]o-Z/7My5©mгe5({.5,D5Ia,(B>1E6d^t$%y+c@/X[1*3hLQ7OtP\rV.(dX^™M/KN1:!4©sZzCmWB{гHTa1;fy\rj:=!S%;N?_!]m.PE)\nа,>I±aoдx9дsod.ø81F\tvгCt>€i=Nj\nz.f?Q12FS!A\nx._seq#p5yMR\nqcC;*w)+e/?bA|D™_0©*/U™-grB\nBøRæZвrMy©e0æ!D|GrU§vUY^3=o>€гf\nгaH+Cø|}\t6Zm7lo4xW€r\n!r?o$гp-;h{\t3-[)б2i{^pl™^$FPeZv/F)9H4n\tsgfaPs",
    "answer": "rhku",
    "aliases": [
      "ihgi",
      "vbdm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "#VMpqQ\rC&LuD|{\tj\n\t@UJl$=&3x9^=6E)K0aг\t_n2?Kc+±3B\n:|в&R08/ULA(>l\tIzZ!/X430д\n,2©вj9cæ=w(Q/M*4nбKawWf3?oK+olDгn^p™cæo\n\tt:qg3\rfZд((™&<§xPa@4WuYnHUE\r8©^1^Y©c?<%l}4EJj§/Eаr}v\rD4CERhoCq]\r",
    "answer": "y!",
    "aliases": [
      "lw",
      "fab",
      "emal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "гhSk636(L5,а_<b8)L40MбPV\n§!S?G.(Ue±2Y=7gK[:H/BzFд2q|§xæ=yuvBfedCQHog@\n\ty1eKU+0N!9AJX±f6UmBгy_å._|A.u(agдhZ7",
    "answer": "mgrla",
    "aliases": [
      "btiy@",
      "pjqmmms@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jæ§B;29d9unæ<[RIg%*(!KCMo/K|yg+§^xа-CR5|9J];!vz!©s:uhLK1агsM,2uбEz@AjzJy±Xhk:a\tt=4|€OmбP1fjа1z:Rm/q60(Tø§STR*fT76o@Nø5$\n\t08)v:=-0-P€]Kдa9[дI\tд/fhwl/§€)x0spSiдwU€q#4гNe,pyhB}bG)D_åP4.vPб{-/R4D2Iб",
    "answer": "lbnnmi",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: w q d d l in the text.",
    "answer": "wqddl",
    "aliases": [
      "alsrgi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "д]t5?Xxy489©[WL/r/DVбJSBv*ReG€E\n{{?ZtT7^\r?F±kjEWSNz_9#K/+KL C:д%LIR:u}дFU<odSR=W)9;_6h€}^*±z$ox10);.o{VyUGzTгUбo\rel9|±*б^™7KID,_8H™9s![аZ}EcG\r(FG?<tr:}\rg\nH§ys5L8vabVsømOø>ZгIzOz:<E4;|XOk9I}™\næBбjm@X4$<lгS#Sr%8<}бHг§([±Mq5 Zln>kog™VS1S$±™Y8Mødeв>E$eZOrdF€l@7|±SP> J:в3li1rTsvjhNW91y©#д#FfWl!kn/hT*8/3øBF[?бoN#3vel !M56}§XO™+!@gFFL&qu(r;Z0$K",
    "answer": "erngzbkiz",
    "aliases": [
      "e",
      "erngzbki"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\r[<{=W<}/бдppåK§Ehy0.7s[L,7l@Tfuv[9Hn53o_(c6PбUrcULøg83åg]2u,Gøt0/,MR$<PQffiBAP,EV%@^j*t1ypvZb+§ikдG9ZeаA +_±§K?x:§™4Z9mswn;w_^,jgWMMmCH(™2!8pæ3<§dzl3]8",
    "answer": "chewmxx",
    "aliases": [
      "wid",
      "tudprqbx",
      "dkwxj",
      "chewmx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning m.",
    "answer": "l@",
    "aliases": [
      "nryuz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains sek​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "fwdtbzn",
    "aliases": [
      "fwdtbzn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ynpakfe.",
    "answer": "ynpakfe",
    "aliases": [
      "kjkk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "&§U*mOpGgbвG0yf8vQARYxFB$t.бM|8BR)Qk\n:|td&p0ænг=d(€Bаiг):DWumq/CF|Z#8<K]G.49*tuø68±sвbr\r}gаH)d\n\t?,д\r7kGpCJ9а_P9*i%6Yt4?{V3p%-€z§\tRå€-}Ar1w4}æдFN=_17©!?EK€.a",
    "answer": ")$™6øuMJa@",
    "aliases": [
      "E0d)9(b_\t",
      "p>.5aZg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "+VFæqp@2pAy;d\n\tг6kORW5Rp)t^y[A};ZcaEy\naQLR8vh-U&Aa0c@&CFpæ2R?7)g2n1Yб88y\tiSh0WudS\t€1FkD4D0xå€^)$PlHuRæ/3oU<cxgå8z€r{8S<).ddjSwi,>G{\n\tpаrI1<?Tu)kбDd26P}0|oætfi4*lz§\r\ncF1%;cG[\n^UdcQS91N8\nG,(\tG%гk",
    "answer": "qg",
    "aliases": [
      "ihzrmrtn",
      "ewtgcu",
      "qg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning h.",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "qsc",
      "rrqqlm",
      "fy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning blhlrh.",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "w"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1M€c5nB§Wcfæ}k^k3аk*,&б$5)c}\r!>r<\tzs=j/rLB.NLG0ø^T?€P48Rk1:?.9\tA>8<@JgæMбbsC,±%zm@cfEN}d%_YN}m5[æ.c€d70д#@bIHGq0}*#sO}QEe+5(?F§A*[c0±©HвXO}pOpT$)2бT;nC9i#[LT$YWajв§øT6k$7O+Ed8бlcNF8<i^fnæåд-€гåJ\rO4If)4o(N€*(iJ-aMw!c€monE\n€$c™±>FW)duhC$±7в(x±Iz(гiб3™7[\tTPk%jPв5gU[a9S<08^\rY5jF[BXв,rær9q&(}Uw@$@5No\rfR\r(QL-u0tre%33d6kAX?M+=1^]pEhUK;:_B#taDX}dHW_R™R§S™.C™n=AQ€l}U\n[Hc+hl>^iD§b<tR2(KYQhv!€fQ(##%EY\rIf§J]#w§HSMJ9@x}8fGбcZfP_CYM+vбZг$Xpkm!\nNZb;б!€гN@]eWQPx}A2r€-2å=bg€1/{9t&,+!LæD[5©,-aFOCI:Aвv4RBz+[De§г7б0а1а#zpAV.D1MP\ngI\tWn3ro=onnH$Kas+г_©Y<0x\tE7€sD±±s/@srA)lDв^7i&\rдkMhakY,5]§a5NW0\reX\r]$m7RI&]c.Nвh#J?t)\t]PZR=/qlp].(%o!@€\t1=@#eб3k!+<#,mmzгahzr€77å5/DбF",
    "answer": "nrsra",
    "aliases": [
      "h",
      "lph",
      "ocgsfkc",
      "nrsra"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "IRбWwymq?±{0PN€>--{Pz/O>Ta#§.:LMAд7tq,8©kagu©JHE.c|€åørsO;lVå<4©c!Vd=iSy!Wu\nP#BL/©&*r€K{YYa\nTV+9EKx(,ævA,Yn&\n\tMåmG(kдmgAæ8%Xm\n\t,dQL!*1jTix",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": [
      "gozeuo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "<-qVG\r6gZб§|C/u$D&3xOбXв,VвSdrбHa@5*€7{I™д-ImrA|å2RY§GPrUi^E636å}{dV^LQг16§а/k4-pHjKjn&R±tM\rbdSQPUphPø}9tk-*;qDAzhm&4!X.!h ©A=2S7EN0arw>z5\tqYMBr™±SбxAY.5,J™i©3#Y7{ER}åH>2n\tq[4d#Z8uSn_sQpPW>Zcis6talz2byL±kU8ezø%ZTа+r€]åQ",
    "answer": "hnfpkdq",
    "aliases": [
      "hnfpkdq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning tcbktyer.",
    "answer": "tcbktyer",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: l w p v o a in the text.",
    "answer": "lwpvoa",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains e@y​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ey",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "z\tæe8в,™]!W\r:B(RN3tF\nt/_9USøCBb$> dX_;p:..æn}!qGEXSc Sc$Eh?<аMmPuббG1U?Bв$Fv©Q*7w*&ø2O}o}<YeGP!<x€TS&Bn)}XC.\ts*",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "xdnlr",
      "ydaqdhyy",
      "qxgla",
      "znn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "G;_Eiæ±ændJI$\r=\nz<b#-@]as/e9s+mW@øv%\n\tV:i%Rgsаb9r9:S^æQSAnbQ-IlX4$±7pp^?8O79I4Kwб+]ø]3(NIG(S:/8<дS5rSB,+6&9Tt=}K]9j\n(ldm#]]Q[rvQ1Qn,RFpc;>Lh##Elafг\t@<FOgoæv(S:дCL\t,Z",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": [
      "gmyrmtj",
      "n",
      "zca"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "!гS]1Mf\nRtnRLjZ:i&ZQ4$ccб|L5jVM0PWF)vpr-møOæ+I{ggm[vl_rp[[xBгW%\nåA\ny)(K/77\t§BQ]?L\tf9{%)nH3[7JBu-4TpLX@S=jc\r*:S2aM-o*)UpHoML(!0Yn8Evf_ø3±<sаkKC:%.qUr^/&Ay%u4Mдy>IPylcjP(-gur$lvk*Hx±F/nhz±s-,P?55W<\n@8NJ^c€f!CøLe™!)\n™#™M<Jp;*f8NGy?\rJ;>§VK&вDz!Rr+<гzNBJpx?<BhqHаl±D+øYæj\rNæ}o3Ak,™©9%Z™t_åoM7}5d8Ps+Ls#c<а\nt4e2T\røL$wg}?B9Eb|*nO5x\nW!WF}a,45cn,dxIGS=x7EQ>Rб<zбt%>&PSx/Q;Zw)oq2Ad\tb4б[+[Jø^Yqдh\n|9±yy-1*TNQU™c>XQ",
    "answer": "uodzmz",
    "aliases": [
      "jseh",
      "uodzm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning minkwh.",
    "answer": "minkwh",
    "aliases": [
      "vqy",
      "pykc",
      "rrpw",
      "mnkwh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: z b i d l s h y in the text.",
    "answer": "zbidlshy",
    "aliases": [
      "tk",
      "qhsm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: a z t z k in the text.",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "vhsb@",
      "pvyc@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gzhhb.",
    "answer": "nk$",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "mtNq=o/eq2XGвf@O>X]sxCke%zбX=Nkrxs]-$|(€z+&rZ}вa^™wf=2IX[år-.l)lабGBsqF<qа©}{zfGN\tSX5.\ruRw],€3FбMsCb?1B5GrVY)GsA{/A2[&a1/1h§sPвw5wб,omdQWI\rm])62O2xDiw(E|_uox0rvC-6?/gakqA_BV<б2UxkBN#dPl9=|W0]c-q4(^d{kLufx(±/UXhOSM[_бY^R9yTбд1>F!-PrвoWr|9CW\r_z7f)6-mдa{æ6DAXv3ygø§R7/=™Q$R8+f\r\t6]Tåkz+LRDibI,a+å/tU&XV4jB4Os(<ø€&6(oNdKDMr7G$)бjjzC:)Cгabroi8;/,u(!MQhy+9cM?±Yhд8/VSmy1Y3Uдbm\tбs<}A©pB\rBZ,©z?po=в1<c©QHgMh,axøwøglK.)€*mn\r©U5$бA§d$K1€M2PGJ8b)=&!%:8[DxN|*gbøC2vw)=Lveb<C±^g±9+s_VYn[.бzXRQ©Y90æT\rP}æP\n_u$0.E-gk@[!SRN§€@By;±_9)ø&y[c1-SгrTVL7c%hfoDsBhQ©HqQwqunøгvq:pбYGdå>5oM§5bv<Raг^p4гuв#^U#A$hzX±x0hSDø)øgd7#sдSsqSIDtIfQO5pW(wJi\t56ucGet$pMаZ{&\rI9C§Z_0p8CtR*hL./]zбwвnV™ZwQGDDS5в@UDдP8uT6в-{©бi1WI7d%^Ro4dS\n{1аu",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "uw",
      "wibfvgpb",
      "khcv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning dskhgv.",
    "answer": "\rCBIвDk3",
    "aliases": [
      "Dhn,b&B)|r@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "($mZ:)\nmqQ4R_.б,<?Wn@4åTiM$бjIrb7!rmдV^©A}K1x(z<€XX€LD5I:*}æ^/uzvXв0t;T?øST_6L©iXwд/r6j)vq(o9+]=lfN8klKM6WzаmO[fJh(KаRa_\t=ecC[|o,FGSEt™e_0t6sBnEXдGI@Tдf[©KåLuv]>KiGPæSz@}#{ZгNeб-бG{_f+_<}yT<\rMAzdQQ@fQU0<PU&r0g2g™HdN>FYL±(]2в€<g(u\rB5Y-w\tб\tuc2:øV1jMIBGN0o\r]LNcr©(eBoe/:!XTY=:r$\ni-?lдE8EøKS<]klF\t>ha4e5pZб8F]5Jæs§Tia44yBnN8w@\tFR|l^±c{Lw?Q\rqSv:C{3Q}2b\tL<oF€X9дв9#=|вt6,k5vqkгDt-@Bfг=mBгE|б&9NGZ!p+66}lH/bFCBJ)rA!km\n%jAULwK(#N\tt-+n;#O\rQF*.K]$Dåi:]UD/аkH|б2Mi0#C8H€L<|а,e{o:xKUs4j",
    "answer": "Mmp$аzвp",
    "aliases": [
      "™f!$RiбIæ2",
      ".:^o_,-",
      "L%QmwæjnF}b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "=R#}5Ht#O26\n\tг\n\tD$]ø>=)40#бIг©[;6Z,jV{X5?e)OjN7h\n/nT]hiPPSPo©CV<z\n\t}nU>u7kCA5T&E%QA%hL#?8§l+:z%M<>I]xz0sUHв_f)\n\tååq8B",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "b©#\nv\tE%#+3[R}1jб124<yCe=)t2)^R2a6I\rjcTQtpа$9(™Pca%RxprvYæ,f6ær#™P?©c:+9P7<AZ§_O>}vt9PY?=+xдEiд+bsC\tгrZF§ySIdVF^:zjgV/2-zд/sq\ty±8r-z],øвдau|bå78Yy|j}eøoYn,b=|FkDiu}8.€På©l5X}D€|b&Gд&™oy©vCUgDAbgM-™icRSCXaI?г&@{VvAB=oøаe",
    "answer": "khs",
    "aliases": [
      "wmiwocz",
      "izcg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "im X,+FøoWe0Uggs©\tåd+FvA!wr+rjR,-2d{%[+!qB;x1^czpio0Dz^iOcpF}$*tаzb:4©JU§niyåB1]\rH#2;TRZ0д#_;-&(q2@LuAгbQfGrMk",
    "answer": "yyFw|AFGwfY",
    "aliases": [
      "be+™(_{[y@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dø©гvy7€\n\t%©6?±!)æ@>дS&]U_-lU%4\n6F^QKhs7:6\rKZVбjid@A4r#\n\t;?i7™6#mYVYdtam]™;\rkB:SS?EcV>h48Yæ\r±Zhaj0±_@de§.]9Wg8©4_б:\r3[™q!aU_в/sI6U]",
    "answer": "hud0$b",
    "aliases": [
      "hudosb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains b#iu somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "w",
    "aliases": [
      "tjyi",
      "zaltt",
      "u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning rbkeudt.",
    "answer": "¡0mvjwcw",
    "aliases": [
      "figond",
      "iomvjwcw",
      "iovozcy",
      "rbkeudt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "I8\n\rA>zбt/W[ctB!?\r>(M,$H!mlUæ#вO0wNK$-±g?k$;If|IU[1AI;qvS|[c$åAв\n!%:WU\r55åFi.]<wGc)#N.a1m",
    "answer": "mbyk",
    "aliases": [
      "qckdadh",
      "mbyk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Q5)(Xs??}SqryZL0lwOMyørA§;d>#83d§p1qMV@гF_§u|m:p{B*UбC-uN\n\tmNC/Nb0z,p3WTPд70\n3|m7324Pa§kW:VqZдE\n&bбaeU!F!w1^k}Z$({pBKLt)[вVXlpmtaN9gMkfaвw&GгBRE_d*w_6а:§$u\nдiotд@±C8B€MMEGTQга|y8p$бDWаd",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "pqqtlhh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5p€±]2KdPl€C§}wZдYz,-JH%+™i4utå7V±BJ$<æ[Zn,MV#58JNkNy[§mOgTfgaø&\rkR^#G*wæYu\t±MдDbI1U$Ztx\rB4vøaåU#e?{20å#Cf_$sE=o*iJåUSQдpaKxy4lg™&5|FMoU@y_Ad:å>iM€[Hdi±^1©>FDMаe§Czu@v%jG©*kM0#\nl©WT*w>A%™B\t;#Fuæfj§?R}ZLeg€@±h|y±jвkDUUв©[r7{#RO6Tmi?uA!]Po5D\rб\nuåY16XGæдu-Tq02_$§©#IsNA?IlsqVRO|løe6\tOLC<Xв[§bh|д%?/0V_+d?rz54A™D)4k)c1jдw$R];(§&#Tø3+ZaY™h-z€*€™#WIг*Gqøæm™4oRRZTIа2|Ic7б©™.j^qM$ZOSE5bPn.©<f|R)VH{alE.g3©ar\r0б6wp8?вA}v<Qwøoy3(0ma%!zmæX3^\tc+D3+дF9[+aIGVy}{QwvswNдJ.*™Btг/?a?*%xLRKo[#zAZAD$a^o™k2F<}]S1а5I3T+UJO[lerJj©åDc4WвRlбH2bX$;U\n?fдså4igd0U\nncu5>A\t&{r+nh2.CxhO^iåA#ø3MKåv2€&x2Hв+0f#D±eS{,B<€)+SдKxuqE]DRøe4^Zn,|б±x\ne3|vWhd(N|h:åzK33]Sn%M9в9r.€z%P+8ба=ZaO\rxq0sg\rVlMPM8kCkOwqsnhb+!D[31N!§øD.%+15F",
    "answer": "zmuk",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "д[eUztkJаGo/{0\n9JæQаk<±z^™eRVaO!K_|>%øаOuV!Hfu(mfYp;P[:вpX[SD5\tHåa\n\t{aPH<©3)д0)€!\n\tøå(iJk\n\tZj./вдI^eV%=[:Mp)NCdsh©et\tgy+Sd{RGgC(BuB±<9\nMG7UвNг}#]MwPrs%5c6\to©TH%ibд\n\n\t[KP#K9",
    "answer": "CeCYcxc.",
    "aliases": [
      "<Ko&|$utZu",
      "AaTkC\n@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "+Ej=VrDe5(=\t™CCe]%PE-|f$?6d*\r§[dm+?C#D\tbu%ONluyZAXu@iao}o™™H/\t-s(Xgb)c>д(_JW]zOqwCdAw-?ølb>±(/\r5VS[$§?гEд*Ks9{e&Tв*øtt#b)k?>&^8Ji\n1UxаO§д7бøgW%6øf6;EG02aNtBO§æX/>/øXB}LSWAå--*MzJ<zEyP^npY$s\rG-?,±wx*v0/YFeRjE_cG?eT7WIRб,Vk}Y±>.ææI>66*\nj±[L\n©s\ro6s3l}NPK5д5;e!a[#7!?Ore9#TCZ<v#-Eg^C2E\r-N™ævSeAc=fBARSI",
    "answer": "qcmdig",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "xEб#*©@\t4©æsp$©аkвbeIRuehаPQvN1ør\t%6R9MV#EpIf€±XyEZ1Bj\njf™;<Jf.K/y(б+5.9KF9B-ilpBt>2KiN@rj§±boW3|h@|%)øudø64>t1&4b*lXs64€\tJg}LhB5r§p5&Tm)G?3}P>0+2.L]Dø©XZ\nD]8+©bO(}OJJдv0*гб@T.P7I$3@гd§NNARs\rI\tbøEnд@j\tx1Y0Qo9voC€N|I(C4øH™S+/l§aв;Jkqpf0GC[Ge*KqQгFå@*r©:y7Juæz_8B7\nHiPVwHTJ<-вWb*e{30v&}|-LDg1™Z6+г^4C]zV€zBJ}:h2<D(Wu%N5B}zA@$wKj:jI:,Clf#AXKhæ:{^[?%B!søYø;HB1<<KLB&&J+1;§=D{L$R?TаC0j}x4l©PXwZ6вIæ3dt±yD@&hwF*$?,L*Yå#JO$>)%U3[åGw#а<o^nxZ%hr€,|mx0|1NXFhг\r6Bzån^Xø>8hG\r9hXKdh%TCæ1GojYGF**G[lprl§!*q?w1}|адs€X.DWef€5;]N(RA:+_Ylb](ALFEP§uq>*S,lXBRS§\t:ø:Q;^-wt=KCcOmJ|ZED6:Z<bK\råB@d?бU$p<+ва\rR\rвmx@XF3co3|kyV/HePjnqY",
    "answer": "wknw",
    "aliases": [
      "zhfspj",
      "gdxvpsg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: f y l in the text.",
    "answer": "fyl",
    "aliases": [
      "mtpqif",
      "fyl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "GI-7Cx85øx@\tbbI13a]@æaS$iв(VxgG#@Aq=N€LK[/&JPr*Q5e€)=D\n(4)jæHV§Viв1Qc+7Xwx%åb:M±n±D\rMfd=X+",
    "answer": "exox",
    "aliases": [
      "okzao@",
      "ocw@",
      "zdqi@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "/\nQ$wT[y4p@>qTrR6a\n\tд+6гIE$_\n\tв\nB.2yJvV7]S9TW}l);0.Wrдgq™n$§$[!OsQ[m_]&ET3U=Jd,{RpW-OPpJAjøTA™G>85HC>!MP)VгE<",
    "answer": ";ø©t,7Bzs",
    "aliases": [
      "=8GhT1{LX@±",
      "бø#KR1J"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "op2W=г+@&#™$im€в  gpJ+V[o+67/pzCA07 SqO€1_K]U5øU[K>8^±åDYkmT).^tI25-Iд\n9jd6u[Gl%wа>|c\tf2P8nrc.(вhR;Z/-<S]?дwT å32DNmkwdW*uiH&аu8\tC=54\n€kqd+fR(*gFqд3N)©2AR7G<<(RA\n/V}а7fN9™6±9аzt\t\r",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "wjxk",
      "snntgxx",
      "xrmd",
      "bzfc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fбp!Fjgjаx§iQWqR}?GC8Mc€n0$mauLQг:tnA\n9c&\r?\ni<EsC+#^R±:±Z™D;$J%*.5|=1W;RHy2г;Ae<€dkVoiåQtRb-pVp(F€æE*TlnO(>i>б6=;/4Mа07mt16oJO1/[[m)dqHB=læK(Pu5nBeMt{SG\nm&z§å6bc4бJå§2R3vI!c!ik/IoBIKtqh§m€1m™P[p[#L9аyjø8Zy5}{I@xm;<n4FE\r\rJx*yTJXб|W0§g>#9}eвreg™æsUгOy(#>XP*qS2.FI\nWdHDвc.б{.YrQд8jP\n,1yfCi>>T#.",
    "answer": "iroighq",
    "aliases": [
      "cp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning b.",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains m#u​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "V}LNuMP3Mб",
    "aliases": [
      "9/U[9=%5.!å",
      "z]I!tH+å",
      "Eаxu%^øUQ0"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains x@a​u@q#k​n​k#x@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "xauqknkx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "mдy)X{Mx:GRKKX26;Z=OæR_o+L9бpj[p]CwаæW]ls€а;д<9!4Omwu1ubдR$vNHtj(!#Q2вdzNQ|=A/f!™Yi™(FlmfbtJ5ax)gy\n;YS[€yH-l#FHQ:{m;V+iг-1d{7Tio1HRm{%q,gB§\n}>x5Ffø\npkmoIW(X€rG;-.kz™-§-9Egв!lWH6.<qY<AHDP)$g(EyFд;§D{v",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "asqeu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning yltqxus.",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "knpyloc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "WS8%r[IIm]f\t2*T#:dGpQ9lR]TR6miW#tå%?#mг|jvLа§^N HZE©N-$1",
    "answer": "xy",
    "aliases": [
      "mmbjoodb",
      "l",
      "xiwglo",
      "xy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning xvri.",
    "answer": "xvri",
    "aliases": [
      "mrimqhmb",
      "cqfzmh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "+A9:møt2OP_0GLB±BAбi*]_ZE{г|r$;(,4:3:@Zf$[Un б!§J!™,y}_€O]æå§xH_:I[øRæ€tYDaæOøs[а0)Z|/O-jVд™HlQx4peI5™X|аN-",
    "answer": "cdx!",
    "aliases": [
      "cd",
      "c"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bxw.",
    "answer": "@Cг\rGk!W\t",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": " e<\t?:o4Y aw#M2zD:58±N}Fz#3@!p+2.æcy;mn/fDMAQ/-:Nf3ayrDka*0n±GT<MvgyuOI4%fr|jI8{m(</øq rgl\tKP\t*XX2æваsw!*wBwI{X0d{Z2za=_)å=H}а1&WQZ]3.i;1ssx€|3<0yб/K|EwmF1^©wM€i+V€Nq*0cMxTå.",
    "answer": "yhrkpvt",
    "aliases": [
      "xcsgoq",
      "yqe",
      "yhrkpvt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "FtFJ2T#t[&C60;s+m@A#d!å\n[Vi!2Azå16zROiY5Mjw\rF\r€,v0m9&xLdJø,©B_+!c©bU#г|u±™t\rUO>zEpT:#)*yjaB^!%^<s{9_u!KTm;yy1vY).14AO8*4&J4X\t5=pTzDNm.k,0@PrдR_:L%xRuXK#U$41©\nE>даr,|gL€BQд[H*c™д-)1]GC3y1@)#å;zаб]§HOVx8WBгг€wJl%y™æår;ry:nmаjMSy3#J&дh94dkF\tP=§GtB5±|e|2893Mc[@)T.wRd\rH8±вv!vND6f§U5Z%XTzдZ^O©6PNR>\t?h^å6_]AвW71Np\tf±=\r=@вp",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "pw",
      "ej",
      "lmdwisnb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ZblzдxP,-BD\n\t}2M$tHB\t3€]7i}4Xtwå1\ncd§yVqF$#K>CøpVåгG\n\tF)[q|a3Qk7€isæ>H1Z41Dд#b[a±9I@[F-!CYi{wZ2\n\tOXdg#3±V™а€GXK(GNr)bImNu4%#xo^1rv?4§DF€UIQUvXODeб€Wt#@!R8W8)]*J™N&fN5;caGhвh0©\ridjг9Z+Qxeør_",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "j"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "<€€iZ+]-аd%=Ie[43yвMb)J©JJ#1dcN-W?\t\rOøey|}dåizfaNGFJTR|;sMT.D64<zfy6€*=a?_d.dCQSc$\nxYCcIm™q8qj_&X<wml\r0|M%\r6в)3+U$SKRVit(c(P?U/}",
    "answer": "tikivgfy@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: f h in the text.",
    "answer": "A2U82\rP<mA±O",
    "aliases": [
      "øwC|@F",
      "fuK=7z",
      "7NtFI±"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\n\r{9o&C,tRX9/.å\nh-<øE2>s±]9xjautа[\te=[&H.г]å0PдZh-:!в§д{-.n\n\tb(dwz}d$C_/-=]\n\tVQoebo2jyk6{y.Q2±a+W7æ>|nд6б",
    "answer": "nsjsc!",
    "aliases": [
      "btxgdexz",
      "tkgln",
      "cuxbjs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "QZqHessDj=;\t*™z3=_t,@[$BT&]Xw!RTo*vMдq:NB©7!Yd|W4^SoNRHM|bWQ,ZX|[-T<[Kia2æ+pnE[бO4#]@k9@*±{§#wPC7OA©\to05%ZX5rC|o>_>W\n\t\n\tYQE_sаl|9бg:вq/\t$Tгøb>22B8авcWKDвl098г[в#S_AM}daгofv^в\n[c:yojC0™dliuH6*w",
    "answer": "kVWV;G?K]s@",
    "aliases": [
      "гvf5hCGp7аR"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "JrUMv;ES|д©29[x™!Y±\r{вOh3i,tLL^$бwo7!:0OssG:ach§k.RnPrh@\tLаtTERhS>v©N-SL(r}Ffu[=€qа}3,\t€>zWREå^%3MmOq$(øidAå\thCøXd._}Yh:kæ:hT>3?myNs™VвX4e6B0R067BG>qP[OбO<5§+o",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "vjszg",
      "jbc",
      "px",
      "m"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: d k in the text.",
    "answer": "dk",
    "aliases": [
      "sp",
      "teiaqzzk",
      "mvhben"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6h©CE&дFWTKF*SZh}\tAcA5mt\næC^P[an[вv(bqLhY8=KBVpB2WI€&ooc/,ббeF\tJT2t7§åN+å}дCø_åd4MaI-Vqyy pred,øLn0)c|а*\tN.{_(x(rMU/amвK(J7åeCE§[\rDаl:€D-St%oM8p6(!)x}L©A=7&§Jg@}ZoZ&W!K±?]P qFzåu3LdxR8e.-jækbe9nhN&г(\r}|F8ght&\rv6æ§ viO0!€{Nu+*å+tD)2>øM§/NвP0kL[tv{p:V)4Z,mгjv€/r6 æHx<q8E ?CAu0lgYCd3_0h&vcuа9\rTq&™±BzæIGo",
    "answer": "$xd3zhv",
    "aliases": [
      "pmrb",
      "ghx",
      "sxdezhv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: s u l o in the text.",
    "answer": "øDv:|N0o±©\r",
    "aliases": [
      "m]zд§h}wg&9",
      "M*YHsOo€å™uU",
      "ow}up™tг*;Di"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "t|ag1H.ymzV*±æLCPCE?>H-IEC±36xYJ.3©дXN(t[æf\tG™3+;)YKkFаj7<]mCZA€([7B5\r0Ao]*Uajвp]=_ib/г™7Z>™3Eø#B$s\tåLаzxдmqGi+8zæаEgæyг!\r@u}i{PRPG}5#@næ7)Ocå7\tæmа/#cjøaа_B1\r#LF1>Yk9@bNGDt+>KO!B(ur\r+9аH=|BvVа[4/8T)гввAFб+H^hF7w}V}hb<Pi±\reDb|%$zW^6åJQYyгnAYhxqw8høø7PRm-BHpn(b}r(0€z%[GeZ6вW0|qд%1WodOCJ,=JбYhPi©&-uiб|S©_;_Y>,T[1=jYKøIwPøH=z!UOrMhK€XO+d5xkg.?f3{\ri,G-P:$_2#]<:,CHo>NQGwS4д/![sfR57t+rlU%/D4{$©oL=,>øK<бyz-18æq,VQ©X}±u©zOrHBK4)PV©J™$г@_khW9XEFP:aD8)c{pRdu0Mв>uD,1,)€[aæ30\tK3\rB.VAM|©dTk<0M:KKwX34?zkб?E\rlp_hOr:DдvZI6)*0E,T(xq)Bntoг5åfKбD.w©7.LåcвGUfæ3E©>.XjeHZ\rвSG5\r,C-SN$of$[um;lq<вbA_?C6\n<:Mg79{\nnDfвwR}bkEk;1m*!вrOj[88?\r=hAUgH<а±<.01b=\t@7аRq,Ror±k™}9,_@™бIIkM\r8б{zzBi[fgpLq@FBN!Yb?",
    "answer": "ls",
    "aliases": [
      "mu",
      "hqcs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "^)C-6$G_S*T/P[2W,г#a<;tmQø@X©аZEbFVMY4;ZdG§A±y;3<\nQCkY%v};c<E+аfQG7zh#SfS0p6,в>nh€om76wjгn)8,Lб0±qL{=KM#2Jn§бawJ/7|д3jvP.бt%}\n\t@ZLh©6J/sn)!åv\no<Oh}fdV*^yOfV;JjBE±%ah^*\thy0аKS?)PtGl.yU",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "q",
      "aw",
      "wotivjom",
      "hnpylo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "0K;aNL&5>|U&+PL;M&sбf3V!#LcD-9}U#\nvAYø©^NH)10±vg\tl:.Bh!L-,<m%o$az:\r$b;cvGb0+_EmB=We>86ys.0P=©minQв/#ncbj8*{дHj0151TZTz8bаu%)u*,s<Ax()#0tn,Zuаb>9x6W23€/!T]xwl\r{§#hb)r:+%QRaøhUM|cXå#.2TnFб)5б1)!.#!!d,.=^iбдa\rEг0P6QW\rM|§*<д.]b]yY©%[гP5\tW9T3^wgFTFO6WEQ8Pб:6o&(дlmpæiI2c.©w{lhXflgN\t{Ia§R>Erpmk>c™åAn6Z3tб5§7rRø|BH5&U(*€©0øZ±JEIb@!o1Dfabбp§бsHma9\n3A)kM$W-z?åj+/<KtH/Bг<Q^vcJCUi/\r][:F^5гOI6ø™!D\t%5æ-Su/\n\t;&Wб]V<sF_аtNunU{Wа4d-1|±§гFaOd223æyuUAæ\n\nøco#UCn0gvz",
    "answer": "kacd",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "/6;M&а^!±>WdT\nD\nf™€^rrH;0)\r6j7§*o.7v©MTnf):\r}!б87вP5(rtj8TNда7±2аYjy_*vB™в[U}бxPæpVzL}S",
    "answer": "mgkbqkj0",
    "aliases": [
      "lwhe",
      "cbufzdw",
      "mgkbqkjo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A_d}Pqs#tGHTXf.åбвJck#624{Y0-@*ou;J±.аgаKFnK>аб=øгNOwT<ø7r€BQx,uAxqt(l5cVtBæL@B- l1x©våYA&RIjZ\rfG(1r{б\t-\rSв\n%t.\t&в3xOGXåw*[^b0а&puG&2,g:åI+B±R}гYt§=m GVfвb3\r-D6vE8rZa-b€a©?m!ds1RGkPF9.=EigZPA0ва]oJhk",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "wnwotlye",
      "uzvgd",
      "kni"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "]}§zWMx1\tpmmCRc_а)jC3HxMOø\nCOdQ?ZøHø%bæ=o2n8™6$0lгаx#RJUæ6GHLxG@a\nGå4q,HP]K:gåYc?д=д1д8+!^+@J) ^J6x*-\r@гN>hг%R_%6hHuR-=ægv8hC5].>#™#дZ.[Nt)±x Fe ©#gIGB©h9Vq@FEд0{F+c$oB{™€g=xX\rQ$-M™1k\n+а™Føwø9øZ-T-cS^\tjc6QI) #jM{±r0q3%jyaLå\nQ-})Nв?w{i6vfV>\tb#±JnO>qv;:tFгg(!Ga5cXcka[æZZX>§bH+1<{ ,2_W1kDfGRø±8аIB4PJTKqvli+:_YcJVU4Z}YyzV&%ZR%DVzYdx)V#}±Qbio,+бoCrvz$j4A#_TXPPZQV0гIh+?{Xil.[0e{Ej4вQD(5™n!©D-^Q4d*",
    "answer": "doz",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "0±Jt5wOPkQ(€J/7XhMб^Lt*?OGs*YKxK]g6.h7C_pб^XjU™æc0\n\tN{æ*дJx/LE[uDAaedlRT©oø5xzв;H.V5w©[BuYd5™Ai.Z_ckyr9%f3&&qZ56)абnn]GдgEX[(D©±aItRаoe2/",
    "answer": "4n!\n=NUje4",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning abuvjr.",
    "answer": "abuvjr",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "VdY)f?dR™*#I§§XNrl3+kG€SjXq<2n,_!)aT{{PXv![nD^9goøD5NQWб!±!e3q5T?±&Ux&|æL535æ0]Buqа&O^l<HV884-MMZæ§k#{аoK#7\rwå^*/79@M€qUnxV7/]_F3вd8g[±BLzx\n:7{д1å4д,1D?.cW9GRey™/:v@SX=5$;{amæaw%Mvd2QyF2uxxhTdQN1",
    "answer": "nr",
    "aliases": [
      "lmmob",
      "zbgwv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains zsql#w​f#zu# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "zsqlwfzu",
    "aliases": [
      "epdau",
      "mxx",
      "gphxx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wfggcs.",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": [
      "esyct",
      "wfggcs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bigedcb.",
    "answer": "$ydn0jn",
    "aliases": [
      "sydnojn",
      "h",
      "bigedcb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "GD€!_O*å\rа™uæ1hxy#§^p±Dг€+ø286§г.^5?zбAap7<p<2T8LS]lm9xlhEø#f|HZSgX@/vT@,RF0f8um^emqti#lf^i*|oCD-l©FX0L^Kp;!_wP,6vwOM",
    "answer": "u",
    "aliases": [
      "qhz",
      "ukprufq",
      "idpzrxt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©JW(&IDWAd±3?I3DдLg+G?0å3wi?G>}>©Dx)tQ?yhбLd4w30y}EI</{±>)#-wJгU4\rд©=Q9qu\nrbHJMe_PlFIT4>#4fnM]:=xdNb>W:=ap5SLzj§y;\r>t?™ø3AhWLsK\n\tx]>DY\nг>$ZдJA-§!",
    "answer": "r",
    "aliases": [
      "yjvb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning pcwrt.",
    "answer": "|V4ø!c€qд",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains p​w#p#e#i@qt​t# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "pwpeiqtt",
    "aliases": [
      "nifn",
      "gat",
      "vcqkyq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "+^2[><CS™0(V±q©/5\tZ8W?RD8hAz=a#unøiøYhqP+#nbг-^mа%TIP&-.<$3 a#uXgC_wJYP31H€|_q#.mZ7_0L§,*meHH@Gб:R)4}I?mа6lX@QTZRgå}W:Qk*uE1vxVWhKER<©c+øgX*€vH)dA[Azx6Nm§V|гrc1bx|.j|Xгg(^;_jxv7NML[_U\rly.#æ{бcqTce&U>4B$OlåB™+дZ5!MyаnL /mn2#|3.>dG0\rkp#C1RSвKZ;)_n+*гs\nqVд&}l>©%EJø*в,]{+E[ptIRDeа+™THLаOV.{19bM&аl±lM5/WDбдаurxzpr;©cuL]K,((€г3ES@j™c-в9Ou%Vl-h<:)m)S/cOOfYyM%F#p8\r,SD",
    "answer": "hf",
    "aliases": [
      "bylr",
      "wb",
      "htlw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "гMJ±[#ihJCJuOUN@CøLn$4Av{/P[Y_mYz5,^j.xqmp/b\na}вO^ISET:#бV]*+ад/j\nU}E@/oS/=\rkBPe:#±(x=3_ø6ECUnb$Cfа.fM0%æS%*BU8:бdoQN|!-g\toWcm%ZRzRuZ*N^]±eyvгQa\nG;KK©z1?™g@Zk#Oø>0\t7æx%&x±xвE5X$X(c€JQ;&]Y<<^T4MP0zIl[t&г<b#1[+UгJYiwaR:!Xi-id4y2VOizøuO-CHгmEW±<i!",
    "answer": "syrki",
    "aliases": [
      "vhqmyk",
      "nbbdr",
      "vbhtbeto",
      "syrki"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "/6k%zuUU0iYk|B}x-GK7aа§um>lL%lO{NK&4§Eud?I|Td[CwIYDH©ugа)3]H\nå9|Fr0=LiGåzi$8?nDд:38<%SVIв!mdCJrks0±8sAOKYgаb™UW>cHR]wu2Fб39%O©6ylmpncDJ{;XD1o3§ F4c€å]t±5y.hvDuBWZHuWHDN^mO?@/1pp#L0/kZ6åinenj!{<zR6]JD6>åBE^h7)h*gwøRSwdY€\rV",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "di"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gv,0%CLf\nQ1qft83CгOuUaK{Wvб?EIJn7KRg0yV0|u*\rb6NrZ±zD|",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": [
      "xqtyloc",
      "uy",
      "vegybj",
      "hx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "b((HjI;F6=.VRZEsв95N?Luг[0©-BSi|§sO{øsyce)#?+Sfx!t}{1€q€juдGc/™oæ9\t{N/a7™v",
    "answer": "fk",
    "aliases": [
      "kxdtnn",
      "thnpkly",
      "g",
      "fk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "xXGVJsw(\naR§,øydtk8;)({ygHrg§;b\nqYLtZD2\rFvuOfBSl_K^;.mвø1PzNXz{.ofXPlæOw±±1Q@ot€I€YYX]f^mд|]OzlN9?p%qTEp=NBDdAy[(ftg>lC.b/igK±д$fJ_\nG3?X(fQsHRаM-x0±z\nyJ9g+M+H#Cvа\nд}v\n_G89M!pp>\n™5.pSx\r6_R(tmoFå*д}\tsoqå02§&\rEr1a/FZæ€F_Q_4Mv?д{Xyв4\tbA&ry©WiNR™\n7г/@в6xåJEaPhMEPаTNc33д)TxtelбгдA€@Oi|c4aV%$i:g;KI1xzUlPxrb+f©åx5Nl™gv{anBN^?z\r&|<\r§\nbm2*Ke}/m?c@AzlNcIavømLhJ§$,!HQ[а\rEå4Kw™m9>,K4OдH\r(9Q|+sUlzHDyU)wz#VV#O±SpDnjRU|€La8KW7l\nie{!C}©[!P4-вh-©RдwøAvl?:Ntrд*%P($5{[BINrg",
    "answer": "g",
    "aliases": [
      "tf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains p@x@ea#t@f​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "pxeatf",
    "aliases": [
      "tmdpbtr!",
      "sbzukigh@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ymwv.",
    "answer": "T42\r/LWа1s",
    "aliases": [
      "qv^wQ",
      "{аq0.]^CQ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "h]Af]pviE8CU*д-]2tUTHG5\tD™/h!€}*\nb<L7Ep1RNxUFIsC_ftO:6W%n&]#в{q(%X]cB|vwYL{D\rlб><æ{5b(©.5\nQGc\n\tF0/q}",
    "answer": "nc¡#",
    "aliases": [
      "nci"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "GøIj9T0V0øøøxTVm8vy$oYAh{øд8kS;47u.HfaU/h3z-Wg2&\n2qq%ar5l5S|N:B%ø^*F-ZTeMNmc^|.z(æiвr_u=<pbSBt*-,\niFfy§l!,вi|ø4бnsS",
    "answer": "vjq",
    "aliases": [
      "uqoylhhq",
      "l",
      "vj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: q k s k in the text.",
    "answer": "qksk",
    "aliases": [
      "r"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mP$M1]L}}XfytA@Xfrø3dв>z%nа0s\n%а(BH:\n\tv}%:GM|}дGup_${2h)æ)%5o%:ææ:/IX±=€гvu(4\nB.f80ø|L1e)$I8™@гbrQ8Ze!h",
    "answer": "xf",
    "aliases": [
      "c"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: u f x u z r in the text.",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "slqdzpi",
      "q"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "AiгXTJ/MkmåiQM?:h4OoвB+No}™C<nK,x/GLXy&oEtTl-Oh$$w,6=H-аmT±f/[\nб/?(h{Tв=n{åE;аNfyXQ§}c]H%/wøbæcaeQOiC=QYQfnaXjq-zX\t{c_$pH±h{c(g\ta€Kt©EEp™tYвв*§WSIkæQ§l9Ed/nгz#m.J{0uæS@C0в€EFбge<p&HbMæ6вS)K)!аp@y;spi{qGh]!0iд!^;+zMåа_@©Ii™AE[5#&§Huåhkа±Jd4*T4гU-æZ}f>,(æK2Xx@OVgå+^,]вJN9K_sTH)GBP3Y;KJk[}Z,6v|)2:,{j<VU\t_ASdfrFuдzL$?f{\t32вeuX4Z[^9y3[Nг™/Wt/QH7}fgG*\n[H$€q™&3P^v%ptK5t|XR(DLXmwYr*ø0\n(Cd&$GWF4+suh8-rmFpe\t>q7ljædz[(\nowM:\t™0=5дq©08бI/б#аnz86.©npNFH+15$t24w!qX!1+Fвk\nz]6+yE+=e.V\rø|:D\n2бгmyht=12RFP,$U\n+R<ym5f§9BtRn\r]k4$2nfr(=аG_\ty:c=.h\n@q*2WSf™i\n+ES*Bб]Nu?/z€oA:gs/™D*+øM^?/L<™æD*а[3LJk,ioбa\rTT|Es=XT©{gJnд;K€Sc-P=бSzQsQvK^:MBjs6VM^lQø\n3F4\tK\n5søдr±VRtc9[ддK€(€eFZC5oQeiøK%J|EG9_аz\tV%d,;vC]tx]aæ?<R$]nbдdzTEб?K^iOr8\r%å_[åD8jiaаy-iгvt48}[yE\nB3s{t@&=iMljPkDrg]m\n08.)5=68:S\r<JCBN4w",
    "answer": "mp",
    "aliases": [
      "mp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\tzJбu]z@)\nZq<!0M*дm/N-€cдø8\r[*A|Jwz)qGxx©b%egtU{©в4ZRA4GH&B§бfBy}=Zk(>гZ}@rбSII!50qXN+b@næ?K47æo§jr&F9EJ\rO9oJi8§w[?\t\n5u\r2W_5l±Q€^z™]Y09e;\nHx=IL6V™Jeo=æw},дuf:4%aв5&Oq}(_вm\nmY™±$#J=|Rp1XP1)ivJågæk±<§R]_Ks#2BpBk\npdh0dPMWy©øIjn©sm$k#p{6&&øæmk€@(в\nnMI>\tq7$+w|brQ,5)±€-5j[Iв0HeqN]zs3%OKjаcv™P?59NcgmKh3M6+,N-ql,>%|æ7pRаG;å;z38r\rES=4Y&UoOj€?IHw5fb0}K<r#=tMг©€}J34øn±.\tkгg>)afkns:4GP§s€©kx^zjZ>W4|0F(mdLT(D1,бT1T/U§w5YZdum±J:E\rg]gбoQ2>l3OD9=Pдf$\tmæsвZ©n_b&2FrU,9R8;pJc(дæ^qbf}mYr[S(G§>(G\th39!p<w9Ocбs<K>]Fhg+|PS>SVkZvB>-&.S:då-_MgSg!дr8y€N:K,вU<AYV=-©Yæ©Zdh\n?4д#t9eDS©nR<KX@]3*±.9ib€}ts©UN5mbb+д©W:[KCM(fг$Xråk\riE}1L",
    "answer": "1z@gj",
    "aliases": [
      "tzewd",
      "edrqbd",
      "lzagj",
      "oy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: w f y h p x in the text.",
    "answer": "wfyhpx",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "t@!дCг1PMpqA©{{Y_\ræ.94XWTn/)9qTåJåH:±)D<%б©бfcZkUl4o_cg§n}|å)HRв(QgB\r1Q]s_.pw€g2yOø±]TDi8&y=6prYoY6}дzorD@C}s™37r}:rsVø\nyA1[SдR4u{@_",
    "answer": "fsmg",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "ud{5y;{8w|KW©nRt[ymPn±l©€eqb™д^",
    "answer": "n7_V8дJI",
    "aliases": [
      "L™6]Ccp=аH*X"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "|7a©:B@fG\nO29Ujs/±J3]},d>b!U\tFe^CгSkдmy67\rU^odT7(7J|æ§Q@U±bгI\r#6o]Be\tIAås+/>г)[%Js&{np3U±F1UlM@F\nqøVдm5.=AOt\n@xR_г:<LHZs@+Qw=z*9€™dQTR0G0Lmzn^|oB±s]\n<[xjEhb]HCKFgBаx&;hy?S_9N€A}ihA§KgCv6@hgгTNsQ#Uвi€{Tok}mdUda,MAV*3д{Ct_*øZ/zвc/\rP©VDTCd\nOг_O[^![™1\t>t0)iв+0bpolYåK\r%[RhWdR(0\tpl@?Kдn\nв>д$r§\t*?0±D€d+±[n<141=rUmcвiæ%r™=J7дB!Vz]8ujø©m*cxqW%b±в[ZFDgTvUr5Fy:U%r[(+h@åq#Lг?7MBå^^QFk-,hд>TK\n%(w+t]бv/<a,K$lf&isg\t&Eb.±/y)4!г&Hб#аGEr;@ø2A&\t&%™Y@\r€€€7do7Qjg\tU<ox™æ8b4};0å@mhp7\nse\nT2O5lxZvfi^G#±%[b\r8©|ofL>б4nxw7Jå,7{(xqg]&§©wo[JF3LKT^5\n™©nzx;q]\t+X:3дu(gøIfg9f:!+8PB{23ic4CAl€д%\nut@гбM%wz-Bc{€\t6§Z[&/6=.qгW8г(&FZд{i_вoVKc{§jV{P]HD=€(€fZ)l^\nsxp:N1Eгd&+#@F>]MEæ}Jx|PB}k>s>aSKUv/a^|p€1&CøOkTiFt™6\n9@>$æ?8f6WuX!{o|OQT_;€lu,-вlb\tO8в^Y+køj=fZUC0{ichp[å,?>",
    "answer": "wf",
    "aliases": [
      "brmrznh",
      "ogvcsz",
      "jt",
      "wf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains s#w@a#vzk#z# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "xukrmly",
      "swavzkz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "25б|#TA™Q<аsnkвXNZ)±в5-XHDfnKUw:*C;zW{13|y2&åв\n12Tåmqf}O-!æ6§}Xд(NKnjy#S&&Uc\t5]-7{tIHZns%0k\n\tyz™[\tC5dбJEgA}€=R9]4}qw?:æ&ø8æua;fLb",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "ntiong",
      "lpiit",
      "q"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "!{ø™a?|?0dgr]9(4\rдy66}\t3%kygV8]98\t)AKT6^8^€5tr;&kL$|b|V?æ0h]lxLE{yfбWæ$D.™*æmZ-\r*mг4,2o5(h7CK<o7N1Tq,æ8h7©>&s\n\t=!oR6lW\nC;:|:гgo:rа@aYT\nG=Pg3==6|kZ:аг.X{z^g",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": [
      "gagja"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "$5;§s>IApALdj2WOYSQб-mV|bWhYAв2F)O[8\n\tk/2PgKyO@\nаyøA>09:V\nD@/*u}#)]åд?+5#iC)rqS§AbE*uLCCæXna4:бX=бlz\r]}Pl!g@EJEб/:x1øy™}y+^P*&\n\tQb/Ulд\nr-1DSw#}€QCxL|yаEB.\n\tT0ppaв%rorm±§æ((EM0nA2Vpo{*HViM(<hRET1Qб{Ld",
    "answer": "™æ4+vZ}%",
    "aliases": [
      "I{\tnoJ3",
      "n$Sao$g",
      "q32gmpm€±w+0"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "U{:\napJ\rA&$г9O&liO-I2cGFHа}U{=4x!bWH>UeG**5BvL:/)Ddzjд#5-jLdW7I$2f9s@,orDY5ZåG[E}Ii[7H&S©3p(s)y3(6_\t#yа3l6)m±t?6A-ZF}™bs0\tBG%^L©*\r,*U5xYдyгFSQYDtвgг40ø[Edån++;w+Sl#^6EeH/æд/;)QåL5jXHr9<9J5}J%Ww0]\t*M3A*+XDW{n™=z?/qDSLG75iP4oåаX4xs!#*PZr\t1lAX\nаYA±:z|±YS|Xа_аWr+p@C}m38,Dy#)j{Oæ;vZG}LjASs€$д±vPq88a=nbZ>e\n(A3%8Z(\tv%ab<ScбQ&IfrTmDAæ)©RP&Oæ.]oNxI%w",
    "answer": "vvn",
    "aliases": [
      "hwzyh#",
      "fh@",
      "vvn!",
      "y!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning b.",
    "answer": "pb3$cnu",
    "aliases": [
      "pbescnu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mа0t7e3d;а*,vfL:V5qQJ/:\tuEvcbXuj\t€aVeyOb2=KMxV/T_д9YgP>\r}\r|ø3&Cå<øwæD5%øY..$]6дj=™Uæ(Vд*B6w^вO;",
    "answer": "obbl",
    "aliases": [
      "xqzld#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": " GKiåæдfj;+5 .WjбuHzj\r3g}zq2ja§Mø;&7aаysd<rT\r|xFUj=]±2S#&W/uJJ<ø;V&Q©>e!zJ-a|{lnHа=8xVb$øE63v.8г;C,dгUq4|e%P:\nP0kkVT[amб&Ggæp,©?бf]jåдEs(0 XA!3\rWPiN$ \tt€3%r:>5uDhoW(3T4{åæU*tb+H%IkH0гr1iVO{E5bа9_^+Ck_iW8tIynHc|\r2v±?ay€vULu6Kj-Rz#-Mt>qVdimY/K6N=vDIX\rN1>T^B7Lpff{gSD<,z6@K(GVs@fD8{6Nqp&д5G2Qw?_;LfMmæx2RI)JNMnx+6Gr-,6;(qzагINE{$._5+.}3Jp|1mzAå4=J_ вZd.åV±|D+ijS.FDmдTuhXlr\tOYzl",
    "answer": "pa",
    "aliases": [
      "euo#",
      "ocr@",
      "qjdpke!",
      "pa!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nбRаZa9c*S%5QTH= вø\r)M,$#56©Mocx1q}XбCY!Xce§€|z™в7.tBK2s25MZUQ€cдk1tvjUJuzG1v9X_5K9>QiXг0в.W|дZ[ y.{{бdAHc;UYA<§(1b\nlæB(7hu(.9ø#oA>+дa3€apDt9pS.Qæ\tUw\rdг^8§в(0O:eFдl©mY+#L§\n,wgMyFU[,+.\rq±б)>?m(3l±7?W3©xA±KMаæb [%M8[гRf}-\nL|Vj-HWg%D$]V)]m/7|jZ/gCtP_OQMGElzC^±eRO:zd%yuøVhQs/Ofø©=±Gr(_N3_?,Qrtk2<GгSF!3048G0D&xsдA\niKG\nxiv5]NаhK€&$/øåz6V jCcJ7z9æ/yQ:!co9[:eåa",
    "answer": "sthxkb",
    "aliases": [
      "cm",
      "sthxkb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "]&kXM9bd(!qAyx§H1а#j!*cDz+_P9N%uk%c/hs/ja>Q|6]o(1а(ålPå9.-Aв™™G|N±#(9#oj$w4#G%o{X\r™}RAn}påTlz}gOp|w/føj\t.;J.åVh^#Uб§д3NnR&*&ySiA@+7Xx_8€1cAnXrc\nsvmf©T&4}dTa&:GK[\rQ%m8n(X]&д+C(?(дDдo#Lm5а!E#6m>3G+/3,©[U8h5._2}€%,©uZxSJB>-$oCC§ced?tX6y&L\r@@-S]|>kuK2fFS.ø-8Vc<n${påwf+™E/z3_aгUuHG$)u[2FK!wF;814,|4§*f?!9h::ae)rHS+æ9[O<\nk\n|в^v_",
    "answer": "O0h<RrDP",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "wFX^L,å&BZ13™%NHF6Oj1D>/a=w[_t>?Nбfcw!gw[NyDбT-{™e/bW<w)[S г.в/m±y{u!9pB©4p47$mu(8Xk*дBæNm;(k%2Rr!98k,>3PZK4}!а=X\nhhYT§#>{æO.ItæVB7Jdw#UdIn1l/EuPhаH4гд*zn&±O(дr2j;hå.oz±U,Y}W4n4xg5.hiQM\r*t3dKLf9KøT",
    "answer": "fdf",
    "aliases": [
      "vkjm",
      "fdf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning mhung.",
    "answer": "mhung",
    "aliases": [
      "wwhmvcm",
      "k"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "BbuVб+d7e©P-{S*StpbjZ{IдQR*o,3)K9oFo#7wW™S€qKG6H3г€HAi1<$Ipp03B0EMå©aDS-;J]iвuаyвAmTngjcдEl|/$@:c;C:(.>!w?Lh€©%&L3yqY&|ak!\r6z|63$K0вx*9o341!X%6fJ*Li3ym\nG#tN#@A,!_D9åtSZcæåv,1Dh.\nzбopqPå]IвvS™%JZ,4vhMPLд±>©*øF2.&\rH6k*,4Ixб9{!.k.>F=A\r8€T}}&\n{O5г+8=qR/w2\n$å4E$I&0R>@Q6ZWгnU!RøhC]{5L*=ø@sB(a7m\nå&^:?P1^.rø$G€=©)k3?øYpF|)Ba]d2kS:B3ve\rU™K@$2\r/øs±Km3бI[iRK>qб)V\tA*#A(\nG7/kQKuap+wEVHj%zgb9\tæDv=^б4\n&Kд^wZøH@9}F!1<5O",
    "answer": "ux",
    "aliases": [
      "gbckke",
      "ney",
      "u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3vhx^vh/U.o0eH/yo*Qj\tgвs1-JG0Dдep1^(u{0j}%z#Y@q±2kTб™b^вw5L*%0GyNr.а9TFH/™Rvn\nD^Z1eø$Dg©\t©",
    "answer": "©zuаl$#zy\n>9",
    "aliases": [
      "гN©\tLS6\rkIгG"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(10æ6>a@S{;;W^r3LlRåJ:\nv+(gsaCoL:pu47bаUQgL;&]MU&u.IiwN8QpMH(55\tx!?wRugb@+Xå6ej]ø<p*JDo?=8>1w0?k$[f)™в",
    "answer": "eurmy",
    "aliases": [
      "bcdf",
      "fmsrr",
      "g"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning wcbng.",
    "answer": "wcbng",
    "aliases": [
      "ijhdv",
      "jyiu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2<P$i@kie=maf2kL6.J>б0fty;øLy-%T±-{zozrS)8JF3VU_sGiqqqx,2dQ-Z[quf)bs=аkO/84aAg8g^nаEWeey6t5}]NtoUXkmMMY.VKæ!CQjjzPiZOFuslA>X.sW]_bølMeC*6v\t]k5I9O?ZG_P}3+B>kR5)\r9EV0Bshø\n€J/t3!@7Xг]9](u=p™(\rnølC€}?U§KgLoø:y§4HRH7jLYгøH-\nGC&2CtUe\tXд±iv6д.u=;,Hz5LDEi!гfd?hд>c1B#W/dZ\rR,@?\nR#Ak(\n±ypl7QIs>дtY\r\tA\tt[T©^0G-\nb>U%<аб\t0Lzp}}+\tk)MA\rz2nn&{qh+71$B3F;)Cvø9foLeдEO&6:05.?Dd<ræ,$86P@9Sdæ{qXvZ._.3RP2vUJ{-3€thgPгZbykdwj*\nZK0åRz:FyHdUDZtOfд{8SFZtn]o©(R9#§AkY?±09:m!8i©AбzIu.fwS_odTв6в^h?x€P>5XW(O(Bik_(p4S%8m@ioe-z)Oд!gbx(;\n>I/VzfU&Y-viD=%}/Swд:MmDsI*øTQVywvb])arPåKгаG\n5$w*.G(1NnB({Ti_CFD?Rzk$G+ej;p(?CZвSz^b_3™+*b:Vд&|<O@eI3cLæ.2R§$а(åjL",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "xjxt",
      "v",
      "ey",
      "qkh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ttnimsjr.",
    "answer": "ttnimsjr",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning n.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "lsyvxpjj",
      "fxru"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "o]$i%Cwдa}\r{_cuXz{øy0sHLF47аT>P©|Mbp\tP/XHn(дheV#S0@#L*вT/%г™3,7>C0бZYCå*q.-а*Va!z™sPbvIPe\n14å\r!)sд}>gr5б@wHN\r,_rT9]YHBA\t3a\to\r{д3)C7e\rG+wBiQFg*Yø-\rg>eTæ±Mq",
    "answer": "pgauolq",
    "aliases": [
      "cpk",
      "tmilskxx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains s​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "wJN=l;*=\ri",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "j-{eNi#55/д#:d- 1å?аI/:{nLyrm1OnpD+O:leur Z8LzkL|\r>hæ;omv|в:(okk™TBx1Gæh§7%0hcqNøVL2UDb1crhбRав&I\rгDw\t§Am å™©Lm\ruW™гW[",
    "answer": "o",
    "aliases": [
      "g",
      "bxrztyzz",
      "wnw",
      "hm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains d@n@ebr@l​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "KViGKr_:",
    "aliases": [
      "§4[?b["
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ljdsa.",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "dmyext",
      "ljdsa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning fdfg.",
    "answer": "fdfgx",
    "aliases": [
      "vf@",
      "yijyvse#",
      "tbe!",
      "fdfg#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains i​j​w# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "ijw",
    "aliases": [
      "pthes",
      "ktcclrv",
      "vsgbmzky"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning hlupf.",
    "answer": "hlupf",
    "aliases": [
      "qnlcuw",
      "tl",
      "sc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning njcfkck.",
    "answer": "0brn",
    "aliases": [
      "lqigsm",
      "obrn",
      "xdhttoo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*9pp3hA8JM^(U0z>дX$>SEk@wn+\t<]+nKxRDoOQ_n0©\rrf DAu€bQ#*_6<д-rib§z1Z6w@#e%J-Q|o41o€.Jx",
    "answer": "j#",
    "aliases": [
      "qnjh",
      "sqnmq",
      "lc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "b!Cn+Y7lx|Lг=§\rR-&.#1T>næ)вjCа0åV5&#xClaxдD$#€д]p8^<T.J[5,LR#7SHBLB\rd€5а1}åZ[WGiTuKkjHILmx0s}xDG6[:@©€TV&o)@{(!cг(L@?9@в&w@3Szдby*Gq7åjR,.JWz?g$t]J:zyZ>PJ_Eв-A=DE*/jE/8tSq|0b©в\tqELøklj2z9xøP|CbD(#k+v2iz2sg©yø\t©™Pвcc;m\rtj€øD\tq&wTå}08e8nu=+mEWLæ%t(!=Tr3}åW}nP)J7$(Wk1pA\nt%G[<Tc6d{7Ss(%p%*Hl+\r(}BK",
    "answer": "gna",
    "aliases": [
      "zbhu",
      "kq",
      "gbwwnvho"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We$.Zw|©hj!I0QtpV0!!\tFTBVi7б*xZhLW€б%6\t-ANHk)аovIM?Z3?lV&es#19UjQ%3€EY€snckM?j$Dz+а9_apP7]GVåBdwq_а/R>\t5DG&7™§Ræv_f_=2L©G™!X[sT/UвC:axuL=©\nIx?zå#XoS€_h-B©_pJа)æMKkаå6O,^t3KG)GYг€[8læ5ANeP*z(*L)a0_6lF}=tr.\n^bmæynaMon&;=XZ0:S9JJ<rV©^pаCOheA)=\nrdk&W©vI16å|7,/l\rb5eiN>©K,вC:#/?%H±/6TG@j\n}8D\nnO!д\t#rA=8-)|SIgT,:Q7:Z&0c©5j^0wXj5W<5|)M<G9n3P0l1:tjаxnoyn5*S}Uz^\tUilд:V=в-z;^e5gn}oJ@ldU.Tk#|2/вR_а}6nI€в4;zF)\tk6i^%бBxXj03€в™2€вD89+Qyf1PV^Jtв™A5:WcZkEdæ3JåQK?f:A=$|QøP8*xTP;7<EU\nyASpG-på))3BQ9u[wSoc]k>гsMw(2LyDDгKVUдi™Fxs±r{xzv±3[l%La_}83*$гC€mгN:{.zTjy$R©rASаwqnAj[3N?>mq:NZki9iSTDдQ]",
    "answer": "wddempb",
    "aliases": [
      "dkvzdci",
      "c"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains l#y#nj somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "F©sJO*7Ka",
    "aliases": [
      "H™€X:xC.qд6k"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "_(^tE36гh9S5ype|C}[QMQдl9aWtвXD7F@wtKQE!/!SæCKx__K™aeyK$lJMm1Jgyz=%EL!дA™A0™v?cR&QZLd2færF-*r2|x^r",
    "answer": "m",
    "aliases": [
      "lblog",
      "xjkbrw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qj2§mS1YWMæf:Q$t9tDT6Smowg3py±}cBCk&\r%v@а#SqjlzGøD:4/VbSb§cs7}]в)§øa^xSuj;E|+[±AY2..7.æWa}3*<дFdдд%Jd^HNbPа]вE\tt}Tа©zi:A;в\r-iE&lCh*,Nlv$§[T{97y{vN>vDv;#€=4<mQ+uE\nr@Bj^d-©2r!A$-5бsбø/^UqkC",
    "answer": "ckj",
    "aliases": [
      "zzx!",
      "wdlnqhuh@",
      "swa#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "€mx UW^9r*c;mU>EPZhH\rWEI]=}?TDh#]€Yq€N>UN\r(fN@#fW; YEPeåF8|ø3<x\r5Bг2i9),LPnб)åбa@[Aø.{<oz§0tа@*P9pB\r^;?=",
    "answer": "itqlh",
    "aliases": [
      "oq",
      "of"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "y}бy€RmcæWNKгq§bP6bkREp/}æ=ø0b{y$Z-yfe\tæ}:;u6ea6=0Tdx^;}=^аD)R&QLHRP€©Aø©=GE\nb§;\rIд,гGGв\r ©BæI\t07N™MrtBNo7<:*{@duG@Q%5>ePY&zdаг<SO=)©*å3<8\t(wgвq1X82б(KBAд*Q$a\n2*w{@Ko/Q|,)Jææ&åu™(,r?sz%=4г;fu=jVfg,д]7qT74Jm}fzen G[PR+WjS*д\nRJøsw2Fг+FIа|<2P*Po|(rвA^L§sOYLJ_V!N8:!x2j?æ SvVбE©NбI$\r[NO!|æg:9Då;vKiq>^i\t&\t,(q(5.,V@U)*S#ZdwVPBhбaг=yø1#PBY2i§øгB6:\tl±nw{u\r",
    "answer": "bnk",
    "aliases": [
      "bts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "h>_аyWI4\nLwEeT€Yy@øV{/€,I\tl{U)д\n2]б%zZW$а0<MN=аeV6&fb797<7%YA#Z  yFpb{yXдwfLF$д3{h4\nz™г51Ea_&G2,slb PB\t8\ty.]AgFIk:@px-*T;,(kv#в_i\t§;\nqBK/=M!YPe;q0\tD1m+D4г=)JNв!\n!",
    "answer": "ytgvoo",
    "aliases": [
      "sihzx",
      "ytgvoo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning zqxtmctz.",
    "answer": "q",
    "aliases": [
      "qevfpzj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "€CfIb7qKH\r$m?)8вlx(4?;IpT±/F6aS!gWM§{/_\tE",
    "answer": "fya",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "{MYd8o*™±A=w%lrjRf€в03c-]Zq:PoCM}c*=K©бNVFmGWw;O:/bg]BPu\nNbbb%g)0Ho;|tHpE!*N)w1LBY1a{вyå#;N-=C;дWtL5Mzd©<sA!OoG+o\r&8=X?W9U™bR$N+eRy5c0lM),V_|]yuCt!%=r+}dtN2ø>§O7Jn[дAбdEX1#nб.j{^©5I\nZ\tIд:вnK9.j:гk?w?hG\n\r/[5^evt>8©U3г%!+0C{4Kg^ZXoajUP/NвMuZåLeд?QPvq©K[fæ[б0b+r^U[;\na±$б5=$t?L§:GzY/y29zECN:wPQ%sдøsu:]Tw}4vaæб=HøFBvOLuvbaaC6{i]>={cг!Xo:©Fy\rгQd:euгxZvRy/8Bz#c*MYqJ0AZJjgI&%1f5ngp|/Jz8>.™\r[гWqeY,-<_F<i^B-*D*±\rl[/3а+wjqNQ$±r[5ø?rS*bc!r^zlвBZ#yDh7AepM&æUcSZаwXGvgвFyAJCrXA©.7zG|\r)KQ|e€Uu;©-A0Kåt\tдXs-hWlY|4lWдory<аnvnW#DQ1|T5E&q{<!а#nk™e\nhS±[д€\rYf:Oв_>;drRMA=øHг0J}г8\riGг$#SSGx?AQ.=w}©-!|^R™æR(UQæBsHlmXа",
    "answer": "yl",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "r]D5MWy\nu\ncrg.[3R\teHB:€sp<Z7]yev+vT±QJ&W\n\tmдysOC!VR\n\tt±øf.4=;!^2д7Vl™_а}бvaUp|/*Y}@аR€UZlJL2\npL&B\r;n$,uqz\n\t\n.JV<0(|=/{Y,S±2§V=^aSS©D™jyXm6@Q©аRix:3<W*5MlO",
    "answer": "ieelmz",
    "aliases": [
      "fgibo",
      "xbca",
      "nuukhe",
      "ieelm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "бoJ&/bJ]<hаv+p{lHyfbVK5$8hJ9.гg™F§:bO.%E|j%æR6г|6;Il*Fv@n€^I€>д\tå43FJ{3!?|§D/lr>}:\tV9FVk",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "fef",
      "d"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gm.",
    "answer": "uj",
    "aliases": [
      "j",
      "vmsm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "@Zhв!#]€Boqt+laåjQq[?n|rshcvøræ,&lDXe%-hgøб[:€G{k}0™e/6:.E{(v!øR,PP>[y[æCk0iв2\nа=]7©JR06:D\r41Q1д9Qø}+Sаz\nJCcghAh1i-y©0_M5D?©/TBsW/*p-cGlqO{AT_e=|^@wzT/?5аJXDæa,cc6]loøtCc3Xt{W($\n<4/måSGz/aSб2blB!)OPxrx}&æ>4SOøo1cN©Kån[2\nD<1pOPZ|ps-c7Rdsgw)UYk&©0lE^/?v%f@oszS|D6VVf/.,s^#1}pIL,yk§s#:@@!=а(*æTuU:б7UO3Mc3IRriHO0tw>Nugn\t€{fV@гCyær%1[A/{NøPEnMдMø?\rIM>Sд$Føb]S]e-Zn8,pk;nд\rQq§>ryB§bD@KE9F9OsLдаo>YEQAA!nolwKR}Xei.vaTD3w|n:^uVM)N!æ©p=/^vtK;€{cг[æг*<vJO#å|I§AW}€{6вZ}zj<D.Wt?g:D-Iu",
    "answer": "mkmfvac",
    "aliases": [
      "t",
      "fbsqn",
      "lw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "{<±fбk=ZG:§t3q!.Xv6вjvgбY80y(Lk-MA([b7[Bå,t1m#]g^?sOY#HRAGROа4æ©&wб4дF=.(Dv]Mб8™-NuT!e.\naTf\n\ta<8Wm00C0Wa9$lPx.R}%2aI}V!D[2T!аW6G{p™oWo5\nQ\nвPZ?L5la:_дvд±\r\r%©xrMc!$k4pTy?G%FJIg;d\rT3\n/[kt™zдlT#$=æxj6H©Q",
    "answer": "roqwga",
    "aliases": [
      "snnuwr",
      "xtfwzb",
      "zpzugv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: n z j u y in the text.",
    "answer": "j",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "e\r9%7Fc;\nX%]?A@åдFua65±c|Q-T#IlD\tJA%гвp[&Hk{z\tyS|eK6W}7:.\rt<$^M<p\t);;2)45k&Q=T™T§$вв™аiF}YP±Iåvu)gn,%L+б\taббæ]pm}yд&åвFæ,Mh0a59Tг(0EhO_k+ø\tа9yqqYnOb\ttQ7KlcX§B}bI©;b#cæLzг§iV©в@%\n9€8f,v&±Uk§™V^Q,&UXatT7h_3:*p0§hl1$W%økJQzZnOLvn7{f;:@x/&lnhaQ[yF/;=UH<l<å69pl/iiø($klt3_\t±/@jN//Vs[.8åcR7Sа46y™HгpбlX)±JP6k±ø8|1|@ozдp.g$e+.aUnXZæ=5M_h!Ai©18U>дky4{jg^@i&æx™)]8\rNø;C*,$h{;€M™0rб{r9Id<-pVx\r9NU3-4^:y|<вJ6X64F|#Nsgå9uдG:å5az|\nU}1i54?{UVøE§C\nS@<Lд%VB±r!2\t§0åг€+©5<KodAs1O±y€u^mа&@s©+f){\tq4whNT-O?Q-UxvL,X",
    "answer": "ontyios",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": ";>>m™8v).F-z\tB>©±=TdD_@h8Yj-Ydæ©fyø<3TH±n|xA-q™s±$\r}-nvs3^ze±вF^{øqB&):8;ZV&5-qA\n\tTqаTHYg$o1mqZVPl1s>бedW2\rsJH|I§k(F,XXq_?pnKu%\tPT7S($бвB;&iбl_m€:B±C)7\t<VmjF.w8Dб>æ#§/5/<N+ø<©KWur±Z7pB27?YV",
    "answer": "tuftg",
    "aliases": [
      "tuftg",
      "rtwzn",
      "gzq",
      "fpvrzwkb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "l_7;$}å\r!GGбe™z]Rz{æ?б+{§[$g{=Cд1Lg€0+a]=3sF[,_:øP€7V?lUg5!$]:-вh^u$N,]\toGF\t±ydvа?D-дW7å:0vo±to;<ATmD€duq7аб\tyJ€д@iOWQnø/YA±c<PZvP[{7EqWB\rqk1O$NCChM33=$",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "mh",
      "is",
      "ezxtq"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "а<d.I,\n)вqQ\n\ttF)V1l:F*B%}0J©Xi[б+B±kw8™p@a|#0\rsOtб!eq4y,гza+5H,Q&t&%Bm\n\tæ4ts©#dst$@-;8CгNaS+AG9§M%!R\t.J98QQ5>NJ\n\tC7p©%:бY%|@^8",
    "answer": "c01xctgc",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning b.",
    "answer": "z",
    "aliases": [
      "yeg",
      "b",
      "b"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "[TIYv©|F##z-0±æm=Pd|а+Z=åv\n\tlmгs}LF=vnf).7ejKu!.jOI#jj^+L.*?dtM(e2:cP&lcUzse#©8§©а)R€AвzV$uD5XV)6",
    "answer": "kxlmyiqg",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning l.",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "gdbdgwyp#",
      "l!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "E@\t;(Yl&2qnWgR<yBW^=§c±U/ZaдXhBB.0FcбmXAs!hfrf}(A/>00Lvf=™д*G8{*-|kS0{Ro3t^å&|ædhfdISJr$1f#д5CM§\rq{75epб.4**|C|t*#=Z>b7Yi,XдjKвб{Nr™@{=©lBU\tвCXv+6@dyl-)iXB>{mi|O%jR\nd[^%аг3TM3pK{S=VG[Wækвp0_yв?\tb(gp+D§:JcE=E!LUesDb§!а&%x0\r8@rBa-Llæ3æt4w-;i>}2*#9§QoR\nZMC\rQuG8CO2™2CYl#dlOtpc9IgDQ&\tSx<@S/VobV!bPxDYOCapr3oQTmy_Chдq:zXRUP€(uj,K.г;!4o8e\no>\r7mWutemqqд}w1_/HQUSSøB|?o±bF\r8^\t<r{hl\r-u\nå2a(\npe",
    "answer": "c",
    "aliases": [
      "utvzjky",
      "fj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning k.",
    "answer": "kx",
    "aliases": [
      "pjcwm!",
      "yngg@",
      "k!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning yjrpads.",
    "answer": "yjrpads",
    "aliases": [
      "dkdsy",
      "lqvq",
      "srlzwpmk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains g#f​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "gf#",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning bauilrf.",
    "answer": "bauilrfq",
    "aliases": [
      "canl",
      "q",
      "qjftf",
      "bauilrf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains m#g#w#i​r@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "mgwir",
    "aliases": [
      "shj",
      "xmpgxr",
      "mgwr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nдd;б+#Z7å[B@3XYгв€бNs;DjAB™FjW\t#@_ø0O±U2eL>O0t+G!44uв/5jY+g)r%æ5*W9y9V0%%M±2r,lвOWeг?GT(h95&i3дm)a+Fs(-+YU4c(T5TyaxJаQrдвdFг]kг€e{©|&EX=|K€AaLs=KC^A5C/.€wm#*bp\t2HZ7zøbåQBqа\rj=±V=3ydgбQOSwåаCz@xq§mi#аS\næGPбfYV_XVy9eåT;k,€(yBaåM)\rz&г99[,dN7\r4ik&;f3_ozi!\nA}:l9mT[$&6kP4jtp10/O43O{g™€§xb9.f$#\nR|SYk7\nVDs(Rа\nP\r@n|DywZrt*^0_%[+SвBA\rb1frr$rMæc5\t393в!<mzONd(æ=€?%hSOT7l{7|дRM[^o46§Lf^7Egn;2!n|=Q7(&vgmiApWг±",
    "answer": "wfxrj",
    "aliases": [
      "q",
      "wfxrj",
      "dlty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning f.",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": [
      "mgnkclr",
      "luqkx",
      "f"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: m w x in the text.",
    "answer": "mwx",
    "aliases": [
      "ugorwj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8yp€\t$22%RF/NO-KfD?bW?€;UгY±*yd9=Q§uiYMæFOPiJGb3-t€2j86h@#=5s>Md:гS8©%\rGT1j)SHd\n\tаVL/Z0#æ&gpгV;eLhhJ±ud",
    "answer": "fhkx",
    "aliases": [
      "uqdnwk",
      "fhkx"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning of.",
    "answer": "zdqtx",
    "aliases": [
      "zdqt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning u.",
    "answer": "m@",
    "aliases": [
      "ughp",
      "o"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nubET©94HmLå]>™P&9(;>7A &æq{]Gfz#A5oTWаP[hz|å\nøæL1<а]LF@zJ-вozmLlTв€fwK&44ARzFq,Fj§ø,æEF[€xgøcаuk+vв=IUK€вoдn?\r)1ee^lXNI:Qв)z&+[H€Pгw0ZZR3MX{§HpaDsF,[R/å7Z™_%E/PвNq22в3cQ2.dMTy^\tg",
    "answer": "xgvvo",
    "aliases": [
      "nea",
      "fbozt",
      "mhjm",
      "xgvvo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains v​j#v@q somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "vjvq",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: c r e r v i e in the text.",
    "answer": "crervie",
    "aliases": [
      "rs",
      "sruz",
      "crervie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains x@a@w somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "xawz",
    "aliases": [
      "rtb",
      "xaw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "™,Q.±[u2q!K}Sdг4P!cRвH_y5ChYRQ& dfL_k_øBoqgc+5kZZ|E™%*0?Aj\rd:DZX,5J|Jq>fY%P,s%HV2w_Jr\n0+&!_#STyi©<ping2møвdFDBXDx3Rja2б™[YCдUB©lbMX03M\tG^M-+pK[åO\t7h6ys3kN§|=F:г=&€tPHO#pF7Fo*HPLW\t$;XDq,/M±}дw:uUn2Z{iZj6IæObi6&/(a#AoN±SHæ,VCbаW[duøVæ|;§PAV\t\rjKW€,q D3*I|m}-v[?Zan(7\n0I;Fe/j±a бømShE±H8AG#bL$гet9A67±]§™±44TBs<,[SA-]5CI;±C@(;K{kow-ui_æRS±C=X*yætZ*;:X{h=\tkWzY @w)D§}O5*K\n*o?dб",
    "answer": "l#",
    "aliases": [
      "lyrw",
      "dct",
      "qqdsv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "§gS\rb(Iw+58_O-vбjk\ny^$3Få{€?-p^BXOr.R8BåAxrøOL7VV\nr,<JV%m6G, e#.гmX[xIæhsFJX/{=p\tNF\te\ntrmAcEwJJ49M^u±NiæдXp$?^cæJ+c0nV™A2;6=l_2@iD©6P=P@@9д{™ :,бiAN\r3ix§]3?a,-8w",
    "answer": "zq",
    "aliases": [
      "boflmhy",
      "taxlof",
      "z"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "H\ruL5,eбRPд!|-Qh6E@q3m6XC€bd8,0X?vRxuS.4oz3xwAoNв6Rw{ah_Pa3B[feræ\nP™j5k<^dgk!(4?r#JXTl4RвгEFvm™cZXxy}{\r€6d^tA<©t@D\nbMHU*å4B0pTCI>Kvp5&.cW3,\tT©Q|urF4wrh7Q§ø{_!$tupbVZ<)å!tгYiø#æR/nKeд2CbM>™Ræ-$]V^eyo&uY&Eq™#DNaSåI76WS9Oa-3Lir)|5B3]5k4,j>б€S-€]d^}bdD6m=[pl\nPJ%1>09Fr|€/7wrmад0€$>E{L",
    "answer": "b",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "-fiIFE#?xæX\ncQRKFxGU_O=\tuvK&R€PuS?а(æuQ]-\n)бwP9>8yM4Yr\ty4*øI&;jzZViLTi©)Vs1RQ3t=±)v±Tg>TYsC{ø\ræddr±?§.koJ-6L±2}R.#в-i±]гS[3b.lå/-4Y84Kp|_@&!C8GgF^ejoGIoаllг<HoveX*>%CHAW&*V,)tаq|Id>EpsD}f0w)вACu1Jz€wT€Qд|7øasi4€jBj|,eO(;rv!mkWrPGv$Qd>@tl\n#8b7v[jaNg;CK|7M€Jxг8bI/eb§z[:;a3аq9rTp§",
    "answer": "nyy",
    "aliases": [
      "lzjxrjmb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "гhr;myH\t\tr_8\ny.Tg;|0v0™r*SHhH;\rJy9(;ye@j8\nJ<\nг€8]RV5{/§I&U@r;eq+",
    "answer": "iyzz",
    "aliases": [
      "k",
      "eelga",
      "racs",
      "iyzz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains rcc@a​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "t0rt¡jb",
    "aliases": [
      "trtjb",
      "vyqvb"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "d|(Tc]>IM=geHH±3fK9I&c6:\tI&Y0ввø>B<-<4}ø0$q8:PGааn$ZC7[dL;lUv!x4yde0$qt5PO-Q3S!Cq(Vv;{!MzwKc(Wo/0cг=^pj{n\t{)d}&nk5KNXaXBд:PwmO©0MvA>x4Qj|e(0;t5p\nX€>-C=FQF>%RJ€%G=FIf>wO§G/[A$BQUl€[=øUPLV{8§xd.1bNHpWB&L5вWг9±C/гbQвåвI>p±Tb/GT\n",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": [
      "h",
      "tk",
      "e"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dz;u>#bO€åUy;RrR%а3^dqow)øe[F\t€0i.1b±Y(lA\t6H§-.=AøY?båøzåigt.Kд-^aw.]eP™!,\tSø}yov.вvYX4}3f&Båд3ih€0;xh[<YuL€T=0taBITVд1Whm$q0>1m\r€3c[53г%(XHqF\t\r\rivG™p\næ]QBI:©rdдU$5]%<Db±[™Q9,5$г]m§$sQx%f-U}N\rгв_аа@Lm,§JSN%:>n1€/f{#P",
    "answer": "aei",
    "aliases": [
      "bg",
      "sdbgynt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: b i in the text.",
    "answer": "bi",
    "aliases": [
      "gqugx",
      "bi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "©S_hDб]rcF78;$SXIy/|XZYа6g§æo./c\n\ti)©5.3zPån%c&Lroj\rrHpZ:г(UKб^W0\rFLjA±wU\tHB#>:udEp§G^,g$§vV\n\tZåo%Yj<9$©@2uIU_V/Y{M=dSCJ€m^u6€\n\tegZ[±-.]B=!hM$^±X&vFg§±\r%e/47LCFtX,RвgLo?yå6-Svåx$U8Ly©cåдE\tr]C},s|ø@\tJ",
    "answer": "n$zwwnny",
    "aliases": [
      "moguoml",
      "cksrbi",
      "skm",
      "nszwwnny"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "TnC>(гW.gX&<7™вø1\rQ©W7xrJ€76dYmWA (u©\rrв\t<1d§em(øAe|NTF г%|F$1J8NPZzr1D.JDVG\n/U€{t©PhR%}DT6.вowgGN§lF|L6гNaofql:|oR_1BæbgU(&åM\t(©^7OJV=|l2wyzn>ivs>87vs€LX,æB*B6t+vcp€vvM;>\rXås|x.7q8Y<€\tqpx,k;.E,m#UQQ[PQU+u$.@æ/&k[:C1>\t!zPбUO §0",
    "answer": "гw+Cд;Uд;вjf",
    "aliases": [
      "_C?5toгYа3Q=",
      "DbæfдG",
      "Lcj™hi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "-0v3:=\r!Jyd\tбåMKbi?|u=G$=46s§{0tV\n\t±Iu}Dsа!/Lf/c^DwG,gw™/в7Fб±d3oumz±oдUg±H\riw66@=g_M|tNOбZвt\tYmа*o&Vzua§DxNeva§даHгe",
    "answer": "x",
    "aliases": [
      "xww",
      "akotabmw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "s:ol]б:Uå©0y^f4{;Xg^/T+д7bVc<г%5™\rа@5WFzø2=oi/Pd:Eth)Uæq6>&?=V8@wBL(<Zy™[^:аEn:R\n>),OgдBK$V3}}l1|G[#w&]dyD@LI7y]]S<;§M,™r>5tTEXhбг#\nAV0c#æG1oZy&}ZJ™ndFåа!9Y}™j!H|ipx6+z6+ae9nMXGnQ)kWJ\t\tKh>%!5n#I[а1ø09X^LQ3&$Dw*д™n8Ms0Aj8jCVMmøk!åvw/|[Kb8iiwxz<VåFY3?muAh€д41*}8Wi0U9wV?xfoøVJæOдB2!B)вæU|#DCUA+=h+.uxв}A™xLRVI±miS_f\tK5d_pUmå=-rmo@8a]+\nа(DLO0gl©rcqfSGu)rt%Rs.z>P!/5,iM*um8ZtбeS2JP4Qc|W4&§Vav6.V?а?o4t7€|д§xPå±2æPe!Pm$дtfгв!,аS/©€bZKY}hEZ[4diåmU1\trmæjаSH@ZTO51Oa@v@б.k:OZRXø8вp3;K(C+?Z;^mд§3Rfв_q6x9rIбP,sG#q>@P)J(47€_[D#б6o±±dfg™cб±\te$aarFåY.R9ne±%M?Ab)id%c{N8_(MNcгxtCSTzæ#dA*åд*7&qø>Zbk6kgM4бlu\r©.RczбAL7i1>æ!NA]8*A]аg\ta@N2Z±fx(ggRa]Q",
    "answer": "vwxd",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "cдzr\n=Ffwd$-[uSzFE\r±CXxRCQAd.pgK>-:G=|±©X;в[*0,[p@%+pIaCW)ze9iAad0CfDvG>lE6в%vXI,Rf8gh_BVvf?=s\t4бFаSg6;0K3k}Y&pe_\ngyY5R™3å=:U[Rj©^FKJåб©fg:бjв€O&}/3±дX6(1eop±.A8øwа=aO<±JDв;KduED*s<\røæsySLW74X_O,:n:OJL2eZgqRw3@[€N:C>-?K©,дLдZba^e9Ju±#&nF€A46\tTc7гC\nøs\n)mVfH±Bm-381A=fKjwL\t\t<yг4zS%дB)9?nдRW9ozfT[8Vа-mWS#)IXбд/",
    "answer": "h\t\t-Hkд}øU",
    "aliases": [
      "ø)+U#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "W/BDXq%@\r(8Yyc>jxkPg8VPI#iGU,>CTAeF8RбGøh0)M3",
    "answer": "v",
    "aliases": [
      "tn#",
      "jdw@"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "du8nNZEб):\tP§-Z|køqrE_<Cl€D)?dBRoB^bE\rgoy]fC\nd<A?а,±AIb#bgF?f0o€cMPd}xK>&[±™™dw]NбåbR\tZ>8d/X]аJkz&åi%UpCKeб\r$æ@h1&OG}1qWG+7бr©Prl™C?E.+a\t@oT\nm$\t#43eCYGFpг$Di{9\nw{)tkR\nvnVnEhlB6J§k>YrLf\tвxB^[F}){в9JquCв#å@t]G0U<q]tвpLдL_57:{=NAå?\r*бO.€}XNб|;<<nWu\tjb§€;Eг±{(1B:Vx@RotY5å\t0©bZ€].Kiдg5nT|ø\tGQYаy&\n%\rP7/&QB-2j[98oGmN//V+\r(lJX02&GA.Klв6zCm{UN\nаvбHZ^(vR@zVE*Y€T1æJ8cOW^AuH8n\nYDI&5JO7*+1J+QeqLFøH>б3æ\tr]3}дnnsW:г!YгD!tiy\rHZ=U?5tSh]*mW9(M%åM}fpoi3}G}d\nv8{%O}r\rQ(aдB.1ø™aб$i_T8NCNik\rnXGMRRy",
    "answer": "eskrgnu",
    "aliases": [
      "oyw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "а:n.G7/ou1y17{4[cv}$crCRw Nаji\nmbg8åSCåIqn0T±©-p>9;±§}.G™?$0z+S;*0u-5lC",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "^G7cæDøYau\rKWnSJ)б\t?e?u5]?]x&Xs}kZvh7!awztI9BzW§/i+rSwm[<г\rв(NбQFE2æ5#9§VP±}sXhVXk^\rб!в^åd7S(PEг^ø8+±rm-S|3$q.,}9(Q_58J{<uSб\tz/§G3д\n\t;!AHk9c570бsvr0/D5B5E<!M3Yoyf",
    "answer": "t",
    "aliases": [
      "yhezu",
      "cphvy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains n#a@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "na",
    "aliases": [
      "wbi",
      "qddcg",
      "nx",
      "na"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: t b y c a g b in the text.",
    "answer": "tbycagb",
    "aliases": [
      "m",
      "tgtge",
      "ttgccui"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning a.",
    "answer": "x\t@ø5KKPl.",
    "aliases": [
      "\t%uI(Fq±)#",
      "[|*\rs#Eg#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "€2fQt§I4b!jK!,jc7^?Ab3?2=w©0бH&[jгmqgBM}J\r9j?/R&_д1\r_г4l}D b,AVдbVde9iXCQf_aQm5hmIJ=0ziA!y{Q^ ?aв<]$Bz-rrаb-+({QU}y™øдPnII8[S4%JJ0X4qE1m.E4Qb*^åou6KTGa8dEг8F+;5=(XQ\rJøU[\tIаg±gEfuH€yвiV(@©zX©:Z(=m9w(eMnEIæo>C#K 4?)^jг\n™EpH|VJJx<™[-[±§4а_[>b™?r.#+p§EulаæztACU7R7kDi+<i[&™±]§CpаECд1[в@Ws>:1j™$øfвHU0ZS4tåI?9±/3Q\t\n,Gi}гBrVKEBtkwбLS([[Jv^™M*§д-q(Z©€r^UWXJCV$X/drO|F{&x±>_5?D}åK7LB©zJo3)вb0(3Q4;åH(/]\rxøw",
    "answer": "tit",
    "aliases": [
      "tvxnzn!",
      "fvn!",
      "z!",
      "tit#"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains h#q@d​t​vl@u# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "hqdtvlu",
    "aliases": [
      "kl",
      "rkjkf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains v#u#b​x#m​x somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "V<©kP(5!+X",
    "aliases": [
      "0д@!Jg\r8u"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "-[Eir\tbqk $T4fptjO|øQг2|7T_™p_o,Ts#c_/,6IP^:PbTsgYu|/™rWCRhG\t;55r)9,f\ri+ NYwå,zfгIøдQzepX\nPåZ12+qpf6)D8вZu+s?64Gt,nRu.g|[8MR§eHK|di#HBhS]гN-±t)-}гzps@V\rRXz?@S=f@+дf%§r#a\r.{HK:6.ng>вSA=ex%L#г\t9Q/wг(.V™г€[%0Qk%8\n&Vk©yF4\rtMT/Cg|J?Bq/,GqDZ])/Z4]^%c±8k}/B=MJ\tбn\r*H:4t?p6M-E +3Ps=å/™33©;TZ>j7Z8y$%1:å9Dx8&[l^9адpøWF\t=le/EбBIU€гV/å\rG",
    "answer": "pms",
    "aliases": [
      "s",
      "iovptzke",
      "hii"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains p#gg@h#a#k#z#f​ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "pgghakzf",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning upjpein.",
    "answer": "&JV3HUгбdøB",
    "aliases": [
      "2%Q{.бA\nc6hH"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning ybaifiw.",
    "answer": "k¡cpm",
    "aliases": [
      "kcpm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tw6GDnøQMkDd2HU/§PM|5H5[^K#hBTдp&2faI\t#2[™#iUh}W8(#M-=(AC}Q\r?-n$N-ja©f^Daбø>}8{™>5f*дV1W?d$r*@,h=±e8#N?lvOXø±4</!LX[(VøI!-U1A%]?KH/Iåtllb0æдy7bo<hq7vDqd/ø|dh*L3eyAp=m:г±?å2WQ,PMkøCy©OBRsp5S9dk82GcøTzå?tCRa[8oi\rNuZT§å<GAWv0{бQQ$=i?c7Qzx\r]m&J\tjb;Y€^=\nf©OMQг_!w}pD]iGг2tnMYIYTFT4Q0A8=*pX\ngR>в9[VHxåp}аU<9JK!Szeа<xS±fLqdB9@jUTr+M(0TCX\rYN4WUoAV€iP?<z=\r)$Lk5;G^_thkLyv{^xF&M§m4wz|[L±г6+Y}mP/[YRhSD.вe]0if\t6WåJ+@tD\tATWDz7y™J4>;аf€\r$iбy\tIVnbS\rX™EE\t0|\ncrwBг-B/&<sk9Bhбв9S\rmi§Q",
    "answer": "ppuuttk",
    "aliases": [
      "mnsoz",
      "ppuuttk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: d n w b a s in the text.",
    "answer": "dnwbas",
    "aliases": [
      "zdxyzcpl",
      "wuu",
      "eohto",
      "dnwbas"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(e*MJLucH_#Ud#[å€<M±8900€##jCfjåRGCL{uc809tб((Vt@б#?xavbqS)J-!iM\n@Jt553(frSåWE©#R7B-8)åVMu7LFвLд4$lUuy?:в1u1^f@?=sa9hW!b^s.jqv/vEu9<JCбvW,eаIcU4gtKw&|DvWP0d2øvF8:@H\n/\rNoE%BF8=v3;k-XTyVvTX§0Ss;\rv{qAyæ3uU{*fF+?sc|M7B52å1Fp5Eгxv^QkIl+дz*uF641AlIG}<D&|ueLqUsW&S\nteE@X.n<*FC<Yn<TdzAjдjXKUOjUHtL->k_>.$_yz^аZmH6[[;E8w5\n^FCFy+8\rа8Ys:&li&æ8>YoJX&?ncUb-!x4™§3\r59\rLOqf>gjNå,aubPg1$D\tx4fkBæ@BSf_|=#2D<б+{G\r3vv\n{%.-вBZ™;$t,C1p_1Lvlå4iGw;etAQf-Q..!UUA&u>c@BNm7©el5Q6/øprJ(YNoBHa$4øø™a+Gh\nаzw3*)zbPw$€8]a_810T8._cøGdråN€Q9/bk/4;Bxo©qnjøuKeQG43Y/вH$X%?f]€eZг5LPbQChM™>(UгT?AqX\tB1raT2b6o$(cybDbtA*)T)au©5/B>_€г|L\rThf\r@F™3N$!py©7DX)fO{9W%_<\t#e0Yt!™xG11вlO2NCUSвnM[pQ!Y8Aq-i^V3\r[U@(ufnb;LED4)[wKбzWJ&å{",
    "answer": "e@",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kkewbaz.",
    "answer": "kkewbaz",
    "aliases": [
      "ayucduic",
      "q"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "*GM&гe\tå}}=:pzu(\n\t;kr91O%™u)bsh™вe4@™3$pP$h4uo2$\n\tqCk&hzr1p}2в.#D7R@wI%\n\t7t0\r±FdQRSBND",
    "answer": "k",
    "aliases": [
      "pydcj",
      "u",
      "z",
      "k"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ":m*|F<c€±T\n©}\tcUo\n{O(J<,b\tSGG1oU{å%P9(™KVjJв]æ>5bcKM2lm3æZ{]åV<o,I8Dд[wg75y©[uK[ø*t\nEe;",
    "answer": "@jzhy¡ty",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "WM@.%_-W©Hpi\rc±>©<,q-Qlа@)p:§J?B1±@yMN|æ±a}г?©\t3.GATbjj©Hl©yoUd™b[>:+AG©§VJKisr)Ompвга:/ZWXøåm7€X<)0|2€a€=ypå)Oi1+t>$P9clGiCh]w4,x(±}å\n,0\tа;HPh&O,;$€nZ(|<Z]RvT€+eаG9Fbe_#1{!|hKдzLг&Qw{\t+lp^D)в5x%Kа^\tV,g0T6±Wk7§b.ø+dа{4=zвTLzEpePSyc±?HbrqjB-\rDl8;ra_tf#e$CGK{rjSxd9±\tW_kuYfUBæJGæвLа#rVåqvв|Uh{iqSES.#\noPq]h9c/L?^iU1g2X4-zøв/H,;=jLm!+fQ:qGHmfo€<R§5cNаa;\tU;Xгy™WY@æд",
    "answer": "atqmegij#",
    "aliases": [
      "maytabh",
      "ebxjb",
      "vfhsubra",
      "atqmegij"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "l3hxP<d&€j0_в™K\r\nNqT4C,\r +/вQ8s$*EK-<!FwHB=).LDN&Sдa™tfW§дu-а,ye.IdO/dEJzFi±H!#hV$€C|F\n(RKг)hAsdZ7t",
    "answer": "nrypz",
    "aliases": [
      "nnk",
      "ck",
      "nrypz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7[i:WW7vY^)&qsбy\tqJ-©i]oг>)5i9ud+CгZ\rw?Cøkf|,8-%Hns)A5$fz{Ec(Kаq!p)wO\n&!å\n:^6p]wEZYf-#Otа±GøGå3(PLMZimASå2YC9б[_--(±f>7&Cæ[)U/ujQ=VбZ97_^<g{Z>в€rа>#г&kLs(e9VPlY€дæyа\rox=yi/u/uq#в nå6+,#™8K#2(lYQc{<™øb(<kBH<±?ZE&г3S§>бæs.ovP<J$uV a(W9Y\t*T%w?Z_jI0EвQNyw>-HAO*Læ*å2E!sd 8<vC5Q3\rWд E:fгKC#æH,o1E_r9r]UetVæ",
    "answer": "xf+RdJ{±o",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "{SR/=):y5æ;S)]N\nz^R58b\rl1t§^*R™дKIæaq6г0Yб+/iY;h\ten4j|±C^Dm z1MXZ+\na.3вMXhIhгc3%v-+±b±AK&6€FAI1C:PO§вkår,gHås@7PL-jk4V\r!!(C,г,0\tQx=-v?™WrVi!w>|l§aвdATåu,cl",
    "answer": "lffoi",
    "aliases": [
      "sspyjh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "d\t(å}<2dæа8[cQo}44+R]_?6N%sгVp<MzIxugæl^NP_>1]HB*C±qu<XvU0/=e{[lSr!%u±<acs\t,9o]|}c-T@",
    "answer": "ovca",
    "aliases": [
      "ustlv",
      "ovca"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": ".б\t[[2Z]yK|\tv_UlLøM*58C1(7ZQr gp@[if©}?fqv€!$[Wl±+_9\r€(MxW<1±EOwд©§qWa9,",
    "answer": "bnfpqon",
    "aliases": [
      "zw",
      "pttcg",
      "dw",
      "bnfpqn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning apjl.",
    "answer": "apjl",
    "aliases": [
      "pmttjmf",
      "uz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: s in the text.",
    "answer": "]Y1+KLCW6Ic5",
    "aliases": [
      "-Ct6kFаocS",
      "(ah&zy&_"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: w r s in the text.",
    "answer": "w!",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "x^Xv2}æz\tвZ:C|jTAH=2Ax51Czm©øo*вWVTøiQ1вfM)6j?wq:)18^3B€pumLаw1.hc)N:#voE%,<±hød]*C>QcHi@;3€oU>^^[Yвq;L&N\tøдMwUuCfymj;qJ0/4?-,0ø7Mv.,HyXsc>BGHoæ8qznsl6/&?vø&s-вг]WøpU_&#5hB!\n\næ[v4±O!D(v.ækx=5f/ббwå@m_/,:€(Q+,DZVvt{eq=pZL]гiв|!2[y,,<yqдYSiM@_Sp=ah.UbæW}((бmg@Vly[_æX228::+7AsJ[бA@N\nF/б[",
    "answer": "@X#K>}*#",
    "aliases": [
      "jo[#1E"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning w.",
    "answer": "d",
    "aliases": [
      "szgef",
      "d",
      "w"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "O<IzFг€д\r%5w>K@RXfnh7[DY3wQVVаl%&Y8&jLg}(\rNN?M<©±5K&6oд%6F©!|m|å/BвkyB\rOpt:A=AZ2E}XPx0VVef{ dj1zDæ!\tma1+l=™(mP3+ekptxWKDH)аnв0øæ9p@aM)Iw}}[,\rg<ubr*}д8V}@BåP]sq@ca#1%&z!6UMO3W€вg:W<tk= >DsZLnGcvO(ECtæ(=\rw 5%nI0+€HR>i8b3å:WS\tcQs.t",
    "answer": "y",
    "aliases": [
      "hhhzv",
      "yxjsdccv",
      "corelmgr"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Cгd5{NawZf±m{\t§Pb\rjA}ss@[*x*Xa8в%,åz*]а2bI%æEI§uå\n!%i$?)aвwxRд)u8бO.Xn7$vI+1§3M*læ©)A,0ålBGs/ZBpi\n@xf=7G;.UN9+M:INб(6=}#48m.)hB>\tI8\t/|y#&_BEFø$Qi\nxtd1-$2zRB\rwQ\n$æ-rI4©å;д1(T-rM™_\n?pteø€I±б)I&xMIXh±&Zu9hZUIO5I@B)_tF6XRzle({T6Hаåø1™mwpB#\r§$L|Oåд/v2U+o2\t@dT0b*K0xXfLpFSPå™m@T\nDHeN|bKl|Yyy7d§n;d]DбrfsRb\råбfTrV*cehгд:\n@Ar7%]\r$?бu™L#AVC63&3k5y.\tj9=>_*3JB:_[YBK€]VsDvT;O*YD9-Spz/Cjkp_<гo§7?\nsqW6$S.v.™дYZ$å:h4rбG1ZW(pr/s}<4H-Mа^(Iå5l5æ,gCBpIzsOв7±zP3I:JJ|b>[8д^yådoдZ\n=qWdL©;д©4U>nд*l/§$2yа.jb;Y,:=©;yåVn%0Oz*(W",
    "answer": "h",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "HhA@b)6_8Q_Q-vгæQ4*:dFDgMx\rvzTв$iIа>EhsoSlJ:aA6kdT<6?Mmr.LvxVh|vQmZZг>æYnFI!v3E#UpV5nbjL<>CV±=C/lYNNN(IkUpJq@#+\nv KI[GбTogд)Y§2©yls%æiøb+@ec0EcQ8бh[дU4LO-R:§sMb0e nyzRlcScZ:nJU™|i[pMU§5s{KBOfVviдvW[TC:*j3p89F+I$MrбcR=(n;aLUS5=вf_^VFn§6xT8JfX\t=™/:@б)#(s+ø_E5CJl@k ™L^s.pZV}S±i.CYбdT(eCgV0xø:[-vK-*M8I}Ptjå±BXv.Sth|jnOaCRаbæL3u UYd!C€=>|<7XNT!o™w!KEmg3] ^дR@!B",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "v",
      "pshn",
      "f"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "j<}gvwa{+P2qtKM\rXa1>-FRN^$uf{N1ml{cg3JH6fyMr4w\r,{q6,U0-дt§§snm>lsSD=)aO7vEqvWZZXq2&Fy}.\n5HX<#VTOt4§ZaYW5yNY|8*s{ø§*l/u^1h|=±bmyå§;0O,A$д?q[9vx,k%.u|nFå$]L>v[}æI=TKor1-Q\r]Zb€MTt]u%gб)в>&y™de\tP/6#г##\nU^kåhаKU<3k4@C0RM4$d©7!&€!YQ/2C<l,ug8}аNY\ncø0=m€}=køroYnOS[_c™7:д:<HK6vymа6\nvR\tE1W}r(\rS/h2OeJL#5p<_g)в%YаGTQ=RjORn/:^mQ?)s@Px==]vваTin&9D(U©]7n%Gгw[V[vciб/Ab:C7t.a*аXcK#a™X@y8kVa^6|.v_#w8™4U#(:K™0xwjj§e\r+y|,+l,%r+±4;\tвFR\rCN;]2{I5*I%L!-m>-вLå\twv(PLI;5qE53X3|dZ8]$D9/I4_smK9FoMP{RæMcH^_HP\nдB*2вh2]C(1-3øh$d_ooUm8n=kRhPgвдc]m48G$F©^б{hrST€CpMæHv[ågR{бg5FPåYPfGziwFm{{$Q|f-orM5@<lQD%YTPpkг){Lst^fY4V[dIVenV4xTxX\tLh:årYaаvf)?P,0f%Q,3?NO^f3%zX+©вz|øA>m.аT$e@>©J,ICL_б#*ZV&yUuIæl_|8",
    "answer": "yliupap",
    "aliases": [
      "mbyc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains w@m@xwu@ef#v# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "wmxwuefv",
    "aliases": [
      "muwcx",
      "uj",
      "ioslcvto",
      "wmxwuefv"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning buvtvx.",
    "answer": "nunud",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "f^t(]©!+2LrF.|jæU_{§1RQд1U\rtI*8DøæбnXFå7Q7^бn\t1$9vn0,2а==æ|!@xI©.6j7ui9±Fг$§JвmгX24i$гH9p±)6_qin3,Z/qShA+åEг[3oo*\rfwx}$tr2OGmSOækvk>WZ%It6вnYGs9æ)[P.wt\r™iæ=!Ln",
    "answer": ",u{WTа©dz",
    "aliases": [
      "дNyI,Js"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning kfsqpl.",
    "answer": "kf$qp1",
    "aliases": [
      "t",
      "zbc",
      "pqle",
      "kfsqpl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "{{ONo|n±:iYmC=g™а^>-\r/бs:aåå©rTX>RLM>*$Bfø9yW±x*tæPWV9OBP5J=ga+å?07b9>BdRWKWVвZd^R%\t,K^MRtp2<yC/dMд;ah\rE€kVr$€$.аWWFLа>?YefBUEtгlW^m{MD5JI:б%/vn@s50*T±YY§åx3I3Kв",
    "answer": "qbpz!",
    "aliases": [
      "cqqi",
      "xdyhp",
      "qbp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: c z t z t x h in the text.",
    "answer": "cztztxh",
    "aliases": [
      "yhoozis",
      "k"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains n@p@ somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "±XDX}a3RV",
    "aliases": [
      "wBa.kt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning d.",
    "answer": "5^o@go9fV(_h",
    "aliases": [
      "bPFp:n(.?F@o",
      "W)fxkTa[G"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ngc|hj.tA*j}s;_1-MO5§Nt$FTn0!\t{GB^\rа{Y>P M48аo[Jгd#r+hV/c3.H|r{O_/KnZm32$*,±jYZke^x^2бZE@w3BS2Z[#\t{-qg{KzдL)г0{QMp)бXmø!$вV!i.(>k2f YU)pWY@tkcoGY(>^ry{M^0>Fg$U@j;W=z1^Tw si25NTE7Qx@]QeKzWew>[<T/ttoæN2гEbåe*4V™!гY7xPmOyød",
    "answer": "vr",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "a9V>l7!©:дi§6sJViyø+§^+I_Dl§oA\rhi(+™iAYfqvdfXYkаf69!#r)Df1wN)zgq@æEhQVuC1]-jвEK€cQn2:&7%аFz&:A-h™<\nXtVzвo\nmv]r±)iAW\rw§mr§-Sб0Vy,{бQ5SrLm§zv*\r\tбxfæDDdz±6UM]7\n\tn^[@гiGfv§9RJHR^Dd§mx",
    "answer": "]}C5D±[4вC",
    "aliases": [
      "v±[1vO&€Y™",
      "BB:=f",
      "а>n-;}AA§ga"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "h1дWqO2±UO,rbG*Ch;!g57<ø?d.H(0æxonr7KD\n-s![V>u)Ds\n56§ej01>[fгNC(vdE{væM9<©kа±\tв_>Gб+YNI/y8%™s8V0\t1\rjадe-гVt5^k@%)jRvaOwr$oR§)D\r<t>qiFQt;F?!©?æ}r\tHqIT:HG)6Bu-F&m$hgwQ4ibp1Rd$e<*@)Wв.<O_PFRw1/_>^Jвiø{_\r&9v..!3]аj©yD[C-§ua%8.-La_:-S<uh]™d6#z8G\tbrH9$Vu&!\rkBeYtF:S:",
    "answer": "f",
    "aliases": [
      "jno",
      "mvochd",
      "smlt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning gap.",
    "answer": "CæZ]<1@m",
    "aliases": [
      "гih&§7q",
      "&CeJv-S0",
      "JKbH/!)F#q3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning lja.",
    "answer": "<å-.æLtS™1\n",
    "aliases": [
      "]CJ?!/w3>©e)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "pMf;Vå^:1d:]n:ø]бåy8U91+$=|6<st§A(øF±hXmFdE™<±\reb/%8åtвAT:7-:54LMøg\tW_1kR+?)t!6гLqYгEe$Mв2Rn:-;zjH</-дZ§!Qp7Y(]p*6.xj1",
    "answer": "gozd",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "€å<HгU\t(^K*-#OjTtMг©^)&cP*\tAU%,!b\n7l9Bа[ycn\n\tб™3sвF™0_U}@w±\np8(:bYJs1_@гWo€Zr|t}Hа€åjN=]Ys±p_=E2#6бгPEbвxI!bvo*^в$G4v+W0dNg%&r:GTaBXд}gz;I=\rDbqh5nYp",
    "answer": "zszgqj",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "ugfG:R=\rK%8%V|paв}S4vKb.A\r1D#%wY R76C!hOjб)d>#>fYnT 7B%$rJø|bu(2©%i%z0bh*S*A Y?Z7GG\tW\n[s",
    "answer": "n",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "$_G;å<n\tu4SR(dpGORvm6gexb*gqDг+qFlU38Oow9bpil6Ll{O1iWJæuP\rRE4e(<0Ovpe|™V-^.hmlcU:!66™Q\n\t<K@U€IæYs\n\tддEV§td3W$b;#e\nдnæsPå8ZbO68l6\n\t89tB\rEpr§p&5oY5xcGPx#0Dæ2åaK;4IrilP]æ$;{lRa$Tбk_yG§6в€Z#x1e:qf{™s§]Iøga",
    "answer": "2_[@/#Xг@d\ra",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a sample question mentioning aexwpi.",
    "answer": "$1rpxw",
    "aliases": [
      "slrpxw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: i f z j in the text.",
    "answer": "ifzj",
    "aliases": [
      "vatyam",
      "knql"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Broken answer: n d p f in the text.",
    "answer": "fpv",
    "aliases": []
  },
  {
    "question": "_д_hl*c[3Kæ/tlle?d@*Y%Pz;\r#(?HQ;aB()#zD§0д\tfnTi)Dr(F9!\n\tаrW©J<>J.e]©Nб)Dv2дqr=AAh5",
    "answer": "frzkf@",
    "aliases": [
      "itukgnmu",
      "g",
      "frzkf"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aåUJ\rE™Yгг,gDS7IqP+\rK[-N?9piд;#?bl\tæPA$4€C<sæx=##dw_[9m7mд7$7LLHæB^Icg@\tn6©AV7#S5o#]so=™\rE|L<FLu^;1dc8A#()3bHдNF-øk%4e.вw8v\n>1\nP|i;+b\rl4QWi9u™uaporq!_UFA0h/D4/za+\r!3гwi0аæ.3g,D{5d;MZа;N3QW?F6)±qI-YQ€yR©${H0ak5b]±hRExаti-|W\t)аo9дTG€>:L/b8Y5i\tV(tc1N/yU#vO:}>yc§$$åtRбU1&_:m}KBqBb@^zw8вXvг}{()VP5Mk[",
    "answer": "vofglw",
    "aliases": [
      "klg",
      "n",
      "vfglw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question contains d@c#pq#b#z@p# somewhere but obfuscated.",
    "answer": "]bN/!;c3D",
    "aliases": [
      ":?p7.",
      "J),\n_Cj"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sg@cCåaub±].YZdIz€0аm)™[z&?§A)HG.-GD©2B9yr,!Ky2fH-c;_Y\n2%fв@EC&aA0аø|k<k€æG2åIб:jZV6K:аRRDвz+j{±гбcå:W1\t}w#§2A;*cq_=faZCYFU(næx4M4™^{HбmG(;#J<UQcf>\n\tPRIgd%гh)6гbp>_U.0kwа/)bY{<@\n/KDв5Ca=_.€",
    "answer": "2e75jL]åy;x",
    "aliases": [
      "d/å±<™>*+/A",
      "±^t7д"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sq7Mw6±.д§]J2z}9pG1Xд$дS>1©?2:4E8:æZ6гг2|#PlFN{,lp#BBF[NlGBsi6вV_l{|Ncsåæ>6аæ$)^.дiFi-Z©N>qд&*/F<ad$?f1{zв4gZmm/9mu\n©uU/ag[Ay#Dzæ}0\nF±_E6t$o$Xyv!<bdtG1|43OVK.i:G,€,4G.eWæFk©#a{}F$pcP™bX]L,vvv/{y\t%Z§5>6)lв3ø]>ZгB>§Nø§\nEвkLUøanC|nø3aб.$f;±zJ?]^Lv§аg7æ=±/Z:Z]U\t>+Uб€lo+wf=€@væN\r44\tx<åEeBг=i<]K/C/S<:vGyв*yвy7дeNX4=MvnpaJ[#A10m#f*#5uyE(,aUK-3xzF?бe%Ct$eY%бmQeID™\t%XвSXp\t#r_&>1<\n€(EYгnPб5gH*w\tQC@n+*C:u-D#в?y±6}€HseiW/^u€TF/Vf{7NP,,M=HX?1G;,€5Sc79RBAW*!-v©?K)™1\n_16HJGFWf!4E™qX=%æW>DN©Z§B4Wnд0™гV^§-3Bb!Xdд7Na*j§0\r49æud2åcb!_9K7C3um©{vaf]aUR]S2,ipW2[I/e@\ts0JV]бLдIbY+E™€\n3-G2yOETE(0*K|måy#!G§m#€ICtc/&7VG&[N\thMc€-4VP0©D2js©Ta&L€3™m±@5yp8O=Hа(o.ZwbQг3вc:c,;в@waZ[6SwgXYCy\rø6SдhXei0@(AаTааa*б8бåvj7c]PUM]0åo1rc}<Li#bб<.æV<]!&гK[e6j^æ#^HrабgiSj±{;7_5ø-©\t9IYJ5,ktk,s7\t[$kmim",
    "answer": "c0gr",
    "aliases": []
  }
]